Hey, Adam, man, hey, this is Alman, yeah, I live up under the overpass and San Francisco.
You know, I was there when the day you had to put that bag over your head to save your hair on the day we're raining.
We don't mean we could consider ourselves kind of financially challenged, but I heard about this bum rush, the charts thing.
Well, me and the guys were thinking, if there's any money to be made, we'd be happy to volunteer to rush the charts for you.
You know, because, you know, we just want to get a little something to drink and I'll say, and come on, Adam give us a chance.
You know, on the DSC 567, let us know how we can rush the charts for you.
bum rush the charts. I like that. I have a financially challenged bum rush in the chart.
There's $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I don't know if it is bum rush the charts thing is all about, but you boys, but I put those charts back the way you found the way you're all dumber from tomorrow.
You can't do it's rush rush rush rush.
There's a place I used to go.
There's a world I used to know.
There was a light under it was you.
There are everything I say it's true I say.
There will be day. I will win.
Doesn't they all find again?
I will not know.
I will will dances.
I will close, I will open.
That's nobody around me.
I can see it dressed in red
All the secrets things you said
I and barefoot in the grass
All my heart is in your heart
Every day, I'll always tell you my love again
I'll know that every day, till you're mine again
There's no words to explain, no beginning, no end
I will dream, I will pray, you will be right again
I'll know that every day, till you're mine again
There's no words to explain, no beginning, no beginning
There's no words to explain, no beginning, no end
I will dream, I will pray, you will be right again
I'll know that every day, till you're mine again
I'll be right again
Blacklab, mine again, on March 22, the official bum rock the charts date
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
First, I code episode number 567, coming to you from the afloan suburb of Surinone
Gilford run the westside of Gtown
It is the curry manner
to my attic on the third floor.
Ah man, I'm still messing with the sound.
I got a lot of complaints from people who say that it's all, well, messed up, essentially.
Ever since I, this is me off, ever since I, I leave everything here perfectly and then
I come back and the mix has been unplugged and this is Yamaha Alpha Whiskey 16 golf is just,
it's an impossible mixer to save all your states perfectly.
So, apologies and advance.
Anyway, today of course, bum rusted charts.
You've been hearing about it on this show, you've been hearing about it on a plethora
of podcasts around the world.
In fact, this seems to be a much more global event than I even expected to check out
the promos coming in today.
This is a message from least trying listeners of the Daily Source Code.
You might've heard about bum rusted charts.
You may wonder how you can get involved.
It's quite simple.
Simply, go to iTunes Music Store or Australia.
Pay a dollar 69.
Download money again by Black Lab.
Not only would you get a grize song, you'd be trying.
They traditionally really pay for that way, main business.
Yeah, kind of an abrupt ending there.
Oh, yeah.
So let me just quickly explain the concept.
And then as you can imagine, there's a lot of people who've sent in stuff who are calling in
about bum rusted charts.
So today we'll be more or less about bum rusted charts.
However, I have to say I'm quite happy.
Not everyone is, you know, there's some people asking questions.
There are some contrarian views.
So I like that because, well, it gives us something to talk about from multiple angles.
So the concept here was to see if the podcasting audiences who are
clued into this, if we could actually make a song go to number one on the iTunes chart.
And as far as we know, this is actually, you know, this is how kind of loosely
organized this whole thing is we don't even know how the iTunes charts are really compiled.
You know, I presume that they're compiled based upon download sales.
Actually, I looked at it this morning.
Let me see what is on top now.
Beyonce and Shakira, beautiful liar.
Number one, Fergi with glamorous number two, A-Con.
I don't even know that fucking song.
The hell, can I play a preview on my allowed to do that?
Let me just say, that's iTunes still.
You do that stuff.
We don't vibe, we don't vibe.
All right.
Okay, Avril Lavigne.
Number four with girlfriend and then we get Jim class heroes with
Cubid's chokehold.
I'm telling you man, this shit here I've never heard of before in my life.
Well, I do like this quince to find the song.
That's kind of cool.
That's cool.
Anyway, so presumably this chart is compiled based upon based upon purchases
through the iTunes music store.
That's what everyone presumes.
That makes a lot of sense, obviously.
So it was kind of like a social experiment to see if we could get one particular
track one song onto the chart and up the chart, hence the bum rush, the chart idea.
And if you want to find out more about that, you can go to bum rushthecharts.com
and all the informations there.
So Black Lab, the song you just heard, mine again was chosen as the track that we're all going to
go out and buy today.
I've already bought my copy for 99 cents downloaded perfectly.
In fact, what you heard was the copy that I downloaded from iTunes.
And the way you do it is you go to either bum rushthecharts.com where you can go to the show
notes for the daily source code at dailysourcecode.com and you'll see a link there.
And from there you click on the big ass.
I'm talking about big ass blue iTunes button.
You can barely miss it.
It's at the top of the page.
There's also some explanation there because it's an affiliate link, a good portion of the proceeds of
this campaign, I should call it, is going to help kids get through school, through scholarship funds,
of course, Chris from the Financial Aid podcast is involved.
So you know where that came from and that just makes it that much more interesting as a social
experiment because we're doing some good.
However, the actual reasons and what we're trying to prove with this, I think has become a little
bit misconstrued and I have to say Eric Bergen, who of course is my buddy from the Jersey Boy
San Francisco version called in and and had I think exactly the right question.
So I'm going to play this for it's kind of a long comment, but I it's worth it because with all
this euphoria about bum rushthecharts and actually I should just say before we get to that
that the well maybe I should hold it to laughter but the news reports, the amount of reporting in
mainstream media San Jose Mercury news did a piece I believe today were in the Washington
Post with bum rushthecharts and you know that that's some I couldn't actually read the
Washington Post yeah I had to go register I'm so tired of registering for news if I just
wait a little bit I'll get a copy of it from somewhere else. Eric hey Adam it's Eric Bergen
from the San Francisco cast of Jersey Boys sending in an audio comment not about Jersey Boys
believe it or not. Well the second part is the first first part I want to ask, did you see us on
what do you think? Okay dude I did not see you on Leno because I live in the UK and I forgot to
set the the Tvo the sky digital thing I'm sorry. Is it on YouTube yet or Google I did hear from Brian
know from the nose on the you guys kicked whole ass so when Brian says it then he you know it's true
so didn't see it love to see it congratulations love you mean it. Let me tell you it was the coolest
thing ever it was out of this world wild okay anyway ever mind the second thing this is why I'm
sending in this audio comment I want to talk about this bum rush the charts thing here's my
problem with it well first off let me say I'm not associated with bum rush the charts I don't know
anyone who's putting it together I'm unrelated in in every way possible all it and let me just say on
that Eric everybody is unrelated in every way possible um this is not a pod show promotion this is
uh as far as I know I think Chris from financial aid podcast Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff I think those
are probably the two main drivers behind this but this is not anything you know it's not like an
official thing just kind of started which I love so much because those are usually the most beautiful
when something just kind of starts and we all just kind of want to go and do some all I know is the
information that has been given on jelly source code as well as other podcasts right okay yeah
here's my feeling on the bum rush the charts thing I think it's a I think it's a cool idea and I
it's something that um I think is a noble effort but and please correct me if I'm wrong so let me
oh Eric don't worry you know I will let me state this not as a problem but let me state this as a
question a let me just play devil's advocate here while I think it's a cool idea and I think it's
absolutely a a obviously it's good natured I'm unclear as to how this bum rush the charts project
proves that pod casting is a powerful force in media oh no boy I care for now
because that's exactly what it proves but the reasons why well let there continue so we've already proven
that the podcasting is a powerful force because Billboard magazine picks up the story or picked
up the story excuse me about the bum rush the charts project that already happened so we know that
it's a powerful situation however it's not as though you just played this black lab song on your podcast
and people liked it's so much that they went out and bought it either on iTunes or the
music network or whatever it's not like all these people that it's not like pod castors all
to sort of discover the song started playing it and people loved it so much that it shot to the
top of the charts okay let's I just want to interrupt Eric here because he's getting into something
very important um you're absolutely right however if you believe if you truly believe that the
way records get to the top of the chart in either let's just say the billboard chart as the quintessential
example you know that's not because people heard the song it's because the machine kicked into motion
and this machine look we know now for a fact it's been proven that as recent as 2000 to 2002 I
believe Payola was going on with some of the largest radio broadcast companies and some of the
largest music companies it's the way it works it's like you know there's there's tons and tons and tons
of great music I having I come from top 40 radio I come from MTV I know how this works they're all
just cogs in the wheel of this great machine which is all based upon making money which is fantastic
I love making money but because of the limited resources which is what broadcast mainstream broadcasting
is all about is limited it's you know is is having a piece of space on a limited shelf you know
there are only so many frequencies only the people who have lobbied and have made it their business
to acquire these frequencies have the frequencies and can make money off of it which makes it seem
unfair that there's so much great music out there that only a sliver of it actually gets through
to the public so all right and but how it gets through the public is not because the public is
saying play this for me no the machine is playing it for you and by the way it's literally a
fucking machine it's a computer that is spinning out playlists across the the clear channel
empire of stations you know it's programmed it's it's spreadsheet business almost so yeah it's
you know these independent promoters look I know this business that you know this here's $40,000
you know and I'm expecting 12 spins a week for it that's and that's probably not enough but
that's exactly how it works and you know there's no contracts but you know there's shadow stuff
and it's just it's okay I'm not I'm not against it it's uh it's their businesses what they do we have
a totally different business so the mechanics of what's going on here is showing something very different
is showing that yes you may have that very expensive very well-oiled very fine tuned machine
which works in conjunction with the music business by the way not all radio of course works in
conjunction with the music business and you know and and and rules and regulations and and payoffs
and payments and licenses and all kinds of stuff and I think what we're about the proof here is that
we have a machine too okay now I do have to say that when songs are played on podcast they do
move product absolutely when songs are played on college radio people go out and and look for
these songs even if they're not available through a major label so any type of promotion you do is
always going to move the needle um there is in the way podcasting works it's uh because everyone
is kind of their own entity their own show their own network and you know they can do whatever they want
there's no you know forced you know there's no funnel effect that makes everyone play one song at the same
time unless you specifically get set out to do it so this is more showing that we have a machine
as well and um it's have you ever done something to someone just a fuck with them have you ever done
that you know just a you know what do they call it here in the UK uh are you winding me up that's
it are you winding me up it's a wind up basically it's a shot across the bow I guess and what's
so I'll tell you what's so interesting about it to me after we continue with Eric because he's
under something good here this black lab song if this bummer us the charts project doesn't
do you work and a song gets to number one the only reason it has gotten to number one is because
and I don't want to say you I don't mean you but you you the the podcaster or whoever
goes out and promotes the bummer us the charts project is telling the audience what to do
the audience is going to do it because they want to take part in this project because it it's
cool moving what they do what they love works yes and it's about yes thank you exactly and that's
what it's supposed to prove we know that if you have a machine and you put a quarter in the top
that a dollar is supposed to roll out of the bottom that's what the the music industry machine has
been for many many years um let's just say they've had a they've had a Mercedes 500 you know
SEL or whatever and they're cruising down the road and I think all we're doing is saying hey
hey hey hey record industry we've got a interesting car over here as well it's um well
it's it's the color of baby crap and it runs on biodiesel but you know it's a car and it's working
and it's the understand the metaphor that's really what it's about and by the way we're all in the
car together okay this proves the power of the audience so this is not about podcasters you know
but I have a ton of songs that I'd love to be number one on the iTunes music charts but
it's never gonna happen or not in the foreseeable future because my audience probably just isn't
large enough to have a percentage of people go and do that going by that song but it does show that
there is power and um that we actually have a way of kind of harnessing that and we do have a way
of grouping together and doing stuff you know what I mean if you had uh for instance that lower
clap song or the pit hop console uh if those songs were an iTunes and you played it and some
other podcasters also played it and that many people heard it and then they loved it that much
that they went out and bought it that would prove it I'm unclear as to how this someone telling
someone what to buy by saying this is the song you have to buy this is gonna prove something
this is going to prove that pod casting is powerful well I think it's a great idea I'm just
unclear as to it's not because it's not coming from an actual creative uh it's not coming from an
audience member or an audience that actually just wants to listen to the song it's coming from
this rule or this this rule of this project I don't see how it's actually a uh how it actually
proves that pod casting is a powerful force and media so I just would love to know your thoughts on
that and and why I'm wrong okay all right I appreciate it I really do so the reason why it's
to me this this has already been proven it it already works and it's not because of the press
and it's uh and we don't even have to go to number what we don't have to hit the chart at all
what has already happened I believe I told you this yesterday is that two major labels one of
the largest independent labels and one of the uh a label the belongs to one of the big four
have contacted me directly and personally and said quote I really love this bum rush the chart's
idea could you do it for one of our artists do you understand the significance of that this is the
music that we're not allowed to play we're not allowed to play I mean independent uh label is
a little different but I you know I'm just bringing that in to show that you know once you're big
and once you're growing and and money's coming in that uh you know capitalism kicks in and even
the independent guys they're into to make money what do you think they just want to try and
make it on different terms however both of them set exactly the same thing how can you can you
organize this for one of our artists and I'm thinking of myself okay I love this because if we can
make this happen uh and already have the major uh players in an well established uh decade old decades
old industry uh come up and say hey wait a minute there's something going on here we have already
moved the needle we really have if you take all of the things together I believe that this will in
some way probably affect what podcasters can do I it may actually turn the tables it may open up music
to uh you know I'm most interested in back catalog I always find that an incredible shame and
a travesty literally that uh I can't play um back catalog stuff from 20 years ago stuff from 30
years ago stuff from 50 years ago I cannot share that with a new audience who I know for fact go out
and actually buy albums and get interested and buy more songs so this is about showing an industry
that we're here that we're relevant and it shows a whole massive industries what we're capable of
now do I hope that one day um a song will become so popular which I just don't see how it can actually
happen but that we would collectively through audience um demand that songs would start to sell
particular songs yeah of course you know if I had an audience of 10 million uh or maybe 20 million
I'm sure I could do it all by myself just by by repetition it's how we buy things people buy
things because media tells them to buy things make no mistake look at the commercials they're telling
you they literally say go buy it now get to one free buy it get to three for the price of two
this is being and by the way we threaten in commercials if you don't buy this product you will never
get laid if you don't buy this product you'll get pimples and you'll never get laid it's all
it always comes back to not getting laid trust me that's how advertising works it's what media
as a party if you don't watch this news you will die just watch the six o'clock news you need to
watch this because there's something poisonous in the air that will kill you stay tuned we're
gonna do it in 20 minutes almost near the end of the broadcast you know hey how can you not become
fucked up like Britney Spears I mean this is what media has become commercial media
so it's they were playing on the same terms and it's very exciting to me because it's such a small
it's 99 cents it's nothing and look at the automation of it look at our machine look at how
that's put together this is going to register with people and as I said it already has
and I'm really fucking proud of it actually so bum rush the charts dot com or you can go to
the show notes for daily source code dot com for this particular podcast you're listening to
and just click on the humongous humongous blue iTunes link and it's an affiliate link so money is
going to help kids get scholarships and and help show that we have a machine okay it's it's built
up of all different pieces but we do have a machine little pause there for these serious satellite
radio listeners as they yes which stuff boy are they missing some shit huh having someone
looking over your shoulder when you're trying to make art suck hi this is Dave Jackson from the
musicians cool and if you're a musician that's just been dreaming of getting that big record deal
then you've got to come listen to the latest addition of the musicians core podcasts where we
interview Paul Durham of the band black lab he spills the beans on the music business it's been a year
of a life a year and a half of their life the how many years they spend writing it's all how many years
of this band working and sweating blood over those songs giving those songs getting those songs to
the point where they were first class to make it the best possible rendition of them and then
the label decided well we need to need a christening egg yellow effect this month and so we're just
going to put this on the show be sure to go to bum rush the charts on March 22 let's help put Paul
and black lab on the top of the iTunes charts then check out the interview in musicians cooler.com
yo yeah you may be surprised but what he has to say remember black lab had a mainstream
big record label deal they were dropped they fought to get their songs back and now they're
sharing them with the world and making them the first input and output of the machine that
we're proving does exist it's the machine of you the audience this is not podcasters this is the
audience okay and by the way audience you you people there all over the world you can put the link
on your weblog as well you know you can put it anywhere you want and you can participate it
is about you showing that you can make happen what you want to have happen you know so if we have
tens of thousands of people buying this song you know yeah a thousand people will buy different songs
when they hear them on podcasts and it may not move the charts but it is happening it's for real
I will talk about other stuff today besides bum rush the chart at promise
from rush the charts can can we buy them the UK or not I don't know be useful if I know because
I wouldn't mind you know doing something this and just right yeah of course you can and it will
there's a separate chart I believe for the UK for every territory every country there's a separate
chart so please keep your eye on your local chart and let me know if you see any movement or anything at
all actually let me um let me just check out iTunes right now this thing doesn't refresh automatically
is that I thought there was a webpage where you could check this stuff out but I guess I'm wrong I have to
go into iTunes specifically every single time let me see uh what do I look for under the M and uh nothing
look I bought it I know I know I registered for one vote oh man
hey there's so much uh excitement about Twitter I don't know if you've seen this or try to
yourself I I did register and I immediately I almost immediately turned it off and and I realized as I was
listening to the latest tweet it's a tweet 91 which I still haven't finished listening to that
uh the reason why this I think this is exploding is because it is the quintessential app that has
suddenly shown Americans specifically Americans what SMS text messaging is all about you know
for Europeans uh and UK of course proud member of the EU uh but yeah we've been text messaging for years
for years it is part of our culture I text message with Patricia and it's always been amazing to me
how how few people use this in the United States mainly because a lot of the cell phone services
in the early days were not I'm not entirely sure of the technical details of this but I know
that they did not use the GSM protocol which I believe also includes the SMS you know the short messaging
service and and by the way it's it's become what do you call you know how you don't search for
something you Google something so you don't you know send a message to someone through your cell
phone and so I'm gonna send you an SMS I'm gonna SMS you which is kind of hot and so I believe
that this is all of a sudden has shown uh people in the US the text messaging is really useful
and really really cool for short messages which is exactly what it is but you know the idea
being able to send a group SMS I mean that's that's kind of like built into my phone already you
know now of course this is the opposite of of me determining who's going to receive
it's more of a published subscribe mechanism which of course is is fantastic for the blogger's
fear because everyone's like wow it's just like a weblog and of course there is just like a weblog only
with a very specific use but for me the signal to noise ratio on Twitter forget about it I use
my SMS text messaging for business you know I do not want all kinds of shit cluttering up my
inbox and besides that it's annoying you know unless you use your your text message unless you
don't use your text messaging and you know you check it like your email once once or twice a day
and then go through all the Twitter things you know then it makes a lot of sense and you can have
some fun with it but this is you know it's like when someone really needs to get me a message
whether it's my family or whether it's my business associates you know SMS text messaging pretty much
assures that I'm going it's not like an email in fact it is the better version of an email because
it costs money in some cases I think it even costs money to receive text messaging depending
on where you receive I think if you are roaming in another country it will cost you money to receive
a text message it definitely always costs money to send one from your phone but I like it very
much for for that very reason because the stuff I get on there I consider to be of high value
because someone has my personal number first of all so I've given them that or they they may have
gotten it from somewhere else but I've given them that they're going to be identified when they send
their message yeah you can spoof it and all that stuff but it's great you know I love it so I
I hate having a whole bunch of noise in there that is just in fact I only follow one Twitter
account and that's a comic strip blogger I found that an an I unbefriended everybody I you know
I've sent one or two messages and I'm like now I don't this not for me it really isn't because
I don't want to be a one way street if I'm if I'm communicating in some type of protocol so I
don't want it to be only send no receive and then I'm just not going to send because I got to
get that's a clean channel for me I don't want it to I don't want it to pollute it in any way
I just wanted to point that out as an observation that and I also I don't know if Twitter is
catching fire as much in the rest of the world as it is in the in the US but I think it's good because now
finally people in the States understand how incredibly convenient and reliable SMS messaging is
SMSing. SMSing. Hey look who's here is the candy man. Hi Adam it's Luke your
800 BFF splinter go daddy. Hey listen I'm sure that this rum rush to charge is very important but
I would like to talk about something else. My colleague Phil from the UK is going on a week long trip
through the Sahara on on Sunday and while you may think what's special about that but
actually what he will be doing together with his partner Susie is to run full length marathon
every day so they are going to run a full marathon through this haira desert every day next week
and they are doing that to support a charity in the UK which is helping kids with the
learning disability starting that's pretty important charity for you know to give kids a good start
in education and so yeah I could send you the links to their website so I mean it's
difficult to explain those of a voicemail comment and I hope that you and your listeners could
have a look and maybe give their support to the charity. Hey Luke are you calling from the bathroom man
sounds like you're in the loop. On the website you can you can follow where they are
you can send them also some emails to support them through the website and the email will be printed
out and they will go to their tent I understood so that it's something even my assistant is not doing
so I think it's pretty amazing I mean I'm already out of breath if I walk two flights of stairs here
into PowerPoint Palace and let alone run a full-time full length marathon every day in this
haira desert so I hope I hope we could all support that that's what and thanks in advance for
all your support thanks by Luke. You can tell Luke's in sales man it's pretty funny talking about the
powerpoint palace you know that shit is I think I saw Jack Osborn when he had a series where he was
doing the unbelievable things with his new tone down body and his new healthy spirit in mind and
he I think he did one of those tracks and he did the first day and I mean and he he just couldn't
continue maybe he did a little bit of the second day but this this literally kills people there
people die on this it's an amazing track so I just can't believe I can't believe someone would do it
as shit man is like can I just send let me just send money all right please send me those links Luke
because I I want to just send money for the kids I'm way too lazy and I like life way too much to
participate and something like that but hats off to those guys they got my attention for sure
which of course is exactly why you do stuff like that but man that's that's no joke I loop by the way
who turned me on to something called the cloud in London it's actually in the UK but it's
really prevalent in London it's this blanketing Wi-Fi network which is nothing super new and of
course you know don't please don't send me all the comments about phone and all those yeah yeah and
but what I did like about or what I do like about the cloud is that you don't log in to an access
point every single time with the any hundred you basically look up the MAC address that's the
the physical ethernet adapter it has it's kind of like an IP address only for the one layer
down in the stack for the for the hardware and any of those is just as unique as an IP address
or even more unique as an IP address I should say and it and and the minute your device in this
case I'm using the the the internet tablet the n800 the minute it goes searching for an access
point and it hits the the cloud the Wi-Fi zone the cloud I think is what it's called it's going
to automatically register log on any kind of course then do stuff it updates my news aggregators
a built-in news aggregator but yesterday so you understand the concept right it's like 995 maybe
that's a promotional offer but I think it's 995 a month is really it's not a lot of money
check it out at the train station boom it kicked in
run and I were having lunch boom it kicked in even at the office I was getting a Wi-Fi
access point from the cloud it wasn't even using the office access point didn't even know it
and here was the cool thing we went to have some lunch at the hawkston which is a hawkston hotel
it took fabulous hotel by the way which is right across the road from the crash pad and shortage
and and they have free Wi-Fi so you know and I've already been there before so it automatically
connected we had a conference call and it took Ron I think a good five or eight minutes maybe
to call in through his cell phone was having trouble getting the carrier getting a signal inside
the building and and as often happens you know you go through you have to dial all these
extra long numbers because 800 numbers sometimes are recognized and meanwhile I had already
dialed in and I was listening to the fabulous hold music in when I'm stereo but through two
head you know two ear buds because that's what comes with the 800 is two ear buds in a microphone
two ear buds in the microphone and I was already on mutant ready to go for free no cost
I love it let me see I speak in of unbelievable things we're achieving with music podcasting
you're Adam it's good in Seattle I wanted to let you know that I am driving home from work
listening to a metal band from Ecuador and you are solely responsible for that I just want to
point out the impact all of your years of action and working for people who enjoy media
have taken and I really appreciate that this is awesome you rock. Oh man I'm actually I'm quite
lame but I really appreciate you saying that because that that is entirely what it's about and
I told you when I played that song in Pablo from Ecuador called Pablo from Escobar and Pablo from
Ecuador called in and said you know dude here's a metal band they've had some number one hits
and they're really big here and and I played it and I was a little apprehensive because I don't
play a lot of metal on the show and then I realized like who cares who cares if you don't like
it you're just going to fast forward it's no big deal yeah man it's working absolutely it is working
love it
he had his he had the phone number programmed into his phone which is something I recommend you do
I'm going to give you these numbers with a handy little jingle which will haunt you
throughout the rest of your day as you'll be singing this over and over again the point is put this
into your cell phone right now and use the plus so you know you could do oh oh if you're in the
state you could do 01144 but just do plus four four well if you're in the US it's going to be
plus one and trust me you just want to do it because you're going to find yourself one day in some
area that's not going to understand just the 201 or the 10201 put the plus in front of it
it's different on all phones how to get the plus sign but please do it and here's that jingle that's
going to haunt you forever
just looking at the the time here almost 40 minutes I got a hurry up we got the
dinner with Dr. Cockney tonight
all right is it embedded in your brain yet
Adam Hi Charles I would just want to do a bit of always for us that does the
put your own light the female UK voice because I like a voice I'd come out I might want to
maybe use her on or or not at least it's like a real phone her yeah I think
male foot man yeah yeah let me just say something about those are the tags that we have
at the end of every show that come out of the UK it's interesting you say that because there was
quite a discussion we auditioned number of voices I have no idea who they are I did at one point
but I don't know anymore it's not really not important because I was just listening to the voices
listening to the reads and I said hey I really like this voice and I got a lot of pushback people
saying well you know is it no I got a feeling that I don't know and maybe it's maybe it's not a
stereotypical you know media voice or something you it's just I really liked it it happens with a lot
of stuff that I don't know I think that one of the things I pride myself on is I think I can spot
product and media and talent that I believe will resonate with an audience and it resonated with you
and I appreciate it I'll find out who it is now let you know if you want a caller for or something
for yourself remember it's voice work only okay I hope you're getting the right idea here
so they come and say to me I'm something that made me laugh she said you're the food bar boy
and he wants made a mistake you replied to one of my emails with your two bar boy at gmail.com
so I knew what she was getting out there I wonder how many other people understood what she was
getting out there because don't see your personal personal secret email address but of course the
big secret anyway maybe no no I've changed it now though I'm using the Google apps for my
domain I've got to call the Google peeps because I'm having some trouble with my MX records
yes it's a very long story you don't want to hear about it's a curry dot com still isn't fixed
either let me see okay just to wrap it up and I do have a very cool song from the
pot to music network I want to play for you the end of this bum rest of charge edition
of the daily source code uh first two more quick promos of people participating in uh in the campaign
hey there Adam it's Jennifer it was so great to see you in New York last week and I hope you
enjoyed the tasty dinner that chef Mark prepared for you oh yeah in honor of bummer's the
charge stay I wanted to let you know that for the first time ever I'm featuring a musician on food
philosophy I found bohal on the pot safe music network and I've used his music ever since because
I just love it and you've played him a couple of times too on the DSC so I was happy to hear that you
found him and he and I had a chance to talk about that and also the sassy rhythms of food and music
so you can check that out at foodphilosophy.podshow.com and I also wanted to address
Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff's comment on the power of new media because that really hit home for me
since chef Mark and I started the culinary podcast network to take back food media and to
feature the kind of content we wanted to hear and see so we are with you all the way and we are so proud
to be a part of this movement and DSC listeners can check out all of our shows at culinarypodcastnetwork.com
now I'm off to download me some black lab so have a great day Adam and I'll see you again soon
by the way thanks for the kiss on the cheek. Oh yeah yeah hang out with Chef Mark and Jennifer
in New York I didn't even tell you that Chef Mark cooked for me he had brought food for myself and
sales we go weasel Greg and it was funny because you know I said no hotel I made them go warm it up
because I tell you there's a couple of things you can do for somebody when you cook for someone
that's a real love man that really is and I appreciate it and we're going to be doing some big
things with the culinary podcast network peeps or is we just say Adam damn food shows those guys
yes how we shall them we got some damn food shows uh speaking of which sponsors for this program
title and all PM check out Angie Bees brand new show it's unwind on wind dot pod show dot com
to get you in the mood it's the only show that is actually designed to put you to sleep which I think
is a pretty spectacular full just coffee uh the gourmet blends of course and a splendour yeah I was
let me see final thought for today this is from Nigel you know I always read Nigel's emails
the minute I see him pop into my inbox because he always turns me on to some amazing projects amazing
music he brought uh he brought Tom's Dolby to my attention and he's all over the place so this is one
of his uh it's not a personal email even uh which Gmail a nicely identifies whether it's sent to
me as the primary recipient or not but it doesn't matter hi all really pleased to announce that
60's icon sandy show will be joined the pod safe revolution from Monday the 26th of March now sandy
show I actually put some uh he put some great uh bio information here that liked the way it was
written so I'll read it to you because this is exactly what I would have said the original brick girl
chiseled cheekbones sophisticated pop operas independent girl about town other worldliness
impossible glamour voice of an angel bear face and showfooted in a way kind of the Kylieman no
good for day I would say uh first number one hit when she was 17 uh two more before she was 21 hits all
over the over Europe the United States uh the UK Russia uh first British recording star to perform
behind the iron curtain the last to perform in Iran uh first British to artist to win the
Eurovision song contest first British female artists to produce and own her masters and copyright
ding ding ding ding pay attention there let me read that one more time the first British female artist
to produce and own her masters and copyright a leader in the field of pod safe music because she
is now chosen to put out it what is this girl power knocked into a cocked hat that's must be
British woman power there you go and uh let me just look um he put a uh how do I get to the link oh
hey uh Google notebook changed you click on a link and then it says change or test link and it
opens it up in a new window thank you it's Google dudes what you appreciated let me see
Sandy's let me see if she's still hot oh man oh yeah ha ha hold on gallery it notice how
uh it's using the same words as a porn site oh shit coming soon uh I hate that hold on
Sandy's Shaw dot com oh she's a milky she's definitely milky oh man they don't have it so uh it's
too bad the uh the gallery uh the gallery has no pictures there are pictures throughout the site
oh I don't like the welcome to Buddha world drawing that's kind of harsh um okay so uh you
remember puppet on a string the course you don't because we can't play that song anymore you why should
you know fucking music history well Sandy Shaw's back she owns her own masters and copyright so of
course makes total sense for her to cut a new version titled puppet got a brand new string
bit of an old dude James Brown now enjoy it it's part safe
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
So yeah baby yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I love yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah... yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah... yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah bro yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and
I can't see you, you know me madly, I'm madly, you think I'd go up in on a stream
I may run, I'm running round about
Then I'll lose on the swing
In all our boundaries, never, never a doubt
Just who's pulling all our strength
Cause I'm all tied up with you
But when it doesn't lead me to you
When the if one day you'll see that you can't
You see you know me madly, I'm madly, you think I'd go up in on a stream
Oh yeah, I so weird, the other version that I have in my head is so incredibly different
Pop it, got a brand new string, it's Sandy Shaw
A leader of a generation of musicians
And I think taking a fine position once again at the front
Leading into the pot-sake music revolution
Alright everybody, please
If you do anything today, let's show them something
Go to bumrushthecharts.com
Buy the song from Black Lab
Through the affiliate link on that page
It's a big ass, you'll see it
It's going to be in the show notes as well at DailySourceCode.com
And of course you can always send me an email
That's Adam at poncho.com
And I will be back tomorrow
We'll find out how we did with the bumrush
And it'll be a full bar body
Another poncho podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest
Saved up Daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery
Pot-show and limelight