Well, hello everybody. Welcome to Camp Curry, third floor in my inner sanctum. This is the
daily source code episode number 525. How you doing everybody? It's been two days since
I've posted a show and I apologize profusely, of course, I'm behind on my best of
Charlie's but, no worries, because I'm just going to carry on throughout the weekend.
I have not been able to build the studio, as you can hear, I'm not on my regular setup right
now, I'm just on the Sony Vio using my sound blaster PCM PCM CIA card, Jack the wireless
microphone into it, so I'm going straight in old school, you know, the mobile setup, essentially.
San seo, excuse me. Oh, by the way, since seo with a little bit of splendor, I heard the guys
just renewed their contracts another three months of splendor on the network, happy to have them
aboard for another 90 days. The girls are gone, Christina's at school, Patricia is at the other house
working with the cleanup crew at the cottage, of course, and I would have to say we're just about
moved in. That doesn't mean that anything's unpacked and there are some problems we've run into.
The biggest problem being that the podcast console, essentially the piece of furniture my father
and law, my 81-year-old father-in-law made for me, doesn't fit. It does not fit up the staircase
to the third floor in her sanctum, and it really can't take it apart. It would be a real shame to
saw it up. I'm just completely in limbo over what I'm going to do with that. I really didn't have
one second of time to even build up a temporary setup. We were just really, really, but if you've
moved, you know what it's like. Now, of course, we just have tons and tons of shit. And Monday,
believe they're not, there's more stuff coming from, there's a truck coming from storage,
and there will be a truck going back with stuff from storage, but Patricia's doing some kind of swap
out. Anyway, really like in the new place. Still sounds a little bit hollow. I'll tell you what,
I'm going to stick the microphone out the window for a second so you can just listen to the nature
here on the west side of Gilford. Actually, here's some, oops, hold on. Don't want to lose my
microphone clip. Well, you can actually hear the road when you amplify with the mic.
Trying to get you a good sound scene tour here. I forgot about it.
Anyway, oh, before I forget, I promised I'd play a promo, and I'll tell you why right after it rolls.
I'm Andrew. I'm Andrew. We do a podcast call just one more book.
A podcast about the children's books we love, and why we love them. Because we're crazy about
kids' books. Three times a week, we go to a coffee shop in our neighborhood, and we bring
a children's book that we love from our own collection. The amazing style, the way she puts her
words together. We talk about why we love the book and how our daughters experience that book.
And they just show themselves nothing, and they're just in total suspense, and it's a complete
page turner. We interview authors and illustrators. Hey, this is E.B. McKenley.
Lee Edward Foley. Shane Evans. Sheriffette. E. Wipe out. Played listener, submitted reviews.
My favorite book. Talk about how and where to find great books. One of the big secrets to our
gorgeous book collection. The great book Shamina of Hurt of the ones that aren't prominently displayed
at big box stores are on Amazon.com. They were just so in love with this book. Oh, yeah.
We're just hanging off every word. And all the characters. Oh, yeah. You can find our podcast at
just one more book.com. Julian Smith asked me to play that promo. And I'm happy to oblige.
He tried to get it into the show the best of Charlie today, which I guess you forgot.
And today's best of Charlie is from Julian Smith from inovierhead.net. He worked
kind of payment in the last minute, but worked really hard on putting this together. And I'm
completely chuffed about this particular best of Charlie because he really went back in the
archives. And if you want to hear when we discover Don and Drew together, when we discovered
Michael Butler together and much, much more. Even before it was called the Daily Source Code,
I believe. And I haven't listened to the whole thing. I listened to the first half and I said,
oh shit, I got to stop. I want to listen to this fresh. And I want to be surprised. I don't want
to get anything away while I'm introwing it. I'm really, really pleased. And I think you will be
as well. It's a bit of podcast history. Today, of course, is the 12th of January. Let me just double
check. Yes, 12th of January. The day that stomped the yard, the brand new movie opens up. If you
want to know all about that movie, go to stompedthepodcast.com. Tony Costa will be more than
happy to tell you all about it. He's got a couple of episodes. I think he even has some interviews
with some of the stars, or at least they're coming up, perhaps. So this will be the
Fubar Friday edition. And it's quite fitting because everything my friends is Fubar.
I'm going to take a couple of snaps of all the boxes and what it looks like up here. And maybe a
couple of shots around the house were really, really happy. Thanks for all the nice emails and words
of encouragement that you send. I mean, it's not like the end of the world, but yeah, it has been
quite a bit of work, I'll say. When we moved to the cottage two years ago, it was like a pick-up
and move. We just want to get out of the, get off the continent, come over to the island. And we
stuffed a lot of stuff in a lot of places. And now it was really the time to go back and say,
all right, what is this stuff? Or is it shit? And can we get rid of it? And actually we have,
I'm still still getting my stuff together for the big eBay sale. That's gonna be fun.
All right, I'm going to shut up now. I want you to enjoy this best of Charlie. I think you're really
really going to like it. Once again, thanks to Julian Smith in over your head.net. And I'll talk to you
guys over the weekend. Enjoy. I have recorded this intro so many times that it is, I am becoming
almost obsessive-compulsive with this best of Charlie that we're producing here. Hello,
good evening. Good morning. Good night. This is Julian from In Over Your Head. I produce a podcast.
Well, I just told you what the podcast was. So I'm not going to say it again. But today,
I've got a little bit of a treat for you. Old podcast, man. Old podcast. I went digging in the
crates and man that I ever go digging. I was up to four on the morning yesterday. I listened to
about 20 daily source codes in the past three days. And so I think I've got some really cool gems for you.
Mostly podcasts from 2004. Times when I started listening to podcasts, when things were different,
everybody knew who each other were. There were dozens, maybe hundreds of podcasts and not tens of
thousands like there are now. There was a very different world from what it is that we're experiencing
these days with podcasting in 2007. So I'm just going to let my clips talk for me, man. I've got
some really cool stuff. You know, all sorts of stuff. They speak for themselves. And I hope that
you enjoy what it is that I found. Because for me, this is a golden age of podcasting. This got me
started. So check it out. Daily source code best of Charlie number eight. One of you are listening.
If you want to check it out, my website in over your head.net. And I'm sure you'll find some good stuff
there. So that's pretty much it. Let's start off with a track. And then afterwards, we're just going to
go on with the clips. Tell the end. All right. I'll see you there. So I want you to hear the song
and tell me what you think about it. Because I like it. But I was just blown away by, and this is maybe
just 2% of all the stuff that people were sending about this particular song. Deathcab for QD.
Title and Registration, please.
There's nothing to keep my fingers down and all my fun. I've seen the mirrors from better times
before the clip of your tail lights fading. To find yourself a better life.
I was searching for some legal document. It's the main beat down on the hood.
When I stumbled upon the issues I tried to forget. And that's how this idea is drilled into my head.
Because it's 2M more time to stay the way it's been. There's no way how our love did slowly fade
and now it's gone. It's like it wasn't there at all. And here I was just like the disappointment
and I'm regretting that I was just like it wasn't there at all. And here I was just like the disappointment and I'm regretting that I was crying.
I'm regretting that I was just like it was a shame.
When I'm lying, I'm regretting that I was just like it was a shame.
Wait, think. That's not your style. I know.
Well, we got to comment from Holland Hunt. Oh. Yeah, it's cool.
Dear Adam and Patricia. This is Ray from Holland. Adam, you know, I'm a big fan of yours.
Although I'm not in the situation to listen every day. I really love to hear you on the Charlie and especially
the shows with Patricia. You're to really make it you're the complete. Anyway, last Wednesday,
you were talking about all the burping and the senseo. Actually, you blamed it on the senseo,
but come on, Adam, you know better than that. Really dear Charlie, friends, way back in the 80s,
even before the workoffing machines, Adam hosted a radio show in Holland on Friday night with.
Do you remember this? I remember this. I remember the moment. Okay, I'll let you tell the moment
after he plays the segment. Well, I think three million listeners. He was already doing these
things on air. It's not new. He's just a boy with a big mouth burping on air. When it
was a dream, you had an Amsterdam. You're doing it. You're doing it, you're doing it, you're doing it.
I was even better with the senseo. I was the one who came out of the house and didn't find it.
That was the four, four, four. Yeah, M. C. It was the M. C. It's the midday. Yeah, I don't know.
That was bad in these days. So this was 1984, I think, or 85. And on Friday, there was only one
popular radio station that was legal. We both come this, do they do that on the BBC right now?
Burping? Yeah, can they? Yeah. Can Terry Burp? I don't think that doesn't fit with Terry. But
Chris Moiles, I'm sure, I'm sure would do that. But in 84, I mean, there's just no way. No way.
And so this was my co-host who was reading a story and then he couldn't find the words and all
and I just, I remember, I had this big gulp of coke and I went, and then I immediately blamed him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it sounded like he did it. Yeah, and I remember, I was in the car.
Because we were having a secret affair at the time, right? I know, I was driving to you to your house already.
Like 180 in your poor. In my purse, I had to park the car. I was in shock.
I was in shock. I had to park the car and I was thinking, did I hear that well?
God, he was burping. I couldn't believe it because that was, that was no, not done. Not done at all.
No. No, I've never, and it was my, the first time I heard it from him. I'm such a visionary, aren't I?
You are the first with everything.
In my boss at the time, Lex Harding was on a boat. Right, but he was on a boat when he heard it. And he
almost fell overboard. But it was called you, right? Yeah, yeah, right in your heart, you sure? Yeah.
Yeah, he said, dude. The red telephone dude. Not only can you not do that, but you almost got me really
wet. But that was it. It was no problem. This one, you might want to sit down for.
So I listened to some really good shows. And obviously, I was able to start the sniffing
to tears song. And I probably can do the, uh, I probably can do the theme song at the end of the show with a
little too much to be cruising through segments and pulling out bits today. But I do have my,
my iPod handy. And what I'll do is I just want to talk about a few of these podcast
because it's just, oh, lovely. And then when I get home, I'll, I'll edit it in just a couple of
bits so you can, so you can hear what's up. So it's almost live. It's, uh, well, it's live on tape, right?
So, uh, first there's the Don and Drew Show, a husband and wife teen, which just cracked me up.
Um, and it's good to hear a woman's voice on, uh, on a podcast. And so far it's been, uh, men, men,
men, men, men. Um, and so they're just kind of shoot the breeze, uh, but they're funny together.
You know, when, when you have a husband and wife teen, that, um, have known each other for a while,
when they talk, they kind of fill in the blanks and they can also rank on each other a bit from the
Don and Drew Show. Welcome to the Don and Drew Show. I'm Don Micelli. And I'm Drew Donkis.
And this is, I show. That's right. So listen up, bitches. Enjoy.
For this evening, the role of Drew Donkis will be played by James.
Welcome to the Don and Drew Show. I am Drew Donkis. And broadcasting live from the
satellite of love. That's right. I'm Don Micelli. For this evening, the role of Don Micelli
will be played by Chris Moore. The Don and Drew Show, and if you want to subscribe to that podcast,
really easy, just go to iPod.org. Go into the download and shows directory. And, uh, you can find it
right there. And the way I'm doing it now, though, I'm going to start to split up into different categories.
Is every single time, as a new, uh, new show added to the directory. It'll be listed on top.
So it's kind of reverse chronological order. Oops. I just, I'm going to leave this. I just
remember that I have to make a pit stop in between here and home. So basically, I'm driving from
Amsterdam via Rotterdam to Belgium. It's one straight line. But I have to stop off about three
quarters of the way in Brida. That's where, if you ever in Brida, be our EDA in the Netherlands,
Brida, lovely town. There's a coffee shop there called Purple Rain. That's where my, my Moroccan
buddies are. And, uh, well, it's time for another refill. Moving on with some cool podcasts.
Um, I found, uh, oh, I didn't just find it. Of course, you know, every single one I
add to the directory. I pretty much subscribed to it, at least to get the show in and listen to it.
The rock and roll, uh, geek show. Now, this is hosted by, uh, Michael Butler. And Michael Butler is
the base player for a band, uh, which I don't, I think I might have heard them before. American
heartbreak. They've been around for about seven years. And when I liked about this podcast,
is what Michael's doing, uh, and by the way, what is it with base players who are named Butler?
You know, every year of geyser Butler? Black Sabbath. So, um, Michael is doing it a little bit
differently. Instead of recording a complete show, he records little bits and they'll just pick it
up. So it's kind of like a diary. And, um, well, uh, here's, here's a bit of him, uh, in the morning,
after, um, after, uh, he went to a show the night before for the New York Dolls. And here's how
he was feeling. It's Tuesday morning, the day after the New York Dolls show. I am so tired.
I'm on my way to work and I do not want to be here. Now, of course, always not lost. Uh,
he might have felt really crappy. But he also got a great ID for the show. And when we talk
about IDs in the radio business, that basically means, hi, I'm fill on the blank celebrity name.
You're listening to fill on the blank radio program name. And our buddy Michael got one from David
Gioyance, and the New York Dolls. This is David Gioyance, and then you're listening to unfortunately
the record roll geek show. The only thing that was, that was missing from that is he should have
said you're listening to the, uh, the rock and roll geek podcast, but all right, close enough. So
anyway, so Michael really does this whole thing. And I don't know what it is with him and his wife,
but he keeps threatening that, you know, his wife, uh, who he says doesn't understand what he's
doing and why doesn't agree what he's doing. He's taping it all in his bedroom. Whenever she comes in,
they start nagging each other and he keeps threatening to record all session. So we still have
that to look forward to. But really nice was a bit that he added onto the show, which was a recording
of him and a couple of the band members on KSFU, which is a college radio station, promoting a show
that they were doing. And also played a couple of songs from their album, which I think they're
at, they may be on some independent labels, uh, in Europe, they've toured Europe, um, here's the
traffic jam I'm already seeing that we're slowing down to a crawl. That's good. I'll get me some, uh,
maybe some time to queue up some stuff even if we really come to a standstill. What was nice about
hearing the college radio show interview was that all of a sudden that hit me, you know,
do you remember, and many of you will, back in the 80s, certainly at MTV, and at MTV,
primarily college radio was always cool, you know, the buzz. It's, you know, college radio is playing
this. This is up and coming. And college radio is cool to listen to because it's, you know, it's
on, uh, it's basically almost unsensored. It's, you know, it's non-commercial. It's just kids haven't
fun and people, uh, saying the truth and playing the hard out. And, uh, hey, it's someone,
someone's holding up his iPod. Hold on, roll down your window.
Eggs, you didn't think you opened the name, uh, here, come here. Who hate you?
It ain't on boards, but ain't on boards, okay dude. Yeah, what? Dude, we checked out a guy just drove
up next to me, and he's honking his horn and he's holding his iPod off. And he's saying,
I'm listening to the podcast. God damn, and I said, uh, I'm recording one right now. So,
Raymond, buddy. Oh, that's very cool. See, this is what I mean. This is what it's all about.
Oh, that gives me a boost of energy. That's fucking great.
Started singing before her lips arrived in the position to match the words of the song.
So she's lung off stage and said her bed played it wrong.
57% of Americans have sex outdoors. 51% and sex on the first date.
48% they don't get them, but they're not horse. 12% and sex and work. They couldn't wait.
Halloween has been canceled out of Washington State School, because it takes time from their
studies and the scientists just so cool dirt the feelings of real life, which is it makes them sad
to sing up some lead and pointy hats and noses cackling at high pitches, state tune for late
Viking Pop Dates. That's the tap dance and podcast. I guess maybe one of the things that you
need to know about all these cliffs is that they maybe out of context, it may not be as significant
as to somebody who who maybe has been following progression of podcasting for a very long time.
All these are clips from early daily source codes dating back from 2004. The clip that you just
heard before that was the first time that Adam ever mentioned the Dawn and Drew show on his podcast.
And obviously the first time he had also mentioned Michael Butler. Like I was saying at the time,
you know what I mean? It was just you could go ahead and you could just find whatever podcast you
wanted on on director. He said, you know what I mean? They weren't so overwhelming as they are now.
And before that clips from Adam burping on on Dutch radio in 1984. And the tap dancing is
another clip. I mean just one after the other. These are just amazing bits that I probably amongst
other people thought was lost. And so I guess one of the last things that I want to play right now
because there's so little time is the clip that really got me into podcasting. And that is,
I remember I was sitting in a cafe on a rainy day. I think it was even a Friday night and I
felt like kind of a loser for not hanging out with my friends or whatever. And what ended up happening
was I listened to this daily source code where Patricia talks about her affair with, well I
wouldn't call it an affair, her encounter with David Bowie. And I remember sitting there,
I was sitting at a loan at a table and just listening to this clip blew my mind.
And I was like this, I have to do this. I have to get involved in this podcasting thing. This thing
is going to be huge, it's going to be incredible. And I started my podcast like probably days after that.
And so that's it. So I mean I found this clip. It was one of the first clips that I found.
And I'm going to play as much as I can over the next couple of minutes. So you guys get an idea
of, uh, I guess really what podcasting was like in its heyday. There is so much more that I
wish I could share with you guys. And I'm trying not to go over the 24 minutes. We'll see how it goes.
All right. If I don't, I'll see you guys maybe soon. See you later. Peace.
I didn't think he was sexy at all. He didn't look sexy at all. He was very strange. He was he was
his guitar was hanging around his neck the whole day. And he was playing it. And so everybody said,
oh can you please tell the guy to stop? What was he playing? What was he playing? Oh,
sort of things. And he was always saying, um, so we went to the, I remember when we went to
for a walk on the beach. And he was singing songs from me because he was making,
one is a good, a good, a good, a good, a good, a good, a good, a good, a good, a good. He was trying to make
an impression. And we was quite boring. And what song was he playing? He was playing, um, I remember
he said, do you like this song? Listen, I'm going to play. And I thought I heard it already, but
okay. And he played ground control to major time. And I, and I thought, oh man, and it never ended.
And he was based on it. Yeah, and he said, and he said, and he said, and we don't
you think I sound like John Lennon? Oh, really? Yeah, he thought he sounded like John Lennon.
That's what he was his big idol. Yeah, he was a sound like it. But that was based on it. And
but for him, he wasn't a star yet, but he was actually, I think they sent it because I thought
there is something going on, but we don't know what to do for color eyes. So, and he said, I just got
a record deal. And that's probably going to record this song. And I thought, man, I hated already.
It sounded horrible. And you had to see him because he was, he was not wearing swimming
trunks or anything. He was wearing diapers. He had sort of, you know, he wanted to be different.
And that's, you know, he still was wearing diaper. He was so different from the rest. He was wearing
a sort of, you know, what you see when Jesus in, you know, he's seen the Bible there.
Like a joint cloth? Yeah, a joint cloth. Yeah. Really? So, it looked like a diaper.
Like a Roman thing or just nothing on. He was very skinny, very pale.
To like it, it turned his eyes off. He needed to slide it up, you know. He was so white.
And he was singing, and proud, and proud, and controlled the whole day. And I thought, man,
just shut the fuck up. So, and he tried, and of course, he tried to kiss me, you know,
these things. Wait, what was it? Did he have the orange hair? Was that the Ziggy hair?
No, no, just blonde hair, nothing, nothing. He said, no, he was not attractive at all.
Okay, and he had the two different color eyes, one brown and one blue. Yeah, green and one blue.
No, he always had. And it's teeth were like horrible. Horrible. Horrible. One, two, three.
You were even, you were even considering kissing that mouth? Well, I kissed a little, but I thought,
geez, no. And you could feel like the jagged edges against your tongue. Yeah, I guess so. I guess so.
And then I remember his girlfriend. He said, yeah, my American girlfriend is coming over,
and like, she's very nice, and we could have... We could get together. And maybe have a trio,
or maybe she's so much. Yeah, and I thought, geez, and I saw her coming, I thought, oh, no, no,
not Barbara Streisand. So they were trying and trying with nothing happens. So, but years later,
when I was really, really famous, well, you skipped, well, that was that. It was the song festival,
and he didn't win, I didn't win, I don't know, it's enough for that. No, no, he was not,
you kissed it. He tried. And he was actually trying at the whole time that I was there.
Yeah, he was more. I was way too pretty for him. And he was the star, and he had a shitty song.
No, no, he was the star. So what happened was after that, it was really a hit.
Yeah, he was like, you came in, he's not the star, he was like, geez, I thought, that's a song.
That's a fucking song that I heard. So a couple of years later, after he had a couple of hits,
there was the... Is that a question you had when he had his first hit, you think?
Yeah, I should have done him. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
but then then he had, after one, he had that red hair, and he started, he came out and everything,
and I had to do a big event that is, that was every year, that's called Kangala Dudes.
Kangala Dudes? Yeah, it's a great gala, no, it's an Amsterdam, and it was very famous,
Barry White was there, Dobby Gray, the three degrees. So this was like 74, 75, maybe?
Yeah, I see, so no, 74, 74, and the gangala Dudes, and they asked me and my sister because
we were also doing a lot of backing vocals because we were in the best backing vocals you can get,
to back up, to back up some some ex from America. You guys were cute. And we were very cute,
and so we did, there was a big orchestra there, and Barry White, we had to do the backing vocals
for Barry White, his backing vocals, but they couldn't sing that well, so we were behind the
curtains, doing them, and we backed up, he had to be backing up them, and we did some backing
vocals for the three degrees, just to make it a little bit fuller, because when they, you know,
on the record, it sounds better. But that was like a reo honor, because that was cool, because
you were, we thought it was a good gig, yeah, and it was fun, it was very musical, and you know,
you were your own star. Yeah, sure. And then I was standing, we had to do a couple of things in front
of the, the solo stage of the, the audience could see us, and I knew I heard that David Bowie
came in, because he was one of the guests too. He was performing on the show. Now he was performing
somewhere now, Amsterdam, but he was a guest in the audience, and with his wife. You sure you don't want
to drink a water? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You want to take a sip of coffee? Yeah, it's okay.
It's good. You've never told us. Oh, you're dribbling. You're so excited about David.
No, yeah, I am. No, so I was working, and he probably saw me standing there and said to Angie,
isn't that, Patricia, we met a couple of years ago. She thinks he's lesbian, but she's just stuck
out for me. Let's, let's go snobber. So afterwards, there was drink, of course, with all the,
all the stars. And this was still a seven. And I was walking around there, and, and I bumped into him,
and he said, I thought he was you. How are you? Oh, it's so good to see you, and you look so pretty,
and even pretty, and he didn't have, what did he fix? It's very hot, very hot. Because he was, you know,
he was Ziggy Stardis with his suit. So he had the orange hair, right here. And he had this little thing
over his head. He had that out of the party. Yes. No way. Because you know why, because he told me
later, because he had a, and he's no one of his, you know, one of his eyes had a, uh, cataract,
yeah, something, something, because one of the, you know, they're the different color. The different
color, there was something going on. Cool. So that wasn't just a thing. And he had a sort of an infection.
So it was not even, but it looked so, of course, cool. And his teeth were also still fucked up, right?
Yeah, teeth were still crooked. Not anymore. I've seen. Yeah. But it's in white. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. That's why it's. I think she demanded to do. Yeah. He said, dude, I'm not going to run
on a high degree. I think this is the time to fix your teeth. So, um, uh, someone, we, we met each other
and he said, you would, you'd like to come to the hotel and have a drink with me. So we, it down
says we had a drink in the lobby. And Angie was there too. But in the meanwhile, I heard, and I've
seen a little bit of it, uh, he had quite a fight with the Angie downstairs. She was very drunk.
As she said, I'm so pissed. I'm so pissed. And, uh, she was right. Yeah. Yeah, I'm pissed. I'm pissed.
Now pissed drunk. And she behaved horribly, because she's, she's a rough lady. And he was very
ashamed of her. And that's why he wants to go back to the hotel and he said, would you like to
come with me in the limo? And, uh, I said, well, I actually have to go home, but, you know,
I haven't seen you for a long time. So, that might be nice. So, I went for a drink.
Oh, and you didn't think of that moment? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I didn't know. I mean, I
had to slay thee with him. So, um, I'm a decent girl. Of course not. So, we went upstairs and I had
a lovely, uh, talk about it during your, in his room, you know. Yeah, it was, it was in a big,
the biggest sweets in the am store hotel. And we had a drink and we were talking about the
early days, because what happened in the meanwhile, and I was telling you, did you tell him that
fucking son can't believe it? Oh, yeah, I told him that he had to kind of believe it. Really,
you were right. It was it. And, um, and did he say, yeah, told you so? And he was really sweet.
And he was smoking really his head off. You know, cigarettes?
A joints, of course. He was an Amsterdam's, uh, problem. And you're ready to just get
high just for being in the room. A little bit with him. Oh, no, no, no, I smoked. And he, of course,
he loved that. So, it was just, it was very romantic. And he started to, you know,
just touch my hair, my, my, my shoulders, my, you know, my whole body. And I thought, boy,
okay, his fame is now. And that was nice. I know he's much nicer. I mean, I thought he is David Bowie,
of course, you know. And I said, if I tell my sister, I walked away and I didn't do it.
She'll never say, are you crazy? So I went along and we, and he's a great lover. I have to say,
Anna. Really? Yeah, don't want to hear that. But he's a great lover. He has a lot of,
so full of the girls that are done and done, done, done this. Are you listening? He is a great
lover. He's unbelievable patient. And he wants to give you everything you want. He led you from
me to you to your head. He's not afraid, not at all. His penis size is medium. Not, not, not
that. Thank you for answering that question. So my speaker, Dave Bowie. Oh, absolutely. Boy,
I think he's calling. That's right. Hi, David. I'm sorry. We're going to finish the penis size
conversation. I have to say nothing special. Nothing else matters. Nothing special.
Very nice, nicely shaped, but nothing. Is he circumcised? No. No. I remember that. Yeah.
No, no, no. Just a normal English dick. And it was nice. He went, oh, and he went on and went for a second time.
There he is calling again. He was going to say it was actually three times.
Yeah, yeah, I remember that. And after that, I brushed my teeth with his toothbrush because
I always liked brushing my teeth afterwards. And then, you know, when I know that you hate to hear
this, I know that. No, because knowing that my penis is bigger makes a world of difference. Oh, okay,
no, no, no, no. Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Pod Show Media Network.
Howard by Pod Show and Limelight Network. Control your part in the show.