It was a tough day on the beat, murder, scum, clean up the streets, and the king pin was
still in the loose.
I got back to my apartment, kicked off my shoes, sat in my favorite chair, and jam the
earbuds in my ears to listen to the DSC 627.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I've got some more
All I've got some more
I have some more
I've got some more
It's not lonely, maybe blue or whatever you is what we're looking for
We got to play it till you feel happy
Till there ain't no more love
Until there ain't no more love
We got to play it till you feel happy
Till there ain't no more love
Reach out to jail
If it's the moment
Jesus, I can get out of the way
Reach out to jail
alk away
I don't know what you think, but I don't know what you think
I don't know why you thought of living
Tom, I had a wild Jesus Rigby.
Of course, I dipped into the official mashup pool of the Charlie.
That would be mashuptown.com to find this one for you.
For episode number 627 of the Daily Source Code mixed up, I had a wild blue Beatles
Eleanor Rigby, and Eleanor Rigby, and of course to Pashmode's personal Jesus.
Love that.
From two time, of course, I put a link in the show notes at Daily Source Code so you
can find out more.
And listen to the song over and over and over again.
Perhaps put it on your iPhone.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
I'm here in the UK with nothing but a big iPod iPhone envy.
You know that if I was in the States, you know, well, I wouldn't stand in line
for anything.
And certainly not for food.
I don't stand in line.
And not to get something.
I don't think our parents fought in the Second World War for us to stand in line
for any reason whatsoever.
But I certainly would have dropped by today and gotten one.
In fact, I've already procured one, and it's being FedEx to me, which of course
has me all nervous because for the first time in my life there's going to be
a cell phone that you have to activate via iTunes.
And I do have a US iTunes Music Store account.
So hopefully that'll work.
Of course, I am an existing singular customer.
I believe I'm a business customer, which means my activation is probably going to
be completely host.
But we'll see.
I've been, you know, surfing around, looking at what people are saying about it.
And it seems that the interface really lives up to the video, which was, of course,
for me was the most interesting part is, you know, these commercial looks so incredibly
slick.
Does the iPhone actually function that slick?
And that appears to be so.
I know where he's.
I, I caressed my E61 eye a couple times over the weekend to make her feel okay.
She's been performing just beautifully for me.
Everything's in there, everything I need.
I'm, I'm hanging in, but well, we'll have to see.
I'll give you the field test when I receive one, of course.
I did see the Cali Lewis had a whole bunch of problems getting her account activated.
Actually, on Twitter, they had a pretty good, uh,
uh, mosh pit of reviews.
Uh, and I'd have to say, you know, everyone kind of duck it.
Hey, it's, uh, 230 in the afternoon on Monday here in the curry manner on the west side of
G-town.
I was supposed to take Patricia to rotted down this morning, but the weather is just so bad.
Now, you may not see it where you are because, you know, it rains and then, you know,
me a little bit of sunshine that pops through, but then it'll rain again.
Up top is really, really bad.
We've got winds, uh, gusting up to 35 knots, which is not a problem to fly in,
but it's definitely not something you want to be a passenger in.
In the back, being a passenger, you're going to get thrown about quite a bit.
In fact, then every aircraft has that, uh, only if you take a much larger aircraft,
like, uh, I don't know, an airbus.
You won't feel it quite that much as you would in, uh, in the Delta Sierra.
And this is, um, there's embedded CBs, so that means chemo is nimbus clouds, um,
embedded in the regular clouds.
So you could be flying along and thinking, oh, there's a little bit of cloud.
I'll, you know, I can go round it.
I'll just go through it and just go, uh, underneath it.
And there could be a huge, you know, a CB, a thunderstorm cloud in there,
with all kinds of crap going on.
You do not want to be in one of those because you have so many up and down drafts
that can shoot up, uh, sometimes these things go up until 30, 40,000 feet.
I mean, it's just amazing.
It would really what can happen is you can come out with bent wings.
You can be flipped upside down.
Uh, you can get pelted by hail.
Uh, you can get struck by lightning.
There's a lot of crap that goes on and then beautiful, fluffy cotton light clouds.
The best laid plans seldom become the desired outcome in a perfect world of business.
Alex controls every situation.
But when agreements fall to pieces and associates are winding up dead and new world emerges
and the bitch within finds new life to complete the final plays of the game.
Relying on the pure powers of sexual persuasion,
the rules have changed and the lines are crossed between business and the art.
And the art of sex and the realities of bitchiness.
From the imagination of Terry Woodard, ASB,
the art of sex and bitchiness,
where nothing is safe and the easiest way to befriend a foe is absolute sexual enticement.
Coming exclusively to pod show this summer,
the art of sex and bitchiness,
the erotic murder mystery that will make you second guess who you get into bed with.
I really recommend you listen to this audio novel.
It is outstanding.
I've heard the first episode is up and I listened to it.
It's actually, yeah, it's a prologue that is up now at ASB.podshow.com.
Mark Yoshimara Nymkov jumped all over this immediately.
I got to sign this for pod show press,
which is an initiative that is starting up as we speak.
Very similar to the pod-sick music network.
Only a couple of interesting twists.
And it will bring a lot more of this very successful format to the network.
The format of releasing a book in audio form,
episodically, chapter by chapter by chapter by chapter by chapter.
Chapter by chapter by chapter by chapter by chapter.
That's why we call it audio novels.
Really listen to this.
It's sexy.
It's hot.
It's like one of those fobio books.
Only you're listening to it.
And it adds some kind.
So you have your hands free, basically.
Hey, so I couldn't bring Patricia over.
So I called the KLM and booked her business class ticket.
For the one reason, really, so she could get around all the other crap lines.
Of course, he throws still a little busy.
Not that bad.
I have to say terminal four.
But man, there's a whole other set of cops that are outside now.
It's not those, it's not, it's no Tommy with a Billy Club and one of those high helmet hats.
These guys are like bad ass.
So I've taken a picture.
I was afraid to probably get beat up on the spot.
They got massive hardware with them.
These guys, just in general are massive.
They've been growing some different kind of cops here in the UK, my friends.
So by the, actually, she probably is just about landing now.
And she'll be going for the rest of the week, which leaves me in charge of the manner,
which is always a tough job.
As you know, I can never get the cats in at night.
I can, I'm glad I get my daughter in at night.
She's off to go look at her new school, which should be going to in a couple of months.
And I'm all alone.
Just me alone in the attic with my trucker friends.
Oh, the random.
I got two times.
Yeah.
Two.
Two times here, man.
I just want my quick comment on the UK versus Bob Joe on video side.
It's you two versus Bob Joe on video side, buddy.
And say that, Bob Joe is lacking a lot on the interactivity on the people.
It's watching the videos being able to comment.
Yep.
And a live active counter and stuff for this.
And that, you know, like, it's worth on YouTube.
I make a lot of video stuff.
My travels and a lot of pod save music with some of them.
And make music videos even.
Yeah.
And then trucker two times.
I think took a.
Took a nod from a trucker Tom and has been creating videos of pod save music.
Well, road videos, basically, which are really.
Yes.
They're awesome.
You know, I put these these things in a channel and just playing one after another.
You get some great music and some entertaining visuals.
At least you get to see the world.
At least the North American part of it.
Of course, I give the creative stuff out of the pod safe music and the orders and stuff.
It done that.
But they're all up on YouTube.
I raise a few of it on pod, so.
But can't tell if anybody's even looking at it or not, though.
So, you know, been a show off.
You know, like, see, if they're even being noticed or what.
But that's one of the suck less items.
I think there could be help with pod show.
And I want to bring it to your page.
Man, see what your thoughts on that is.
So, just let you know, though, by the way,
I am a proud member of the folder, society.
Crazy folder, society.
And I'll tell you later, man.
I'm back quiet.
Yeah.
Catch on rebound.
Yeah, I think I understood where your question was.
So you said that we're doing okay on the videos that you upload.
Not to a show, but just the videos that are converted into flash and are embeddable.
In fact, I think our quality kicks YouTube's ass time and time again.
And we're going to do the 16 by nine player as well.
That's all common, damn it.
But indeed, there's no view count.
When you go to your videos, you can't see how many times it was viewed.
So itself, it's not visible either, however.
So this, of course, that's a mistake.
Of course, that's being worked on.
You can't, if you know the title of your video, search for it in video.
So you go to the search box and then type in the name of the video and then select video and then hit search.
Because the number of views are tallied up in the search results.
So the information is there, the information is in the system, but it's not surfacing the right place yet.
I told you that fuckers built upside down.
So that is forthcoming and you'll be able to see.
But right now, just as a crutch, you can take a look at how many people have viewed it.
I was amazed because I did go through a number of videos that I had posted.
And yeah, there were like a couple with 18, 19,000 different views.
A couple with four, 5,000.
A lot more than I thought, actually.
And I appreciate it.
Talker to time for you sending.
You comment and we're staying on the road for a minute.
Hey, Adam, what's up?
Trucker Tom here.
Been listening to you talk about the channels feature the pod show website.
I've kind of been scouring the web and scouring iTunes and scouring pod show for HD content for my Apple TV and to play on my computer.
I got the idea of setting up a channel that's nothing but Apple TV HD video content.
And as I find new video podcasts, HD video podcasts, I want to be adding those into the mix.
So I think that's a very interesting use for the channel concept.
Of course, you can find my audio podcast at truckertompodcast.com.
We'll catch you later.
This is exactly what I hope would happen.
Exactly.
Trucker Tom, thank you so much.
I did check out your HD video channel.
Looks awesome.
I'm going to post a link.
Actually, I'll post a number of links.
I'll post an RSS link and an iTunes link.
On in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
So people can click on that and then immediately subscribe and iTunes, which of course will make it available on your Apple TV.
And also put the RSS feed in there for the the loyalist under us who were void anything from Cooper Tino when it comes to HD.
Yeah, I did a little bit more work over the weekend on the channels.
I also posted a video on curry.com of project cheddar.
So you see what's coming and how that's going to change.
And I'm very excited about it because this is something that we expect from the very beginning.
It's the entire architecture of the site is built around channels and built around RSS.
And now finally we're figuring out how to surface that stuff and what people want.
And well, of course, someone's going to come along and piss on my parade.
Let's have a word with the nylon spreading the news with the smile on where the roll is right.
We go for light.
Let's listen to the nylon.
Hey, Adam, I got cut off.
I'm going to try again.
And my point is enough with the channels.
I didn't ask for channels.
Who asked for the channels?
Ah, you see.
Let me stop you right there, nylon.
A lot of people have been asking you about the channels.
I haven't really asked for channels, but I've been asking about the channels.
And I think that this is going to be a real revolution in the way you collect and the way you share.
And the way you discover new programming.
So who asked for it?
I did.
Bitch.
The geeks are running the country company.
You need to hire a heavy, heavy marketing person.
Yeah.
Who would launch channels at the same time that you're launching a huge survey to find out what your listeners want?
Again, nylon.
Go take another look, man.
Channel's have been there from day one.
So this is a natural path of progression through an iterative process with the users of the site.
A lot of the audience, but I have to say a lot of them podcasters.
And we'll only get more information and more data as we surface these things in a useful way.
And then, of course, when we have the survey, we'll be able to ask questions about it.
Because it's not one surveyed, Dork.
It's a super panel.
It's an ongoing process.
You'll get the test out new advertising.
New ways of advertising.
New songs.
It's a continuous panel.
In fact, the next survey is going up very, very soon.
I understand.
So have you signed up yet, nylon?
I would have thought you would have held your resources.
You found it.
What listeners want it?
And then jumped on those top four or five priorities.
Who asked for channels?
I don't want a channel.
Yeah.
B.C.
You don't know what you want.
You don't know what's good for you.
It's a feature, dude.
So it's not supposed to take away.
It's only supposed to add.
All right.
The other thing is, I have a channel.
You know what my channel is called?
My channel is called iTunes.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, you don't have a lot of control over the way your shows display
and iTunes and the way they play.
Unless you're doing exactly what we're setting out to do here,
which is making playlists, playlists of stuff.
And still, it's not going to be automatic because you have no control over how many episodes
come through from a single feed.
So you can't really create an entertainment experience that is tailored to time,
that is tailored to interest.
And one that you can easily share without overburdening people's experience,
because there would just too much media flowing all around.
And of course, iTunes is fantastic.
It's like, what did Job say?
There's like 500 million copies of iTunes?
Absolutely.
But if you want to make the process of managing what's in your iTunes,
and thus your iPod, and thus your iPhone, and thus your Apple TV,
you may want to give our channels a try,
subscribe to one channel, and let Ponsho do the rest.
I click on a new channel, technology channel, entertainment,
and I get my shows.
Yeah.
You're missing the point.
I don't have to figure out what I want.
If I even click on DSC, it tells me of people who also click,
you know, subscribe to Twitch and Dignation, and others.
Yeah.
But how limiting is that?
Because that's exactly what you're going to get from those types of recommendations.
And for those types of recommendation engines,
what you want to see is who else has DSC in their channel?
And then you want to go look at their channels.
It's like the old Napster.
And by the way, that was pretty freaking awesome.
Well, I have a channel.
I don't need a sub channel.
So you're being particle-ed by the geek.
Say, develop the bell and whistle.
You rush it out.
Come on.
And again, this is not a bell and whistle.
This has been there from day one.
Oh, then take it.
Here's where I think you need to focus.
You're finally some advice.
Need to say, our goal is to get one million unique listeners
per show for all top productions.
Well, one million depends on how you count it.
But on a daily basis, we're doing well more than a million in audience
across the board.
So we might want to set our heights a little higher than you're recommending.
And if something doesn't lead you in that direction,
don't do it.
So stop being a technology like company and become a listener like company.
And the other reason why I know the geek's around the show
and you don't have a heavy, heavy marketing person,
you'll say, don't I miss a city out there looking for a job?
Do you have a company hire him?
Oh, dude.
Dude, what are you taking me for, Nylon?
Just what do you take me for?
Do you not think that I didn't reach out immediately day one?
And what do you think my meetings in New York were about?
Dork?
That gets you to pass the amount of unique listeners.
By the way, I'm just not sitting around waiting for a job, okay?
Not true.
It is not that simple.
Or not as simple as your thought process.
Don't hire a print journalist with no track record of innovation.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who by the way said, shoot Apple stock, which I'm,
wouldn't have been a good idea this week?
Well, now this tells me that you're obviously not a financial analyst.
You didn't even, you didn't even take the time to look at the Apple stock.
Yeah, sure it opened up a little bit on Friday.
And it closed down pretty much where it opened, you know?
And by the way, you should know.
You sell on the news and buy on the rumor.
To revolutionize your content.
So, I don't need channels, you know, who needs it?
Yeah.
Give me compelling content.
High quality and things you'll listen to.
And don't give me podcasting features that only 8,000 podcasts will do it about.
And to hell, funny enough.
You're such a dick!
Whoa!
He's an island.
I'll spark an expatriate.
He's in London, but he's from New York.
Whoa!
He's an island.
Can't you pursue an island?
He's in London, but he's from New York.
Today is an island segment brought to you by Coca-Cola.
This summer, when you buy Coke, you get music.
You can win an iPod or free songs on iTunes.
Might as well get something out of the bastard, eh?
We'll just sponsor him.
Ah, yes.
I still waiting for some responses, by the way.
Has anyone used that code in the UK?
Have you entered your code?
To see if you can win an iPod or free songs, please.
Let me know.
Call it into the voice mail line.
If you're in the UK, here's a handy reminder for the number to call.
If you're going to call it and tell me if you won't free tunes on iTunes.
Or an iPod.
Plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 16, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
Looks like I picked a wrong week, please.
Yeah.
Today is Monday, July 2, 2007.
A date that I will forever remember.
Last year, in fact, the second fell on a Sunday.
I remember it very well because this is the day one year ago today that my mother passed away
of lung cancer.
After a pretty fucked up ride, I have to say.
Luckily, all of her children were there.
Well, if you just go back in time about a year and listen to this.
Actually, if you listen to the podcast from a year ago, you'll hear how I felt about it.
Everyone was so incredibly nice.
Friend and foe, I would have to say.
And today, again, no different.
People are sending me messages of support, text messages, emails.
Very, very nice.
Everyone remembers my mom with her butterfly hang up.
And everyone's sending nice little messages about butterflies.
So I really, really do appreciate it.
And of course, I want to play a song that will remind me of my mom.
I think I played this a year ago, so it's pretty much going to be one of those tunes that
is a part of the soundtrack of my life.
I've been down.
I've been out.
And I've felt like my lives came in.
And I can't seem to find your lives about.
And I've lost my direction again.
And I'm feeling lonely at the end of the day.
I know that my son is phone call the way.
Because it's you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah
I'm feeling like I can't say again more
There's to remind me what I'm playing for
I don't feel like doing any more show today
Adam and podshow.com DailySourceCode.com
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow, bye-bye
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear