For those of you who haven't experienced the Charlie well it's kind of like when you
have something important to tell your girlfriend and she says she has something important
to tell you but you convince her to let you go first and you tell her well I just need
a little space I don't think things are working out I think we should take a break then
she tells you she's pregnant yeah that's kind of what it's like now enjoy the DSC
548 in a world where TV networks movie studios and record labels still think they can
govern what you see in here one man has the power to return control of entertainment
to the masses and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants from pod show
comb of the world's most dangerous new content comes the daily source code with Adam
Karrie was sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass then the next generation
radio content in my ears I like to think I'm flying you to the future
we don't talk with just punks of clock can't bend each other in the same old grid like
maybe a little escape what we need they love and you work like a dog every morning
the city's a pain like the loud taste stain on your dress hit in the band before you
break down the don't cause the band to leave this town yeah on the road cause we got
again out of this mess so let's drive away let the sunlight chase us all day
in a way drive away
love is a word no song yet I took it for granted
open the road not really part of the drive
come on come on it's all right you made me believe tonight the van makes you so
damn good to be alive
so let's drive away
let the sunlight chase us all day
in a way
let's drive away
oh yeah
sorry if I seem fast but I gotta be going
it's gotta be more than the coffee shops in the bar
baby baby it's still a baby baby it's just a baby you take my hand again
come
let the sunlight chase us all day
baby it's still a baby it's still a baby
baby it's still a baby
drive away
you know what it's the date of El Presidente president's day you know so
once out there somewhere listen to this podcast
driving from or two relatives maybe back home
top down driving around from Matthew evil drive away
one of my favorites from the podcast music network
good to hear that song again
it is dating source code episode five hundred and forty eight
coming to you from the newly revamped Adam's attic
on the third floor of the curry manner in the affluent suburb of Surrey
known as G-town west side
hey everybody how you doing welcome to Monday as I promised
I do a show regardless even though everyone's kind of off today
there was enough enough material that's for sure
are you doing
okay first things first I'm not in San Francisco buying
yeah there was some some business that was interesting for me to
attend to in London town so if post-pone the trip I could
be leaving as early as tomorrow morning but more likely
Wednesday but either way I'll be bringing you a full-fledged
Charlie's and happy to have you along for the ride
now even though I was home last night
I missed a whole bunch of good shit on TV
I missed top gear which of course is one of the three shows I
watched religiously here in the UK apparently
they tried to turn a a reliant into a space shuttle
luckily I have this thing on my my sky digital so it's been
recorded I can't wait to see what the show is about
why were we so busy
excuse me as you can tell it's still a little bit there
oh by the way comic strip blogger is now ill as well
that's going around it's the nasty ass bug
you could whatever I have to laugh or whatever I inhale
really deeply then the flimp but you know what I know
anyway
we finally did it we cleared up the entire third floor the the
bad cave is now complete I got to tell you this place looks
fucking spectacular I haven't decided yet whether I want to take
pictures during the day or during the evening or maybe even both
you can definitely want to show you because I have you know
like four sections literally I've got the living room area I've got
the desk area I've got the studio area of course with the
temporary console since the big mother load wouldn't fit
up the stairs then I have the flight sim area and then I have
bookcase keyboard guitars are kind of like a
music area if you will which is the more like a display
and by the way I've now surrounded myself with all of my
favorite things which is nice you know it it's like
well is it's it's the ultimate boys attic is what it is
I'm so so happy okay pictures coming I promise
speaking of of automobiles you know I'm a big fan of this
Nokia 800 internet tablet some guys have put together this
a diagnostic program and I didn't know this but let me just go to
page here for a second you know how when you drive your car into
the shop particularly a more modern car in fact the car
will actually tell you it's time to go into the shop because
they have some you know little light or some warning or
perhaps like I'm BMW's you know first you see green lights
then yellow lights and red lights which I'm pretty much
convinces bullshit and it's just based upon time or
maybe mileage or whatever but you know so they get you to
enter into the garage into the workplace and they use
something very similar if you have an OBD to compliant
automobile and believe it or not most cars built after
1996 are you can use a scan tool device and connect
your Nokia 800 to your car via USB or in some cases via
Bluetooth and I you've got to see this man so they've got
all kinds of of diagnostics let me see where they have
engine load ATP the hell is ATP must be some kind of
pressure RPM of course speed they've got it's it's beautiful
they've got all kind I don't know anything about about vehicle
diagnostics but how cool that be and the interface is
very realistic is just fucking beautiful it's amazing what's
being done he stays and this is done by this is because this
device is is basically open source people can build this
stuff and another thing came out a preview of a canola
if you read curry dot com then you'll see links to all this
stuff you'll see why I'm so excited because you know we all
spoke about from many years now we've been talking about
all of only we had an iPod the way we wanted it let me tell
you that time is here you can create the iPod of your dreams
and in fact some people are there's new canola interface is
much better than the iPod interface and it understands
podcasts in a different way it's completely customizable now
of course there's lots of I would say the typical end user
won't may not be interested until all this stuff is really
short up and it comes all prepackaged on the device
but I guess that's kind of the the the tradeoff and maybe
it's kind of the agreement I'm like in the way this works so here
here you go open source world developers here's here's a device
here's the basics now you go and build some cool shit and we'll
support you I'm speaking is Nokia I guess and then when it's
when we've got some cool packages we'll really I guess release a new
device or an updated device so we're all kind of working
together and there's something about it that I'm I'm really
really digging I like it
prismalone
send me I got lots of links to post for you today man you send me a link to an
automatic toiler dispenser which looks like it's built out of
macano is that what it's called macano I think that's what that's what
we call it and like tinker tinker toys or whatever and it
folds it folds it cuts it slices it dices you got to see this thing
it's amazing
hey Adam this John from the Star's Hollow podcast and I know the
whole how do you take your toilet paper debate is long gone
but I just had a little moment that I thought share with you
I'm recently reading a book by Douglas Coopland
Copland I'm not sure I can say his name the book's called
J pod which is it's a really good book and on page 388 here's what I
came across John do asked what's a folder or a crumpler both
their technical terms used by the pulp and paper industry said
Caitlin meaning toy that tissue manufacturers divide end users into two
categories people who crumple their paper and people who fold it
each is 50% of the market Mark said what about you breed crumpler
folder Bree said this is like the white versus black spy versus
spy thing you're changing the subject I'm a folder obviously
no I wouldn't have had you down as a crumpler surprise
to geeksq in any particular direction I asked Caitlin said I suspect
they're more likely to be folders so there you go Adam
I know the whole question of what is the proper way to take your toilet
paper is long gone but apparently according to Douglas Coopland
geeks should be folders thanks a lot man
well according to the latest survey of the daily source code audience
79.3% of you out there are folders at least those of you who have
texted in the word folder or scruncher there was an odd
full jurors that came in but those obviously don't get counted like
three or four people sent that in thanks appreciated but it's a
wonka counted towards the final tally so yeah 79.3% right now
for for the folders you know thinking about it how come that automatic
paper toilet dispenser doesn't give you an option of
folding or scrunch maybe a little bit too tough for the robotics
I guess but I got a agreement I think geeks are mainly folders
it just seems to be that way over the weekend actually this
happened last week news came out of the Netherlands and as you know
I speak the language about podcasting and using license music
the NVPI is the national association of record publishers
so this would be basically the record companies who own the
masters and half of the rights if you want to include a song
in a podcast the other half of course being the performing rights
societies which in the Netherlands is the boomer now they previously
had already published a podcast license for a nominal fee
of course they said it was experimental because it's only part of the
equation it's the performance right I think that was
forget about how much that one was it was negligible but everyone
was kind of waiting for the publishers to come out with with their
part of the deal here
I'm sorry I tried to have a folder's moment there but didn't work
okay so here it goes this is very interesting for a number of reasons
first of all as far as I know it is the first time a national
organization has sanctioned or even published a rate card
or fees for using license music in a podcast
per podcast non commercial 50 euros per month
now that's about about 55 between 55 and 60 bucks US
that is up to 10,000 downloads
if you have more than 10,000 downloads per month
of of your podcast regardless of how many episodes you make
you will pay another 25 euro per extra 10,000
so let's say you had just to make it simple 20,000 listeners
which is quite a lot actually I think by any standards
you would be paying 75 euros a month so say about 85 90 bucks a month
which of course you know is like a grand a grand a year
now if you are a commercial so if like me
it's 135 euros per month up to 10,000 downloads
I haven't been able to find the additional but I'm just going to presume
it's an additional 135 per 10,000 after that
which brings you to a pretty hefty sum
now what's interesting about this is a it's an astronomical amount of money
it really is and I just don't understand how how they think anyone
yeah even the non commercial rates how can anyone afford that
I mean you really got to be in love with it
but even for commercial podcasts
it's like you get punished the bigger your audience is the more you promote
the sale of their product the more you have to pay into it
because of course the way they're calculating this is saying well
you know it's a 10,000 people downloading so these are you know here's the amount of people
that are going to have the song for free and probably won't go buy it
and then there's probably a portion of those who won't go buy the
buy the album it's like
you should be paying me 135 euros a month to play your fucking songs
so of course the the response is pretty much long live pod save music
but definitely definitely worth mentioning
along those lines i i certainly invite
the Dutch podcasters to participate
in something that a couple of podcasters seem to just kind of like organically sprouted up
although of course part of it is from a part of it being driven by a Mark Yoshimode
and i wasn't quite too sure about this at first but anyway it's called operation
bum rush the charts and here's the idea
um the thought here is to show the mainstream
that podcasters really have their shit together and move product
and the way um and this has been figured out the way to do this
is by playing one song and and getting the audience
to buy that song on one day to influence the iTunes chart
and presumably the iTunes chart is pretty real and is not gameable
other than the gaming we're trying to do right now
um so uh a song has been chosen mine again by black lab
and the reason for that as a black lab actually was a uh had a mainstream record deal
like i dropped and of course they're doing great in podcasters it doesn't really matter to me
which band it is i mean the whole idea of showing that we can actually make this happen
is a pretty cool idea
go to bum rush the charts dot podshow dot com bum rush the charts dot podshow dot com
you'll find uh all kinds of information um about uh you know
uh how you should put this together
make sure that uh your audience is only buying that track
and on Mark's 22nd which i believe was chose specifically because there'd be no other competing
music being released on that day uh but i like this idea and i'm definitely going to participate
so um beyond the lookout for a lot of uh black lab airplay uh in the next couple of weeks
and uh and of course a lot of promoing of March 22nd March 22nd and you'll see uh i have the
little uh bum rush the the charts logo on curry dot com i'll put it in the show notes for today as well
it's a really cool idea and and i think it will uh look if we can make a song
a pod save song go up the charts by purchases and look you know
guys in the audience you know if you're if you're sending me a text message
saying whether you're a folder or scruncher it's probably costing about the same amount of money
particularly if you're calling from if you're texting from the states you know so it's one or two
text messages spend it on the black lab track and let's we'll make news with this there's no doubt
about it this this will be headlines and this will really show that we've got something to say
and that we've got an audience and we are powerful uh lots of other cool stuff going on
the network as well this weekend
it.
Yeah, you gotta listen to that, man, that's awesome.
Chuck D has always had his head on straight,
which I think is nice, cool.
Hey, let's see.
So I'm really excited about the stuff that I'm doing in London.
Although I would also be kind of excited
to be in San Francisco.
I think the weather is probably beautiful right now.
It's not too nice here outside the manner.
Oh, also, I blanketed the entire manner now with Wi-Fi.
I finally got, I had another airport
which I'd left at the cottage
and the real estate agent had it.
So Patricia was kind enough to pick that up
for me.
And so now I've set up WDS, which is,
it's kind of like a long head for your airport, I'm just kidding.
So everything, you know, throughout the house,
no matter what base station you're on,
there's only one network curry manner.
It does actually slow down some of the throughput internally,
but, you know, it's not such a bad thing.
All, you know, considering the source of the ADSL
is not all that fast to start with,
but it's awesome.
So now, anywhere.
I haven't quite tried out the distance in the backyard,
but I think I'm gonna reach a pretty good distance,
which is the first time I think I've actually had
all areas of a home cupboard.
So I have my favorite bathroom where I fold in the morning.
That's where I use the web tablet, works perfect there.
Wait until you see my sitting area here upstairs
in the bed, it works everywhere.
Loving it.
I really want to talk to you guys about Trinity.
I've been thinking about the free Trinity project all weekend.
And I think I've made a fundamental mistake in my thinking.
And I also have a challenge if you're an engineer or a programmer.
Got your attention, didn't I?
I had him.
This is Mike, the kids' wife for a life podcast,
and I am here with my lovely wife, Chris.
No, no, Mike, Mike, Mike, that's not gonna work.
This is for Pod Show and Adam Curry's daily source code.
We have got to kick it up a notch.
Okay, what do you suggest?
Listen to this.
We're tired, we're stressed, we're parents.
And we're coming to Pod Show.
Please come and listen to our adventures
as we try to balance kids, marriage, work, and life.
You can find our show at kidswifeworklife.potshow.com.
Oh, welcome aboard guys.
It's kind of interesting that you should think that the daily source code is associated with disco bells.
But I appreciate the thought.
Hi, Adam.
I just thought it's that by and give a quick shout out to folders and thank him for sponsoring your program.
As I'm used as I was at your past drinking habit to the morning,
I couldn't get into it because I am a folder in every sense of the word.
I use an inexpensive capational maker and make a talk up of D-Caf in the morning
with a tablespoon of melted milk, a little bit of sweetener,
and some 2% frost and top of that.
Makes one heck of a cup of capational.
Oh, thanks.
Oh man, oh man, there's only one thing wrong with your recipe.
Do you, it should have, you should be using Splenda.
What kind of sweeten on you, sweetener?
Are you Splenda, man?
That's when you can really start to combine the gourmet flavors of
folders with the flavor blends of Splenda.
Oh, you gotta do that.
That's what we're Hawkins stuff.
If you have not checked out Marie Claire on the Pod Show network,
if you liked the Devil Worth's Prada,
if you think ugly Betty is funny,
well, until you see this show, first of all, it's short.
So it's not gonna bore you to tears.
Like that movie was long, and it was fun movie,
but it was basically, forget it, one of my saying here.
That was basically porn for women, right?
Whenever you have fashion magazines or fashion in general,
it's porn, Prada, Gucci, Fiorucci,
ugly Betty in its own way is also a version of porn,
and also the, I guess it's the aspirational aspect that
I too could make it into the world of female porn.
And you, you sitting in your car right now,
listening to serious stars 102.
Yes, you too could be in the world of porn.
You don't have to be beautiful anymore.
In fact, ugly is the new black.
Am I saying that right?
You guys can check out more daily source code,
uh, today's source code, a daily source code.com.
And of course, uh, more of the pod show.
And for those of you hanging around with me,
check out Marie Claire dot pod show dot com.
It truly is porn for women.
I kid you not.
Every three, every 30 seconds has a money shot.
A century and a half before the tragic events at Shadow Falls,
one exoters visions of the future will lead him
on a cross country journey to unlock the secrets
held inside his nightmares.
But what he finds behind destiny's door,
may be a darkness beyond his control.
From the mind of Mark Yuchimodo Nemkov comes the chilling
audiobook prequel, Shadow Falls,
Badlands, be part of the revelation at Shadow Falls dot pod show dot com.
How tricky is that, huh?
Waiting for season two of Shadow Falls,
the runaway audio drama hit on the pod show network.
Now check out the prequel, Badlands.
How awesome. Hey, what's up with the,
this done La Fontaine Guy who, of course,
has done a number of promos for me as well.
How can we always says this type of stuff?
How come Mark always has these promos?
Listen to this.
From the mind of Mark Yuchimodo Nemkov.
How come, I can only just,
how come we're just not honest about it?
How come it can't be from the ass of Mark Yuchimodo Nemkov?
He's so much more realistic.
While it's Monday, time to start
your week off right with an update on the old galtrin.
Okay, of course, the whole idea behind free trinity is to take my 1984 poo.
Baby poo colored Mercedes station wagon is a 300 turbo diesel running completely on
bio diesel. She's from 1984 as I said.
So she's had a few issues.
In fact, an update from Rosie, as you know, Rosie has been tasked with
keeping trinity running until she gets ready to go on the road.
Oh, this came in, was it the 16th, so Thursday or Friday?
Adam, as you know, I've been driving your car regularly.
Well, the brake warning like came on the other day.
Took it to the shop and they identified that front and rear brakes
brakes do need to be replaced.
Broder's pads and sensors, $585 total.
The car is pulled apart ready for repair now if you approve it.
Not let me know.
So hard to bring you another sad chapter in the trinity saga.
Actually, I'm not sad at all, Rosie. I'm glad all this stuff has happened
now because I think we've hit all the vital areas.
Let's see, we've got the fuel flow. That's where we've got the brand new transmission.
We got the brakes.
Other than that, Rosie says she's running great. A small rattling sound from the engine
which they identified as the air conditioning compressor.
Which is shot to hell.
They suggest cutting the line to it and that'll stop the rattle somehow.
Doesn't seem necessary at all to look into a pairing AC on her, man.
You know, I got to be honest.
This thing is costing me a fortune.
They got sunk like, you know, $6,000 into it.
It's time to get this bitch on the road.
Thanks, Rosie.
Well, almost second. I have another thing here about what is this from Trinity.
Okay, I hold that for a second.
Okay, so I think I made a fundamental mistake here
and thinking that we would have some kind of relay race passing Trinity off from one person to the next
starting off on the west coast of the USA towards the east coast.
And then far beyond the borders of the US.
In fact, we have invites from all over the world, including Japan now, I think.
So here's the mistake I made.
You know, if you take, so let's say I live in San Francisco and like, yeah, I'll drive
for the first 100 miles.
How am I getting back?
And what if I have to drive 200 miles?
Because that's what that means that every single person that we have,
who's going to drive Trinity also has to have a ride back.
I think it's really complicating matters.
In fact, I have to be really, really honest with you.
I'm almost back full circle back to the idea that Doug Pilgrim had to
to bring his son out to the west coast and then drive Trinity across the USA.
Up to, uh, I was going to drive to Boston and stop it all these stops along the way.
I think that's probably going to be the best, uh, the best way to
to get her on her way because, you know, if she does break down, you know, who's
responsible, you know, somehow I'm going to pod shows going to have to get involved and do stuff.
There's a so many moving parts to the audio and video ideas that we want to get up.
I think it may be better to actually set it up or people who want to make a certain trip.
And have a way to get back to make the trip and stop along some, you know, a designated
route that we, uh, that we compile together.
This is just what I'm thinking today because it, it really, you know, is like a joke
sometimes, uh, I've seen done. I think my dad actually did this once and I thought it was pretty funny.
He was speaking at a conference and he said, you know, just so we can all cut a coin.
It won't just turn around and say hi to the person behind you. And of course, everyone
turns around and the person behind them is also turned around. So you're looking at their back, you know,
but that's kind of what this whole Trinity thing is turned into.
Now, I don't think that a week for West Coast to East Coast is enough.
I know you can do the trip probably in about three days.
I'm thinking it should maybe be a little bit longer because there's so many different places
that, you know, she should go and maybe we should look at people who have certain,
you know, who have certain, um, routes that they're going to do anyway
and wouldn't mind driving. And honestly, I think I'll spring for return airfare.
It sounds like a much, much better deal.
Okay, so I'm just kind of shooting from the hip here and thinking about it. Now, about the
technology side because that's what a lot of the energy seems to be about on the free Trinity
group at Google link in the show notes, of course, a daily source code.
You know, give an example. Here's prolific. Oh, I mean, uh, well, where are my manners?
For those of you who haven't experienced whoops, uh, hell is that? Oh, man.
Oh, the fuck Charlie. Well, the fuck that I do that for. How did that go wrong? Hold on.
Hi, let her. Here we go. Hi. Hi, I'm this prolific programmer here. I look at a Python
at my implementation based on your request of somebody in DSE. If I for seven regarding a Python
at an attempt to XML or PC translator, I will work on a get back on my own. Oh, I'll be dead.
Ah, prolific programming. You slay me, man. All right. So there's all kinds of geeky stuff going on.
And the problem is is you've got all these people who are very interested in helping out, but they
have no device to test it on. And of course, it's Linux. So, you know, it'll work with, you know,
with many similarities, but look, I'm a busy guy. I'm not a programmer. I got the the XML RPC thing
to work, so I can actually upload media from the N800. That was really cool. Oscar helped out on that.
But how do we actually get something implemented? First, I think I need to specify exactly what
it is. And I'm going to do that later today at curry.com, but I'll just give you a thought.
So coming out soon for the N800, or maybe even available as we speak, is a navigation kit.
And the navigation kit also comes with a holder, which will actually hold the N800. You know,
one of those, almost like the, I guess, the Tom Tom Go, you stick it onto the windshield. So,
you know, let's just say there's a holder, and we could bolt it on how we wanted to. But it will
navigate for you. It's like a satellite navigation system. Okay. So, if, if we take into consideration
that we've got people who are driving predetermined routes, or more or less predetermined routes,
there's a two way flow to this. First of all, we want to make sure that they have their route
set out. And I presume that we're going to kind of semi-control which route they're going to take.
Okay. So, it would be nice if they could load up an overlay of the route, or just load up a route
file, which is fairly standard stuff. So, they can, you know, each person or team can follow that route.
All right. Here's what I want it to do. I want the system to continuously be recording its GPS
track. So, that's fairly simple. I want it to take a picture, and I've already checked with my
contacted Nokia when it's in navigation and the navigation dock, the little camera, the little
penis camera can be extended, which means you can roll that towards yourself, the driver, or roll it
forward out the windscreen, and it automatically inverts the picture so you get it right side up.
Okay. So, here's what we want. At regular intervals, I'm just going to say,
make it an hour just to be really simple. I want a picture taken. I want the GPS codes embedded.
And of course, I want the GPS track continuously stored. Whenever Trinity comes within range of a
Wi-Fi point, she detects it herself. I mean, the N800 automatically detects if there's a
usable network. So, it'll log in, signing, and then it'll say, ah, I have stuff to upload.
That's when I want it to upload pictures with the GPS information embedded into the pictures and the
GPS track. And that I think really would be enough, considering that the teams that we have
who are going to be driving Trinity across the globe, we might as well say, we'll be tasked with
creating video and audio podcasts. I think that that will be just by itself cool enough. Of course,
it'd be cool if we could have some of the diagnostics of her as well. But, uh, I don't think she's
ODB-2, 3, LMNO, PASAP compliance. So, there'll be nicer consent back to the telemetry data. But just
pictures at regular intervals with GPS codes embedded where the pictures were taken and the entire
track would be a dream. What do you think? Now, how do you help smart engineers and developers
actually create this if they don't have a device? Well, I came upon, I'd say a luminous idea.
I'm going to ask Luke at Nokia to send me the full blown N800 with NAVKID.
And I'm going to set it up on a dedicated IP address.
So, that she's connected to the net. And I want to, well, maybe we should figure this out.
But I think if we made a challenge where I give, um, sorry for the geeky terminology, SSH
access to each individual engineer for, let's say, three days at a time. Then we lock it off,
change the access, someone else can come in, can try out their builds, can try, you know,
can mess with stuff. I'll also set up VNC so that you can actually see the results of any
interface work that you're doing. I think it would be like a fucking awesome project.
And, you know, and I could just be looking at this stuff and actually testing it as we go,
wherever I am because, you know, I'll use like a, was it dynamic, what is it, uh, the dynamic DNS
people, or they are, you know, so that you can always have the same IP address, same DNS, entry,
even though your IP address changes. And you can just SSH right into the box, do your work,
do all your testing. I think three days should be enough. So, if you're interested, send me an email
Adam at podshow.com. And, uh, I got some syncing up to do with, uh, with Barbara, the Palo Alto
podcaster because I've just basically changed everything off. So, stay tuned for more updates.
Trinity. The cause of central luxury. Trinity. Trinity. Left the bio diesel set.
You bring Trinity. Trinity. Trinity. Trinity. Trinity.
Free Trinity. You save the world. You win valuable prizes. All right. It's Monday. Let's
crank this puppy up. Fresh from the pod save music network. Lemon heads.
It's all on the again. I can't balance in this race. It's no longer familiar to me.
It's become routine. The bedroom is too old. The subway is the old.
What I've heard of your style and I feel, have a feeling, have a feeling, have a feeling
strong. I can move it through the back of my mind. I'm not just fool's afraid from time to time.
I'm with us. We're in about to get no hold on me. We lost our right arm. It's that full free.
The bedroom is too old. The simple way to view.
The bedroom is too old. I've heard of your style and I feel, have a feeling, have a feeling,
have a feeling strong. I can move it through the back of my mind.
The tip to the last tip that's safety outstrip, but I know I'll end up shovel,
less than perfect fit. The bedroom is too old. Simple way to feel.
The bedroom is too old. I can move it through the back of my mind.
I'm with us. I can move it through the back of my mind. I can move it through the back of my mind.
I can move it through the back of my mind.
The bed of number if you're calling from the United States, if you're in the UK, we've got a number
specially for you. Plug it into your phone.
For today, folks, back to the G-Mails. Looking for people who want to SSH me. Come into my
ports. Okay, so tomorrow may be coming to you from San Francisco. Then the show may be a little bit
delayed. Sometime this week, I do expect to go. Who knows? I might go straight to LA because we've
got some stuff going on. Hopefully the Oscars as well. The life. It is so busy.
Stick it in your ear.