This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Roll out the red carpet and strike up the band.
It's time for Adam Curry and the DSC 669.
Six hundred million dollars worth of airplane striatci my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm trying to be short.
I'm casting this out of curry.
Go on, I'm taking out the trash.
And once you get them out, tell them not to come back again.
Go!
That cat in the gym.
To what he said.
To everything you did.
You had a figure out a wild ago.
And I know it's not exactly breakin' news.
But it's all in a little like a trial for you.
And a bunch of time and won't make it true.
I'll come on, go!
Why not take out the trash.
And once you get them out, tell them not to come back again.
No, why not give them this land.
Get them to get straight.
Get them to go get them to go home.
So play that.
He's just making it up.
And he's still a little got you coming back for all more.
Why never ever thinkin' breakin' it up.
Tell me what the bad dude is gonna close that up.
I'll come on, go!
Why not take out the trash.
And once you get them out, tell them not to come back again.
No, why not give them this land.
Get them to get straight.
Get them to go get them to go home.
I'm not sitting on the floor.
No, why not take out the trash.
And once you get them out, tell them not to come back again.
Yes, there's like every work is still.
Why not take out the trash?
It's Friday.
You know it's trash.
Full bar is full of fact on the drier.
Why not take my big Giants.
God, that's a great song.
I do like it.
Daily Short Code 6-6-9 coming to you from the Curry Manor on the west side of
Utah and Gilford in the Apple and South of Missouri.
I am so tired.
Are you feeling alright?
Are you just about ready to wrap up your week?
Cause I sure am.
My goodness.
It's going to be kind of a maximum mashup Friday today.
Some great stuff came out over at mashuptown.com.
I just couldn't choose one.
So I chose two or three.
Yeah, my goodness.
Let me tell you.
I feel like a working stiff.
I've been working every single day.
I mean, not that I don't work every day, but like going to London.
And man, we had the big digital musical awards on Tuesday.
Of course, we last spoke on crap.
Or was it Monday?
Another great two-show week.
Yes, we're doing fantastic.
Sorry.
Hitting the microphone out of frustration.
I don't know if you had a chance to check out the plus, plus TV, which we launched in conjunction
with our backstage past coverage of the digital musical awards.
Quite a few people actually did check it out.
I'm just looking at the numbers here.
And the reason I'm looking at is because, of course,
is a press release being prepared about this.
This is great mainstream love this shit.
We had over a million uniques to the homepage for the plus TV and or dma.podshow.com.
And over 700,000 unique streams served during the actual coverage itself,
average viewing time, peak to about 23 minutes.
Now, you have to understand that this, to me, is it just blows me away.
Yeah, I knew that, you know, people would watch this stream.
Of course, what we really were doing was creating just lots of segments,
stuff that you can get from dma.podshow.com.
You can look at it after the fact that it's downloadable.
It's not streaming.
Maybe it's embedded on my question.
I got to check that.
We knew that, you know, we'd have Dr. Cockney there.
No Jay and Joe Lawrence and Natalie Delcante.
And everyone was creating segments for their regular shows.
But I had no idea so many people would look at the stream.
And so I'd say we're getting somewhere with this.
We've kind of backed into something beautiful,
the kind of happened.
Well, not entirely, not that it wasn't by design,
but I just didn't expect it to pop this.
There's early this heavily, in fact,
when we changed all the redirects to send everyone back to the plus TV.com.
The page basically crashed.
So much traffic coming to it.
And I believe actually tonight,
at what it's somewhere after midnight,
the digital music awards airs on channel 4 here in the UK.
From what I understand from last year,
we will, if not rival,
we may even exceed viewership numbers with what we saw online.
Then what people will watch tonight on channel 4 on publicly available broadcast television.
This is a tipping point for me.
Yeah, I'm really, really big.
So I want to just say thanks again to the entire team.
So many people worked on this.
Besides, I hear my mouth here.
It's dark, not blond.
Our UK crew, of course,
under expert leadership of James Bedford and Woody Glaskow.
But, you know, everyone pitched in and worked so hard.
We had five people with editing stations.
We had five people doing camera.
Of course, we had all our hosts.
We had everyone from the office pitching in.
However, they could doing anything,
carrying crosses, serving drinks,
grabbing sea liberties,
and deal liberties to bring them down to our party.
It was great.
And, of course, in San Francisco,
quite a big crew working on keeping the streams up,
including the good folks over at Akamai,
who at one point did have some issues.
I think we had eight or nine thousand concurrent viewers,
and they had to switch some stuff,
because I don't think they were expecting that kind of traffic either from us.
At least Aaron's, of course,
who has really brought this project to life.
If you haven't seen it yet,
check out theplustv.com.
Just a taste of where some of the things are headed
to some interface stuff.
And, of course, November December,
as when we're going to see a whole brand new podshow.com.
I telling you, we're working stiffs.
We're actually working for singing for our supper these days.
Now, I do have a small beef folks in the UK.
So I haven't done a show for the past one, two, three days.
Three days, no show.
And when I check into the voicemail,
not a single call from the UK.
Shame on you.
Plus, four, four, two, seven,
six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three,
plus four, four, two, seven,
six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
Hey, it being maximum music,
maximum mashup music,
full bar Friday.
Let's jump right into the goodness with a young palette hit-off.
One girl in casting with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam, are you ready to be stopped?
I'm ready.
Adam, it's just a hit-off number 90,
and this is in-drawn number one.
Oh, y'all don't do this to me.
I think the way to deal with that is.
I'm a whole note to me, the other two.
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
Level 42.
We're there.
Living without you, something like that?
Level 42 for sure.
Okay.
I've got one going there.
And this is number three.
Buffalo.
That's easy.
Huh.
A nanacherry.
Buffalo stance.
I think number one was hollow notes, but I'm not sure.
Let me hear the answers, young.
And times up in detail, the answers.
From 1985, yeah, hall and notes, and out of touch.
Tap, tap.
She's getting up is all men with no.
You think the body of this week.
Oh, yeah.
Do you ride a touch?
You're not a touch.
Nice work.
And you're not a row.
Answer number one, hall and notes.
Yes.
And this is answer number two from 1986.
Level 42 and something about you.
How can it be?
Better love.
Come, better can't reach.
Be kind of like something about you.
Baby.
So ride.
I couldn't leave.
Level 42 and answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
Yes.
And then it's Harry.
From 1989.
Yes.
Who's that fellow?
We're dancing.
We're not a touch.
It's sweet.
We are singing a photo of those stamps.
We can dance.
And you love baby night, man.
I need nothing left in chance.
So don't leave.
Fresh with me.
Buffalo stands for Manicherry's.
Answer number three.
And that concludes hit tests number 90.
Yeah, yeah.
10 more to go, man.
The iTunes links can be found at hittest.partshow.com.
show.com. And next week I'll be back for hit test number 91. So, until next time, take care.
And bye-bye.
A young sent a little accompanying note with today's hit test saying,
I had my compressor wasn't working. I hope it doesn't suck too bad.
Yon, it's still the wall of sound man, no matter what you do.
Good tracks. Definitely good tracks. Oh man, it was so funny to see Christina at the digital
musical awards. And because she knows a lot of these bands. She was very disappointed.
Of course, the block party wasn't there. I think they won like four awards.
I've very own Jill Mills, by the way, won an award for the block party video podcast,
which she produces, congratulations to Jill. Nice to see that her loose-site award was stolen.
This is very same night of the awards. She was busy doing segments for the plus.
And someone stole it. Nice.
Christina was basically trying to get the guys from Hadoogan,
which turns out is a local gulfard band.
We have some kick-ass tunes. We're playing the video on the plus right now.
The plus TV.com. She was like, hey, why don't you guys go get me a drink from the bar?
She was making the band get her drinks. Oh, it was too funny.
And then I think she got an offer to be driven home by lethal visual,
which she respectfully declined. And she was hanging out with the guy from the guys from the rakes.
And she knew all these guys. She's seen him perform.
I saw them like two months ago with the back line.
So she's totally into it and was totally in her element. And of course,
looked totally mini-me. She was completely like the lady Patricia,
who was there in her beautiful red dress.
Somewhere there was an interview I think that Amanda Davies did.
They were both about Amanda. We brought her in. She works typically.
She works for BBC Sports.
But she's a producer and man, she did a great job on a lot of this music stuff.
Speaking of awards, just a quicker rewind back to the podcast new media,
new media. The podcast, the new media expo.
The new media expo in Ontario, Canada.
I was a bit disappointed myself with the actual awards ceremonies,
and such a, to do was made about it in the potto sphere.
Hey, Adam Curry. This is Nick Jackson from the Bay Area in California.
I'm just calm to give a little bit of feedback.
One, I just listened to Father Rodger on the daily breakfast.
He actually recorded some of the award ceremony for the podcast awards.
And I got a green and a pretty random award show.
I was hoping for a lot of time to give some good speeches.
Really thankful listeners talk about community interpreters.
Twenty-second blurb to give the...
Yeah, like we had network news to hit at the top of the hour.
We only limited it to speak for 20 seconds.
Side of your podcast, which was pretty weak, but anyway.
Yeah, yeah, I agree.
Let's do that right next year, guys.
If it's going to be in Vegas, let's do a big extravagant Vegas award show.
Do real awards.
By the way, I got to look for that email.
I mean, I can find it.
I was asked.
There's someone setting up new awards.
And I just wanted to give my opinion on that.
Let me see if I can find it.
Oh, here we go.
I guess it's...
P-dilled.
So I guess it's podcast pickle.
He and Brian A bit from Coverville are starting a new awards for podcasters.
And they're compiling a panel of 50 judges to help decide who wins.
So they've got a lot of people on me.
You know what?
Here's my thing about awards.
I don't want to judge anyone's show.
Because that's basically what we're trying to move away from.
I think.
Who's to say that my show is no good.
If I only have 10 people and I have crappy production.
And I can barely speak.
It's good for those 10 people.
So it just doesn't make any sense to have an award show.
Because we don't have a limited channel space or shelf space or anything like that.
I'm just against it.
And it's the same thing like podcast user magazine.
Does reviews and rates shows.
By saying, well, this show sucks.
Production is no good.
Guy talks stupid.
You know, who is anyone to criticize any type of podcast?
Whatever.
It just seems like it's not encouraging to me.
And a lot of the same people will always be winning because the way these awards are set up with.
You know, basically the bigger audience.
It's not the same audience voting.
It's everyone's individual audience.
And so the biggest audience is by default going to win.
I saw what was it.
I got a business week.
Best of the web.
Manchin.
I wasn't really an award for the daily source code.
That was nice.
I appreciate that.
I have no idea how that came to be or who determines that.
Hopefully, just the business week and editors.
No, no, no, no, no.
Awards.
And even a PR company's love this shit.
Oh, man.
The times that our PR firms who have come and gone.
I might say, you've said, no, you've got to do an award show.
I'm like, no, it's fucking stupid.
I hate award shows.
Yeah, but the press loves it.
It said, well, then tough shit.
Then we just don't do any press.
It don't like doing award shows.
I think it's degrading and silly.
More important things to talk about.
I also wanted to give a little bit of.
I wanted to give you a couple of little red pills that you could drop.
I'm reading on the board's dilemma by Michael Polin right now.
And this thing has just been now read.
I'm looking right right at me.
And I'm just going to read you a little bit of.
A little excerpt from the book.
All right.
We've been studying the journal of the medical association.
predict that a child born in 2000 has a one and three chance of developing diabetes.
African American child chances are two and five.
Because of diabetes and all the other health problems that a company will be for these days.
Obviously today's children may turn out to be the first generation of American who's like expecting
see will actually be shorter than their parents.
Because of over nutrition.
I think is what it is.
I'm not limited to America.
The United Nations reported that in 2000.
The number of people suffering from over nutrition.
A billion.
Can you believe that shit over nutrition is not amazing.
And that's what has become.
My goodness.
Crazy.
The world is crazy.
Look this more shit.
That's crazy.
Check this out.
Hi.
My name is Rebecca Nay from Traini Recradio and the rights of my community are under attack.
Democratic leaders in the US House of Representatives have decided to strip protections for transgender people
from the Employment Non-Discrimination Act.
Also known as Enda.
Due to fears that it would likely be defeated if it included a transgender provision.
This action by our Democratic leaders has the potential to divide the LGBT community.
This is ultimately what our opponents want and we can't let this happen.
Call or email your representative now and urge them to oppose
a non-inclusive end-up bill.
I appreciate your support.
You can let me up.
And Patricia heard this promo and she said,
Adam, you've definitely got to play that.
What kind of messed up shit is that?
So there you go.
Statally source code 669.
The maximum mashup full bar Friday.
We've got some more red pills on the way.
Some interesting TSA stories and tracks from the brand new Best of booty 2006 CD.
You have got to check this out.
Link in the show notes on dailystorescode.com.
If you want a whole shit load of mashups to drop onto your MP3 player,
you'll dig it, including this one from the club tour.
It's all the same.
Only the names will change everyday.
It seems we'll waste it in a way.
We're in the place where the baits is also cold.
I've drive on night just to get back home.
I'm a cowboy.
I'm a spearside.
I'm on it.
I'm a cowboy.
I'm a spearside.
I'm on it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, only of this dreams, that won't if I take a picture on my back, I'm waiting for some keys to and we'll some really— uphill, I'm being very old, I'm being never united in the ground—I've seen a million-based dream.
I've seen a million faces and I've rocked him off as I'm a cowboy on a steel house that I ride
That's messed up different brightening the UK they are the best of booty
2006 CD to club tones, careless or dead von Joey versus George Michael it's almost perfect
Unbelievable how the club tones got this to fit and what's so messed up about this is
You know how I talk about the soundtrack to our lives and of course I know exactly where I was when I first heard George Michael's careless whisper as
I do know for dead or alive from Bond Joey and
It's like
It's a memory mashup in my head and it's really conflicting because I remember the girlfriend I was with during careless whisper yet
Dead or alive was
Early MTV days for me and that's very two two very different periods of my life
So mashup memories live more from that best of booty
2006 CD which you're just going to love everything is downloadable again link in the show notes
Speaking of the soundtrack to our lives hey Adam it's Bernie and I just had the perfect storm of podcasting in my ear
But I'm driving down around 17 and you know where that is and I'm listening to the end of your podcast and you start playing the load out
I got to tell you
Yeah, it just made it all very special for me at that time knowing I'm in your home state
Listen into you play one of your favorite tunes. It's one of mine too for anybody who's ever done a show
Or fit on the road or been on that dark stage looking at into that house with house
It's a great time. So thanks for sharing another piece of the soundtrack for your life and of mine
Appreciate it. Oh, man. Can I just imagine driving down route 17 listening to that? Yes, I can
Awesome to thank you
You know, I've told you about the the McCains. This is the young like three or four-year-old
Madeline McCain who was allegedly abducted from their vacation
bungalow or a apartment in Portugal and this thing has been a world news
Now talk about your perfect storm
So about two months ago. I think I mentioned this who hooked up with
With the guy named Gordon Smith. He is the spirit messenger
This is a guy who does grief counseling. He literally
Speaks to the dead and let me tell you this guy is for all intents and purposes as far as I'm concerned this guy is the real deal
And who was talking so loudly down there? Who on a second? I can't get into my vibe
All right, I'm back in the vibe now
So this guy who used to be known as the psychic barber, which I think he's trying to get away from
That's not exactly the kind of business that he's that he's in. I mean, he literally he actually he won't take money for a reading
He gives a
Symposium and conferences and he writes lots of books and very very famous in the UK
But what has happened is
And this is an every single newspaper in the UK. It's been this way for the past week
That the McCain's apparently have approached him to do a reading to see if they can find out what happened to Maddie
And can you believe that we actually just shot our first series of shows with Gordon Smith
Which are supposed to start running. I think
Not this coming Sunday, but the Sunday after next
So yeah, and let's go in like 10 days from now or less yet 10 days from now
And it would be of course phenomenal if we got the McCain's on the show. I don't know if that's gonna happen, but
It's phenomenal this guy when you see his show when you see what he does and he did he does that for regular people, right?
So not for for celebrities not for any again. He doesn't charge any money for it
He's purely doing this to try and help people when you see this show. It's it's gonna freak you out
But it's also just gonna give you goosebumps because he does really help people
Feel much better after they have had some sort of communication with with the deceased
Spirit messenger Gordon Smith be on a lookout for him
Exclusively on pod show amazing amazing. Amazing how that shit just came together
Ah, so so much coming up. I told you until the end of the year. It's just gonna be crazy busy
And I'm gonna be lacking on shows and running all over the world and just trying to make stuff better
Make it all work for you. Here's the question that came in that I definitely want to answer again
Hi, this is Wayne. I'm a listener from the US
I had a comment in a question. I've got an awesome and I was listening to
John C. DeVorac this tech five report and I was looking at it all my
His new seed his DeVorac and censored new seed on my iPhone and that's where I saw the tech five report
Well when I access the web page like on a computer. I get a flash player to play the episode
But on my iPhone he put like a quick time link so that I can listen to the show on my iPhone and I thought that was really like cool
So then I tried going to pod show to see if maybe I could do the same thing with a
A channel I created but I wasn't able to figure out how to do that
Maybe it's not even possible
Oops, sorry forgot to open the mic. Yeah, first of all, let me say
We have an undocumented feature which we have not released publicly yet John and I I think it the only ones who are using it
When you upload a show
to pod show
You can configure it again. It's it's not documented. It's not publicly released yet, but it can be configured so it will automatically crosspost
To a WordPress blog so if you look at curie dot com you'll see it's the exact same show notes
What is added is a download link a direct download link to the mp3 file
Which is probably what you're what you're hitting off of DeVorac dot org slash blog
And it also will add in a link to
for comments to the actual
Episode archive page on pod show dot com so that's what you're seeing there so that is
Indeed something that is a little special and has not been released publicly
I know a lot of people have been asking for it a lot of people want it so it will it will surface
With you know with do time we're just gonna make sure it's scalable and then everything works perfectly because
Shit does happen from time to time when you're talking from one server to another one and the two aren't really related other than this
You know minor connection that it's making so that's what you're seeing there
Yeah, if I could create a channel and listen to it on my eyes and that would be like really great
um
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
All right, so I know what happened you so if you haven't used the channel editor at podshow.com
You really should because this thing is fantastic it gives you the opportunity to create channels
Of as many shows if you want but also to determine how many episodes will actually surface in your feed
So you can already kind of automatically manage how much information is coming in
You can even put single episodes in there that just stay
You know if you just want to have one episode that's in there or if we want to create a a feed of
Individual episodes for someone else you can just create that if nothing will update it'll change until you change it
And we had to make some choices because you'll you'll see that you know if you want to subscribe to a channel
There's a number of ways to do it and one of them is put this on my iPod
So that is kind of typically what you use to put it on to your iPhone however
I've found before I I bricked my
Brick my iPhone by drowning it in the toilet
I found that if you click on the RSS icon or if you just ask for the raw XML when you when you configure it so make your channel
Right then zoom in with your little pinch move there zoom in and
And click on the RSS icon which is that little orange and white kind of like a transmitter icon emitting thing
The way the iPhone is set up it will actually give you a page a bookmarkable page of
Your channel and from there you can just click it and it'll automatically
Open up the file it'll start streaming it in it works great for video
It does fantastic for audio of course. You can't actually save this to the device
But you can play it in real times if you've created a channel and you want to see it on your iPhone to
Go to your channel zoom in click on the RSS icon and
Automatically a page that you can bookmark will appear on your iPhone that then you can use in perpetuity
I use it every single day back when the ship was still working
Behind all my DSC yet. I say it's if you've covered this. It's okay, but part of the reason is is that my
ISP wonly allow me
150 megabytes oh no for our period so no when I knock out it like
You know cut off my computer for 24 hours so it's really kind of a crappy deal
But it's the only choice I've got living in the country here
So you know
Anything that could help would be a great so okay. You got it there's anything I can do with pot show
Yeah, it's done
Hello, hello
Oh
Hang up I guess
So that's it. It's real simple. Hey, we're supposed to go to Germany
Either Sunday or Monday or perhaps Tuesday. Not quite sure
And in case it wasn't clear it definitely looks like Paul's Dom is going to be
The new home of PSG which would be pod so pod show pod show Germany
I could not be more excited particularly on a day like today when I'm thinking yeah
It'd be nice to fly over to Berlin
And you're right. I'm more slowly teased you all through the payment. Yeah, I admit it
I noticed what it is about you. It makes me want to tease you
But I heard what you said about my sticky lip gloss you brat and I heard
Are you sure it was lips either lip gloss lips lob lip gloss? You gossiping about me with Don and Drew
Notty naughty boy and
And you also stole my butt plug joke. What a brat
Anyways
Song for you and it's not love spirals although there are plenty of those up on
PMN right now, but I was song that I think fits
This weekend very well because I know some secrets about you that you may not think I know
What you did or tried to do at the expo you naughty man
And so this song is by bittersweet and it's called dirty laundry
Singe the link
And by the way, yeah, if I had realized when you invited me up to your private sweet that it was just to make a pod cast
I would have so ban there
Don
All right, Angie go ahead
I dare you. What did you find out about me? I already told everybody
I'm a horrible boy. I'm proposition every one of the five women who were at the portable
New new new new new new new new dexpo
New media that's what it's got to be called for now on
It's a good one Friday with bitter sweeps dirty boundary
I've got a bad boy and that's all
I wish me
Just dirty laundry is nothing but I can't get paid
And when you need to nullify
You can use all night
Oh
I'm just too bad girl that's why we're getting
No
Oh
Oh, when you're out of this way, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, okay, right here, excitedly,
yeah, resetting little adhrings, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey... this year you dialed so..
I think I rather miss way ahead of you
You're awake
Was a fun day inside you
Think I'd rather miss way ahead of you
Wohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohoho god atta
You're afraid will swallow fireworks fall into pieces and there's a dream when shine reflections.
Yeah, nice one, Angie, I like it.
By the way, was it not amazing that I got that USB lava lamp in the shape of a rocket
from Skip G. And I put it in my bag, my carry-on bag, and so here's a rocket-shaped
liquid-filled device with a cord attached to it that got through no problem. I got to love
the security of the American airports. Particularly when they kill people. Let's see, did
you hear about this? Let me see. I thought I actually have a comment about it checking out.
Hey Adam, this is Bob Evans and Birmingham, Alabama shopping at Walmart. Well, I was listening
to the DSC and you were going on about the TSA and after getting the woman's name and
what part of the country, but somewhere over here, some woman was putting custody because
she was just acting up too much when she couldn't get on the airplane that she was
looking at and she died while she was in the holding tank. So I just thought that might
kind of line up with the TSA story from hell. So anyway, I thought you might get a, just
you wouldn't get a kick out of that since it's a very unpleasant ending, but isn't
an interesting that you're going off on TSA and that happens. Yeah. Yeah, this is very
unclear. September 28, Carol and Gottbaum was arrested and put into a holding cell in
that Phoenix Sky Harbor airport because she was I rate. She was I, you know, I tried
to see the CNN video, which is an embedded video and it's just not working. It was posted
by Chris from the Captain Chris from the Plain Maddenes podcast and unfortunately, it's
just not playing back very well. But she choked to death in her in the holding cell and
the TSA are saying, oh, you know, that's because she was trying to go out of her handcuffs
and she inadvertently choked herself. Yeah. Yeah. That happens a lot. Doesn't it? I read
about that and I see that on cops every single day. That doesn't sound right. I think
that she might have just been so upset and emotional that she might have choked on something
somehow, but seems highly unlikely that that happened. John, you Dell posted today. Where
was it? John Udella, who's a quite famous in the blogosphere? Hmm. I said, I should
be home by now, but instead I'm writing this in O'Hare Terminal B. Why? Well, here's the
dialogue as I prepared to board at C-TAC this morning, the United Agent. Where's the TSA
stamp on your boarding path? Me, stamp? United Agent. Yeah. They have to rubber stamp them
now and they've missed you. No, for God's sake. I had to hop back on the shuttle train,
head back to the main terminal where a dollar TSA guy padded me down and right about
the time the door to my plane was closing stamped my now useless boarding pass. Oh, but it
made me feel so much safer. Yeah. I've noticed this. This is the new thing. Where the idiots
at the front of the line are just there to look at your ticket, look at your passport.
Don't even look at me. In fact, I'm now wearing sunglasses when I go through a TSA just
to see if it makes a dip. They don't even ask me to take them off and give a shit. To
share my tell you. Oh, next week I want to get back into following the money stuff
because a lot of good comments have been coming in. It's just it's been it's been a
little bit crazy. Yes, so speaking of my lava lamp. Hey, Adam, your TSA buddies are at it
again. I just thought I'd let you know that in the Houston Chronicles on CNN they're
talking about the fact that people aren't going to be able to bring their remote controlled
toys on the airplane anymore. There goes your vibrator, Adam, bummer. Oh, well, bummer.
I can take the batteries out, but it'll be alright. No pun intended. Yeah. Yeah. Now, I'm going
to keep traveling with that lava lamp, dude. That because it looks totally like a go away.
Oh, hold on a second. Okay. I think that's Candyman Luke from Nokia. He's been up my
ass for the past week and I just have paid no attention to anybody who've been so incredibly
busy. Also in the news, this is pretty interesting. The R I I the R I A A lawsuit against a single
a single mother of two. I love the way the press always writes that. Files were liable for
copyright infringement for sharing files on Kazah. $222,000 is the fine that will be levied
against her, which means she'll pay it one way or the other. That's pretty amazing. You know,
and even if she was file sharing, you know, is it really a quarter of a million dollars worth
of damages for one person to be sharing files? Particularly now that records are now being given
away. Radiohead, you know, you choose the price Charlotton's or Charlotton's UK no price free.
This is all changing very, very quickly. This is probably, I would predict this is going to be one of
the last big fines or awards we'll see in this type of litigation. It's it's just not sustainable.
You know, the litigation costs three, maybe four times as much. There's no way that it makes
any business sense to be doing this. Yeah, that's the voicemail message. Can't wait to hear
what to Candyman Lucas to say. Okay, so who knows what's going to happen this weekend?
I may be going to Berlin on Sunday. I really hope that I have time to do a couple of shows next week,
because honestly, you can ask Patricia. I'm really out of sorts. It's pissing me off, and you know,
I got up. It's like, it's nine o'clock. I've got to be upstairs. I've got to do my show. I've got to get
this going because it's just killing me. I can't. Not doing shows. Football Friday, we're wrapping
up with another one from a Best of Goody 2006 CD, Hill Shirt, and Fox Problems.
Let me hear your love. Let me grow. Oh, you know, you know, heartbreaker.
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, love maker.
Let me see. Now, I see you. I'm down on the scene.
Oh, Foxy. You may be, you want to get up and scream, Foxy.
Oh, baby, listen up. I need a fuck about this. I'm tired of waiting for my precious time.
You've got to be on it all night. Let me see. Let me see. Let me see. Let me see.
I'm gonna take your home. I will do you no harm, no. You've got to be on it all night.
Foxy, ladies. Come on, they give you everything.
I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it
I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it, I've got to pull it
I'm gonna fly home home to watch a baby
I'm gonna fly in my land
I'm gonna fly home to watch a baby
I like to breathe on my head
Let me go
Let me go all over
Let me let me go
Let me go
I don't know about you, but that gets me in the mood for the weekend.
Tiltured.
Master of Jimmy Hendrix, Jimmy Bowhorn, airfield and rock team to bring you...
Fuck.
Problem.
Again, it's all on the best of booty, 2006 AD.
Show, links in the show notes at datasourcecode.com.
Yeah.
By the way, that was not the candy man who was calling that was will.
Ah.
The German connection.
Mm-hmm.
We'll ramp it up, getting ready looking for us to arrive.
What the hell is it today?
It's Friday.
Monday Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Thursday.
I'm Friday.
I don't find a fun only.
We'll have to be very honest.
It just didn't have much time to think this week.
It was all execution mode.
Production.
Doing shit.
Getting shit done.
Doing doing.
Not just talking.
Um.
Here's what I'd like you to do for next week.
I'd like you to just do a little bit of homework.
It's really easy.
Just be on the lookout for stories about central banking, currency exchanges.
And anything really that has to do with global finance.
Because I think that there's some moves are going to be made very soon.
Um, and this is all part of the follow the money.
You know, let's just forget about, let's not forget, but I just want to put some things in the past
behind us and move forward and see if we can change our future because I really do feel that
following the money will lead us to where our leaders want to take us.
And we just may not agree with what they want to do.
Now add to that that it seems very likely that the United States is going to make a quote,
surgical strike on Iran.
We really have to step up here as citizens of the United States certainly,
but I see no reason why citizens of the United Kingdom could not do exactly the same.
We really have to manage our governments.
They work for you and I.
And we've got to manage them so that they basically do what is reflective of the majority.
So far, either we're not in the majority,
people who are against all this insanity or we're just not doing it right.
Something is definitely very wrong.
If you listen to that end promo earlier from Tranny Rack,
if you think about how central banks are really controlling a lot of what's happening in the economy,
and what is going on with the dollar?
Excuse me, the hell is wrong?
Things are not good.
They just don't feel right.
So let's follow the money, all those stories.
Nylon, where the hell are you?
Aren't you in this business?
Don't you understand this kind of stuff?
Call in.
We need to understand what's going on.
You've been away too long, my friend.
All right, so I hope all of you have a great weekend.
You know, don't get too freaked out.
Just chill out over the weekend.
Relax a little bit.
Be with your loved ones.
But follow the money.
Keep your eye on the ball.
Remember to take the red pill.
And I look forward to talking to you next week.
Probably from Germany.
Have a great weekend, everybody.
Bye-bye.
I'm gonna introduce everyone.
Take those day food by Friday.
Adam's final thought on the week.
Another part show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily
by the sharpest minds and content delivery.
Pudge-o in limite.