Yo, what's Tony Costa telling you to check out this Christmas podcast.com is the official podcast for the new Sony film this Christmas
starring Chris Brown for Genie King Columbus Short and an all-star cast. The site includes a special holiday podcast from yours truly
exclusive interviews from the stars in the film and a special red carpet coverage from the premiere
You can exchange gifts, but you can't exchange family. This Christmas is truly the next holiday classy
See it in theaters on November 21st and check us out at this Christmas podcast.com
Philip Johnson of Fort Worth, Texas has a problem
I want to be entertained
Philip wants to be entertained
For Philip we have the DSC 685
With Adam Curry and all the entertainment
Phil can stand
Do I take the red pill nail?
With $16 million worth of airplane straps my ass
Transmitters
In the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need loss
Thinking turns me in
I like to think of something
Fantastic
This is Adam Curry
I like to think of something
I like to think of
Something
I like to think of something
I like to think
But I watch someone
I like to think about things
I like to think about something
I like to think of something
Everything looks like this
It looks like this
What does it look like
Yes, people come up with and
The first thing they came up with
It's not like it has it is too mad
It's not like someone
It has some kind
So I don't realize that
That has become my
wonderful
I've jimmed it so that I can use the internal mic. Now, of course, if I had another
three and a half inch to three and a half inch cable, then I could have used my proper microphone
although this doesn't sound too horrible. I mean, how sinky my friends it is it's really weird. I've no idea.
My body is completely confused
because only a few days ago I was on San Francisco time that's eight hours different from London,
flew to London. So, you know, kind of made the change over there. And this morning, after a lot of
crap at the airport, I finally got on a flight to Helsinki. The flight is only two and a half hours,
but you gain two hours in daytime, in hours. It's basically, it's two hours ahead of London,
so 10 hours ahead of San Francisco. Right now it is my body is saying it's 12, 23 in the evening,
which UK time would be about right, about time to go to bed. In fact, I just spoke to the lady
Patricia and bit her idea for the evening. She was a retiring, but here, of course, it's almost
two thirty in the morning and it's not like I get an extra two hours to sleep tomorrow because we've
got a number of meetings throughout the day. I'm definitely going to sleep on the plane ride,
ho, that's for sure. Of course, we're up here meeting with one of the few companies that
that everybody knows, a worldwide, which is a fine finish company called Nokia,
and they make all kinds of cool shit. Like, well, you might have seen a cell phone or two from them.
And of course, I'm a big fan of the 800 and they have a new device. I think we're just shipping
this week, the N-810, which is their brand new web tablet, which hopefully I'll get a chance to play
with tomorrow. Lots of people I've heard said it's pretty awesome. So I'm in a really depressing hotel
to give you an idea. I'm overlooking a shipyard that's building a cruise ship,
which is in the harbour. They've like three harbors in Helsinki, and I'm on the
southwestern side, and I walked into the hotel lobby and there was like a junior soccer team for
England, actually, and they were checking in. So it's kind of like, yeah, I'd say it's on the
level of holiday in something like that. I've got a nice little couple of espresso here,
a nice espresso machine. They've got here in the room, and so it's going to be kind of a short show
if you don't mind. Just play a couple of things, got some music, sure my brain will reset itself,
and I can tell you some stories about the past couple of days, because of course this is the
delayed source code instead of the daily source code, and some calls coming in on the voicemail lines,
it's our Savant of all things nuclear, a topic that animates raw atoms, your atomic Savant.
Yeah. I noticed yesterday that Al Gore has joined cleaner Perkins, your favorite
venture capital firm, was wondering if you do me a favor, if you ever get to meet the man,
can you ask him why he is reluctant to talk about atomic energy as a weapon in the fight against
global warming? That's a good question. That's a good question at topic, Rod.
And I do have a feeling that I may be meeting him soon. There's talk going on, you know?
It was a big supporter of the initial development of the technology.
Al Jr. made a whole movie about the dangers of global warming and some actions that can be
done to prevent it from harming the planet. The only time he ever alluded to nuclear was when he
mentioned some of the information we have about the effects in the Arctic came from visits to the
region made by nuclear submarines. I know you're a big fan of atomic technology, and also a man
who is interested in starting challenging conversations. Uh-huh. It would be great if you could
get that discussion rolling with Mr. Gore. By the way, do you know when you're good red pill
pushers? I think I'm hitting my supply too hard. They seem to be getting harder and hard to find
in our blue pill dominated society. Yeah, I'll thank you. Especially because I'm doing such a fine job
of, uh, man, what is going on? This is really not working for me. Let me see, I'm just going to message
or was that still atomic rods, uh, it's just complicated. Hold on. See, now when I want to switch
applications, my thing, hold on, crap. When I want to swap applications, if I do applekey tab,
my hand actually covers the microphone because it's in the left speaker back. Oh, I know this guy
can help. I'm extra. I'm extra. I'm extra. I'm extra. I'm extra. I'm extra. I'm extra.
I'm extra. Hiya, Adam, chicken te comasara carry. Here is your eucorrespondent
CSV. So Frank of Ratini is an eucormissioner who looks very similar to Stephen Colbert, and
he has some ideas. Some of these ideas are not so good, but some are cool with things. And
example of such good idea is blue card. Just imagine this. Hello stranger. Are you talented?
Are you skilled? European Union needs you. Come over to us the very cradle of Western civilization
and get blue card that will give you unlimited stay and work payments. Green card was yesterday,
but now when US dollar is worth just 15 years since, European Union offers much better future for
you and your family. So yes, European Union is launching blue card for talented and skilled
immigrants from Asia, Africa, and South America, and it is blue because blue is color of
you flag and symbolizes peace. So fuck you Adam carry. You. You. Thanks CSV. It is pretty interesting.
Finally, a European version of a green card called a blue card. Interesting how that clear
card that I talked about the other day. It that you can bypass, you get your special security line
from the TSA. Interesting. That is also blue. I wonder if one has anything to do with the other.
Big scandal going on in the United Kingdom by the way, by the immigration or speaking of immigration.
You know what I'm hearing a delay in my headphones now. This really sucks ass.
I just need to bring a mixer with me. A battery operated mixer. I need something. This is not working
out for me. The big scandal in the UK. The government hires lots of private security firms.
Their job is to provide security. A lot of government security functions that are necessary
are performed by employees of these private security firms and turns out that the government or
a department of the government. I guess it is homeland. The department of
homeland department is just a home department. Something like that. Among all of these companies,
they have tons of them. Approximately 5,000 of these employees are working in the United Kingdom
illegally. One of them is actually tasked with standing guard at the facility where the Prime
Minister's car is housed. You can imagine what a huge security risk that is. It's just
going crazy. In fact, really interesting. This is a big deal. I don't know if it's just coincidence,
but all of a sudden now there's bird flu and that's dominating the headlines and the bird flu.
It's only the bird flu that kills birds, not people. Of course, there's always the fear that
that bird flu will migrate and mutate, I should say, and then spark over to human beings. Then
outkilling all the Christmas turkeys. So we'll have no turkey for Christmas. That completely dominates
the news. What the real news is is kind of being drowned out. And I think it's incredibly
interesting to see how they're going to handle this. I'm just going to run through a couple more
comments because the sound is really freaking me out. With love from the Buckeye Drive Time podcast
and the tone ranger.
This pops around on my head for a while now. You move to Holland when you were seven years old.
First question. When the Dutch hear you speak in Dutch. Do they think you have an
accent or do you speak just flawless? Perfect. You know, total Dutch. Do they think you have an American
accent? That's a good question. You should actually ask the lady Patricia. I think,
well, with anything, if you've been away, if you've been out of the country and if you haven't
been speaking the language continuously, well, you know, obviously, you're going to, you know,
you're the, I'm sure I have a little bit of an English accent here and there. There's obviously
some American that kind of slips through. But if I've been in the Netherlands for a week or two,
yeah, I think I speak Dutch just about undetectably. So I can't even speak English with the
fuck am I doing it? And what's the other question? I don't even circumvent a member. Yeah,
meaning there. There you go. That was a simple question. That was white. Oh, yeah.
The other question was, when you go to some of the other sort of country neary, I don't know,
it's been left or Sweden. Are there similarities to the language? Do you all must understand
or even determine? Yeah. They're like, we're just similar enough to Dutch that you could actually
kind of make out what they're saying. Yeah. If you're in there, kind of like other languages,
like, you know, which we've mentioned, Spanish or something sometimes. British, British and Italian.
Definitely. Kind of pick up. Yeah. Just curious. Use it if you want.
Yes, you have a query. Thank you. Thank you. Well, interesting. You used to say that walking through
the hotel lobby here in Helsinki. It's really freaky because I keep thinking, I hear a language
that I understand, but I don't quite understand. I have to understand that the Dutch is very similar
to some Scandinavian languages. If you really listen, in fact, I'm pretty good at understanding
someone's speaking in Swedish. It kind of sounds like someone's speaking Dutch is really drunk.
In fact, the Dutch, as far as I'm concerned, are back up Scandinadians, you know,
if we need more Scandinavians, we can always get them from Holland. So yeah, there's a lot of
similarities there. Finnish, very difficult, not quite the same as Swedish. And of course, German
sounds very much like Dutch. In fact, it's extremely similar. And, you know, there's what we would
say, a Yiddish South African is also very similar or South African such as say. So yeah,
there's plenty of similarities.
Featuring an inspiring main interpretation of the Richie Havens Classic, Motherland's Child.
Love the swirbles, long way from home.
Love the swirbles, long way from home. Available now when I tune as plus, Amazon and Amazon MP3,
CD Baby, music, rhapsody, or directly from lovespirals.com.
The wonderful pipes of Brian Know Everybody. Brian clearly doesn't have enough work.
We've got to give him more to do. One last phone call, an old buddy of mine, check it in. This is
I would say that Doug Moni was the first guy to pick up on what I was doing,
pre pre the word podcasting. And he published a pretty, I think, a pretty important article
for the company he's working for at the time. And he's moved around. He's a journalist. I think
he's a really good one. We go way back to the mtv.com days and low and behold ladies and gentlemen,
a savont from my past Doug Moni. Adam Doug Moni, editor in Sheep of Bond Magazine,
checking in. I just wanted to say hi. I haven't talked with you in ages. I have to confess. I
haven't listened to the DSC in ages. Oh father, please forgive me for that sin.
But I wanted to tell you I was at a party a couple weeks ago in Boston. And I heard a familiar
set of music in my years. I looked up on stage and put it I see, but Matthew Ebal, and I was really
shocked because you introduced me to Matthew through the DSC gosh, I don't know.
Years ago, year and a half ago at least. So I was able to go up on stage and talk to Matthew
and fortunately enough, he had both of his albums, both the beer and coffee albums and the new
album that he's got out. I guess goodbye to Planet Earth. But I was able to pay him 20 bucks
and bought both albums and left happy. But I just wanted to let you know that I was thinking about
you, but hopefully I'll get back into the habit of the Charlie scene. Dr. later.
Right on. Cool man, welcome back. And that's totally okay. You know, life gets in the way it
shit. That's what happens every single time. You'll want to check in with the daily source code
and life just kind of gets in the way, which is also what happens to me in producing the damn show.
All right, you asked for it. You got it. Sally went down Matthew Ebal on the Charlie
from Hell. Stinky.
Right. What's he with? Oh, buddy, but you never saw the life never heard the train coming
when he did it in the back. Sally went down. Sally went down.
Ew.
Set it with a cabbage. Something for my head.
What you got, come with me up, not to have me now, it's a girl I'm like her gonna do.
Sadden never made it to the world never saw the black never even heard the drink coming.
Sadden I went walked on the track, never where the rails took and never thought to love it.
Sadden not to see what's doing right, but she went home early, but she never saw the black never heard the drink coming when it hit her in the back.
Sadden went down, sadly went down.
Sadden didn't want to get it all, never seen before her.
Keep it down, walk around the track, maybe they would just ignore her.
But she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down.
She didn't listen to the man anymore.
Sadden!
No, no, no, no, no.
Sadden never made it to the world never saw the black never even heard the drink coming.
Sadden always walked on the track, never where the rails took and never thought to love it.
Sadden thought that she was doing right, but she went home early, but she never saw the black never heard the drink coming when it hit her in the back.
Sadden went down, sadly went down.
Sadden went down.
From the pod save music network link to that in the show notes a daily source code dot com.
Okay, I've just discovered while that was playing.
That's apparently the internet is down here in the hotel, so it's been a fine fubar all the way around, hasn't it?
I guess I'll just have to catch you guys tomorrow or Friday or whatever.
It's been one of those weeks, but know that I'm doing this shit for you too.
Not just myself.
All right, from Helsinki.
It's Adam Curry saying, live life with passion and enjoy your freedom.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Yo, what's up? It's your man Tony Costa from Causes World.
Tell them you to go check out the new Sony pictures release.
This Christmas is starts.
Chris Brown, Mokai Fife for Regina King, Lauren London, Columbus Short.
It just has an all-star cast.
You can exchange gifts.
You can exchange to socks.
You can exchange fruit cake, but you cannot exchange family.
So make sure you check out this Christmas when it hits theaters November 21st, 2007, and a mouth.