Check out some of the world's best music video.
Animation at short films from the Manchester International Festival
and brought to you by Sony PlayStation at M-I-F-D-O-D-R-C-O-D-C-O-O.
Atom Curry was just a guy with big hair who sold his first company and thought he'd just kick back and take it easy.
But he never counted on this.
Adam and Patricia, the king and queen of the matter, or just the lady and the tramp.
Only on the daily source code.
Delta Sierra Charlie 655.
Stink his Adam Curry.
Like these roses we all feed.
I'm counting with yours.
Don't free away below.
Must in the music.
All in foolishness.
All on us.
To be none of control.
Must in the music.
In the music.
Better baby please don't cry.
Wipe the guilt out from your eyes.
Me conscious on the bed.
To no one in a city.
In the mirror you're perfect.
Plastic flowers never fade.
We all turn the gray.
We're captain of course.
On the free way below.
Must in the music.
All in foolishness.
All on us.
To be none of control.
Must in the music.
In the music.
In the others we all are still.
Must in the music.
Baby, please don't cry
Why the guilt out from your eyes?
Make yourself up off the bed
So I won't ever send you
Thought it's glistening and they shine
Love you, baby, please don't cry
Why the guilt out from your eyes?
Make yourself up off the bed
So I won't ever send you
Thought it's glistening and they shine
Love you, baby, please don't cry
Why the guilt out from your eyes?
Make yourself up off the bed
So I won't never send you
Thought it's glistening and they shine
Love you, baby, please don't cry
Why the guilt out from your eyes?
Make yourself up off the bed
So I won't ever send you
Thought it's glistening and they shine
Love you, baby, please don't cry
Why the guilt out from your eyes
Make yourself up off the bed
So I won't ever send you
Thought it's glistening and they shine
Love you, baby, please don't cry
Just when you think it's prints, it turns into something else, it's David Usher, the music.
Every time some atoms all alone, any needs is love right there on the microphone.
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia.
They say to have some better than one, and with this angel from above, there's nothing that they both can't do.
Let me make you wildest dreams come true, to grab your ear buds and jam them in.
And let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Adam and Patricia.
Special Sunday edition of the Daily Source Code.
And we do indeed welcome the lady Patricia.
Oh, thank you.
I'm so happy you're here, baby.
Long time, long time since you've been on the show.
It's been at least been too long, dog.
Yes, it has.
The noise you hear in the background is the fan.
Right in dog.
And the fan is running at high high speed.
Not the dog, the cat.
No, I can hear the dog barking.
Oh, really? Why is he barking?
Why is he barking?
I don't know.
Maybe somebody wants to come in.
He can't come in himself.
No, somebody else.
Oh, someone out well, tough luck.
They can't.
That's going to annoy the shit out of me.
Do you want to have a look?
No, no.
We're just getting the show underway.
When I play the next song, you can go have a look.
All right.
So we are back from the love island.
From love island.
Indeed.
We didn't talk about this since you haven't been on the show.
We were on the fire island.
No, you didn't tell anybody anything.
It's not like everybody doesn't know about fire island.
Oh.
Is it famous?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I didn't.
In from London, from Europe.
Not in Europe.
No.
And I'm quite dismayed.
You're telling all your gay boy friends about this, because I want to keep
this.
I'm special to ourselves.
I don't want to overrun with Dutchies.
Yeah.
But so.
What do you say?
So everybody knows it already.
No, in America.
Everybody knows it.
In America.
You know, land of the free in the straight.
In a America.
Yeah.
So, what did you think of our island retreat?
Fire.
It was wonderful.
Yeah.
If the world was like that.
Everybody hugging and kissing and giggling and, you know, being nice to each other.
That is true.
It wasn't.
It was wonderful.
For all the, uh, for all the testosterone on that island, it was very, very
laid out.
Very relaxed.
Everybody was nice, friendly.
It was like, you, the minute you got off the, the ferry boat.
And I don't use that word lightly.
Very boat.
Yeah.
It's like everyone has dropped away all of their anger, all of their, I mean, I
didn't even see any hissy fits.
No.
Nothing.
No one was getting angry.
No one.
You look wonderful.
Yeah.
You must be new to the island.
Hmm.
Oh, I'm having an overload of co-tour.
Yes.
That's it.
No.
One of the dogs started to bark.
And that's what he said.
I think he had an overload of co-tour.
Yeah.
He was looking at you.
That was Christina and me.
What are dogs?
You're head phones a little bit too loud.
Is that you?
Maybe they're leaking.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Oh, don't do that.
Oh, boy.
No, no, no.
I'll close your mic for a second.
Maybe it was leaking a little bit.
Just a little bit.
With my little.
Little moody gush.
No ears.
So in all, despite the fact that we had shitty weather, we had a pretty
good time.
Yeah.
You know, had my sister there and her two kids.
They were delightful.
Very funny kids.
Very, yeah.
Extremely funny.
Yeah.
You can tell that there's a committee in the family there.
Lots of humor.
Yeah.
Especially the boy.
I just, I don't love with him.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
He was in love with Christina.
Oh, yeah.
Definitely.
He couldn't wait to snuggle up next to her watching your high school
school too.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
They loved it.
I think that it, um, with the weather as bad as it was.
I think having the kids around on my sister made it better.
Yeah, well, and what you do when the weather is bad, you actually come together
and sit down have a nice cup of tea and we did some scrabble.
Yeah.
We did scrabble.
You won the first, uh, the first game.
That was my first scrabble.
Yeah.
Well, that was great.
Especially in English.
Yeah.
You kicked ass.
Didn't I?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You didn't believe it, did you?
No, no.
I, I perfectly well believed that you could do that.
Christina was the one who was going to...
Yeah, right, Mom.
Yeah.
She showed her right.
Our daughter, by the way, who was, uh, who turns, uh, 17 tomorrow.
Mm.
Okay.
Believe it.
Yeah.
You remember 17 years ago?
I mean, I can't believe it, but yeah.
Yeah.
That's pretty amazing.
And she's, uh, now she...
And that's quite a woman.
I wasn't a woman like she is right now.
What do you mean?
When I was 17.
A woman like she is.
Well, she looks so much like an fool.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Well, she's a total...
Carbon copy of you.
No, but I didn't look like that.
I didn't...
No, no, but she's a carbon copy of you now.
No, yeah.
Yeah.
And I was 17.
I was very...
I had no hips, no breasts.
You know?
Oh, okay.
She beats you on those two.
Well, that's what I mean.
Yeah.
And she's a, uh, she and, uh, jaker off to the get-loaded festival.
What's that?
The...
I was a parent.
It doesn't sound good.
It doesn't.
You just don't want them to get loaded festival.
Only English people can come up with.
Exactly right.
You know, and by the way, um, you know, there's a lot going on right now in the UK.
The news is completely blanketed about this kid, Reese.
Really sad story.
He was shot and killed.
And, uh, believe it was up in Liverpool.
Yeah.
On a parking lot.
Yeah, yeah.
But he was...
Yeah.
Right.
So another kid on a bike on a BMX bike, uh, shot him to death.
Well, they don't know yet who it was.
Well, no, but they know that it was another kid.
It probably wasn't a kid.
They have a CCTV footage.
It's just they can't really make out who it is.
But they can see it was another kid.
They don't know which kid it was.
And so the UK is freaking out.
And, you know, this is the top of the news.
It's all that everyone's talking about.
And I'm like, you know, how hard can this be?
You know, it's really easy to see why.
And it's really easy to fix it.
See, now that always confuses me because if I watch a CSI, everything is so easy.
So easy to find out who it was.
So easy.
See all the whoops, whoops on the internet.
Whoops.
They found it.
They do this.
And this is, of course, what we as a people expect.
So this is why the news keeps on dragging it out.
Yeah.
And they're just going to keep on dragging this out.
And now it's like this huge political thing.
And, you know, we've got gangs.
And now, of course, the music industry is responsible for it.
And the video game industry is responsible for it.
And I'm telling you, the kids that do this.
Who form these gangs are kids from, I would say, middle to upper middle class families,
broken homes, no doubt about it.
Huge problem here in the UK with parents divorcing and not giving a shit about their lives.
Well, almost every friend from Christina.
Well, I don't want to say, these kids are bored.
They have nothing better to do.
They're not poor.
They're not.
They have homes.
They have places.
I know they're bored.
They're bored to death.
And they're not being looked after by their families, by their parents.
Completely left alone.
We can't, how many kids a week do it do I have here?
That's what I mean.
From, from broken homes, all my dad doesn't give a shit of a mom doesn't give a shit.
A friend of Christina, just a friend.
And they, they, they, the, two of them fell in the mud, you know.
Just a friend.
They fell in the mud.
Yeah, you know, he gave her a piggyback ride.
They were laughing.
And I know what.
But they fell in the mud.
And he shared with, covered with,
And he said, I just bought it.
And, you know, he had to work really hard for it.
So I tried to get it out.
This is Josh.
Yes.
What does Josh do?
What kind of jobs, yeah?
No.
He goes to school, right?
That's not what I wanted to say.
I know.
But I'm just being a kid.
And I said to him, you know what?
Ask your mom to spray some, uh, vanish on it.
Yeah.
Just leave it.
He said, my mom, my mom is not even there.
I always do their laundry.
Uh.
Because my mom lives with his dead.
So that's, you know, and every week,
there's somebody here in the house.
And I say, what time are you going to have dinner?
And home?
Nobody's having dinner for me.
So I might as well take them all in here.
And cook for them.
And click.
Because nobody has a normal family.
That's what I want to say.
There is no, there's no sit down dinner.
There are no dinners at all.
I always tell my say, ask your mom.
My mom doesn't live with me.
So, and I think that's the problem the UK has.
Just as an outsider looking in.
That's what I see.
That's a, you know, and we live in a very middle,
up, middle, middle, middle, middle class place.
Yeah.
And you can tell.
These kids are just bored.
They get nothing better to do.
There's nothing at home.
There's no one waiting.
There's no one looking after him.
There's no love flowing.
That's why they're here.
Yeah.
They want my hugs.
And they wanted to play with my shot.
My food.
Well, yes, that they had my food dear.
Let's be honest.
Yeah.
It was, uh, I took take away.
I slaved over that over the co-punk chicken.
But yeah, it's true.
So, do you want to go check on the dog?
He stopped barking, so maybe.
Maybe it's okay.
Yeah.
Are you listening to the music thinking?
What the hell was he playing?
Yeah.
It's a mashup.
Eight out of better known as Dr. Art 7 over.
You recognize arrows, man.
Yeah.
So, we should kiss.
There's all you really, really want to kiss your eyes.
Something special about you.
I must feel it's like you.
It's not a lot of guys don't work my time.
Oh, baby, baby, baby.
It's getting kind of crazy.
Because you want to take it over my mind.
And it feels like you.
But you don't know why.
Yeah.
That's where.
It feels like you.
Ooh.
You don't know my name.
Round and round we go.
Will you ever know?
Oh.
We live in a baby.
Yes.
And it feels like you.
Oh, you don't know.
But you don't know.
Another
You're my favorite
You're no one
You're my love
Ah, I see
I don't even know what you're doing
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine
I'm fine, I'm fine
I'm fine
You're my favorite
Your favorite
My, my, my, my,
my, my, my
Fast and
heavy
The, no.
Breez and
Flied
I've never been
Oh my god!
Wow!
Where do you come from now on?
Oh!
Where am I going to go?
Oh my god!
Where do you ever know and so many?
Well, I'm just going to go on this point.
I don't know.
I mean, it was a good matchup, but it kind of lacked soul.
You know what I mean?
Well, I'm glad it fits.
Well, you have to take a picture.
Sometimes I hear downstairs, you're playing all the mashup things.
Yeah.
That's not good.
But those are the ones that don't make it on the air.
You know?
Yeah, but a lot of them are even on the radio.
You hear mashups on the radio?
Sometimes you hear those mixes.
It does not go together.
But you don't really hear mashups.
I hate that.
I hate that if you heard mashups on the radio.
No, not really the mess up.
More.
More this.
The mess ups.
Yeah.
Are we done with the final? How about the reunion?
Yeah, that was fun.
Yeah, because this was the big curry family reunion.
You have a family that is so old fashioned.
So old fashioned.
Really?
Really true American American.
American family.
What do you mean?
The legs on their forehead.
Yes.
We are very, very patriotic.
I think everyone is pretty much a Republican.
I would have to say, although they are definitely not all for George Bush.
I think all of them hate him.
You could make a movie from these people.
Easily.
He's exactly what you see in movies.
I never thought he would really exist.
Still exist.
Yeah, dude.
Totally true.
So what sticks out in your mind last?
You know, you got well.
It's a little bit crazy.
Oh yeah.
A good way.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
We're all kind of fucked up in our little special way.
Yeah.
Special way.
Come on.
What were the high days?
Well, some of them I was disappointed because I remember when we, well, when we were
there the first time when we just arrived in America and yeah, 87 88.
They were all, remember when we were sitting at the, at the, at the, at the, at the, at the, at the.
It's Thanksgiving table.
And everybody was looking at me.
Like what is that?
Who is she?
She's from another planet.
Yes.
Nice bag.
Yeah.
So everybody's staring at me and all those questions.
So you're in show.
Okay.
That was 20 years ago.
So, and they looked at us like.
Yeah.
The two of them.
Very suspicious.
Fishy combination.
You know, but now after all these years, we're still together.
And all these people, some of them actually, now more, more of them.
Most of them are separate.
They're just separated.
Separated.
Yeah.
They're in marriage.
And a lot of them that couple of them have been to some changes.
That's for sure.
And they actually looked at us like it's never going to last.
So the real, so kind of a bummer for a lot of people who listen to the daily source
course that I didn't do an interview with, with Uncle Don.
Yeah.
You know, I did talk to him about it.
And I think that I've now, now I understand why he, he's trying to figure out what
he wants to do after it.
Yeah.
So he wrote that commentary on the book Legacy of Ashes.
Review.
Yeah.
A commentary.
He called it a review.
No.
He called it a commentary.
I heard something else.
Oh, man.
Here it is.
Right here.
Oh, then maybe he explained it to me.
A commentary on Tim Winner's Legacy of Ashes.
Well, maybe commentary.
I looked at him and he said, sort of a,
He explained to me like that.
Like a review.
Yeah.
It was too long for a review.
That's why.
But now just having read through.
It's like, he has like 700 pages this book.
It's a, it's a, it's a big ass book.
That's the one there.
The, the red one that I've been reading.
My, started tonight.
Not, not.
But I can understand why he's freaked out.
Yeah.
Because, you know, this book really,
in fact, what it really says is that he was responsible
the wrong word, but that he trained hundreds and hundreds of
Koreans to fight against North Korea and all of them died.
Just none of them came back because it was so fucked up
with the CIA that all the information that they were passing on
was lied.
Nothing, you know, there was no truth.
They had no real intelligence.
So, but he didn't know that.
No, of course he didn't know it.
But can you imagine that when that comes out that you just like
freaking out when you learn that all of your guys,
of course he knew that they, that they perished,
but he didn't know it was because his glasses were fucked up.
It's very heavy, low.
Have you low to carry in your life?
So, but I think I know how I'm going to approach this.
Yeah.
I'm working on some ideas.
I mean, he could actually do a lot
by telling people how, how the CIA worked from his perspective.
Yeah.
Is he allowed to explain it?
Well, no, he's not allowed.
That's the whole point.
Well, but, you know, the guys almost say,
you know, because I said, you know,
we could, there's a whole bunch of things we can do.
Yeah.
And he's really, you know, I think he's just,
I think he's freaked out about what he's,
what he's learning now, all these years later.
There's learning how is sinless.
Sin senseless, it all was.
Yeah.
So, did you have a nice chat with him?
Oh, yeah.
He's a very interesting guy.
Very charming.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You know, he's got that president kind of a thing.
I love it when he tells stories.
I love it when he tells his stories.
He does that well.
He loved your Clinton story, though.
Oh.
Boy, he loved that.
He thought that was awesome.
Yeah.
And he said, actually, the Clinton was quite a charmer.
And that people had, all the women in the office had to watch out for him,
because he was a butt pincher.
You know, he touched everybody.
I don't think, see, this is the stuff I don't think he would say.
I don't think he would.
Yeah, he told you.
Well, Clinton is not listening to you.
You don't know.
You never know.
Clinton's probably, they go like, oh, yeah.
That's not hot babe with the teeth she can take out.
Oh, yeah.
I love it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's mine.
I can't believe it happened to me.
But I told you, I, the moment I saw him,
I, I knew exactly what women were,
you know, attracted to him.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
I'm attracted to him.
He, he has that.
Yeah.
He's got that.
That's the thing I have.
That.
But then different.
Bigger.
I don't know.
He didn't hang him out of his trousers.
No, no.
In the elevator.
I bet he's not.
I bet he's huge.
I think so too.
You know, when I look at his nose.
He's nose is his nose.
His nose, I do.
We did square dance.
How American was that?
Oh, my god.
I square dance.
Yeah.
What's that amazing?
Yeah, I did.
That was, we'll get pictures from that.
That was pretty funny.
It was awesome, dude.
And, and line.
Blind dancing, yeah.
Blind dance.
It's my family awesome.
Yeah.
You're so right, though.
It is so worthy of a documentary.
Yeah.
Our family is pretty interesting.
And it wasn't this beautiful little.
What was it?
Sort of.
They call it the Quakers.
Yeah.
The Quakers.
Quakers.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, like early settlers bar.
Yeah.
So I said, and that's all.
I'm like, Oh, yeah.
He said, it's very old.
Very, very old.
When I said that's, though.
Because you remember the 1800s, of course, don't you?
Yes, I did.
Now, do you remember the 70s?
The 60s, 70s and 80s?
Would you like to put your knowledge to the test with young Polats Hit Test?
Yes, I would.
Okay.
It's tough though.
Sorry.
I had a, for you ready to be stumps.
They'd be used to test with young pullback.
Hey Adam, hi doing this is hit this number 84 and we're going to start right away with intro numbers going.
I know what it is.
Yeah, that's the way.
I like it casing the sunshine there.
Come on man, you got to be fast on it.
Oh, do I?
Yeah, it's time to have the number two.
I know which one that one is.
You don't know it?
Sweet dreams are made of this.
You rid mix?
You didn't hear that?
No.
Oh, she just comes third and the final one is number 3.
I don't know that one.
So run as it turns yours.
I never heard it.
I did time she up into the each hearty answer.
Here we go.
She's number one.
I got that one in the sunshine band.
That's the way.
I like it.
Okay, take this on me.
From 1975 KC and the Sunshine Band and that's the way I like it and this is number two the
Redmix from 1983
This was in 1983
You're at mix and three dreams is enter number two and this is answer number three for this week's
I test Alexander O'Neill
I never cared about this guy
I can't even sing the lyrics
From 1987, Alexander O'Neill and Criticize and that concludes hit test number 84
What? I don't speak Dutch. He's throwing tricks again. Thanks to be strikes
In iTunes can be found that the hit test of patch show does come
That's also the place to take the weight off
All right, yet am I hope you had them all and you enjoyed these three songs as always
We call the back for eight this number 85
So I hope to see you then until then take care and bye-bye
Seeing your face isn't he doesn't he make you tired?
I love him. Yeah, that's like that's like a marathon. That's a high-paced energy. That's a yarn pull that
You got one out of three. I didn't know it started already
I thought it was just part of the
No, you said he has clue number one and you got the dude
I didn't know this dude. I didn't know it was hidden in there. Oh, I didn't know and you writes some of the songs
From these days. I probably ignore oh, I know yeah, well of course no no no
This was 75
For case in sunshine man 80, but you remember your red nicks don't you remember your red nicks?
Good one. Yeah, that was the same period. You love that one. It's still good pumping out the hits. Yeah, it's like from today. It's beautiful
Yeah, but Alexander and Neil. I had no idea. Oh, no, I didn't know. I just wanted you to hear the
The latest version. This is something we're working on
You've already heard a previous version. I just want to play this little bit for a second
The lost Elvis diaries
Written by Elvis and Presley
I don't readily know if my story has a beginning or an ending
I'm just writing as a comes to me the way I done most things in my life. I cool this that people tell them I'm a natural, but
I'm not so sure what that means. We're bringing them back from the dead
Elvis yeah
Aaron Presley. This is the way he would sound now. What do you mean so that is him?
This is the king the lost Elvis diaries. No problem. She's probably
That's a good question. Yeah. Oh, there's going to be all kinds of shit. Absolutely, but this book is going to be awesome
Yeah, the lost Elvis diaries. I've already read it. Yeah, it's good. Excuse me
Why don't you do that while I'm playing the Elvis diaries? No, you got to do that afterwards. So
One horrible horrible horrible horrible thing has happened
in in the past in the past day and that is. Oh, yeah, but today it happened today. Yeah, happened today
And you know, it's not something that happens to you. It has to be
It is definitely something that always happens to you sometimes to Christina, but pretty much never to be
It happens a couple of times to me. So can you guess
People Botox
When wrong the Botox when wrong now. No
As I do on a nice Sunday morning. In fact, I do it every morning. Yeah, I go into the back bathroom
Daily download day. I'm ready for the daily download. I've got my my cup of chino
I've got something to read sometimes all I'll open up the door so I can still get Wi-Fi not the actual bathroom door
But the interconnect door so I get my Wi-Fi sometimes where you're not here. Please stay away for just about half an hour at least half an hour
And I was listening to on the media, which is a show from NPR, which I like listening to listening to that on the iPod function of my iPhone
Now look I'm my bathrobe on so I put the iPhone in the breast pocket
Right yeah, and I get up to flush
And just as I get up, I'm not quite sure what are you doing? I mean the middle of a story. You'll be fine
To steep you can be fine. You can always roll down the like a
Like a slinky
Okay, so I stand up to flush the toilet
And my hand is it hasn't even gotten into motion towards the flusher luckily. I would say and
And I have the ear buds in. I'm still listening to the show and I just see my iPhone just go right out of my breast pocket
Well, I was hoping that you know the wire the connector would stay and but you know you got that very just
As the connector dislodge and when clunk right into the bowl
Oh no, pre flush
So of course, I do what what any true nerd would do is take your hand
I jam my hand in so fast. I pull that puppy out and and litter this shit all over it
I'm not kidding. Oh my god. That is disgusting only on one corner and
You know and only on one corner again. Well, that's a really the ear corner not the mouth corner
And you know normally because this has happened it's happened to you it's happened to Christina you rip off the back
You pull out the battery and then dry it out. Yeah, I did that to mine
But you can't open the iPhone you can't there you can't replace the battery. So I can see the port
It's still it's still on it's still basically working and then I see it shut down and reboot and shut down and reboot
And I see this thing going on and off and on and off and I'm like I run upstairs. I
You know, first I wiped it off with the paper towel I washed my hands and then
And then I'm blow drying it for at least 20 minutes and it's booting up it's stopping and then it's just stopped
And then it stopped doing anything and now I've had it on the the radiator for a little while and according to someone on the the weblog
There was a
Technology guy Andy in a neat in the dough
In the ink toe whatever's name is and he suggested
He suggested putting it in a top of where box filled with kitty litter because that draws out the moisture
Which is like it's kind of like those little silicon gel bags you get when you buy new equipment
So yeah, but I'm afraid that that's something's fried already because then you I couldn't remove the battery
Which makes it pretty dumb for a mobile device. I have to say
And I'm pretty bummed out about yeah, I know can't understand. Yes, I can
You have nothing else to say now what can I say? I mean, you know, you think it'll work
What happens to the best? I have to say though. This is really important because I don't I don't think any mobile phone is
If a phone can't recover from
Well, if this happened to someone in people maybe they can make a waterproof phone. Yeah. Yeah
So this isn't this isn't waterproof
The with the nokey is aren't waterproof, but at least you couldn't you know you can save them
Most phones you can basically save if you can take the battery out. Yeah, so if the iPhone isn't
Savable that way. I'd say that's a big strike against that as as my phone of choice because
You know that's gonna happen to lots of people a lot of people I think so too
You know because sometimes you have anything you back pocket of your jeans
Never have it in the back pocket. Yeah, I'd always have it in the left pocket. No, I have to because it doesn't fit there
But I I have it on the bot. Oh, I have it there because the special vibrations give me great pleasure
Mine doesn't vibrate. No, no, you're phone doesn't vibrate. Would you like me to turn that on for you?
No
Computer says no
All right
You gotta play this one again since it went to number one and iTunes. It's Blake Morgan
And home me on a line
Maybe all the days that the way I really need you
I
Maybe I'm a little lonely man
It's in the bedroom so I feel that he doesn't really understand
Maybe I'm a man
Maybe you're the only one that I could have let help me
Maybe what you have
Maybe I'm a step
Maybe I'm a maze at the way you're with me all the time
Maybe I'm afraid of the way I leave you
Maybe I'm a maze at the way you're helping me see my soul
Right here when I'm wrong
Maybe I'm a maze at the way I really need you
Maybe I'm a man who's in the bedroom so I feel that he doesn't really understand
Maybe I'm a man
Maybe you're the only one that I could have let help me
Maybe what you have
Maybe I'm a step
Maybe I'm a maze at the way you're helping me see my soul
Maybe I'm a maze at the way you're with me all the time
Maybe I'm a little lonely man
It's in the bedroom so I feel that he doesn't really understand
Maybe I'm a man
Maybe you're the only one that I could have let help me
Maybe what you have
Maybe I'm a maze
Oh
It's exactly the way I want to be able to play the electric guitar
Everybody dolling everybody
Yeah, play Morgan went straight to number one and I tunes
The day of release played on the I think it's uh was it the most the most played
Let's see one of the most played songs
What about music network this month? Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a great song
And I don't understand why Paul McCartney never ever did anything or remakes or any
Different versions of the song or something with a waces together or with a new band together
He never does the interesting idea with a waces. No, I don't think he's really hip and with it quite honest
That's what I mean if you are if because I think of Paul as a hip guy
You know, it's to be very hip guy memo to put memo to pass if you want to stay with it
If you want to stay with it and stay your cool guy you should go collaborate. Is that yeah, yeah
Do a joint yeah, do something with the young guys
Yeah, that won't keep you young but you know Uncle Paul doesn't do that. No, he doesn't he goes with his little you
And it has a little you can lay Lee look you really where's he playing with a ukulele
Play the ukulele on the downs. Did you see the clip on the down? No, you kidding me
Yes, he was on down. Yeah, with a ukulele
Yeah, and I think you know
It's nice song, but it's a fucking ukulele dude the cool guy that I used to know
No, yeah, that's a bit disappointed. Yeah, no, I can understand
But I'd like this version. I'd like would play more than I would be so I would be very jealous if I were Paul well
He does not have to be really jealous because he's gonna make he's any it's gonna make some money off
I know but yeah, doesn't it you know I would I don't care honestly
I don't care. I'm really happy for Blake Morgan. I'm very happy for Blake too
I'm sorry
No, I know you don't want to harsh on Blake smell
You know push away Blake
It's incredible incredible
version this one it's wonderful. It's so powerful
But this is one of the guys who is who is showing the way of the pod save music revolution
Yeah, he's doing it, you know, he's he's he's making a living doing this
He has a label
Yeah, so is it is it growing is it going? It is actually yeah
Well, you saw that an heart and heart and Wilson from heart
Come on the positive music network. So you know there's lots of artists who are damn good who are coming out with new material on new labels
That understand that there's new ways of promoting and new ways of getting a music out there and actually I should put a link into the
Into the show notes to this article that I found at hoodhype.com
It's a story written by a famous music producer. I can't find it right now and
He tallyed up exactly a band who signed with a major label they sold
250,000 records, so that's three million dollars. What are you looking at? No, nothing. What are you looking at? You were looking at a dog because he's walking
Backwards, he's lifting his leg to one of the guitars. That would not be good. Whoa
3p
Yeah, oh god
Adam has all these guitars lined up. The dog lifts his leg right up against my my Steve I
Signature that Steve Steven's a signature edition, which is my acts of choice. I said no
What the hell was I talking about
I was gonna make you real good point
Oh, okay, about this band that's that signed with the major DM major record label sold 250,000 copies
That's at 12 bucks just three million dollars and after you know like five weeks of touring support and all that stuff
They broke it down and you know the band each member made seven hundred eighty one dollars. No, of course
You get 13% over retail, but we know of 90% over retail, so you know that that basically turns out to
To be nothing and these guys, you know they're putting out their own CDs and yeah, it costs some money
But they're making maybe five six bucks on a CD sold
You know, it's a big difference. Yeah, this is why I tried to keep dragging you into the podcast music revolution my dear
Well, you would be so great. You would be legendary
Yeah, well
We'll I'm on the student
What you what do you mean? You can do that anytime you want? No, but I mean the last you know
Let's go to Nashville. Let's go to Nashville
Wait until I'm done with my big band. Who knows where that's going?
I'm not allowed to talk about that. No, but you've sworn me to secrecy, so I can't say anything
The only thing I can say is I found a great big band as well. We're gonna see if we can do something together
I'm not allowed to say anything
Put it together and see what we can do and make you
But you know there's so many I mean can you look at all these towns that people they're dying for great singing talent
They'll do anything to get you into their studio to sing on some of their tracks
I'm telling you now
Yes, what are you talking about? Absolutely
You know how hard it is to get talented musicians really good ones. It's hard for nothing for nothing for me
No, but it's very hard to get them for free
Yeah, but you need to take it to fly in
Then you know I'll fly you to and I'm telling you Nashville is the place to be right now
That's where it's all happened. We should go to Nashville. Yeah, there's all kinds of awesome stuff
Let's go to Los Angeles doesn't matter where there's everybody standing there wetty wetty wetty if we do
Everybody's ready
You might as long as you're at the inside
I think it's time just like me. Is everything you say they're all really old
It's big like me. No, it's like that. They're all big experience
Really really really really really want to meet you. Me's like
We got the mic. We got the pop tape music revolution ready for you
It's play one more song just so you can hear what it sounds like how good this should have the dog two sides
How would you know that I should have said I need to say that I want you to know that I'm sorry for
That I shouldn't have done
There's a design just a side just a side just a side just a side just a side just a side just a side
Besides
I
I want you to know that I'm sorry
Dad, I don't have time
There's no need to decide
Just decide, just decide
Just decide, no need to decide
Just decide, just decide, just decide
Just decide, just decide
Are you participating?
I don't know, you don't put your headphones on
I don't know if you're going to participate
I'm showing you
Dad, the dog
And two sides, where do you think he's from?
Germany
No, South Africa
Oh
Yeah, it's actually sent in by a buddy of his
That's why I did it
It's more kick the dog
We sent this in Craig Nicholson
We saw that blood diamonds movie last night
We watched that, that was pretty impressive
Yeah, it was
Two and a half hours
I was really long movie
Yeah, but I wasn't bored or anything
It was very interesting
True
Yeah
What a good actor that is
DiCaprio
Yeah, he's pretty good
Does he ever become the hero of the movie?
Well, I guess he is kind of the hero
He dies, but he's the hero
Yeah
Good accent though
I really like this
That was a little bit of Dutch here and there
Kind of
Yeah, just a bit
Yeah
He said, he said, yeah
Yeah, couple of times
Yeah, I'll brew
So
I'm going to be home for one more week
It's going to be a busy week
And then I think every single day, except for tomorrow
Tomorrow is bank holiday
Yeah
And what are you going to be doing?
Bank holiday
No, what are you doing all week?
No week
Christina has to go back to school
No, that's next week
That's next week
I'm going to go to the hairdresser
Hmm
I have a major route
Outroing
What is that?
What do you call that?
Your routes are showing?
Yes
Who?
I don't notice it
No, I don't see any grey
No
I'm not grey
No, of course not
I'm young
Yes
What else?
It's going to be actually a very easy week
I'll leave back a little bit later
Okay
Because they are for Holland
Christina
Because they fashion show
Before we go to
To go to school
Of course
Back to school Christina
I take her to a couple of beautiful
Fashion shows
That's your version of back to school
We have to get ready for school
So we have to go to some co-tour
Well
This is good for her too
You know, it's good to talk to people
And we go a little bit
She's a debutant
She will be debutant
Oh my goodness
Because I never take her to this
She's excited
But she's into
You know, it's from a friend of mine
So
I'm sorry I can't take you back
And I haven't seen her for a while
They will be amazed
Maybe I'm amazed
That your daughter's grown so big
And tall
Maybe I'm amazed
She's a woman
What hips and breath
Yeah, okay
Alright baby
I don't know
I'm empty
Yeah
It's warm up here
You have to say
It's very hot
Yeah, it's very warm
And we have jet lag
Yeah
So I'm amazed
Anyway
Yeah, I'm amazed
To use that word again
Because we have a major jet lag
And we get up
Way too late
Every day
Oh man
Today was 930
That was okay
But it's so hard to wake up
I got to get back into the swing
I know
This sucks
Yeah, but we went
We went a bit too late
Yeah, but that's because the crappery
Oh was so long
I didn't know it was going to be 2.5 hours
I thought I mean
I movie is like an hour and a half
That's normal 90 minutes
You know, made a big bite of own
Yeah, but normally I fall asleep
I was awake
I was glancing over
Now the movie was really top-notch
And Patricia doesn't fall asleep
During the movie
Yeah
You go to any movie with me
In the theater and fall asleep
If it's not a good movie, I will
Well
If it's a good movie
You know, I'm there
Okay
Till the end
We're going to pick the Oscars this year
And you know what we're going to do
That we're going to take you to every single movie
And if you fall asleep
It's not a winner
Exactly
Yeah, okay
It'll be the pat test
Yeah
The pat Oscar test
Better known as pot
Yeah
The pat test
Exactly
All right, baby
Thank you for joining us
You won't
Don't be a stranger
And
That means come back soon
Come back to the show
Don't be no stranger now
All right
I will
And what time is Christina coming home
Who knows
Are you too tired for sex
Right now
No, no, no
I gotta do show notes
Tonight
I want to
Homp tonight
Homp
Stop it
With my dude
With my ugly stick
Can I do it
Okay
All right, you're late
I'm sorry
You're late
I'm late
And strawberry
The pissing dog
There we go
Good
I'm spoiled
The show brought to you by Kmart
Who reminds you that
The best way to take your kid back to school
Is either taking your two co-tour
Or visiting back to school
I'll podshow.com
All right, I love you, baby
I love you, tip me
Bye bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight
The best and the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight