It's the DSC 661.
Some people listen for the music.
Some people listen for news on technology, news on podcasting.
Some people listen because they're just big fans of Adam Curry.
Then they're those who listen in the hope that Carmen Tyler will call in again.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
You can find her at CarmenTiler.com, but you'll find the DSC 661 right here.
And now it's gold and you're all over your attack.
Now that we're all and you there was not turning back.
And my heart erased and I thought what could it do?
And I knew there was no hell.
No hell for you.
Sara down the clouds.
You can't fit me in my heart.
But find that room down.
Turn me apart.
You can't fit me in my heart.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah brother we're gonna have that from two, just keep talking for dudes tonight, guys, but that's what I'm talking about, dude, for dude tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight... morning tonight tonight tonight tonight Tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight. tomorrow tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight Tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight today tonight醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫 Gu醫醫醫醫醫AAAA醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫醫
and from the official Masher provider
of their resource code, MasherTown.com,
James Osco, Amy, and Thunder.
It's a football flat, everybody.
It's a maximum music Friday edition.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios,
and record labels, still think they can govern
what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control
of entertainment to the masses
and make big media corporations
wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous
new content comes the daily source code with Adam Curry.
There are many things in life that I have learned.
Like respect cannot be bought, it must be earned.
I have learned that Toggy's cheap.
I look before I leap and I sniff the milk to see if it has turned.
But there's one thing that remains unnecessary.
And it seems that I am just too blind to see.
You know, they say one guy in ten prefers the company of men.
But why do people think that one is me?
I feel pretty single line.
Why do people think I'm gay?
Is it something that I say?
Am I campus like a fan?
Is it my love of Doris Day?
Why do people think I'm gay?
Not that that isn't okay?
But let me ask you if I may, why do people think I'm gay?
Don't get me wrong, it's cool, this world takes different strokes.
Different strokes.
But personally, I just don't fancy blokes.
Fancy blokes.
You know, there's no enjoyment, finer.
Then to play with a lady's special place.
At least, that's what I often tell my fault.
It's what I always do.
So why do people think I'm gay?
Is it the way that I say, Shae?
Each time I hear why I'm C.A.
With my nipples on display.
Okay, I'm sensitive, but I like ten neatly dressed.
Need me dressed.
And yes, I own a fitted like her best.
It's just for joking.
So I'm most surprised, my face.
And I'm a fan of will and grace.
And I wish my girlfriend had a hair richer.
But why do people think I'm gay?
Has my libido gonna stray?
I blame it on my uncle Ray.
And that thing would be day.
How the people know I'm gay.
And they met my friend Jose.
And now I have to find a way to tell my fiance.
You know, everybody, I just had to play that for you.
I heard that this morning on a B.T.
He pod shows traces of nuts of fine show that you must check out, I'll put a link
in the show notes, just cracking me up and I was listening to it.
I think I may be gay.
It is September 7th, 2007.
It is Friday.
We're winding down the week here in California.
I actually just went back to the condo, but I know it is the recording studio.
After my little football Friday celebration at the office at 6.15 in the evening.
All I got to do to need tonight is go out and have some dinner.
It's about it and I'm just going to chill watch some TV and retire early tomorrow.
I got to stay inside.
I got to create a whole presentation for this conference.
I'm speaking out in San Diego on Monday, leaving for San Diego Sunday evening.
So a little bit of traveling over the weekend.
And to get us all in the mood, what makes you travel the best?
Well, there's only one thing that makes you travel best.
It's young, let's hit test.
I'm proud to be casting with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam, you ready to be stumps?
Hell yeah.
Does he use the good test?
Hey, Adam.
Hi, doing this.
He just hit this number 86 and we're going to start right away with intro.
Number one.
Pick it.
That sounds like it sounds like Elton John, Kiki D.
Don't go break in my heart.
That's sure, but it sounds like it.
And this is number two.
Easy one.
John, you are rolling out the Friday hits aren't you?
Forner.
I want to know what love is.
Is my guess for number two in the head test.
And the final one is number three.
Is that Bruce Horns being the range?
I think it's Bruce Horns being.
I think so.
What's your time's up in these are the answers?
Oh, yeah.
This is answer number one from 1976.
Who are you?
I'm going to break in my heart.
I couldn't invite, try.
Who?
Nobody knows it, nobody showin' over us down.
How was your clown?
Oh.
I'll give you my heart.
What?
Nice.
From 1976, Alton John and Kiki D.
And don't go breaking my heart.
And this is answer number two from 1984.
This is forner.
I want to know what love is.
And this is the third and final answer for this week's hit test.
In 1986, Bruce Horns were in the range.
And that's just the way it is.
Way it is.
Still in line, long in time, waiting for the verdant.
Just funny, says, get a job.
That's just the way it is.
That's just the way.
This concludes hit test number 86.
Three tracks from way back again.
One from the 70s and two from the 80s.
They were not very difficult.
No.
The first one was kinda, I guess, because of the very short intro.
All right Adam, I hope you liked these ones.
Love them.
Did you hit them all right?
Almost.
Next week, I'll be back for hit test number 87.
And the answers to this hit test, and of course, the links to the tracks in iTunes.
So you can buy these songs.
And be found at hittest.potsio.com.
Well, thank you for playing.
Until next week.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Oh, young man, I feel like I immediately want to rush off and go buy all of those songs
at the iTunes Music Store.
Hit test.potsio.com.
Young pull that.
Thank you.
I think I got two and a half out of three stars.
I couldn't remember, and I forgotten the name of the song again.
Bruce Horn's being the range.
Whatever happened to Bruce Horn's be.
Whatever happened to the range for that matter.
I mean, come on.
What's going on here?
Oh, yes.
Maximum music from our Friday is on.
The source code.
Come on in my brother.
The door is up at him.
This is Jay Mag from hoodhype.com.
I notice you don't play much hip hop on your show.
So I brought my buddy's major in fro and here today.
It's so white.
This is what I do, man.
We got a track.
I'm going to let major intro the track for you, but, and hopefully,
maybe we can make this a regular thing, but check this out.
What's up, Adam?
This is Major Man.
Listen to your podcast.
Listen to it for a while now, man.
I am.
Jay Mag.
I love to hear a little bit more hip hop on my show.
This is the artist I think you will feel his name is Quest.
He's out of Bronx, New York.
The name of his track is called All My Soul.
Check it out.
That's it.
Drops the Bronx.
Yeah.
Okay.
I want to around.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Let's go.
Uh, let's go.
I feel you now when 50 is better.
Had a lot better.
Oh, man.
For the dinner that shocked the next day.
Life is in funny sweets.
They always told me sake though but I spend like money stains.
My life is like a wonder wave tank, for the funny stick.
I'm so hungry even if they'd come off your rummy kicks.
My manager had a beautiful upbeat baby, a name the kind of spark.
Why he was working over time? She died in the fire. That's saying we time was just telling me drugs
It's tight and so it's last break, but that damn custody was wide
My man just graduated college was crazy on us and dedicated his degree to his pops in his momma
He was happy you left the home when I go through drama
I saw the brain he got killed while drunk and dropper remember 10 from down the block
Always roll the loan never chill drink smoke to even bone he met two chicks to get sassy
Get him stoned this first couple of only one got him in the metro hole
Come on, yeah, yeah
Okay, okay, yeah, yeah
Let's go
I feel you now a bit
When I think about the life that I believe my ass hurt my eyes beat my hip jerk
How I feel need work you ever felt the pain to my point when you need church
And many soldiers captured in the past up the steelburg feel like people still broke
And reals I feel jerks still nailed the film her like a shield that kills worse
I never thought my you forget drill by ill curse because abuse went on to tell like a seal that's still
Rose
My visions like steamy is that I don't wonder my eyes see you
But my miss is like plunges in your heart like thunder
I watch kids turn their feet from crack movers and you dreamt trying to link
Because they blasted robbers cops surprise the dog when it's raining
They beat your ass like it's part of the training
They're the rest the block of trash get your heart again
Painting don't even laugh because you're part of the changes let it go. Quest
Until you have a baby
Straight from the Bronx to your ear buds
Thanks to Jay MacMagger and the crew over hood hype.com
I know you all consider you been listening to my show
It's all right. I know I'm listening to your show
And please feel free to send something for the football Friday any time
Absolutely just
Just consider me to be the white shadow of the show. That's how you can utilize me and the DSC in the UK give us a call
4 4
Yeah, so I've been
Looking for a young Elvis sound alike for the lost Elvis Diaries Mark Namcoff and I have been scouring
High and low and finally some calls are coming in
As I call it here in a hell next tail well Adam
Understand you need a young the over well who better to play over some me
Overspare impressly a
Minimal name starts with a and your first name starts with a that's that's pretty good in it
Well, I got to
But looking for work. I've been hiding that everywhere
Since my mom and I I really haven't had a lot to do
So if you still live in for somebody 11 oh just give me a shout out
I get that all back and not the bad not bad there's more coming in
How to Mr. Curry. It's Elvis calling
I hear another color on your show when I knew I could do much better job in him
Now I don't fancy myself in Elvis in person either and I I won't never as big as fame
But I can't sing like him and
Brooks had been telling me all my wrath that I'm greeted in the taking people so I had to give it a shake
I've been a state home doubt if I've been using the sun just want off the school for the first time
Is city a promise myself when it did I was going to try to explore some of my God given talents and
See if I can make it if it happened before I got to go off and get a date job. You know
I'm gonna let Mark Namcoff decide on these
I'm not sure I like the first one a little bit better in this one. It's kind of hard though
You know, it's it's a real acting gig. It's a real paying gig. It's it's really something you can you can bank on
So Jerry still out feel free to call in
Let me know if you think you are the biggie
1 2 1 6 2 5 6 3 5 7
1 1 2 1 6 2 5 6 3 5 7
Is James longtime friend of the Charlie
Mr. Corriots James
I'm not that's a good news for you
I think I taste good news. There's anybody from the BBC listening
It's a very very carefully
I shall say this only once
I've just got the best of today
BBC radio or for news program
Don't lord it and to my surprise that program was 45 minutes long
Usually about that you have between five and 15 minutes 45 minutes on and it's subject is lechioro
Poverock which is very sad
Yeah, I don't know the podcast and I think now
I'll listen to this a general news program
You know how bad kids are doing all that kind of shape and then right at the end
The talk about the channel Poverock again and how it's very sad is died and then we get
No, no, no, no, no, yes, the play of the entire hookin song oops
I don't even know that you may say put there just a message to them and probably
Mr. Poverock is record company
Yes, I will be going to iTunes today, and yes, I will be purchasing some more Poverocky because
I don't actually have any on my iPod and I've just realized how good he actually was
Which is a shame because he's gone no, but that's the score you just played with so many events
By the way, I'm sure it was a mistake the BBC did that, but I don't really mind because I think
Personally, I think this falls into up-sol organization for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives
And it is newsworthy it's educational and my good buddy the satellite repair man P W
Fenton was thinking along the exact same lines
And send me this
No
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Hey, Billy, because of Barry, he's just a hundred.
Siguensio da di famio
He
the
The Master, the Channel Poverty,
and just a small piece from Nessandorma,
with thanks to PWFent.
Damn.
I gotta tell you,
what a loss.
What a loss.
And please don't tell me that your favorite radio station
played that in its entirety
because they did not.
They don't do that anymore.
They'll just play the last bit.
Which is also coincidentally,
this song has been award-winning
for several contestants,
and I think, like,
pop idol and ex-factor,
or whatever.
And all those the guys who are doing
are good,
nothing compares to this.
What a tragic loss.
What a fantastic voice.
Speaking of pop idol, by the way.
I did I tell you,
this Patricia noticed this.
So we were watching,
I think the most recent series
started in the UK.
I recorded the episode
and I saved it.
So when I get back,
remind me,
please, and I'll dig it up.
Talk about your deception.
There was a contest,
and you know how it works,
right?
They do their audition,
and then you have to have four
yeses before you can carry on.
So it was a dennymanogue
who, by the way, is looking kind of hot.
It's a Louis,
and Simon Cowell, of course,
and Sharon Osborne.
And so I forget exactly who it was,
but they have to go down the line.
It was, you know,
it was a yes, yes,
a no,
and then it was Sharon's turn,
and she had to say either yes or no
for this contestant to carry on.
And she said no.
And Patricia, who's sitting next to me,
says, hey, hold on a second.
Back that up.
Rewind that,
which of course I can do,
because we got the nifty digital
sky box, right?
So I back it up.
She says, her clothes changed.
What are you talking about?
So we backed it up and low and behold.
Yeah, it's really amazing.
You see the four of them sitting there.
Sharon has kind of like a,
like a hoodie, a black hoodie,
gray sweatshirt thing going on.
And the minute she says no,
she's actually wearing a freely white shirt.
It's like it's half a second,
just a word no.
And boom, they cut away from her.
So the big question is why did they do that?
For some reason,
they did not let this person go on to the next round.
And the way they did it was really sneaky.
But something is a foot,
my friends,
and I guarantee you,
I will find out.
That's what it is.
I'll do it with that.
Hi.
I'm on this week's show.
We've got a review of Dragon Ball's E.
The new trading card game for the DS.
We've got a review of stuntman ignition for the 360.
An interesting new game called Dublob.
We've got a preview of that for the Wii,
and you can win overlord for the Xbox 360.
All of that, of course,
you can check out at gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
You're outer.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out
You're on her, please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work and lawyer
It's Jersey time, man, man
It's Jersey time
Yo, how's it going Adam? It's Jersey time
The official musicologist of the Chacha
Have I got a band for you this week?
In fact, it's one of my personal favorites
The band is named Jaco Pierce
They're out of Texas
And when I was in law school in Delaware
I had like only a few albums
And I got to be honest
I played this Jaco Pierce album over and over and over again
So in a lot of ways
It's fair to say that Jaco Pierce helped make me a lawyer
I love these guys
They have a wonderful, cool acoustic sound
And their song vineyard is perfect for the end of the summer
They talk about a girl with mahogany hair
And amnith this dies
And it's just an absolutely perfect track
Check this out
This is one of my favorite bands called Jaco Pierce
On The Daily Source Code
So excited to play this for you
It's six o'clock now in the morning
As I wait for my train to come
To take me somewhere just outside of Boston
As I run to find the other song
And I'm leaving my way high
And then I can't talk about just more pain
Than this heart and hand can use
As this big world I was spinning
All that I thought I was winning
I'd never thought I'd never thought I'd do
This great force it takes me to the ferry
To cross land and water so I'll take
And I'm on that ship my life just seems so very
Small and comparison to everything around
But there's this girl over there
She's got mahogany hair
And her eyes of sweet out my face
I bow as she curses
Doesn't look like she's gonna hurt me
So I decide to write it to my lips
She said
She stayed on the phone for a summer
And she stayed on the venue for me
We'll find the last time we're in our club
And that children is all the way
Seems now that I should be going
As that one day turned into five or six
All the while I'm loving all the beautiful things she's showing
I back up and I'm enveloping by the means
That girl over there she's got mahogany hair
And her eyes of sweet out my face
I think that maybe it would be better
If I just wrote her a letter
But instead she grabs me in my chest
And she's saying you ain't going nowhere
Stay on the venue for the summer
Won't you stay on the venue for the year?
We'll find the last time we're in our club
And that children is all the way
Once again, Josie Todd does not disappoint
Sir Todd brings it on home
From the Pods Egg Music Network, Jackal Pierce
And of course, links in the show notes
Work today's program
Which is the maximum music football Friday
Find it at dailysourcecode.com
Nice
Kind of strumming on the Friday
No count in the curry condo
Yeah, yeah, I like it man
I like it
Happy football Friday everybody
It's Marcus couch from the scene scene
Here with a fat sack of the good stuff
Let's rock one out here on football Friday
This is how I pay the rent on the scene scene
If you're into this kind of music
Check out more at the scenes scene.com
This is one less reason
And the track is really bad analogy
For you go that you could call those people friends
You lie right to my face
You spent me to believe it
You said you'd rather walk away
Let me fall to appreciate
Cause I know it would fail
The salty catastrophe of major betrayal
But getting disaster
You're walking no matter
Struggling long as I dream
And I'll give you a chance
For me to give you a chance
To be free like I can see
In your eyes
No lie ever
Leave the lost in your heart
Feel it in my hand
See it in your eyes
And no matter how you say
The tide of this place
You're so sick of my face
But I shouldn't wait around on you
And I know that you won't show
Sometimes we all just need
Softens to believe
Something so much more than you
Cause I knew it would fail
The salty catastrophe of major betrayal
But getting disaster
You're walking no matter
Struggling long as I dream
I'll give you a chance
For me to give you a chance
To be free like I can see
In your eyes
No lie ever
Leave the lost in your heart
Feel it in my hand
See it in your eyes
And no matter how you say
The tide of this place
You're so sick of my face
And no matter how you say
The tide of this place
You're so sick of my face
But I shouldn't wait around on you
And I know that you won't show
Sometimes we all just need to
This alone the baby you are strong
You have a weak like me
And I know it would be
From the choices you made of
A prince on the back
And a flower of a face for the day
You're the day I'm trying to smile
Because I knew it would fail
The salty catastrophe of major betrayal
But getting disaster
You're walking no matter
Struggling long as I dream
And I know that you won't show
You're the day I'm trying to smile
When you've seen
Until we're not getting sick
And no matter how you say
The tide of this place
You're so sick of my face
And no matter how you say
The tide of this place
You're so sick of my face
Now I can see it in your eyes
And no matter how you say
The tide of this place
I'm going to write through a party on Fridays, my friends show up, bring in gifts.
Like us, Kyle, you can see and see.
We are rocking through knocking.
I don't think we should be stopping because it's the Blue Bar Friday.
Maximum music edition. Keep it coming though.
This is Rick from the Rock by Three Shots Podcast.
Here's a great song from the Podsake music network by a great band who played this summer's Warp Tour.
This is Mayday Parade with Jamie Allover.
I had a dream last night, we drove out to see Las Vegas.
We look ourselves in the bright lights.
I wish you could have seen us, but you'd be changed to get home.
I'll release it when it's school.
But put it said on the high tide.
I'd spend a summer on the white couch.
I was just going to sing a song from the Podsake music network by a great band who played this summer's Warp Tour.
But we are rocking through knocks.
This is the Black Friday.
We have a song from the Podsake music network by a great band who played this summer's Warp Tour.
So let's go!
I've been wanting what to dream another such that we'll be able to find you all over
When it's over, I'll take this cabin sun ride with me, and wake up with the formation of memories
We may love our the ocean, as the waves cast throughout the ocean
So it's never we're so bright, and this guy's never so blue, to open up into my arms
And we laughed as I held you, I'll never go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to
To the land, to the land, to the land, to the place you're putting it down
To the land, to the earth, to the earth, to the ocean
So it's never we're so bright, and this guy's never so blue, to open up into my arms
And we'll dream another such that we'll be able to find you all over
When it's over, I'll take this cabin sun ride with me, and wake up with the formation of memories
We may love our the ocean, as the waves cast throughout the ocean
So it's never we're so bright, and this guy's never so blue, to open up into my arms
And we laughed as I held you, I'll never go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia
I'll never go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back
to Georgia, not at least until I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least until I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia, not at least till I have to go back to Georgia,
I've got to be honest with you. I forgot what their name was already. It's going to be a bitch doing show notes today because
Nothing in the ID three tags and that means I have to go back and
I'm listening to all the intros again to figure out what the hell I've played.
Hey for those of you who tuned into the daily source code to hear more of Carmen Tyler's sexy
Sultry voice. I would not want to disappoint. Hey, this is Carmen Tyler from the Carmen cast
and I wanted to talk to all the podcasters out there who are going to be attending the podcast Expo
in the next couple of weeks in Ontario, California. Kind of coming up quickly.
But I want to invite everyone to a worship service that we're going to have on Sunday morning,
September 30th. It's going to be 8 o'clock in the morning in Ballroom A. I think it's going to be an
awesome time with the word and I'm going to be there and I'm going to help lead some
present worship and then we're going to have a really awesome sermon by Jimmy Bradshaw. So I would
love to see everyone come and just we can all get together and praise the word and I'm
really excited about what God's going to do at this service. I got to tell you that's a great idea,
really is. If I do make it out to the Expo Carmen, I promise I'm coming to the service.
Just to slow down the mood a little bit for your Friday. This is Terrence Blunt's Shard
and Dear Mom.
Thank you so much for your support, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
with thanks to Sir Jersey Todd, for sending the pointer to the Pod Save Music Network,
oh yeah, turn off one shot, not an unknown my friends, dear mom, and when I heard that, I could
tell, I knew exactly what kind of emotion was going into that song, very, very nice, okay,
what's going on this weekend, the big MTV Video Music Awards, which is kind of funny these
days, what they should really do is they should bring on the shows, they really in the video,
they really put on that network, bring some of those crappy sweet 16 kids that you want to
punch in the face, you know, let's bring out the paint my ride guys, you know, all that stuff,
they don't play anymore music on MTV, and it's true that they're, or it's clear that they're
completely clueless, what is the big star they've got, they're bringing back Britney Spears,
yeah, it'll get your ratings, it'll pop the ratings up a little bit, I'm sure lots of people
are interested in that, but man, you have alienated your core audience so horribly,
oh I'd be, it's just lame, it's just completely lame,
all right, what do we got? 44 minutes, not bad, it's Friday,
one day Tuesday, Wednesday, food about Friday, Adam's final fun on the Wii, well,
the only final thoughts I have for this week, which of course, has been kind of weird
with the passing of our lovely, lovely cat, you almost want to say child, I mean,
you love them so much, remember of the family Cindy, and by the way, they had the girls had a
beautiful ceremony for him, buried him in the back in the woods and got a nice little
grave set up with the flowers and everything, I'll get a picture of it and I'll post it up when
I get back home, which by the way will not be for another week, more than a week, even this is the
mega marathon stay out here, could not be worse timing. Fortunately, I got lots of friends and those
of you listening, you're it, and I really do appreciate all the beautiful thoughts you've sent to me
and to Patricia and Christina, it really, really has made a difference, I'm not kidding,
it's I'm sure that when I get home, the lady Patricia will want to be on the show and show
I want to thank you personally, I'm quite, quite convinced of it, so that's really my final
thought is that I got a lot of people to thank and even though life brings this
sour grapes once in a while it brings us good times, sometimes it does just bring us bad times,
but there's always one golden rule you can hold on to because trust me my friends,
it's going to be all right.
And I'll tell you where I love you, don't tell back on me no more, I love for you, it's all all
fun, you're it's all I'm waiting for, you're gonna break my heart when you will fall
you're my own forever, you're gonna break my heart, what's gonna be all right
when you're on my side, don't let you hide, don't let you hide, don't let you hide
all right when you're on my side, don't let you hide
what's gonna be all right
don't hold on me no more, I love for you, don't let you hide
and stay until my dying day, you're gonna want to stay instead
into my world, because all I want to be is say, baby, baby, you're gonna break my heart
when you will fall, forever, you're my own forever, you're gonna break my heart, what's gonna be all right
don't let you hide, don't let you hide, don't let you hide, what's gonna be all right
when you're on my side, I know you're there, I think you're also very much
stable source code dot com, add them at podshow.com, have a great weekend, talk to you on Monday
another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear