Hey Adam, you're listening to Box, Carral Prelude, Kedia, Goethe Vatter, in Avikite.
I figured this would be great in honor of the new Pod Show, Putstom, and coincidentally,
it is B-W-V-672, and B-W-V for music people.
They know it stands for Bach, Verca, Verde, Cycness, which is basically the chronological listing
of Bach works.
And 672 is also the chronological listing for today's episode of The Daily Source Code.
It's pretty good to be here.
The next step before something in the TSA, you know what that means.
Don't you know what that means?
Do you know what the letters to D-K-S?
They stand for...
Back!
Copper wins...
ублиive dollars was made winterpped with fire,
but next she was really contenting my youth.
I like that you think I'm slaying you into squeezed music...
Hot Casting tears in Adam Curry!
Tell me, I know...
I need you to know...
to know sometimes they're alone forever
I needed to say in the impossible way
Sometimes through my window
I wanted to show how we live in that ground
It's on how you love the ride
And if you want me so
You better tell me so
Because I want you to see the call of me
That can't let go
Let me know
I needed to try as long as going by
Sometimes now you need to
I never could say in the way
I wanted to say
But do you ever do you?
So tell me I know
How to make you go
Sometimes now you're alone forever
And if you want me so
You better tell me so
Because I want you to see the call of me
That can't let go
Let me know
Because you see the call of me
That can't let go
And if I want you to see the call of me
But do you ever do you?
So tell me I know
How to make you go
Sometimes now you're alone forever
But do you ever do you?
So tell me I know
How to make you go
Sometimes now you're alone forever
I needed to try as long as going by
Sometimes now you need to
I never could say the way I wanted to say
But do you ever do you?
So tell me I know
How to make you go
And if you want me so
You better tell me so
Because I want you to see the call of me
That can't let go
And if you're alone forever
You know as the fire rates
Let me know
Perfect Monday morning song for the source code
If this had been done my west life
It would have been number one in the charts
I love those guys
Fantastic
How are you doing?
Welcome to episode number 672 of the daily source code
Coming to you from the curry manner
On the west side of G town
The affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guilford in the United Kingdom
Okay
What's this?
I did a Friday show
And here we are doing a Monday show
What is wrong?
Well Tuesday Wednesday and Thursday are planned London days for me
So maybe I can eat out another show tomorrow
I told you it's going to be messed up until the end of the year
However, I have been extremely motivated all weekend long
I've been receiving tons of feedback regarding
Republican presidential candidate
Ron Paul, Dr. Ron Paul
Some great feedback on him and on politics in general
I know that a lot of you tune in to listen to crap about naked pictures
And I always try to sleep in some of that
But got to do a little bit of the politics
It's been on my brain, you know?
It's just like it's been fizzling around in there
This is your brain
And this is your brain on the daily source code
Yeah, that's exactly what it felt like
Saturday morning really when comments started rolling in
And the weather was kind of crap Saturday
I did something very decant
Just for me all for myself
Just to chill out a little bit
I really needed to rest my brain
You know the only way I can really take my mind off of everything
Is to go flying
So the weather was scheduled to be much better for Sunday
And I thought what a perfect opportunity
I'm going to go get my haircut
You know, I'm a pretty loyal guy
Not only that, but I'm definitely afraid of someone
Fucking up my hair because for those of you
Been listening to the show for a couple of years now
I believe it was in 2006
The end of 2006 when I went to Tony and Guy
Better known as Sam and Dave
Tony and Guy
That fabulous chain of hair salons
And it completely ruined my hair
And it stayed that way for like a year
It was host
So I vowed I would never go to anyone else
But my man Peter who lives in Rotterdam
Not far from the airfield coincidentally
So the most decant thing I could think of
Was to fly to have my hair done
By the way, you know, I'm 43 now
And I have all of my hair
So I don't I'm proud of it
I don't mind telling you that I will literally fly to the guy
I trust most with taking care of the hair
So for me this is a big adventure time
I'd have him flown in a couple of weeks
Gonna make the crossing crossing the English channel
You know, Hitler never successfully did it
Well he crossed the channel, but he never actually landed
So and I got to tell you I love getting up
Actually I went Sunday
The weather was much nicer
Although better on the other side on the Dutch side
Than the UK side
There's nothing nicer than a Sunday morning
Around 930 10 o'clock in the morning
You arrive at the airfield
And you know there's no one is really I think the airfield
Officially is closed until 10
And you know there's just it's quiet
No one's there and you know around 1015
You might hear one airplane somewhere
The distance or someone taking off
And people are all kind of like hey good morning
How are you doing?
Friendly we're all working on our planes doing our checks and stuff
And all of us maybe all of us but three of us
So I've done my flight planning and everything
And done the life jacket
Which of course is a good idea
Since I'm flying over water in a single-engine airplane
And I made the trek over
It was actually the cloud base
The lower than I expected leaving was about a thousand feet
And it wasn't really cloud
It was more like a misty haze
So caution of course had to be taken into account
Because you know it said the weekend all kinds of idiots are out there flying
Put it at the nice 3000 feet for the crossing
And Patricia had made a thermos bottle of coffee for me
So you know just cruise along that portion of the trip
Which is over the over water
We got 45 maybe 50 minutes, 45 minutes probably
And because you're flying over in this case very calm water
It's just you know calm
You can put the autopilot on and kick back and relax
And there's just nothing like flying your own aircraft
Defying all laws of gravity
And of course taking advantage of a whole bunch of other laws
That mother nature is given to us
Sipping my coffee
It was fantastic, arrived at Rotterdam
And I hope you don't mind me saying I'm getting really good at this landing stuff
I can just have the baby
Just kiss the tarmac
And Renee was on the ground frequency
Remember Renee the guy that gave a shout out to me
The other the other week when I was in Rotterdam
So he was on the ground frequency
He said hey Adam when you come back
And I said you got to do them just going to go get my haircut
He said when you come back come on up to the tower
So I went to see Peter and he of course took great care of me
Made me feel like a man again
Back to Rotterdam airport
When I was at the tower
That was quite a treat actually
You don't get invited up to the tower very often
And I was fun sat there for a little bit
Drink a cup of coffee with the guys
You know some real like hangar talk airplane
Crap which was nice
And wow what a great view
And what a fantastic airfield Rotterdam
It's so diverse with
737's leading trans obvious
737's interspersed with
You know single engine aircraft
Just a whole bunch of stuff going on
So I left it five p.m. a local time
Which would be 4 p.m. here 3 p.m.
UTC
About an hour and a half is what it takes
You know there was no wind to speak of
If anything a bit of crosswind on a 2-4 runway
But really nothing
So I couldn't take advantage of any extra speed
So it still took me the hour and a half
And as I got closer to the United Kingdom
It got increasingly harder to see anything
In fact by the time I was a beam of
Manston which is the very
Easternly tip of the island
It was so easy
I was still at 3,000 feet
So you know I started to cruise
Decend down to 2,400 feet
That's the maximum is 2.5,000 feet
Otherwise you interrupt with the
With the Heathrow and and Gattwick zones
So you have to stay underneath that under
Their TMA as it's called
And visibility was probably about
1 kilometer which means
I was I could look down and I could see the ground
But looking ahead pretty much nothing
So got pretty exciting
And of course this is end of the day
Sunday people coming back from from France from the 2K
And this is one of the busiest air corridors
In the world actually
So crossing overhead at Big and Hill
Was pretty busy 4,5 aircraft
No one could see each other
I was really happy I bought that portable T-Cast system
The air collision or collision avoidance system
There you go
Collision avoidance
So I you know I had a little bit of
A situational awareness of where everybody was in conjunction
With the controller was telling me
But it was pretty much instrument flying to be quite honest
And got it back down to Farrow
Boy I'm sure glad I know where the hell that thing is
Because it was the visibility was so poor by the time I got there
I couldn't see the airfield
So I was almost on top of it
But as I said it completely invigorates me to do that stuff
And boy do I feel alive
But today as well it just carried over
And we got lots of stuff to talk about
I mean tons
Hey Adam it's Alex from podcast junkie UK
I've got £8.50 worth of eBay purchase
Flight simulator on my screen
And a crappy microphone but I still don't need a transmitter
Anyway
Of course they want us frightened
Cast your mind back to the 911 events
I remember sitting on my PC with this news aggregator I had
So what podcast junkie UK is talking about here
I think
Still about conspiracy theories
And manipulation of the messaging and media
And probably the truth
I gotta tell you I'm starting to graduate a bit
Out of the conspiracy theories
Moving closer towards some real resolutions
More on that in a moment
Is all these news feeds coming from all over the world
And at the same time these feeds were coming in
About the anthrac scare and all that kind of stuff
But even at that time while the
911 events were going on
And the anthrac shit and all of that
There were already already news articles about Iran
And the nuclear threat
And just like the start of the zeitcoice movie
With the religious stuff
You know laying the ground, laying the seed for them
For what's really going to be the main course
So they've all got us frightened
And no one's going to kick up a stink about going into Iran
There aren't going to be any protest marches
Like they were before going to Iraq
And that's what it is
Anyway
I can't do it as well as a comic strip blogger
Oh here it comes
Fuck you Adam
Anyway
Thank you
It works well in combination with the kind regards to your loved ones
That's fantastic
Yeah
Yeah, dude, absolutely
Yeah, I think I think we got to be really careful and keep our eyes peeled
Well, this other stuff is going on
We really cannot afford to all of a sudden invade Iran
This makes absolutely no sense
But there is change of foot
I believe
Oh, by the way, some feedback from Germany
I do want to keep that currency
This will be moving in pretty soon
Hey, it's very first of all
Sorry for the cracking sound
I did not buy on my bluetooth headset
And my mobile phone
On my headset, voice mail box
Alright, alright
So Ali is calling in through his bluetooth headset
Connected to his mobile phone into a voice mail box
Yeah, Ali sound quality
About a four my friend
Away home
Right, so here's Ali from Bonds
And I did want to comment on your plan
To open up the Pacho journey office down at Pacho
Right choice
I love Berlin
And Pacho
Pacho
Pacho, Pacho, Pacho, Pacho
Pacho is a great place for a bit
Yeah, to friend and I'm doing a grant
Opening party down there
Just give me a call
Send me a mail
Ali at my way home
That you, Ali, Ali
Is
And yeah
What a party would do
Want to be part of the crowd
And want to be part of Pacho Germany
Want to hook up with you guys
Make some party
Here you go
And by the way, I'm a folder
And talk to you I am curious
What's that in German dude?
We got to have the German version of that
Ficti Adam Curry
Yeah, and I realized
I think it was
Earlier last week when someone asked me if we're going to do a party
Yeah, of course we're going to replicate the way we rolled out in the United Kingdom
So that means we're going to have a
Well, in the UK we had a draft and darts session
Which means beer and darts
So maybe in Germany we have a broad force doing beer session or something like that
Whatever it is
It'll be a
Basically an open-house open bar
Everyone come on by
Hang out. Let's talk. Let's meet
I'm getting a lot of phone call
So that means there's a lot of interest very excited about that
And yes, I'm happy that everyone else likes the
Like the idea of going to Potsdam
Because I think it's going to be a nice home for Pacho Germany
Or PSP Potsdam
Pacho
So feedback on the Fubar Friday football
I forget what it was
What the hell did you call it?
Friday football
Adam Curry
Folder
Okay, that would be one strike against the football Friday report
Got a very interesting call
From parky
Hi Adam it's parky taking in
Sorry about the voice I'm up to my neck in a cold
And it's really starting to fucking piss me off
Anyway, I've just been listening to your Friday show
And well, frankly, I don't really give a flying fuck
The Americans actually go in for this time
It's going to be better than the Simeon moron
They've got there at the moment
But it must pick up on one point
Second amendment to the Constitution
The right to bear arms
It's really about time that that really got modernised
I'm looking at some websites here with statistics
About a number of people who have been killed in America
By guns over the last ten years
Also in 2004, for example, five people got murdered
By with a gun in New Zealand
56 in Australia
73 in England and Wales
344 in the United States
Yeah, parky, I just got a stop for one second there, dude
Okay, so there's two things that play here
One is the second amendment and what that means to the United States
And second is having guns on the street essentially
Now very nice that you make this comparison
And dude, I have guns, I don't have hand guns
I've got classic guns that I've collected
I'm not a shooter of guns, but I'm not against guns
And I'm certainly not against the second amendment
Which we'll get into in a second
But to cite statistics
Based upon numbers like that
You just cannot, I don't care what it is
You cannot compare
Those numbers based upon the size of the countries
There's over 300 million people in America
And in New Zealand, I think maybe it's six
So that's not really a fair comparison
You can do it by percentage if you want
That's one way
But just blanketly saying
Oh, there's 10 or 11,000 deaths by hand guns
Or by guns in America
Compared to four in New Zealand
That just doesn't compute
Okay, it just doesn't work that way
That's not how statistics work
So let's just take that off the table right there
Is opposed to say it's godless America
Okay, let's go into a little bit more detail
On some of the stats here
Everyone knows about the
The Virginia Tech University
Blacksburg, Virginia, the worst mass shooting in American history
Yeah, what was that place in Ireland
The one that the boom town rat saying the song about
I don't like Mondays
Let me see, yeah that was
Wasn't that part of this part of the world?
Huh
Shit does happen dude
Gumman shoots 47 people
Killing 32 before killing himself
And everyone's heard of the column by
And thing where 23 people
We're wounded 12, 12 were killed
And a teacher on top
Yeah, you just pick one at random
Okay, so let's say to your team open fire inside
I'm more killing five and wounding four
Before being killed by police
Yeah, it's some kid just shoot another kid here
In the United Kingdom of North
Just recently, I mean, guns
Are a fact of life
I think it has very little to do with the second amendment
You know guns get misused for all kinds of things
Again, I'm not a gun owner
I don't walk around with guns
I don't, did they scare me?
But the second amendment is something else
Listen to the rest of parkie here
In February this year, in November
21st, 2004, and to open the roof
With an SKS for salt rifle
Killing six other hunters
Another one at random
July 5th, Cleveland, Ohio
Apparently angry about fireworks
I've been noisy for the July party
Shot three people to death
And wounded two others
Why? Why?
When a wake up and get rid of the guns
More controls, get rid of them
Wake up America, your kids are dying
Do something about it
Okay, now rent over blue pill
Fuck you Adam Curry
Oh, yes
I thought you'd give it up on the weed
A big misconception
I didn't give up on the weed
I've been trying to give up on the tobacco
That's two very different things
I'm not quite sure how people got confused with that
Okay, 50,000 deaths
Due to automobiles last year in the United States
Yet no one's calling for removal of automobiles
5,000 deaths in the UK
Due to road accidents
Many of those involved alcohol
I mean, we can keep on going
It's just not an argument
It's just not an argument cigarette smoking
Yeah, sure there's all kinds of regulation
It's still going to kill hundreds of thousands of people
You know, it's just the fact of life
But for America to wake up, yeah, absolutely America has to wake up
But I don't think it's about getting guns off the streets
It's about taking our country back
It's about taking back the proper responsible role of government
A particular federal government that we need to wake up to
And then I think a lot of these things are going to start to fall into place
Because there's reasons for for huge amount of guns
On the street
There's reasons for it
They're available
Really, it's not just because they're available
There are many other reasons
And I think we just might have someone who can help us out of this mess
Or at least to pull a lot of Americans together
Who have similar ideas
And if it's not this time around, it'll be the next time around
That in a second but first
Oh, yes
Let's have a word with the nylon
Spreading the news with the smile on
Where they're all all right
We're in your polite, let's listen
He is back ladies and gentlemen
He's the ex-pad who lives in London
He's from New York and he's against everything I say
Alright, this is take to Adam
This is the nylon I got cut off
So let me try to do this quickly
Through many brain cells
The ameral too
To have nylon agree with CSB is pretty frightening don't you agree?
Arrow is the creation of a Canadian thing tank or the phrase
Institute that has $10 million of funding
Not likely to be the hotbed of revolutionary thinking
Ask the sales reason because you don't have a marketing reason about buying power index
BPI
Which subdivide the US into nine countries
Now there's a conspiracy theory
Let's subdivide the US into nine countries
Pick your theories
Central bank debt
Can't even start that one
Only to say 45% of the central bank debt
M1 supply is held by Japan and China
Those are not the people you would have holding your debt
If you're planning to overtake the world in terms of money supply
What happens if they sell?
We go down
Bath theory
To control of money is not the problem
Money wealth is not the problem with corruption
Is control of the information highway that you have
That you're using just like the man to send out information
Peace and meal to influence people
With really no basis of it
You're in bed with the man Adam
I'm going to just cut the British telecom
You're a partner, you're a great partner
Imagine if you're a podcasting in 2001 when B.T. was suing to say
They own the hyperlink
B.T.
Okay, nylon, hold on a second
A couple things here, first of all
Regarding the
Amiro
You tell me this is like a figment of my imagination
Or this is come up dreamed up by some think tank
Ah
Someone I gotta find this
Someone sent me
That link
That I was looking for to
President of Mexico on Larry King live
I can't find it at the moment
Where he literally said he literally said the Amiro is something
That could come into play
Sometime down the road
So it's not just some think tank that's coming up
Why can't I find this crap
I let's listen to the rest of nylon here
And then I'll look for that in the meantime
I'll just say every time you click on a hyperlink
You have to pay them
Now if you're a podcast I can imagine you blowing your stack
But no they put money in your bag now and they're okay
They're the man
The only difference between the man and you
They got what you want
I see the same values and behaviors
As you as the man
This is the nylon I'm going to take a white pill
If you just give me a headache
For this stuff
And finally one more over promise under delivery
Where the suck less research
I don't see any revolutionary change in customer attitudes and marketing
The suck less
Come on Adam and finally the daily source code is not daily tell us what it is
And commit to it
But nylon
The A new one you're called
You know what nylon
You're just not making any sense dude
You're just not making any sense anymore
Oh
I wish I could find that
That's so stupid
Maybe I'll have it tomorrow for you
Working for the man
Look dude
There's no first of all
There's no way we can ever
Get anything accomplished without
At least using the man
By the way
British telecom is not the man
It's a huge organization that was once part of British government
That operates accordingly
And I think they're actually
Pretty forward thinking in revolutionary
To even want to have anything to do with us
Considering some of the content
Which by itself is revolutionary
It does probably not adhere to all standards of
And norms that
British telecom is used to
Is used to I guess
I don't know
I can't even give
A clearer bottle to what you're saying
It just it just makes no sense
Good to have you back though
Dude if I think you're really the patriot that
You probably are
You'd probably be responding differently
Like some of these people
Hi
My name is Kathleen Jagadnick
I'm a run Paul Supporter
And I hear that Adam Curry is
Working for a candidate to endorse
I would like to please suggest that Adam Curry do
Some more research and I'll find that Dr. Paul
Is really the only candidate running who's worthy of people's votes
Specifically
The number two call
I already called the run Paul campaign
And they said that if Adam wants to interview Dr. Paul
He needs to request the interview himself
That they don't
They don't come and ask for interview
So Adam needs to contact them
And their phone number is
So
For those of you who haven't heard
The previous episodes of the show
I basically put out a call
And said, you know, a home I'll tell you what you have to say
No, she's just coming out of phone numbers
I put out a call and said, you know, I want to talk to this guy
I think I really want to get behind him and endorse him
And I'm pretty sure I could help him out
In a number of ways
Primarily with fund raising
Which is still how elections are won
It's how we choose our presidents in the United States
Hillary Clinton said to have
A hundred million dollars by the end of this quarter
That buys a lot of advertising time
So there's a couple things we can do
One is just purely fundraising
Raise money
I think there's enough Americans we can reach through our shows
That we can
Get tons of money
Or I apparently said a shit ton of money
But also
Just the pure reach of
Independent media itself
You know, and we maybe we don't need so many different
Advertising campaigns
In fact, I was thinking we've got to set up some viral campaigns
And I am going to get behind Dr. Ron Paul
And you'll find out why in a second
And I do have some ideas
Anyway, I sent out the call and said look
You know, I really want to talk to this guy on the show
On the daily source code
Could someone please
Again touch with me
And the reason why I did that is not because
Well, I am kind of lazy
It wasn't for any reason other than
I was interested to see how well put together
This campaign really is
And if they really are tuned into the internet
So I put out the call on Friday
And here's what I received today
Hi, my name is Don Rasmussen
I'm a special assistant doctor
Ron Paul for a credential campaign
And I was hoping that Adam could give me a call at 4-2
So, is another phone number home?
I'm just going to read it that for a second
Zero
We've had a lot of requests for folks who would like us to
Avail ourselves the opportunity to have Dr. Paul in the show
And that's what we'd be very interested in doing
Excellent
Excellent!
We only took one weekend
And already these guys are in touch with me
You want to get them on the show
So I'm going to put in a call a little bit later on today
I'm not even head courters is in Texas
I presume so I'll have to wait a couple hours
And we'll get them on the show
This week then, fantastic
Yeah, I don't scare you out again
From Vegas just called to see what's up
And also, I wanted to actually
I wanted to find out a little bit more about this guy, Ron Paul
There's a huge grass roof thing going on
In Vegas, everywhere you turn on
The overpasses people are putting
Like homemade funds that are spray painted on
Like a sheet or something or
You know, papers, cardboard
So, there's tons of things going on
It's a grass roof
It's behind this guy and I'm just blown away
It's like a really, like a really underground hip band
That's what's going down with this guy
It's very interesting
I'm sure there's a podcast out there
Unfortunately, I've been working my ass off
So, I haven't been able to search for any podcast
If there's a channel where people are promoting
Not only, you know, you know,
You know, Ron Paul
But different candidates that will be amazing
I will define that
If you have any information about that
If you could let people know that would
Really help educate people and let people
Make it on the decision that will be great
And if there's a Ron Paul podcast
I let's know about it
If there's a RuPaul podcast
Not so much
Fuck you
That was alright
Yeah, excellent. Gary. Thank you so much, man
Gary Alexander
From the ultimate podcast
Yeah, well, I think that this show may become part of that
Of course, you can go to RonPaul2008.com
There's a
I spent some of some of Saturday going through a lot of the videos
I really like it when he's being interviewed
Dr. Ron Paul that is when he's being interviewed or when he's
In a debate
When he does his own speeches
He's, I don't know, it's not quite as powerful as I'd like it to be
And the message seems to be
You know, a little
Watery, I don't know what I can't really explain it
Maybe he's just not fantastic at
Giving speeches
And it is of course
Something all the other candidates are expert at
But when it comes down to really delivering the message
And answering questions I've been quite impressed with
With this Republican candidate from Texas
No less
Played a couple of bits for Patricia
She's like, crap, that's what you're always saying
I say, yep
You better believe it
And not a single
Negative comment through email, voice mail
Otherwise yet about this guy
So I want you to check him out
RonPaul2008.com
I truly believe
That his
Basis said in constitutionalism
Can really bring America
Roundback
To the initial
And the original goals of the founding fathers
Who put this together
Not that long ago when you think about it
In the meantime
In the world out there
New rules proposed by the TSA
Transportation Security Administration
Check this out
All airline passengers would need advanced permission
Before flying into through
Or over the United States
Regardless of citizenship or the airline's national origin
I saw this originally on
Slash dot
And so this is a proposal
This is fucking crazy
The new rules mean information must be submitted
72 hours before departure
Only those given clearance will get a boarding pass
TSA estimates that 90% of all travel reservations
Or will be final by then
This is ludicrous
So now we're going to be
Examine if we can even fly into
Into my own country
Scrazy
Absolutely crazy
So the
And here's what I'm learning slowly
Is that all of these issues
You know all of these conspiracy theories
All the things that we're talking about
They really come down to some very basic principles
And it really is how
The United States government has just grown out of control
And I would say
And this is one of the things I found in my research
In fact, I'm going to give you this as homework
Homework for this week is to watch
A documentary made by Aaron Russo
Aaron Russo
Unfortunately passed away in 2006
But he began his career
He managed to bet midler
Produced Tony Award winning shows
Let's see
He the member the Manhattan transfer
That was his creation he managed them
He managed a lot of people
But he also produced the rose with bet midler
He has six Academy Award nominations
Seven Golden Globe nominations
Kind very very well respected
And he did a documentary
Let me see
I'm just scrolling through
Through my notes here
And this documentary is called Freedom to Fascism
And it is available on on Google video
I'm sure it's completely
I illegally posted
But anyway you can get into it
And you can view it
I'll put the link in the show notes
It is a it is required watching
So this guy is not just any old documentary maker
Or someone who threw some shit together
And he's my kind of guy
Follow the money or follow your money
I should say
As he investigates a number of important points
As they relate to the United States Constitution
In particular the creation of the federal reserve
That's the guy who print money
For the United States of America
They have the right to print money
And determine the interest rate on the
The lending of that money to the United States
That's right
When the American
Government needs more money
It gets printed but it gets printed by the federal reserve
And it gets given to them
With interest that has to be paid back
And that interest is
Pretty much paid for by income taxes
When there's a whole question about income taxes all together
What's interesting is the federal reserve is
As much a part of the United States government
As federal express
It is in fact a commercial
Entity
It is a corporation
Comprised of member banks
Of whom of which a list is not has never been published
We don't even know who's actually a member of the bank
So if you do follow your money and you follow it all the way back to these guys
You'll see that it's very very important
That we consider
Not just
Voting
Ron Paul into office
But consider the actual message of no longer allowing the federal reserve to print the dollar
That should default back to the government
The government should be printing up money when necessary
As they're allowed to under the constitution
Take it back from the banks
Please and any candidate who is heavily backed by bankers and hedge funds
Please consider
Following your
Money
That's winded up with a mash up from achy
He loved it so much when I played his Banjovi remix
He sent me a link to a page of awesome stuff
Who has a little dick?
Well, GWB of course has a little dick
Chaining
With your help we're going to share a message about the mechanism of national strength
We're broadcasting the message of tolerance
To prove
Ladies and gentlemen, I have a message for military
We win this war
I also have a message for all Americans
I have a small dick
Big dick
and ladies and gentlemen of the congress, a man who can be jailed and have
in the state in this day is one, I can't beg that big woman who is not long enough, who is
not long enough, who is not long enough, who is welcomed as a matter of
Large horse-maw.
You don't want me to saw it, Jayden.
The land here's some in this hall of my mind, Jayden.
It's too small.
But I believe they can be resolved if I'm adequately.
Small things should be able to man together.
And I join the American people,
and I'm plotting your unity and resolve.
Small and short, small and short.
Small and short.
A small and short.
You're going to be big.
Big hit.
Every day we are called to do small things.
I know how painful it is to see a small thing.
Is there a home for me?
Live a chance.
And frankly, you have a small day.
You don't want me to saw it, Jayden.
You don't want me to see you.
Everybody on the message.
I have nothing more to add to that.
Nice.
Ike, way to go.
Short dick chaney.
George W. Bush versus 20 fingers versus offspring.
On a daily source code episode 672.
Okay, two more things before I wrap it up.
So the first is, I truly believe that the message of Dr. Ron Paul speaks for itself.
His record speaks for itself.
How he's voted on many major issues.
He's been a representative of the United States Congress for, since 1975, I think.
Guys been around for a long time.
Never heard of him ever.
So I think all we need to do is get people to at least listen.
You know, just be made aware of the fact that he exists.
If we can get him to go check out his message.
I think it'll be, I think it'll be easy.
So I think we need some creative juices here.
We need to have some shit that goes viral.
I mean, if the guy, if the, you know, leave Brittany alone guy can go viral.
I'm sure we can come up with something equally as smart.
Or as with enough virality that we can get the message out.
I'm thinking, you know, YouTube videos.
You know, why couldn't we do something like, let me see.
You know, you know, how you can do like comparisons between candidates.
Maybe we do something a little bit of, let me see if I can, one, two, one, two.
So he's a, you know, Dr. Ron has a, is a doctor, a proper doctor, a medical doctor,
OBGYN.
Is that it?
He's delivered over 4,000 babies.
So you could, for instance, create a viral campaign that went something that in it had
a line that said, he's seen more beaver than Bill Clinton.
I don't know.
Something like that.
So here's one, here's one thing that I'm very concerned about.
I have seen this type of situation very close to an election before.
In fact, I saw this in the Netherlands.
I believe it was the 2000, was the 2000 elections or the 2002.
Well, it was in the 2000s in the Netherlands.
A guy named Pim Fortan, openly gay, highly intellectual scholar who ran with his own party
to take control of the Dutch government.
And he would have, in fact, his party won in a landslide posthumously because he was assassinated
four days before the election.
In a very peace loving country like the Netherlands, assassinated by some guy who apparently
was some crazy from, you know, what was he like an animal lover, some crazy ass stupid story
like that.
So whenever someone, and by the way, you ask any Dutchman.
They will say, yeah, that guy spoke the truth.
He really was talking the truth to the people.
You ask any Dutchman who is cognizant of this guy.
This party won posthumously, of course, the party fell apart because, you know, the leader
was gone.
So it was impossible.
So I'm very worried about, you know, people who stand up and say, hey, wait a minute.
Are we nuts?
When it comes to the US, look at the constitution, look at how this thing has been violated,
how many times, and by whom?
And that, my friend, Parki, is why the second amendment is so critical because we need to
be able to protect people like this.
In fact, that's one of the questions I'm going to ask a doctor, Ron, if he has any
fear that coming too close to the truth, could actually put him in physical danger.
I truly believe it's dangerous today to speak your mind loudly and proudly in public
places.
Okay.
That's enough for today.
My head hurts.
So tomorrow, I'm pretty sure I'll be back.
We'll continue.
Keep your phone calls coming.
And be on the lookout for Dr. Ron Paul, Presidential candidate.
On this very show, hopefully this week, if not an update, when he'll be able to.
Atomatpodshow.com, DailySourceco.com, thank you for listening.
Have a great, free week.
That means free as in free dumb.
Enjoy it.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and line light.
Thanks for watching.