You've been your Scarborough Wal-Mart Supercenter.
Good morning, so pretend to want my call back to you.
Yeah, hi, my name is Adam Curry.
Okay.
I'm in a funny situation right now.
I'm calling from my cell phone.
I'm in the man's toilet room and there's no more like toilet paper.
Can someone bring some toilet papers?
Uh, we want the front to back.
The one that closes to the McDonald's there.
McDonald's, okay.
Yeah, just a second.
Yeah, sorry.
Can this person bring something to read like,
I don't know, maybe a magazine, something like a Mary Claire
or because it's kind of boring in here.
Oh, you know, sorry if it is a magazine like if it is not paid for doing a lot too.
Delta share Charlie five, five, six.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Sorry, I didn't listen to it.
We working with our set.
Sorry that I spent so much time living in my head.
Sorry, I gave you everything.
Do you know I would do anything for you?
Did you stay too long?
I'm not sorry anymore.
For the way I was before.
And as far as I can turn I think we fell.
We fell.
I'm not sorry anymore.
There's a change you can't think more.
There's a lesson to be learned.
I simply fell.
Must have said I'm sorry.
A hundred thousand times.
Everything that I'm to blame tonight,
I apologize.
I was wrong.
Did you stay too long?
Sorry if I'm boring you.
I'm getting in your way.
Sorry maybe it was but I'll say it anyway.
I'm sorry if you everything.
Do you know I would do anything for you?
Did you stay too long?
I'm not sorry anymore.
For the way I was before.
And as far as I can turn I think we fell.
We fell.
I'm not sorry anymore.
There's a change you can't think more.
There's a lesson to be learned.
I simply fell.
I'm not about to go down by myself.
I'm not about to go down by someone else.
I'm not about to go down by taking you with me.
Make blacks have been straight up.
I'm not sorry.
From the positive music network.
Man, I've been getting a lot of, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sorry.
And as far as I've considered, I'd say we barely, we barely, I'm not sorry anymore, there's a change you can't ignore, there's a lesson to be learned, I'd say we barely, I'm sorry about that, Nick Black, yeah, a lot of people talking about Nick Blacks, ending in comments and links on the PodsA Music Network, if you want to find out more about Mr. Black, Nick Black, head on over to dailysourcecode.com.
Hey, everybody, how are you doing? It's a show number five, five, six, the chat chat, the Charlie on and full effect. If you are looking at your iPod or your iTunes or some other player or the PodsAoMashboarding, you see the picture of the fine cat, let me just explain that.
Remember I built those pipes, the Yahoo pipes, the new pipes thing they've got, pipes.yahoo.com, and I said, okay, take the daily source code feed and the show notes, run it through Yahoo's special engine that is supposed to understand the context of each individual entry, so each show and then give me some pictures that from flicker using tags or whatever.
So it's all kind of like the secret Yahoo mumbo jumbo secret sauce and this picture showed up with this cat literally like flying through the air and every single time I look, I'm just like, yeah, that's awesome.
Hey, shows a little bit later than the normal, of course, there was no show on Friday due to travel. I've got to say in a real English way, I'm knackered.
Oh man, got home Friday. We landed on time. We actually landed a little bit ahead of schedule and of course, what always happens that he throw in the early morning is, you know, someone's supposed to leave the stand or the jet way or the gate or whatever and so they're there and then we're waiting and then we pull up.
We'd like an hour and a half on the ground or really sucked. So I got home a little bit later than anticipated and I was just like, I'd already told P to up for the for serious. I said, oh, man, you, you better get a backup show because I don't think we're going to be able to make it.
And, and I didn't, honestly. And, and of course, I had to come back in time and in time to turn around because we had our our social event last Saturday night, the lady Patricia and I were invited to Gavin Patterson's house is a wife and his four kids in,
what is that, a small town outside of London, Sheperton. And it was a big deal, you know, this is the first social event we've been invited to. Now, Gavin is he's big man on campus at BT. So it was interesting, you know, someone who I met professionally and now is going to socialize with and we don't know anybody here, you know, no one invites us to anything, certainly not like young hit people. And of course, Gavin is wife for younger than we are.
But it was awesome, man. I would two other couples there. And yeah, I felt like we were being pulled into a social circle. And I don't know, is it something in the water over at BT? Do you recall when I met with the CEO been providing known as the flying Dutchman that the first thing he wanted to do with search for food podcasts?
Because he's really into cooking. Well, check this. So Gavin cooked the meal and dude, it was like, it was really, really good. And it was good wine and that good conversation.
See, one of the other couples or two other couples there. He was he's a songwriter and producer. I think he's done a couple of West life songs.
Steve is his name. Steve McKenzie, I think Steve Mack is how Steve. And so that was fun. You know, we chatted him. Of course, we did we looked at the lunar eclipse.
I hope you saw the lunar eclipse. It was spectacular from from London. It really was nice. We stood out there with binoculars and, you know, just kind of marveled.
I think really how, you know, when you look at the moon through a telescope or binoculars, particularly a full moon as it was.
You know, it's really bright and it's, you just can't really see all the definition of the planet itself. But now with this eclipse, it was like a, like a ruby red.
Yeah, like a light ruby red. And it was very easy to look at it.
And it was a freak of nature, but I loved it. Sunday I wanted to go to, well, the aircraft, the Delta Sierra has has his annual coming up in March this month, obviously.
In case you're interested in aviation, every aircraft needs to have an annual inspection. And that happens obviously once a year.
The timing is quite good because, you know, it's still kind of shitty weather and not a lot of opportunity to fly.
But yet it is flyable to do the, you know, to get it to where it has to be for the, for the annual inspection. And, you know, that the engine,
they open up the engine, they, you know, they drain all the fluids, putting fluids in, they're going to check the wheels, you know, the whole thing, right.
But Sunday was, gosh, it was, it was a nightmare, the weather. It was, it was, it was, it was gusting up to 40 knots of wind.
So we didn't, didn't go anywhere, but I knew that this morning I had to get up at the crack of dawn. It was actually quite dark because I had committed to speaking,
actually talking with a group of marketers at BT at British Telecom. And I've never really done an early meeting.
We had to be somewhere like at 830 a.m. in London. So I got up at 6. I said crack of dawn.
I have to door by 7. 717, I call it the train. And I learned something very important because I love taking the, you know, the first class cabin because it's just nice.
I think it has better suspension. They have power there for your laptop, you know, it's, it's, it feels nice.
And I, a little did I know that doesn't, doesn't matter what kind of ticket you bought.
There's no place to sit on the 717, I am drained. There's people sitting in the aisles.
It was really, and, and this is kind of like a fast train. So it doesn't make a lot of stops.
It came up from, uh, portsmith maybe, portsmith, uh, somewhere down south.
And people were just fast asleep. They must have gotten on this train at 5 o'clock in the morning. Oh, my goodness.
So I learned an important lesson there. So I had a nice, nice morning and to wrap it all up.
That's why the show's a little bit late because I came back home and decided to the show after I was done.
But now I'm like, ah, tired. Um, okay. Lots of stuff to talk about.
I did do some fidgeting and fooling around with the N800 over the weekend. I just got the, the European Nav Kit in.
Uh, that's my personal Nav Kit. So, um, I'm just going to, uh, I got to reconfigure some files and stuff.
And then I can set up the N800, which will go on board Trinity on her tour.
Um, and open her ports wide up. Uh, you know, we've, uh, we've been talking about a name since Trinity has, as Trinity is a car.
And she has her name. We have to give this, uh, this device that the developers are going to enter.
Violate her, her file system by entering her ports. We have to give her a name.
Now, lots of different names that we got. Sharon Stone was a name, so call her Sharon because Sharon has also displayed her ports.
I like the suggestion, but when you say Sharon, I think of Sharon Osborne and there's nothing sexy about Sharon Osborne in my opinion.
Uh, I'm thinking why not just call it Angelina, because that truly is the dark mistress of ports.
Hi Adam, this is early from the dark compass pod cast and what sort of the first one came through. I'm not so I'm doing it a second time.
Just so that you know that I was listening to where daily source code 555 and um, you were discussing about multiple sclerosis and we should have had this disease by the boss by now.
And yes, I believe from Tonshikku, um, I was diagnosed with MS over a year ago now, and it's taking me a long time to become emotionally repaired from, um, coming to terms with the ailment.
I'd say that it's, it's not, um, caused lots of trouble in my life, but, um, second me a long time to come to terms with it all.
Anyway, um, there was a thing in the paper about it, um, saying that MS can be brought on by lack of vitamin D, which is sort of some sign and things like that.
So as dusty geeks in dark corners using laptops and desktop and things like that, might be at a higher risk. I don't know, I really take those kind of things with a pinch of salt.
But anyway, just for their blood, you know.
Um, thanks a lot, Adam, take it. Yeah. So unfortunately, no earth shattering news about a cure.
This stems from the, uh, the, uh, the bitties walk promo that I played on Thursday. Yeah, what was I think Thursday? Oh, maybe it was one last week, whatever.
I'm and Monica with the band. Now if you've never seen the bitties, I'll put a link in the show notes to their site. They're all cute.
Okay. And so, and, and not only that, but their fantastic musicians.
And what they did last year with the bitty walk, which is a part of the walk, uh, the MS walk.
They raised, uh, I think was close to $30,000. And it was, as far as I know, was done through podcasts, uh,
no CC Chapman helped out a lot on that, uh, and through, uh, through websites and web logs.
And I kind of, I got carried away. And then, uh, and, you know, after the promo, I said that I had had several erotic dreams about a mandamonico,
uh, who actually does the spot and that, oh, luckily she called in to say hi.
Adam clearly, this is a mandamonico.
Uh, um, I was very, very enthusiastic of you.
Um, the podcast today. Um, but whatever, uh, thank you so much for, um, for posting the, uh,
not posting for playing our, our promo. Um, and, uh, we should good walk with us.
That would be fun. Um, and I hope you're well.
Talk to you soon. Bye.
What do you mean whatever a mandamonico? That's, let me know whatever.
When I'm having erotic dreams of you, this is kind of what springs to mind.
Ah man, this brings back memories.
Thank you at Tom Schuiting for finding this and editing it and putting it together.
I'm going to keep this one on standby because I think we're going to be needing this from time to time on the daily source code.
Hey Adam, Gary Alexander here from the ultimate podcast.
I bet you're wondering why I'm whispering.
It's because my shows about to blow up.
I just sound with pod show bitches.
I'm not bragging and I'm not boasting.
It's called the ultimate podcast for a reason.
It's because it's about the ultimate fighting championship.
The UFC makes martial arts is the fastest growing sport in the world.
I go behind the scenes with these fighters.
I take you into the gym with these fighters.
I let you know who these fighters are when the gloves are off.
It's not that big of a deal on my show to hear this.
I want to win the fight however I have to.
It comes down to cutting his face.
So be it.
Or to hear what light heavyweight champion of the world.
Chuck Ladell listen to on his iPod.
Before a fight, I have everything country.
I listen to they laugh.
I listen to country.
I listen to rap.
It popped.
Change from one to the next.
I've got country to slayer than to rap.
So for your weekly dose of testosterone, come on over to the ultimate.podshow.com.
Wow.
All right.
I think this was, um, I think what didn't he send in a comment or something.
And then I said, I really like the idea of a show about about ultimate fighting.
And then, you know, the ball just rolled and there you go.
Now on the network.
Fantastic.
People send me emails all the time and say, you know, how do I join the pod show network?
It's really easy.
You know, you just say, head like the join.
It's not all that hard.
And you can join, you can join the network whenever you want.
And use all the services.
But, you know, when we really go for the marketing, the PR angle.
And of course, uh, advertising and sponsorships.
I just send me an email, send someone an email.
I think there's a link on the site where you can send an email.
At what are the requirements?
All you got to want to do is build an audience.
That's all I think anyone cares about.
Whatever your audience is.
Open for business.
Hey, Adam.
It's Steve Werner from Fitbitations.
The weekly podcast for runners at Steve Werner.com.
I'm out here listening to the Charlie on a 10 mile training run
Through the backcountry roads of New England.
You might remember that last year, I ran the 110th Boston marathon.
The oldest and most prestigious annual 26.2 mile road race on earth.
And this year, on April 16th, I'm going to do it all over again.
On race day, I'll be wearing a computer chip on one of my running shoes.
So podcast listeners can track my progress in real time as I run from Hopkins
and Massachusetts to downtown Boston.
I'll have details on how to do that at Steve Werner.com.
My show may be just a goofy little podcast.
And I've only been producing it since the summer of 05.
But technically speaking at least, I guess you can say that
Fitbitations is the longest running podcast in the podcast universe.
And on April 16th, I'll be podcasting as I run the Boston marathon.
Again, you can find out more at Steve Werner.com.
Thanks again, Adam.
Got a run.
Hi, Steve.
For Dipbitations.
Awesome, dude.
Yeah, that was pretty cool last year.
With that chip that he has an issue and you can just follow.
It's very reminiscent of a free Trinity project.
Maybe we should just have Steve run across the country.
That's an idea.
Running from Wi-Fi spot to Wi-Fi hotspot.
Oh, man, I almost forgot to tell you.
So I got the navigation kit with the US maps for the N800.
And it comes with a little Bluetooth receiver.
This is the web tablet that I've been using that I'm just rating about because I love it so much.
By the way, this is not paid endorsement.
No money has exchange hands with Nokia.
So it comes with a little Bluetooth receiver, which is really good.
Because I've had a couple of these Bluetooth GPS receivers and it takes a long time from to lock in.
And this thing is like boom, it locked into the satellite.
It's very quickly seems to have a fantastic reception.
Because normally I have to stick it against the window of the car or something like that.
And he had just had it in my pocket and was working.
And so I decided to be very naughty and bad.
And even though you're not supposed to have any devices that transmit on during the flight,
I placed the little receiver right near the window in my version Atlantic upper class suite.
I had to kind of balance it there with a pillow up against the window.
And so I followed along.
How much of a geek am I?
So I followed along on the map.
And San Francisco airport SFO was clearly marked.
But even nicer, all four runways are also on the map.
So, excuse me.
It's getting better.
So I could actually see as we were parallel the runway to turn around and then head off into the wind and take off.
And I was literally watching the runway on my screen.
It was really an awesome experience.
And I could see the speed.
You know, it's sure enough about 170 miles an hour.
We rotate and we take off.
And as we're flying of north, the map actually stayed down relatively low because of course
It's meant for driving.
So it knew my position.
You know, it could calculate a position quite easily.
But of course, what it was showing me was the position that I was at had I been on the ground.
And it was the most awesome thing to just see the landscape and the roads and the towns at 500 miles an hour going.
Yeah, and I had turned on a couple of point of interest.
You know, you can turn, they have like all the Wi-Fi hotspot.
That really slowed down the performance.
But petrol stations, gas stations.
It was really, it was a trip.
It really was like, wow, this is, this is how I'm going right now.
If I were on the road, look at this, look at this line.
Look at what I'm crossing.
I'd certainly recommend that to anyone who wants to break the rules.
Hello, Adam.
So Mike Turner here from Bristol in the United Kingdom.
About pop fading and a couple of you podcasts that you know about.
Perversion for profits, whatever happened to that.
You know, last year's your video podcast.
These are like that one.
You know what?
It's too much work.
It really is.
It's a lot of work transcoding all this stuff.
That's why I'm, I've been playing around with cast blaster mics.
Vig caster because that'll basically take any video you throw at it.
And then you can compile stuff together and then.
Done, you know, it renders out a whole show.
So I think that I would probably once that really starts working well.
Forming is a couple of things I need.
I want to be able to do voiceovers over the video.
And that's not, I don't know if that ever be possible.
But it's not possible currently.
Then I'll bring it back.
But it's just, it's a lot of work.
And most of the work, by the way, is done and.
Excuse me, folders with splendid.
It's, uh, most of the, most of the work is in converting all these different.
Formats, you know, back and forth.
It's, it's really.
It's not easy.
It's just using MP3's.
A bit money on that production equipment for as well.
And also your daughter, daughter's one.
Christina's, uh, pod saves the queen.
He's like that one as well.
Great podcast.
Um, just get the.
Anyway, I can be found at, uh,
The game I'm show.
Don't think you pot show dot com.
Cheers.
Well, interesting.
You should say that because, um, you know, now with the new, with the BFF, the boyfriend.
Um, Andy.
Yeah, he's, he's said to Chris.
Because I think it was just, once she gets doing it, she likes it.
But, you know, she's kind of just a lazy.
Like a teenager.
It doesn't really want to get started on it.
Uh, but Andrew's, Andy's very interested.
And he wants to engineer it.
And yeah, he knows how to run sound boards.
Uh, sound board and stuff.
He's a musician.
Uh, so, um, Christina announced to me the day before I came home.
Yeah, Thursday, when we, when we spoke, she had a really good grade for one of her, uh,
one of her important, uh, essays or whatever, uh, for English.
And we talked about that.
She's, oh, you know, Andy and I are going to do a show.
So I guess it's coming back.
Uh, but I, I just don't want to push, you know, if she, if she wants to do it,
fine, if she doesn't, you know, what am I going to say?
She's a teenager.
She did get a part time job.
Another thing Andy can't stand.
He's like, you know, if you just do a couple of podcasts, then you would make more money.
Then you make an entire week at this job.
She's at, uh, one of those, uh, boutiques, uh, in the high street.
And, you know, she's cleaning, you know, tidy up clothing racks and helping customers.
And, uh, but you know, she went out.
She got the job herself.
And I think that's important.
It was a big, big part of why she wanted to do it.
I think.
And she's really proud of it.
So, but anyway, to come back to your question,
I think part save the queen is in the cards.
I got to squeeze this one in before the saddle I window and hold on.
Hi Adam Simon here from SLAM Idol.
I just wanted to let you and your listeners know,
just how proud I am that the SLAM Idol podcast is now a part of the pod show family.
As you know, SLAM Idol is all about spoken word performance.
On the SLAM Idol podcast, you can hear some of the best performance poets from around the world,
battling for the title of SLAM Idol.
The contest are conducted in audio or video format.
And the winner in each contest is decided by the votes cast by the listeners.
In the current contest, we've got all six poets publishing audio blogs,
while they're writing their poems to a deadline,
which is providing a real fascinating insight into the writing process
and is proving to be amazingly interactive as well.
And I've got a few more ideas up my sleeve to take SLAM Idol into new and innovative areas.
And I really think that being part of pod show family
will play a big part in making those happen.
Thanks again for your support Adam and the website is at SLAM Idol.cast.com.
Right, huh?
I've been wanting to play that for a couple of shows now,
but I had to fit it into the satellite window because it's so much cooler when you
join the network and get stuff going and it's also played on serious.
I know people like that, so I really try.
You know, as we were growing as a company,
there's a lot of things you start to look at.
Cost of communications is one.
We have like a corporate department now with HR and shit.
I've been through this before.
So you start to look at, you know,
we have multiple offices in different countries.
You start to look at, you know, getting a common,
well, I think we have a common cell phone plan,
but you even start to evaluate that.
And, you know, my phone calls are pretty expensive.
Now, the reason why, of course, is because I continue to use my U.S.
phone even in the UK.
And that's really just for convenience sake,
because short of carrying two phones with me the whole time,
which is, which will be an incredible pain in the ass,
which so I could have a UK number.
I just carry that one around.
So of course, anything any calls I make or receive here
are subject to roaming charges,
which can really, can really add up.
So I know that we're looking at a voiceover IP solution
between our offices,
and it would make sense for me to have that here at home as well.
So, and I was just looking around and I'm like, you know,
what is available?
And I know that the E61, the Nokia E61 phone that I have,
that it will do voiceover IP,
and it will use the same address book.
These are all the things you run into.
I mean, yes, easy enough to set up, you know,
or use Skype or whatever.
But there's a lot when it comes to, you know,
coordinating, particularly your phone numbers,
and also very, very minor things that are incredibly irritating
if they don't work, like caller ID, you know,
it's like, I know who's calling me,
nine times out of ten, because the only people who call me
are the ones that are probably in my phone book anyway.
And so I can see who it is, you know, it just helps.
It just makes me feel better knowing.
I can already set my mind to what the conversation is about to be.
A lot of that doesn't work with voice systems.
You know, and it's all just because it's catching up,
and not all the protocols have been implemented.
But I've been playing with two different systems,
which I thought were pretty cool.
I just wanted to mention one is,
and you really should check this out.
It works on, I think all Nokia phones is called
Fring,
Fox Trot, Romeo, India, November, Golf,
so F-ring, Fring,
and you loaded up.
And hello.
I thought that was a lady Patricia.
So you loaded it up on your phone.
It actually will not import,
but it will integrate your existing Nokia phone book,
which is nice.
And with it, you can do voiceover IP chats, of course,
and that's nothing new.
But you can also do calls on G-talk.
You can do voice calls on MSN.
And Skype.
Interestingly enough.
So I guess those guys have some kind of server set up,
and this piece of software talks that server.
I'm not going to share how it works, actually.
It doesn't matter.
But you can happily use Skype out, Skype in works.
And the application is still a little bit buggy.
You have to flash my phone and get the latest firmware
to make sure.
But it works.
And so if you're in the neighborhood of a Wi-Fi connection,
then you can receive calls and make calls.
Of course, not the same number.
Lots of drawbacks.
But I was really blown away by this thing called the Gizmo project.
And there's a client for this for virtually every platform.
Windows, Mac, Linux, and also one for the N800.
And I really like this service.
I mean, it's thinking a lot like I am.
It lets you integrate your contacts from your Windows address book,
or your Outlook, your Outlook Express.
So that's pretty good.
So you can kind of synchronize those up.
But I like about it.
It uses a little bit more bandwidth.
And it gives you a fantastic quality of call.
It really does.
And I have to say it's it's it's changed my N800 into a into a phone.
It really has.
And so this week is going to be the first week that I'm really going to test it in conference calls.
Because a lot of times when the quality degrades and it does happen.
And then it's just not worth it.
You know, just you're wishing for a regular cell phone call.
But I think this is something interesting and something.
I mean, the quality is really good.
You know, Skype is it works.
And you kind of feel like you're getting what you pay for.
But this has the same dial in dial out rates.
And it just feels like it's a lot like it feels like the service has a lot more sound.
Like it's less buggy.
And the quality is better.
And it's probably because it uses more bandwidth.
But I'll put a link in the show notes of that.
If you're looking into voice over IP solutions.
I'm sure someone's going to send in some kind of idea or comment.
But just one of those things.
I'm just, you know, I got interested in it now.
Now I saw the $3,000 on phone bill.
Adam, it's James from Durham.
Not London, but Durham.
Or piano, or the Stav England.
Land of the Principuships.
Yes.
A couple of weeks back, you've got a voice mail.
I think it was from Digital Planets, the BBC podcast.
I'm sure it was.
If that's not the case, then stop this common straightaway because it's not valid.
But if that is the case, I was listening to Digital Planets.
In the digital planet a couple of days ago on the latest episode.
And there's a bit of a clue as to whether these people actually do listen to the DSC or not.
See what you think.
We've had more technology now, built to help us do it.
Well, it's just so easy.
I mean, you can't stop people publishing online.
And that's one of the great things about the last sort of seven or eight years of the growth of the internet.
I'm sure it's sort of Peter and Chris will both agree that there's just explosion in.
People being able to get their voices out there to be heard.
It's fantastic.
It is magnificent.
Yeah, I mean, Peter, you don't need no stinking transmitters.
And you're saying before we actually started putting this program together, that you create podcasts using.
So there you go.
I don't know if it's worth ringing these people to me.
It actually would be genuine and maybe want to do an interview.
But you may already be there anyway.
But there you go.
And I hope you enjoy the improved audio quality.
Yes.
James, much better.
James calls in like five times a day.
And usually as cell phones drop an hour and there.
Much better James.
Well, the guy did ask me to come on that show.
But I was in San Francisco at the time.
We had eight hour time difference.
I'd have to get up in the middle of the night.
And it was like, so I just didn't work out.
But yeah, I think I think he's the host certainly was listening.
This no stink in transmitters.
Yeah, like that.
Um, just to make it shorter short for today.
A couple of comments about about Wi-Fi.
Check this.
This is, this is a good.
Yeah, it's stuck in.
You got it.
I guess.
I did it in the $500 pickup truck rolling down.
Yeah.
Who?
What is this?
Route 7 in Virginia.
Listening to the wireless on touch on number five, five, five.
And the wireless discussion about putting the email address as the SSID,
which is a great idea.
I think I agree with you about, you know, putting in the software that opens the web page
and makes it look like a hotel or airport access.
Yeah, that would be extra geeky, although that appeals to me as well.
But I seem to recall, back in the old days of wireless and maybe still.
Um, people in cities, especially like New York, we've put their router right in the window
of like their apartment.
And then down on the sidewalk with chalk, I guess.
We'd leave a symbol and I forget now what the symbol was, where there was some sort of symbol
that you could chalk onto the sidewalk.
So that passers by would know that there was an open wireless exit.
Access point there.
And, um, you know, so you could sit down on the park bench nearby and and get online.
Now, now a lot of municipalities, specifically like here in Alexandria, Virginia,
our friends at Earthlink are opening up a Wi-Fi network, which is now in downtown,
but they're going to expand it all over town.
Some of the other communities around here are planning on doing that.
I know Philadelphia is planning on doing it.
Much to the secret of some of the other internet providers that don't want them to.
But what a great idea if you want, if you want your, if you are going to have your access point open,
you know, put some little symbol out in the world.
So that passers by will know that they can get online there.
That's it.
Jack.
Jack podcast.com.
On Jack, Jack.
Yeah, there he goes.
What was that called chalking war chalking something like that?
I remember that very well.
And I have to say it was kind of before GPS really kicked in.
And that's what those, I was talking about those Wi-Fi points of interest.
I'm not quite sure where the, what database, where that data is coming from,
but obviously the, you know, the 2007 version of war chalking is to get your Wi-Fi access point,
listed in one of these GPS database systems so that, you know,
people can use a GPS receiver to actually go from point to point.
But I think, you know, looking a little bit further.
I'm a big believer in keeping your computer on 24 hours a day, not rebooting it,
turning it off.
And I'm also in believer that we're going to have just wireless access everywhere.
I ensure right now there's different versions of it.
But, you know, I can get my email on my cell phone.
I can get, uh, I can get if I want to even get MP3s.
There was slow link, you know, there's something in London I think now called the cloud.
I don't know too much about it, but from what I understand,
it's a wireless network that is supposed to cover portions of London.
If not all of it, I really don't really don't know.
And instead of, um, using a, um, a password like regular web encryption,
it uses your MAC address so that is the physical, um,
computer address of your Ethernet adapter in this case, your Wi-Fi card.
Um, and so wherever you go, it's continuously, you know, kind of roaming and
giving you a blanketed coverage.
I mean, that's, that's where it's got to go.
And, and, you know, the bandwidth will go up.
No doubt about it.
You know, one way or the other is going to go up.
And, and you'll be able to get whatever you want wherever you want.
So, this is just interim stuff.
In the meantime, as I've said,
you're free to suck off my Wi-Fi.
Anytime you want, you know, it's open.
You don't even need to email me.
Suck at will.
And I think James came back with another brilliant thought about this idea of putting your email address
as your, uh, Wi-Fi access name so that people could then email you and, you know, say,
hey, can I have some access?
That James is always thinking on his feet.
Hi Adam, it's Kevin Cross from the frapp.
Crap.
It's Kevin.
Not James.
It's podcast.
Uh, with your discussion about James's idea of using an email address and you are, uh,
Wi-Fi network name.
Uh, so let me get this straight.
I'm trying to filter some of these free Wi-Fi because I don't have internet access.
And I see the email address so I email them to get access.
But wait, I don't have internet access.
How do you email somebody if you don't have internet access?
Seems like a flaw on the plan.
I got, uh, idea of getting the web page,
or you can just type in something or whatever.
Anyway, um, just to thought maybe I'm missing something
not to be a touchy later.
It's a perfect great work.
Now, you're, uh, I think you're absolutely right.
Makes a lot of sense, doesn't it?
I don't have access to how am I going to email him.
Mm-hmm.
Ah, back to the drawing board on that one, then.
This is a nice endorsement, uh, Richard Jeffrey says,
Hey, Adam wanted to write and give you a comment on the DSC show where you talked about in the attic.
This is the show with the Rachel Fuller and her boyfriend, Pete Townsend.
After watching all 12 shows so far, I went to iTunes,
bought a shitload of music from the artist they had on a work for a band of sound engineer.
We would sit around and play acoustic guitars and those with the best moments,
which is exactly what in the attic is.
Podcasting my opinion seems to be more personal easier to get the content.
And that hits home with a listener at the point is I've bought and experienced more music
because of shows like yours and not from the radio.
Also, I've not listened to regular radio since I got my iPod.
I hope to have my own podcast up this weekend.
Richard, awesome dude.
Yeah.
And this is good because later in the week I want to talk about, uh,
I want to talk a little bit more about money and about advertising.
Because we haven't talked about that in a long time.
And, uh, I feel, I feel the need.
It's time once again.
Like this.
Sorry.
My ears hurt as much as yours do now though.
Don't worry.
It's pretty good promo.
Good morning, good evening, good day to you.
You're listening to Young Potset Band.
Best in New Electronics music coming to you live from London Bridge, England.
So welcome to the Young Potset Band.
Let's do that by music and nature.
London Bridge, England.
We will be bringing you best in your electronic sounds coming out of the UK
or anywhere else where we find something interesting.
There'll be house music.
There'll be breaks.
There'll be drum and bass.
Yeah.
There'll be a let-tropop.
So maybe the sounds of a durable running along a synthesizer.
Subliminal message.
www.theunpunks.com
Punks is spelled P-U-N-X.
Because of course, in Sakura and they're spelled with X's and Z's.
And when FF is spelled with a PH instead of an F.
Alright, the Young Punks have an awesome.
Friday, of course, I missed the show.
Which means, and that's tough, I know.
I think a lot of people miss the food barness.
But I was literally food barred, okay?
So, so give me a break.
But of course, you know, there's a lot of love
and work that always goes into a food bar Friday,
including work from our own music colleges,
surgesy Todd.
So let's just pretend he's talking about Monday, okay?
Hey, how's it going, AC?
Happy food bar Friday.
Hey, listen, I've got a really, really interesting band for you this week.
The band's name is Army of Me at New York.
They just came out with a new EP released on doghouse records back in November.
And they posted two amazing songs on the Podsafe music network.
If that's not enough, if you go over to their MySpace page,
the song that I'm going to play for you going through changes
has been downloaded over a hundred thousand times.
Check this out.
The song is going through changes by Army of Me.
On, food bar Friday.
Yeah, you're going to like this, I know it.
It's hard to ask strength when there's nothing to eat.
And it's hard to eat when you don't have the teeth.
And how am you losing the one thing you love?
There's nothing below and there's nothing above.
Well, I've been going through changes by Friends.
Going through changes by Friends.
We're nothing at all.
Let's hard to accept what you don't understand.
And it's hard to launch without knowing how to land.
And how it burns, you can't change a thing.
Oh, you can soften the blow.
But you can't stop this thing.
And I've been going through changes by Friends.
Going through changes by Friends.
We're nothing at all.
Nothing at all.
I'm still yours, even if you're not mine.
I stare at the floor and I study the lines.
But what took my place in the back of the crowd?
Baby, I couldn't see it, but at least it was loud.
At least it was loud.
And I've been going through changes by Friends.
Going through changes by Friends.
Now, you see, I couldn't just save that front of the week.
Now, could I?
Army of me.
Thank you very much, sir.
Jersey Todd.
The official musicologist of the Daily Source Code.
Once again, doing your profession proud, sir.
Today, yeah, man, it's still even longer than I expected.
Tomorrow, a whole new show.
Thank you very much for bearing with me.
The ramblings of the Middle Ages white guy.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the show notes.
Everything about today's episode.
And of course, Adam at podshow.com.
I will talk to you guys tomorrow.
Take care yourself, bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.