Check out some of the world's best music, video, animation at short films from the
Manchester International Festival and brought to you by Sony PlayStation at m-i-f-dot-potchow.com.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can
govern what you see in here. One man has the power to return control of entertainment
to the masses and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants. From Pod Show,
home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code with Adam
Carrino.
There are Charlie's six, five, six.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And I'll get on the stairs, close in the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of
the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of
the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the middle of the
middle of the middle.
It is Delta, Sierra Charlie, episode six, five, six kicking off of the mash up there from
the Hoob Boys, suggested by Anthony Barnes, of course, friends, stuck in chemicals, mash up
with the chemical brother, Steelers, Wheel, Gary, Newman.
On this beautiful Monday, August 27th, 2007, the date of our daughters' birth was born
in this day, 730 in the evening, in Livingston, New Jersey, in 1990, she turned 17 today.
Oh, my God, where has the time gone?
I was just thinking, you know, episode six, five, six, I'm moving up towards a thousand
episodes, but that's nothing compared to 17 years of childrearing.
Everybody, how you doing?
Beautiful day here in the UK at the manner, on the west side of G-town, we've got just
a couple of clouds in the skies, temperature, it's got to be in the 20s, tell you, 22, 23 degrees
sun is just pouring down, it is beautiful.
So you know, by the time I leave for San Francisco on Saturday or Sunday, I think Saturday
probably, otherwise there is going to be even better here and it will be shit in San
Francisco.
That's the way it usually goes.
Ain't that the truth, I just realized I want to play a special song from the soundtrack
to my life for Christina's birthday, we'll get to that.
But a couple of actually at whole ton of comments that came in over the weekend, none of
which I played on the special Sunday, non-food bar edition of the show I did with the
lady Patricia, which I thought turned out pretty good actually, in hindsight listening back
to it at the end, that's pretty funny bits, she's nuts, what a woman, eh, what a woman
I have.
I'm such a lucky bastard.
Lucky bastard that you guys are sending in such beautiful calm.
You know, I really, when I was in the, you know, you have to understand, I was at Roseville
Field Mall.
I was depressed because of the weather and the lack of bandwidth and I'm sitting in the
car and I'm like, you know what that frick, you know, I got no time for the show.
I really want to devote as much time as possible.
And of course, by actually doing it in the car, I kind of went back to my roots and it
was really spurred on by a lot of lovely words from a lot of you guys.
I'm telling like, you know, like 40, 50 different comments, I can't play, I cannot, I don't
want to play any of them really because it's seem so self-serving.
But some people were just so beautiful in the way they put it that I want you to know
that you really did motivate me very much in, in just kind of picking myself back up off
my feet at him.
It's Carmen Tyler with the Carmen Gast.
And I have a small beef with you, okay?
Really, I'll have to say is no, no, no, no, no, no and no, you know, I'm sure you're
a guy who's definitely used to hearing a lot of women say, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, you know what?
If you stop doing the DSC, are you going to get as no, no, no and up, no, you can't stop
man.
You got to do the DSC.
You have to.
For all the women around the world so that we will continue to say, yes, oh, Carmen, oh, man,
I'm thinking maybe I stop off in Los Angeles on my way out to San Francisco just to say
hello and see if you can say yes, yes, yes.
This is Rodrick from Amsterdam Hollands, a long time the USC listener and former decibel
colleague.
I heard you on the DSC 654 about a depressing mood under dark sky and dark thoughts about
quitching the daily source go, although it was just a dark moment in time and nothing more
than that.
I want to tell you how I appreciate your almost daily reports and that you inspired me
going podcasting myself, I like you.
I did a lot of mainstream media and still do, but doing my own thing at a completely
free four main to net station called Kicks Radio in the Netherlands uploading and casting
weekly completely free from my home, that is an unbelievable, incredible experience of
freedom.
That freedom of ideas of choice, musically a sound is incredible, I love the show, love
the possam music from mashuptown.com, Blake Morgan, Ethan Stone and all the others, Adam
just continue, keep on doing the great job, folder and red pill are no doubt, nice to hear
from Rodrick, man, it's been about 25 years since we were both at the Pirate Radio Station
decibel radio, it's 80, maybe even longer than that, maybe 26, 27 years crap, man, you
still sound good, massive pipes, massive, yeah, you something that I'm real good for me.
And you know, that is why I got into this before the freedom to be able to say whatever
I want to say, to be able to play whatever I want to play, whenever I want to play it,
or almost whatever I want to play, whenever I want to play it.
Hey, Adam Allison from Craftcast, see, listen, I was going to call this message in on Monday
and put it off when you were having such problems out there in Fire Island and I know
the weather sucks, I hear ya, but what you're going to do, it's going to change, I know it's
going to change and it's going to change before you leave, but here's the thing, I started
finally listening, I was excited to see your show up today and I thought, oh my gosh, I can't
wait a second longer to call him and tell him what I want to say, which was, oh my god,
if you stop doing your show, I'd flip out, what I was going to call and tell you on Monday was
how much I just want to say thank you, thank you for putting your creative juices, energies,
and endeavors and passion in the way that you do because I get to use all of that and I hear
from people and you don't hear from the people I hear from, so I'm telling you, I get to put
a service out to people and they tell me how much they love the service and how I inspire them
and their work and all this great feedback and I couldn't do it without you, so I just want you
to know that and yeah, I know the weather will change, life will be better again, I just know it,
hang in there, I think food bar Friday will be especially sunny, okay? Love you, bye.
I mean, sexy Alice in there, thank you, darling. You know, probably the biggest bummer for me is
when I can't do a food bar Friday and it's been really rough the past couple of weeks
just because of the London commute because so much is going on and you know, particularly Friday,
which does take a lot of production because a lot of sifting through song submissions and I love it
when you guys send stuff in listening to stuff on the pod save music network, art to a dub always sends
in tons of mashups, I mean, you know, and when I can't do one of those shows, really, really
bums me out. Anywho, eventually, eventually I'll just be able to do this full time if I'm lucky.
It'll be quite a big end around to be able to do it, but we're going to get there. Hey,
toilet drop iPhone update. As you know, over the weekend on Sunday morning, I dropped my iPhone,
actually I figured out I was retracing my steps today and figured out exactly what happened. So I
had it in the breast pocket of my alges era bathroom, which is not really an alges era bathroom,
but it has, it's from, I stole it from the Borgella Rob hotel in Dubai, which is the big one that
looks like a sailboat. We stayed for a week on vacation once. I'm sure they charge me for it, of course.
But anyway, I call it my alges era bathroom because it's big and it's really fluffy and has a huge
Arabic like alges era looking symbol on it on the breast pocket. So I split the iPhone in there and I'm
meant, now I know exactly what happened because I have been trained. I have been completely
taught at trained as you can imagine just knowing what my wife is like and living with two women
taught at sea down and always particularly after the morning confessional, always a quick, a quick
scan with the brush. And that's exactly what I was doing. I leaned forward with the brush,
even though it was, well, I was ready, right, because I hadn't flushed yet. Oh, God.
And that's when I just kind of slipped out. It would have been, you know, my, my, the earbuds
tugged in my ears. It, if the, if the fall hadn't been that far, then maybe the plug would have
stayed in, but alas. It submerged fully for probably about three seconds before I jam my hand down
the throat of the porcelain beast to grab my cupartino creation and pull her back out.
After excessive blow drying, I received several comments on the weblog at curie.com. One of the
ideas was that they step on the anti-intose suggestion of putting it in either a
Tupperware box of white rice or kitty litter. We have both. I decided for the latter. And
overnight, the phone stayed in its little tomb buried under a white little rocks and lots of dust.
Pulled her out this morning, hit the power button and she actually came to life saying,
please plug me in. Because, of course, the battery had drained completely. I'm sure that that was
all short circuits that did that. Now, I plugged it back into its charging dock. Not connected
to the computer, but to the, the power supply. And sure enough, bit by bit, it came back to life.
I was able to reboot by doing the, the home button and the power button holding it for five seconds
consecutively reboots nicely. It, it, it, it brings up my customized wallpaper. It started
receiving text messages. In fact, I was able to call the phone and it rang. Identifying correctly
the number. I can see that it has an internet Wi-Fi connection, but I can't, it's completely
rendered useless because the touchscreen no longer works. So I can't answer the phone. I actually
did try answering the phone by plugging in the headset and clicking the little microphone.
Which also should answer your calls. It didn't answer that way either. So I presume that
there's still massive short circuits inside. And of course, when you think about the touchscreen,
which I believe is pretty much based on moisture for the touch. It's not so surprising that even
just a little bit of moisture is still going to probably mess it up and just make the screen
useless. You, you've probably, if you haven't, I've found you know that if you hold the phone,
you say you want to unlock it, right? You want to open it up or answer it. Call you hold the phone
in your left hand and you have your hand on the screen. No matter what you do, you're not going
to be able to open up. Not going to be able to slide anything. You actually have to hold the phone
in your hand touching the sides and not touching any other portion of the screen. So I presume that
there's still a short circuit. So what I've done is I've, I can't power her down, of course,
unfortunately. That would again require the capability to remove the battery pack.
So it'll just have to run down out of its own accord. But I've varied her once again in the
kitty litter and now placed the top of where box on top of the bathroom towel heating rack.
I have high hopes I have to say, it actually just might happen. That would be pretty phenomenal
if it came back to life. I see no reason why it wouldn't, you know, the touch screen
may have fried, but then again, it may not have. You have to expect that there's some type of
water that things are going to have to be able to handle. So fingers crossed. In the mean time,
of course, I'm back to the Nokia E61I, which is, you know, it's a perfect phone. It's got,
I do remember the ease of using that keyboard much easier, much faster to type stuff out,
particularly in abbreviated languages, such as when sending a text message or in Dutch or any
other funky language, I sometimes write in. That's really nice because, you know, that
is probably the biggest flaw of the iPhone is that it only understands English in its predictive
text mode or its auto correction mode and you cannot turn it off, which makes it extremely annoying
to do anything in any type of abbreviation form or foreign language. But the whole browsing
experience sucks ass. I am completely spoiled by the idea of looking at a full web page tapping
to zoom in using the pinch method. I'm addicted to it and, you know, forget about all the other
parts of the iPhone, you know, being connected to, you know, or locked into iTunes for your, you know,
for your podcast and putting stuff on to it. The phone is a phone is a phone, you know, it does
everything else, my other phone does, it fits all the, yeah, it does everything I want there. But
that browsing experience is without a doubt far, far, far superior. In fact, if, if the iPhone
no longer worked and only it was in web browsing mode, I would carry that with me in addition to another
phone just to have it as kind of like a web tablet. I have to say, very impressed and I only know
that now because you don't know what you got till it's gone. All right, come on in from San Francisco.
Hi, I'm prolific program. I hear from San Francisco. It's about 1120 PM on Tuesday, the 21st of August.
I just picked up the book you had recommended by Mr. Incean regarding the CIA,
legend from the Arizona ashes, or some rubbish like that. It's 700 bloody pages long. You don't
accept me to read all that before you interview Uncle Don, do you? Anyway, cheers. It's called Legacy of Ash's
subtitle, the history of the CIA by Tim Weiner, who is a reporter for I believe the New York Times.
And here's what happened with that book. In 2000, well, 2005, I believe a lot of CIA documents
became unclassified and he has poured over those meticulously. By my Uncle Don's own admission,
he says that the book is meticulously researched, seems to be incredibly accurate. And all this
stuff is on the record. There's no off the record stuff. And now, only at like page 250,
or something like that. So I got about a third of the way through the book. I cannot comment on it
until I've read the entire thing. But right now, I've already gone through the late 40s, early 50s.
I'm now into the mid 60s. Kennedy has already been assassinated. By the way, please, it seems so
obvious what happened with Kennedy when you read this book. He was trying to assassinate all these
different leaders through the CIA, through covert operations, including Castro, which, of course,
was a huge fiasco. And Castro even said, you know, hey, where's the end with you guys? If you think
that you can just eliminate foreign leaders, you should watch your own back. And well, there you have it.
And then if you see all the ties to Leigh Harvey Oswald, et cetera, that seems pretty damn obvious.
What's going on there? But I can understand how this change my Uncle Don's idea of just doing
it into you. I think he wants to make a much, much bigger statement. So I'm not at all disappointed
as some of you apparently are. Hey Adam, this is Bob Evans in Birmingham. Now, it's so looking forward
to that Uncle Don interview. And looks like we've got baited for an upcoming book. Oh, man,
maybe you should give us your phone number or his phone number. So we can call and have the interview.
You've got me all anxious about getting the hero that stuff you got to say about Toriyan,
the George Bush is anyway. Just a little disappointed. Love the show, though.
No, don't be disappointed because it's my goal not to disappoint.
I promised that I would read the legacy of the ashes of already read his commentary on it. I want to
give you guys a chance to read the book as well. I must have received 20 different emails
people saying they've ordered the book and are now walking through it. It's not that hard.
It's a pretty easy read. I have to say. And there's only so many names in it because these people
have been around for so long or were around for so long. But oh, man, just incredible inside
information into how government's work and in general exactly what I suspected when I went to
the Moscow Music Peace Festival in 1988. The wall had not yet fallen. It was very much communist
Russia. And we did a live concert from Lenin Stadium in Moscow. I was pretty awesome. That's
a story for a whole other time. I've talked about bits of it before. Excuse me.
Bun Jovi, Motley crew, Ozzy Osborn, Skid Row, Gorky Park, Fine Local Russian Band. It was
quite a blast. But this was a televised via satellite actually. And I remember quite well looking at
the cine video trucks and the westward one radio trucks and we had like in the hotel,
you had to reserve your phone call at least 12 hours ahead of time, if not 24. And if the
lady said, you know, because in the ladies, one of these like real slavic huge wrestling looking
ladies would come up to your hotel door, knock on it and say something unintelligible. And that meant
that, you know, the phone call was ready. You know, you could make you could place your call.
And if you missed that knock on the door, you had to wait another 12 or 24 hours. So of course,
I just sucked up to the guys. The westward one radio truck. And they had the satellite all set up.
They literally had five one six area code dial tone. I could just pick up the phone and just
dial, I'd call Patricia and we were in Jersey at the time. No, we're still in New York.
So just picked up. One, two, one, two. Dialed right home. And you know, that was the sophistication
that we were used to. And I remember seeing, you know, so there's, there was this big feed that
had to go out of our truck into the Russian telecommunications state run telecommunications truck
before, you know, because that was where all the censorship took place before it actually,
you know, went out up to the satellite. And I remember seeing this, you know, really awesome
high tech multi flex type cable running into this, you know, equivalent of a VW van gray.
It's this teeny little thing with curtains drawn. And, you know, something wants to know
all the door would open. You could see this basically the series of tubes sitting in there.
And I thought to myself, these Ruskies, man, they have no sophistication. They've got no technology.
You know, all this worry about, you know, the Cold War and how technologically advanced they
were. It's horseshit. And if you read the book, legacy of ashes, ashes, you'll see that it was horseshit.
With we completely overestimated the Russians ability and technology for years and hundreds of
not thousands of people died in stupid covert actions because of it. Now, the Soviets on the other
hand had much better spies. They actually had infiltrated us everywhere, including the Berlin
tunnel. If you know any of your history, you'll know what that's about. So my feeling is that there's a
story to be told here, which can relate to our present situation with the huge CIA misinformation or disinformation
about weapons of mass destruction in Iraq, about how the current administration, in particular
President George W. Bush views and uses the CIA, which I believe he's doing in a very incorrect manner.
And I believe that Uncle Don wants to do one thing that will, if not said a lot of things
straight, will definitely give us a roadmap for the way forward, which is part of what legacy of
ashes might be trying to do again. I haven't read it all. It does refer once in a while to it, you know,
the lack of intelligence to being exactly like it was in the run up to the invasion of Iraq.
And as I was talking Uncle Don, you know, he said, well, you know, he wasn't quite sure. He said,
money doesn't, he doesn't care about money, which of course I said, well, let's go give it away. That's easy.
But I think he really wants to work with a team that will help him. And what I'm going to,
I think what I'm going to suggest is that he works with a producer who will basically record his
awesome story telling. Now, once we've recorded all of his awesome story telling, we can, you know,
cut out any bits that we don't want or, you know, we can at least make a great transcription of
the stuff that he thinks should be in this package, whether it's a book, whether it's an ongoing
audio novel. I'm not quite sure what it is. But he needs to get his message out. And I think he needs
to formulate it. I think I need to sit down with him again, which I'm happy to do on the way back
from San Francisco over this current trip. Because I think that there's something really,
really good in there that could possibly change the way that we think about our government.
And let's be honest, there's no better time than the present to do that with the 2008 elections
coming up. So it is my mission. I shall not. I promise I shall not let you down.
Hi, Adam, this is Solange calling from Belgium. And I just wanted to tell you that I've been
hearing you talking about channels all this time. And honestly, I haven't had a time any time to
go look at up and see how it's like. But yesterday, my mom called me and she wanted me to explain
to her how to use iTunes. Now, she lives in Boston and we are far away. We can obviously see each other.
So it was very complicated to try to explain to her over the phone how to use iTunes.
She's a very intelligent woman, but there was no way that she would understand. And she wanted to
listen to old, a radio, mystery channel, something that we really like a lot. All radio,
mystery stories. So I went into part show and I created a channel for her. And then I
to send her the link and she clicked on it. And there she had everything she wanted. It was
fantastic. Honestly, it was fantastic. It was so easy. And well, what can I say? This is the best
way to bring people into the world of podcasting without making it so complicated for them.
It's automatically downloaded to her iTunes. All she has to do is click and she has them all there.
So there we go. So red pill and folder. Bye, Adam. Oh, yeah.
Of course, you're a red pill, darling. I could tell. Sim Salabim. It works like magic, doesn't it?
That's right. Go make your own channel at podshow.com. I saw some of the new interface over the weekend.
Now that I finally have enough bandwidth and connect to the VPN at the office. Oh, my god. It's
so radically different than anything I've ever seen. But yet it's fun. It's fun to use. It's
now we've got a real discovery mechanism that it's just outrageous. It really is. I'm sure a lot of
people are going to be confused by the switch. But once you take a look at this thing, oh, man.
I have no idea how we should roll this out. It's so radical. I'm thinking that maybe we
we start something along. I don't know. It's a radical change. But man is it awesome. It is.
I think what we always, in a way, what we always intended to do. Again, we've had all the underlying
technology and the features in our toolkit, if you will, for, well, ever since we started building
it. In fact, some of those technologies have been brought in, you know, brought forward from
development a year and a half to two years ago. Next, excuse me. I still plug Kmart back to
school at things. Back to school.podge.com, Kmart.com. You're going to like it. You're certainly
going to like the thinking behind it. Well, see, maybe you'll hate it. I don't know. Anyway,
something I normally do with my daughter in the room every year on August 27th. I tell her about
the day when her mom said, it's time to get this kid out of me. And, of course, Christina was,
you know, a breach position. So we knew it was going to be a, a sea section. About two weeks
earlier than was scheduled as when Patricia just said, this kid has to come out. It was a
beautiful day, not unlike today, I have to say, it was in the high 70s, blue sky. We drove down
the sea, Dr. Ladocy at Livingston Hospital, and Livingston New Jersey, Barnabas Hospital, and Livingston,
that's where it is. Same Barnabas Hospital. And Lewis said, all right, she's right. This kid has
got to come out. And she Patricia went in and first there was an epidural. They sent me out of the room
for that. They wouldn't let me stay. But I was allowed to be there while, and I tell you when
when you look at the person you love the most in the world and they open that person up and pull
out of that person, a whole new human being, it is just an amazing experience, accentuated by the
soundtrack to my life of that moment, because we had the radio on at the time. And I said, you know,
why don't you turn on, it was, why was light FM? WLTW106.7 FM. And this was the song that was playing
at the very moment the doctor lifted Christina from Patricia.
And some remain, all these places have a moment, with lovers and friends, I still can recall,
some more dead and some more living. My life, I've loved them all. But of all these friends and lovers,
there is no one compares with you and these memories are meaning. When I think of them as something
you know, I know I'll never lose affection. But people and things and what good went before,
I know I love and something about them. In my life, I love you more.
I know I'll never lose affection. But people and things that went before, I know I'll often stop
and think about them. I love you more. And that is exactly what the soundtrack to our lives is
all about. Taking you back, bringing those memories forward, the Beatles in my life,
whenever I hear the song. Of course, you can only imagine I can't think about anything else, but that
glory is day. Happy birthday, baby. And congratulations, Mama. Good job.
And the Daily Source Code. So check it out at worldofverning.com.
I've been looking to try and find it somewhere on your website. And I was wondering if you might
play it one more time so that I can save it. Or if you tell me where I can find it on the
potro music.com. Keep up the good work. And we're forward here and turn you. Take care.
All right. Well, that's very interesting because of course I went looking for it. This isn't the
days before the Pod Safe Music Network. When I figured that, well, if I at least took a song from a
composer that whose work is in the public domain, I'd be pretty much safe. Of course, it's a remix.
So it was created by someone. If you Google rock money off, not rock as the correct
for spelling would be RICH, but ROCK, rock money off. This is the Burris remix. Happy to play it
for you. And shutting up so that you can kind of snip it out and use it. Here comes.
...
Just our own song.
Don't believe it!
Come on!
in a car.
There you have it, and it's entirety, at least, all of it that I could find.
The rockmoning off previously the theme tune to the Daily Source code, you can see why it was
so great.
Oh man, it's really has been a soundtrack to our lives episode.
Hasn't I remember when I did the Daily Source code episode number 200 live on stage at
NomeDex, was that three years ago, two years ago, three years ago, two years ago, at least.
I just remember just potting up the tune and everyone went and he was so recognizable with
the time.
How am I?
How times have changed?
There's something that some homework for you to be discussed, hopefully tomorrow, if not Wednesday,
tomorrow is going to be one of those tough days in London, Wednesday, or anything until the
afternoon.
So, I might be missing tomorrow show, but I do want you to take a look at this for some
homework and article from the IEEE Spectrum.
This is an engineer's geeky site.
A couple of people sent this to me.
The first one was Kenny Man Luke, who sent me this, and I've receded from several other
people since then.
It's about the use of compression in music, particularly in the mastering process for CDs,
and I want to tack something on to that about the use of compression on radio stations
and on podcasts such as this one.
It's kind of geeky stuff, but it is something we definitely should discuss because it's
about deprivation of the soundtrack to our lives, so, you know, me, make sure you check
that out.
Definitely place this link in the show notes today.
Oh, crap.
Hold on.
Operator Air.
Hi, I was Gary Alexander from the Ultimate Podcast.
I'm a question for you.
I was just listening to ESPN radio to talk radio here in Las Vegas, and the guy, the radio
DJ guy.
I don't even know if you call it DJ, I don't the host, I guess, unless being very
nice.
One of these guys.
And he started degrading bloggers and started mentioning that, you know, people bloggers
or guys in their basements that only have four people, four buddies who read their blogs,
and they sit around in their basement, waiting on those four guys who read their posts.
The two, you know, I see, you know, I'm calling it, it kind of made me think, you were
in the radio business for a very long time, and you're very, very familiar with what
guys like that would think.
What is your opinion on what may be going through the minds of traditional radio guys,
host, if you will, with this changing new media, with podcasting, and with the way
that blogging is?
Of course, there are some guys that only have, you know, a couple of friends that read
what they have to say, but there are other people out there that have found an audience.
I'm very curious of what do you think, because the guy, obviously, was very defensive.
What do you think is the state of mind of these traditional radio hosts and DJs?
Thanks a lot.
All right.
Well, good question.
Before the days of packaging and completely tightening up all FM radio formats, which
happened after the glorious days of the 60s, disjockeys really were relegated down to the lowest
rung of the show business ladder, and with that, they're only hanging on by their fingernails.
You know, disjockeys used to be very powerful, very influential could really set a mood
for an entire town or city.
People would just, you know, talk about what the DJ said in the morning, and after
while it became a place only for stupid comments on the news and rim shots, you know,
after the music became completely packaged.
So this is fear that you're hearing.
These guys, they know that they're hanging on to that lowest show biz ladder, rung by
their fingernails, and they're worried.
They're worried of any, you know, completely afraid of anything that comes into their
into their space that appears on their radar scope.
That's what it is.
That's what it always is when people start slagging on the people off.
It's it's fear, complete and utter fear.
And it's a, it's a lost art, you know, being a DJ.
Some of it comes back, but since we don't have the real live aspect, you know, the real
real live aspect like RF waves going out with a localized station, um, I think the art
is pretty much a loss forever, at least I have no way of influence.
Can any more do I have any, nor do I have any desire?
I get as close as I can by doing this show.
But that's what it is.
It's just fear.
And anyone you hear talking about bloggers or podcasts or independent producers or media
of that way, hard just consumed by fear.
I had a bit of a map from Game's Weasel on this week's show.
We've got a review of BioShock on the 360, Guitar Hero 2, also on the 360.
We have a chat with WWE Superstar Mr Ken Kennedy, one is in London, and you can win a
copy of the new crazy taxi game for the PSP.
Check it out, the gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
Each man, one way, each horse, one stance, each church, one butter, each master, to his own
technique.
This is okay tomorrow, I see you all, trying to compete with Black Style, or have
a like bust a little flying zebra, you're pregnant, not scared, it's very good, but
I don't think you can compete with the conscience from style, but you can do it, you can
do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can
do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do
it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it,
you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it,
you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you
can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you
can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can
do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do
it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do that, you can do it, you can do it, he can do it, and it
I was looking through the top pod plays of the day and I saw this located boner. I'm like, I know those guys
This is the big bad China man. They've got a ton of tracks up on the pod tape music and that
worked in the show. No, it's a deadly source code.com. So you can find all of that. Before I forget
the new episode of, was it third episode of season two of port city PD is out. Oh, man. This
is getting good. I mean, these guys are, I think they've got, they're on to the format now. It's, you
know, it's still short, but it really, really wants me to get to the next part, you know. And
somehow it's got a really, I don't know what it is. They've got a real dirty, grimy street scene
kind of feel to it. I think those guys are doing awesome. If you haven't seen it yet, port city PD.podshow.com,
I guarantee you will not be disappointed. All right. So hopefully tomorrow, if not Wednesday for sure,
I'll look for another daily source code, find it at daily source code.com and send me an email anytime
at potshow.com. Talk to you soon, bye bye. The other potshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.