Delta Shira Charlie 5-9 or 7.
Adam Curry was just a guy with big hair who sold his first company and thought he'd
just kick back and take it easy, but he never counted on this.
Adam and Patricia, the king and queen of the matter, or just the lady and the tramp.
On the daily source code.
This street has come true to grant your invites and gentlemen, and let the family show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia, yes Adam and Patricia, Adam and the lady Patricia.
Shira, that's pretty, you're a pretty little thing that comes on on the street, not pulling it away.
It's easy, but I don't know about a thing, so need a thing until you won't lie.
It's easy, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don
Don't know about it, but I don't斃 it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, but I don't know about it, it contains a context in the literature, alright?
Yeah, I heard about it, yeah, alright.
Right.
Me?
No fun.
Yeah.
I'm out of thing, it's only nothing, until you won't lie
You're safe if I'm the winner
And expose me to your allergies
You get under my skin like a splinter
And you've gotten a sneeze and at the tree
And if I tried to leave you, you'd hit me with hatred
You think what's up, girl, I'm your worst nightmare
The mixture, you're such a lucky girl, please don't want no more
Me though, you're my control, I'm not getting on that train
But we were the distant, I was through the night, you're hey, hey
Everything is fine, I am your sugar, I'm free, you're a pretty woman
But I'm out of the street, I'm totally the right
And you're safe if I'm the winner
But I'm out of thing, it's only nothing, until you won't lie
You're safe if I'm the winner
And you're safe if I'm the winner
You love it, you're a hey, hey
Everything is fine, I am your sugar, I'm free, you're a pretty woman
But I'm out of the street, I'm totally the right
And you're safe if I'm the winner
And you're free, you're a pretty woman
But I'm out of the street, I'm totally the right
And you're safe if I'm the winner
But I'm out of the street, I'm completely beat
Addable red, sugar and spring.
Could have been one of your bands.
I was thinking about it.
I know. I did this.
Yeah, and they're done that.
That goes way back.
We already did this in the 70s, huh?
Ladies and gentlemen,
wearing the good girls go to heaven,
bad girls go to London T-shirt.
Yes.
It is the Lady Patricia everybody.
Fresh back from her incredible journey.
Incredible journey and showbiz extravaganza
in the in the in the in the pay bar.
The low countries.
Yes.
Baby, it's good to have you back on the show.
Everyone's been emailing me and leaving comments
and they love what you did and they love you on the show
and they fucking hate me.
They hate me, but they do like,
No, they like to very much.
No, I'm talking about people listening to the show.
Oh, okay.
You know, that's everyone else except you.
Well, you cannot satisfy everybody.
But you do, you do satisfy me.
It is Wednesday.
I have a sound in my ear.
You have no idea.
You don't like sound like a bunny.
No, you sound great.
Well, not in my ears, but it's okay.
Because seriously.
That's a disc, this jockey remark.
And I always hate that when they do that.
You know, talking about the sound actually.
But you see how easy it is to talk about that.
It's not you sound fantastic.
Okay.
As long as you think I sound fantastic.
You sound wonderful, baby.
Hey, how was your week?
Do anything fun?
Why, it's a trip.
Do anything exciting?
Every day, I ran around from here to there.
And I did all the promotion I could do.
And lots of interviews and I did all the show programs.
So what else can I do?
I don't know.
I expect lots of people to be cars.
There is not much I have to say in Holland.
There's not much to do.
Well, there is no, there are no, say, pop programs.
You know, like, top of the pops.
Yeah, but that's it.
But you're not a show.
It shows you can do music.
Well, you did the only one that was relevant.
You did the dancing with the storm.
That's why I did it.
Because this is a great show to do a real good show this thing.
So I did.
And I have to say, I think I said it yesterday.
People have no idea how much work goes into setting something up like that.
I mean, it's.
Do you know how hard I mean?
People do not realize how hard it is to get 23 marines to dance to a different song.
And they do it.
No, no, no, no.
I mean, there are all, it wasn't that I'm purpose.
You wanted them to look out at the time.
Well, out of rhythm.
No, but we didn't have the time.
Because that takes an hour.
Yeah.
And you only have an hour to rush.
And another hour or two hours to get them feel the rhythm.
You know, they're not used to doing that.
And these are not Americans.
Americans have this.
You know, it's in them.
The rhythm is in them.
They're hardly any Americans that cannot swing.
You know, that is the way they clap and everything is always on the two and the four.
It's right.
And most certainly Dutch audiences.
But I've seen the bridge do it as well.
They all clap on the one and the three.
Yeah.
Is there a way to explain how wrong that is?
I mean, I don't think people even understand what we're talking about.
It's about a feeling.
And whatever they feel, and if they're happy and enjoying it, it's all clear.
But it is.
Now, of course, you are our musical sabond here on the.
On the Charlie.
Yeah.
I mean, I would like to.
Can is a way you can explain why clapping on the.
How do you even find the one and the three instead of the two and the four?
And what's it? Why do you have to?
It's a feeling.
But why do you have to do it on the two and the four?
Is the one and the three wrong?
So.
No, to pass.
And if it's a march.
Can you give an example?
It's a march.
If it's a march.
You can do it.
Okay.
Which one is?
Ta-da-da-da.
Da-da-da.
Ta-da-da.
You've been now you're doing that every beat.
Yeah.
Well, that's a march.
And actually, there's hardly any song that you have to do it on the one and the three.
But what is that?
Can you just explain it?
Two.
A.
The one.
Two.
Four.
One.
Two.
Then four of all?
I look like an idiot.
Yes.
Benish people can do it.
You know, Chuck attack attack attack attack attack attack attack attack.
But that's a different story.
I don't know.
As long as they have fun, it music is about fun.
And if you do it on the one and the three, it's a...
Just not in our show.
But it's sex with sex.
I have to say people who swing do it better.
And of course, the most important question of the day then.
Am I married to an American yet?
Yeah.
We got the rhythm baby.
We know how to do it.
It's a rhythm.
It is an American thing.
It's a good thing.
Do Americans make better lovers than other...
Well, I haven't had that much experience.
Well.
Because I only had one America.
Thank you.
I was waiting for that.
So the trick question.
And like, let me see what she said.
I had an English man in American and most of them Dutch.
Not that many.
And...
I don't know.
My numbers are low.
It depends on if they are in music business.
It's much better.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, oh.
So everyone wants to know.
You know, like the after party after the show.
You were like hanging out with all the lesbian girls and hugging.
Yeah.
And what was all that about?
This was purely for my benefit.
Because I love them all.
Uh-huh.
I love them all.
Mm-hmm.
You know that I was so hot.
That was so hot.
That was so easy to say.
I love people.
I don't mind.
I'm telling you.
It's a boy girl.
It was so hot.
So hot.
I know.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Comic strip.
You know that I met comic strip blogger last week in London.
We had our first face-to-face meeting.
And he has something to say about the Netherlands as well.
So I just wanted to pop in his comment for today.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm Kerry.
It is me.
The CSB.
You're a servant in areas of mobile phones and European Union.
So it was fun to have a little chat with you in person.
In touch office in London.
And your employee Lydia was one.
Foxy lady.
Did you do her any time?
Oh, man.
I hope Lydia hears this.
That's funny.
All in all.
You are not that tall as I thought you will be.
That indeed you are blonde.
Not so dark blonde as myself.
But contrary to common opinions about blondes.
You are much more competent.
Then I fought initially.
And you are competent in various areas.
I am surprised.
Yes.
So investors and potential ink truly can trust you.
You are one fucking competent entrepreneur.
By the way, I would like to mention that Netherlands has just opened its labor market
since May the first 2007 to work as from East EU.
And now Dutch no longer are races.
Thank you.
Oh, that happened.
How did he look?
You know, I have to say I was expecting.
Was he good looking?
He didn't know.
He was pretty good looking guy.
If he lost 20 pounds.
He showed me a driver's license.
Does the people are a little bit heavy on good looking?
No.
Especially man can be very attractive.
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
The comics are good looking guy.
I'm attracted to him.
I'm not saying that.
No, just checking.
No, I mean, just in general.
Yeah, no.
He was a, you know what?
This is a really smart guy.
He's a little brazen.
Yeah.
He speaks a little breathlessly.
How old is it?
I think I asked him that.
I think he's 37.
Oh, no.
41.
I don't know.
He's very mature.
He's been around for a while.
Yeah.
For sure.
Funny.
So I had a really good time dear.
I did a good time hanging out with you.
Yes.
It was great being your group.
This time it was all about me.
Yeah.
I'm following you and entertaining everybody around you.
Did I provide a appropriate services?
Absolutely did.
And wonderful thing is about you that you are never ever jealous.
Oh, no.
This is very hard.
You can kiss as many lesbians as you want.
I mean, there are also a lot of men.
And you know that we are very touchy.
You know, show business people over.
Touchy touchy and I know a lot of people.
Hold on.
Can I just define it?
What can I touchy?
What?
Since we're very touchy.
What can I touchy?
You can touchy everything.
Yeah.
No.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
You're a bit glowy.
I agree.
You know, and for people.
Well, listen, when you work, when you work, it's a bit like,
but when you're working on a project and you're working in very,
it's almost like flying.
Now, I don't go around hugging guys that I fly with.
But you feel so close.
Yeah, of course you do.
And especially making a good show, working together, trying to,
you know, everybody does his best to make it in just one.
It needs to be how many seconds it was four minutes, four minutes.
Not even, man.
It was like three and a half for something like that.
Yeah.
So it needs to be so tight and so good.
And everybody was working so hard to do this.
Yeah.
I had some very, very talented people around me.
That was, I was very thankful for that.
They were all hanged and picked by me.
Yes.
And selected.
It was hand-selected.
Yeah.
But they all delivered, so.
So the, for me, the exciting news is that your remix is now on the podcast,
I'm using that work.
I heard.
We put that up last night.
Yep.
Thanks to Willie the Kay and Red Bull at production.
Yeah.
They cleared all of that for us.
I saw it was played.
It was already played this morning on some German show.
Oh, really?
Dude.
Are you kidding me?
It's fun.
We had a lot of fun years and years ago in German.
Hope you don't mind it.
I hope you don't mind it.
I don't play it on this show because I've played it like four times of
people going to get sick of me.
It's sick of me.
It's nauseating.
Yeah.
Right.
They can go back.
But you know, just, I want to say that,
don't fuck out of like, they're a very good job.
Now, this is the guy who was your manager for 20 years.
Yeah.
And producer.
And he is, he did a good job making it really, really.
It has a very happy feel.
Very good beat in it.
Yeah.
And Julie, the choreographer.
She really puts some cool stuff together.
Great dancers.
Yeah.
My home is partner.
Ramco.
Your own dance part.
Drive it.
Dancer.
I'm your proud Dancer.
Dancer for money.
While we keep him, we keep him in the show.
He's good.
He's very good.
Yeah.
So, now it was the dance on television.
It was announced in the newspaper.
It was announced on that incredibly popular show.
The daily source code.
Yeah.
That you're going to Afghanistan.
How about that?
What exactly do we even know what's happening here?
Do you have the exact details?
I have to make a phone call when I'm done with the show here.
And see exactly what I can bring.
How many people, you know, what we can do.
Because we have to do three shows.
I told those guys who in the PR.
I said, you better get a C 130.
That's like the huge, that's like the biggest military plane.
Yeah.
The bay of the bus.
You better get a C 130.
Oh, dude.
Well, I have to go.
I have to go.
I have two cameras.
I have one.
I probably.
Two cameras.
Well, I think.
I don't know.
There's more people who want to maybe dunk you.
Documentary of it.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I have my own photographer's coming.
I was going to make a hole.
You know, we could do our own documentary.
And we could produce that.
That too.
Yeah, we could.
But I heard.
If.
He's.
He's like the.
He's like the Dutch.
What can we compare him to, huh?
Uh.
First of all, he's.
He's a.
He's a great performer.
Um.
Uh.
Somewhat can be.
If I can put it lightly.
Yeah.
He's almost like a young Cliff Richard who doesn't take himself as seriously as Cliff Richard.
Let's do old.
No, that's.
A Cliff Richard.
A young Cliff Richard.
Okay, young.
Who.
At least admitted he was gay.
And it will be Williams.
But then a little bit more old fashioned more gay.
More gay.
Much more gay.
Yeah.
Sort of gay.
Oh, isn't that right?
Well.
Why?
Quite.
He is a very good entertainer.
Oh, he's fantastic.
He's number one.
He's the top of the bill.
He's got his TV show.
He's got a huge concert.
It's not.
I think it would be great.
And he's a very nice guy.
So he.
He said I want to come and he has his own camera with him because he's doing a real
I've sort of documentary about himself because he's doing the arena.
Yeah, but I don't like that.
He's giving a whole lot of stuff.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
I don't like that.
Well, there.
I don't know.
I don't want to talk about it now.
I'm telling you right now.
If there's going to be any video documentary shit done.
We're going to do it.
Then he can use our.
No.
He will give him some footage.
But we're going it.
I don't want it.
Because he doesn't make the documentary.
Some fucking production company.
Well, I don't want them all.
Everybody was screaming.
Oh, can we come with the camera?
Can we come with the camera?
So we have to see how we can find the camera approvals through me.
Because I've already set it up with the, you know, with the the Ministry of Defense.
They have satellite.
Connect.
Uplinks.
We have ever since we did the stuff in Iraq now that now they really understand what kind
of internet pipe you really need.
So they have great internet pipe.
So we could do live stuff.
From there.
And by the way, one of the three camps you'd go to would be Condahar.
Which has, it's the international base.
So there's going to be Americans, Brits.
And you'll be performing for them as well.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to bring some nice guys.
I'm going to bring some, you know, because they're girls over there.
I'm going to bring beautiful beautiful dancers.
Yeah.
I know you saw them.
Didn't you?
God damn.
Some of them were really cute.
The blonde one.
Yeah.
She's very pretty.
I think, but I think John already has a group.
She's standing in John's tent.
What are you guys doing?
That's how we talk.
It's the way showbiz people talk, huh?
You always have to think you can get them.
In a snap, in a snap of a finger.
Like that.
Not a problem.
Come here, baby.
I'm not.
I'm curived.
You heard my show.
Don't pay attention to my wife.
No, please.
No.
She says it's okay.
And now we don't understand each other.
That way also.
What do you mean we don't?
We have it on the stand.
We haven't understand anything.
I was looking for that.
We have an open relationship.
It's okay.
Somebody is open.
Oh yeah.
Why open?
Oh, god.
I was a lot of fun.
So I look forward to hearing about Afghanistan.
So you have to come by more often to give us an update and let us know what's happening.
Because I would presume this has to happen.
Well, I'm going to have my first meeting this afternoon and see what they're.
Okay.
What they can handle.
All media, all media through one, please.
I'm serious about it.
Oh, you're good at it.
I know.
I know exactly.
I don't want it to suck.
And if Khouford, your photographer will come along.
I mean, he will make the most beautiful picture.
Just of, I mean, I know exactly what he'll do.
Yeah, that'll be awesome.
That would be exposition type material.
Okay.
And I did also a great photo shoot.
Yes, you did.
One of the best, be most beautiful glossy magazines.
In fact, it's called glossy glossy.
glossy.
We have a couple of very nice magazines.
But this one, I didn't, I haven't worked with.
With.
Yeah, you know, that's because dancing this is a star.
You've been in Holland so long.
Yes, my, my accent.
I've worked with him.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
So.
And, and that went very well.
When does that come out?
That comes out.
June June.
And then I have the second, the 22nd of May.
May.
I have a special on the where I talk about my living with a heart disease.
Living with heart disease.
So that's very interesting.
And so I'm unbelievable.
Everything goes like a little.
And the cool thing is it's just like a jigsaw.
Everything.
The cool thing is it's actually cost us money to do all this.
Yes.
Are you really invested?
Have you really invested in this?
Yes.
Park.
I think there will come some fruits of this tree.
No, it's not, it's not about the money.
No.
No, I mean, fruits.
It's, you know, it's enjoyment.
We're having fun.
That's what it's all about because it's a lot of fun.
And I remember people saying and asking Patricia should do something.
Here you are.
You're doing.
So if this catches on and I know you're not going to do anything small.
So I could imagine the maybe one or a series of really big concerts that you might do a full show.
Um, you realize that if you really want to do that and make it work and make it efficient for our home life and my busy schedule.
Yeah.
That I will have to fly you.
Oh, did you tell them about?
Are you kidding me?
Of course I told them about yesterday.
So we do that maybe after a little bit of a music right now.
Do what?
Tell them about the flight and I took another one.
Well, they already know that.
Oh, you already told them.
Well, of course I did.
I did show yesterday.
Don't you remember why that's right?
Yeah, I need some music now.
What kind of music would you like?
Uh, uh, do you have some swing?
Uh, no.
Unless you can swing to this.
Oh, yeah, of course.
This is like you can't get more American than this.
Woohoo!
Junior, what was I thinking?
It's never something better wrong.
You feel at least so you give up a call.
You never thought that this could happen to you.
Please forgive me for the things I do.
Do it down into the neighbor's yard.
Makes an edge of mama's grinning in the car.
Looking for love and all the wrong places.
Don't know the name, but you know that faces.
What goes up would have come back down.
So you better get out of town.
What was I thinking?
Yeah, when I got some truck I saved my head.
Through a fun life, that's where it's better go.
Get the hammered on my way to school.
Walking in, thinking man, I'm old.
Not teach you get me as because he was a freak.
He said, I think you're a little bird you can't bring me sick.
In the morning, you will realize.
And on the 9th, you won't first cry.
I ain't drinking games naked, twisted.
You knew that she was ugly, but you couldn't resist me.
Now what goes up must come back down.
So you better get out of town.
What was I thinking?
When I got some truck I saved my head.
Through a fun life, that's where it's been.
What was I thinking?
When I got some truck I saved my head.
Through a fun life, that's where it's been.
I was having naked in my hands.
And I woke up.
In the back of my neighbors, being a truck.
Yeah, what was I thinking?
What was I thinking?
When I got some truck I saved my head.
I'm going up with her mother.
What was I thinking?
When I got some truck I saved my head.
Through a fun life, that's where it's been.
What was I thinking?
When I got some truck I saved my head.
Through a fun life, that's where it's been.
That's where it's been.
Pot-save music rocks.
That's where it's going to go.
Shit.
Kylie Blansteef Cox Adam.
Ho-foss.
Three guys who grew up in redneck infested small towns.
With dreams of someday escaping the country back roads,
trailer parks and barn dances to be in a rock and roll band.
That was Junior.
God.
Isn't that awesome?
Oh God.
God.
Oh my God.
When I hear that, my blood starts to boil.
Oh yeah.
What I love to make that music.
So much.
You cannot do everything.
Someone else's blood was boiling while you were gone.
Oh yeah.
Your daughter was very pissed off at me.
Oh.
Yeah.
I don't think you've heard this.
I should play this for you.
Where are you?
I called you 20 minutes ago and you never called me back.
You told me I did it that you were going to pick me up at 11.
And if I know you're going to play, I would have made other plans.
This is like the third time recently that you promised to do something to me.
Dad, I'm completely flaked out on me.
I understand you have to work in your busy, but I'm your daughter.
Will you promise me something?
Something is simple.
I was coming to pick me up when you say you're going to pick me up.
Then you do it.
I'm so not fucking standing here in the middle of the night on the sidewalk.
Like some crazy homeless person.
I'm really getting sick of this shit dad.
You keep making all these promises.
I can't tell you more that you are the weed topic.
You're trying to run a little stone or pot head.
And now I'm going to have to fucking take a taxi all the way home.
And when I get there, you and I get to have a little talk about responsibility.
And when I tell you, better be standing out the day with enough money to pay for this cat.
And you fucking better be wearing men's clothing.
No!
Isn't she a little actress?
She's so good.
And you know, have you seen that footage of David Hasselhoff?
Dude!
I watched that yesterday.
How sad is that?
I was in Holland.
That's his daughter.
She's right.
She's, you know what?
Absolutely right.
Yeah.
We're doing the same thing.
Same thing.
Oh yeah.
This is good.
Did you see how, well, the first of all, the guy is ill.
Alcoholism is a sickness.
It's a sickness dude.
I mean, it's not like he's choosing to do that.
He's sick.
He needs help.
He says dead.
Will you please stop?
Please do it for me.
It's just, it breaks your heart.
Broody breaks your heart.
The guy is sick.
If I hear the other side, because I thought it was,
There's another side.
Well, no, if I hear the other side,
It's like, you know, where you got the,
The, the, the,
Oh, Ale balled when you made that.
Yeah.
Then I'm all before, for him,
Because I know it's happening there.
Yeah.
You know.
And you can feel that the pain that he has is, as a dead,
Yeah.
That he feels a very,
Uh, hurt and, and push the side.
Push the side.
Mm-hmm.
You can hear that.
And so I assure hope that people are not going to be angry with him
Because that's totally different.
But I also think.
A different story.
People shouldn't be angry.
There's a lot of dead, you know, who are in this position.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh, he really loves his daughter.
That's why he's saying this.
Yeah.
That's why he's acting like that.
Absolutely.
So that's the other way around.
But if I see, um, a David, David has a...
Dude, the man is sick.
He needs help.
You know, we shouldn't be angry at him.
That's sad.
How cool isn't, is a sickness.
You can't just say,
I'm not going to drink.
It doesn't work that way.
Well, you had some experience with that with family.
So it's...
Thank you.
That would be my point.
Yeah.
That's painful.
So this, although, hopefully, this will get him into rehab.
Because that's where he needs to be.
He needs...
He needs professional help, dude.
Yeah.
This guy was, I mean, he was combatose.
He couldn't even...
Yeah.
Think straight.
You are still hurt from that.
From your youth.
I'm very bummed about David Hasselhoff.
No, no, no.
From this heart position.
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
You know, it's...
But it's an illness.
And it needs to be addressed.
And he should be so ashamed.
And I bet you no one's doing anything.
Because that's how it always goes.
Well, I'm going to laugh at the guy.
But we're not going to actually...
Well, please don't laugh about these things.
Because...
Well, I was pretty funny.
Yeah.
It was shocking.
No, I...
For me, he was shocking.
Yeah, it was pretty shocking.
It's disgusting.
I was so disgusted by it.
Yeah.
Unbelievable.
But our daughter is...
Is an actress.
No, that was good.
She did...
She did that just like that?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my god.
I gave her the script that Mark wrote for her.
Yeah.
She did it in like three seconds with her.
Hang it out of the window with herself.
Aw.
Yeah, it's great.
No, we love you.
You're good, Daddy.
That's speaking to which.
Now you want to talk about how cool I am.
It's my turn now.
Yeah, it's now.
It's my turn to hear how great I am.
Talk about me.
Yeah, do you mind just talking about me for a moment?
No.
So I was flying KLA yesterday.
Yes, you were.
And you were happy I did it.
I'm very happy.
Did I?
Did I had a good feeling?
You had the right feeling, dude.
I mean, you would have been okay because I was not freaked out.
I was not...
No, it was not flying with you.
It was flying in certain conditions.
Now conditions and circumstances.
Because, you know, you never know what the heart is doing.
If you get sort of a little bit of panic, you don't know that.
No, that's my point.
So with what happened once I hit like, you know,
once I flew over the coast, what happened there was not fun.
And only because I've been in it before,
that I realized that we were bouncing.
It was, it was not everything.
I had the bouncing ball.
I had to slow down to like 100 knots just because I would have flipped over.
I mean, it was just amazing.
The wind that was hitting me.
Can you imagine me sitting there next to you?
I was so happy.
I was like, oh man.
You're copilot?
Me?
You would have been like...
I mean, I know you can hear it.
But who knows?
I mean, you know, you...
I'm not...
I'm never getting nauseous.
You know, I'm good at that.
Dude.
And while I was listening on the radio,
because I was monitoring our frequencies.
Oh, yeah.
It was like, you know, go off, go off, pop in, you're trying to go.
Returning back to the field.
Due to an ill passenger.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I can just imagine that cockpit.
Like, oh, no!
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Oh, big jets.
You know, not being able...
Not being able to land, doing go runs and stuff.
And at that point, I was like, oh crap.
No crap.
I said, oh, please don't let it be like that at Fair Oaks,
which of course it was.
So big jets dripping from throw up.
No, I didn't see that.
Okay.
You know, I should put some bags in the plane,
just in case we have someone on board.
Yeah.
I was thinking, what happens if I have a sudden got nauseous while I'm alone
and flying?
There you go.
What do you do?
Because I do know a little bit about helicopter.
You could always say, take it off.
Just keep it steady.
Yeah.
You know, but...
You couldn't have kept anything steady in this weather.
No.
Nothing at all.
I know.
But, you know, you never go up with the helicopter in that weather.
Anyway.
Well, what do you...
What do you...
We've done there.
We've done 40, 40 not wins.
We've done it before.
You've been in there.
But I do know the helicopter.
I know how it works.
But I don't know anything about this.
Nothing.
I couldn't help you.
So, I mean, you wouldn't have to do anything.
I'd just throw up and continue.
Yeah.
Well, we have to buy a autopilot for you.
autopilot.
Sorry.
Another pilot.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, I have an autopilot.
I mean, like a serious one.
Now, when you want to...
You want me to...
Yeah.
All the money you make, you're going to put into the plane.
Oh, no.
You're going to buy an autopilot.
Okay.
I'll save up.
And a Gucci bag.
And a Gucci bag to throw up in.
Now, at www.watsup.potcho.com.
Join Mike Dell and Jim Farley for a podcast.
That will make you say, dude, what's up with that?
Jim and Mike talk about the new stories that you probably didn't hear about on your radio dial.
You know the ones.
The ones that make you say...
What's up with that?
All in back on the time honored descent.
Namely, his claim that he believed he was a female elf at the time.
Uh, well, fast and proud.
What's up with that?
Hey.
Police were looking for a person after we were able to flush the suspect out from the portable toilet
where he was hiding.
A porta-potty is not a good place to hide, but there's only one way out.
Well, technically, there's two.
Dude, what's up with that?
We also play a wide-bradding musical
the pot-safe music network.
So stop on over and give us a listen.
What's up with that?
Yeah.
All right.
I got to go to the city, baby.
I got to hurry up.
I know.
You know, I could talk.
In fact, we have been talking for the past three days.
Non-stop.
And we're still talking.
Yeah.
Didn't we have a good time?
We had a great time.
Yeah.
Yesterday, I said...
It was enjoying life so much.
We had a great time.
I accomplished something major for myself.
You know, it was wonderful.
The moment that we were all by ourselves.
And it was raining outside.
Exactly what I told them.
Yeah.
That was beautiful.
It was raining against the...
Well, the awning.
Yeah.
And all you could hear was the ducks.
And the two of us, making love.
Oh, baby.
I can't stand up now.
I can't go anywhere.
All right.
So will you keep us on the high?
Yeah.
We all...
Let us know what's going on.
Because we want to know what's happening with Afghanistan, baby.
You know, we also have to...
Don't forget, it can't be in August.
Because we have to go to the big curry reunion.
And upstate New York.
Me grow.
Yeah.
So it can't be in August.
But what if they say then, you know, that's when it needs to...
Sorry.
You're Patricia Pai, dude.
Change the course of the war.
Okay.
It's...
It's June, July.
Okay.
Is it hot?
You do.
Dude.
I think you may not want to go in August anyway.
It could easily be...
And July, hot.
Oh, man.
It's so freaking hot.
We went in February.
In Iraq, and it was a...
30 degrees.
Yeah.
In the...
Well, you get sandstorms.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Sandstorms.
Oh, no.
If you think this is...
I'm allergic for dust.
If you think it's a fun party, you're in...
No, no.
I don't think that at all.
No, but I'm saying is...
It definitely...
Because I said to the guys, I said, look, getting to...
Camp Smitty in Iraq was kind of a journey.
You know, so we...
Could we had to fly to Kuwait City first and from Kuwait City.
We drove 400 kilometers through the...
Through the desert essentially to get to the camp.
And I said, is it kind of like that kind of journey.
He said, no, about three times as bad.
Oh.
Two military planes and the helicopter just to get to the first base.
Wow.
I'm a beaker.
With you getting to first base is much easier.
Oh, oh.
All right.
Yeah, we are.
And I'll be here for a couple more days.
Yeah, that's good.
Please enjoy me.
Yes, I am.
Please enjoy your time with...
Yeah.
With the Sultan.
The Sultan of Swing.
Sultan of Savarn Spady.
Okay.
DailySourceco.com.
Adam and podshow.com.
I'm off to London and...
I'll talk to you.
Keep it posted.
Keep me posted.
Okay, baby.
I will.
I love you too.
Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest.
Daily by the sharpest minds in content
delivering podshow and limelight.