After a nice relaxing weekend, you need the DSC 698 to make you start thinking again.
Here's Adam with today's topics.
All in a brighter note commercial break.
The government has now banned the carrying of spheres.
Stop about every thousand miles and ask too much is it?
You might wish to stay on and listen.
It was a place where everything was legal.
I meant this woman.
So if you're looking for emotional satisfaction,
my advice to you is seek professional help.
For $16 billion worth of airplane strapped by us.
In the next generation where you can't anymore.
Your name is Steve.
I like to think of science.
If you're not going to do it,
I'll be asking if you can do it.
I don't agree.
Television.
The drug of a nation.
Rating ignorance.
A feeding radiation on television.
The drug of a nation.
Reading ignorance.
A feeding radiation TV.
It's satellite links by United States of Unconsciousness.
A prosthetic therapeutic and extremely addictive.
The methadone metronome.
Pumping out 150 channels 24 hours a day.
You can flip through all of them.
And still there's nothing worth watching.
TV.
It's a reason why less than 10% of our nation reads books daily.
By most people think central America means Kansas.
Socialism means on American.
And apartheid is a new headache remedy.
Absorbed in this world is so hard to find us.
It shapes our minds the most.
Maybe the mother of our nation should remind us.
That was sitting too close to the television.
The drug of a nation.
Reading ignorance.
A feeding radiation on television.
The drug of a nation.
Reading ignorance.
A feeding radiation TV.
It's a stomping round of political candidates.
We're bears in the woods.
I chased by Christian form of the particles.
TV.
It's mechanized politics remote control over the masses.
Co-sponsored by environment-only safe gases.
Watch for the PBS special.
It's a perpetuation of the two-party system.
Where image takes precedence over wisdom.
Where sound by politics.
I serve to the fast food culture.
Where state keeps in your mouth a more important.
There's no words to come out of it.
Race-baming is the way to get selected.
Really hard and no willy not get elected on television.
The drug of a nation.
Reading ignorance.
A feeding radiation on television.
The drug of a nation.
Reading ignorance.
A feeding radiation.
On the street isn't a threat.
We can be a new tag off in your world.
It's a bluff.
Okay.
Got the idea.
All right.
Let's go.
TV.
This is a reflector for the director.
Does it imitate us?
Do we imitate it?
Because a child watches 1,500 murders before he's 12 years old.
And then we wonder why we created adjacent generation.
That learned to laugh.
Rather than a boy than a boy.
TV.
The players were armed, chair, generals, and quarterbacks.
An experience firsthand.
The excitement of video warfare.
That's a theme song.
It's sung in the background.
Sugar sweet sitcoms.
I leave us with a bad act to taste.
While pop stars.
And met a more precise and consoled pop stars.
You saw the video.
You heard the soundtrack.
Well now go by the soft drink.
Well the only color that I support.
But yeah.
You and T.O.L.A.
Costs of living a lion.
It's all television.
The drug of imagination.
Breathing ignorance.
The feeding radiation.
All television.
The drug of imagination.
Breathing ignorance.
The feeding radiation.
Back again.
You and him.
Turn to our irregularly program schedule.
Hidden cleverly between heavy-breasted beer and car commercials.
CNN, ESPN, ABC, BC, B, C, B, P, N, T.
But mostly BS.
We're oxymoronic language.
Like virtually spotless.
Fresh frozen.
Like yet filling.
And military intelligence.
I become standard.
TV is a place where phrases are redefined.
Like recessions and necessary downturn.
Crewed oil on a beach to moose.
civilian death to collateral damages.
And being killed by your own army.
It's not a cause.
Friendly fire.
TV is a place.
Well the pursuit of happiness has become the pursuit of trivia.
Where two-paced and cars have become sex objects.
Where imagination is sucked out of children.
Fire cap, old rainfall.
TV is the only wet nurse that would create a cripple.
Television.
The drug of imagination.
Breathing ignorance.
feeding radiation.
Television.
The drug of imagination.
Breathing ignorance.
The feeding radiation.
Television.
The drug of imagination.
Breathing ignorance.
Breathing radiation on television.
The drug of imagination.
Breathing ignorance.
Breathing radiation.
What do you say Charlie has?
You got your ears on listening to the lyrics.
Television.
The drug of imagination.
Impossible heroes of hip hoppercy.
On the chak chak.
Okay, got the idea, the people in America can do it.
Go ahead or let it be, you're telling me.
The people in America can do it.
Okay, got the idea, all right now that's kind of it.
How about that for some red pill?
Hey, buddy, how you doing?
We source code number 690.
What are we?
690 eight coming to you from the curry manner on the west side of G-town in the affluent suburb of
Surrey known as Guilford.
It hasn't been very nice this weekend.
I got home Saturday morning for my San Francisco John's two weeks on the oil rig.
And I came home to high winds and at a high home.
It was wet, it's just been totally crappy.
It's okay because tomorrow I'm leaving on a jet plane once again off to New York,
which I here is even crappier.
It's a really, really cold and chances of more snowstorm.
So it should be interesting.
Yeah, it seems like the past week talking about consumerism,
talking about perceived obsolescence and planned obsolescence.
And lots of stuff is thrown some red pill juice out into the ether.
I should say, and we'll get to that in just a sec.
I have to say, I wasn't really getting into the new sign-off thing.
I was kind of like it and say, and fuck you, Adam Curry.
But after hearing the Hanukkah song on today's day, the source code,
I have to say, man, I love you, Adam Curry.
That's a awesome song.
Anyway, keep up good work.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm amazed you hadn't heard that.
That's, of course, it was the new version part two of the Hanukkah song.
Adam Sandler played that on Thursday.
So we're going to do some of the food bar bits today on today's Monday show,
which, of course, is emanating from the attic.
It's so nice to be back with my, with my setup.
You know, where I got all the sound that I want, and I could...
I can boost up my headphones as loud as I want.
And oh, yeah, it's just...
I wish I could travel with this whole kit with me.
I'm looking into some more gear.
I think this persona's stuff.
I need, like, a Mike preamp and more compression.
The can never be too much compression.
Anyway, so we can't put some interesting things last week talking about the wrong brand.
If you look at today's album, aren't you seeing nice stab at that already?
And the wrong brand would be a consumer attempt, a rebellious attempt,
at slowing down consumerism out of protest.
Of course, we need a message to go along with this, which is basically, hey, hey, stop trying to control us,
because look, you can't...
Which means that you got to turn off your television.
I mean, you cannot be programmed by the man to go and shop as much as you wanted to.
But, of course, you know, I'm just like getting into this myself.
So it's not like there's no call to action yet, no call to arms as of just yet.
I don't think we'll be on time for the Christmas season,
but maybe we should even wait until after the holidays,
just to see what we did collectively as consumers.
I think we'll probably get close to, I don't know,
a billion dollars in shopping at least, maybe even more.
Oh, there's been so much to think about.
Hey, Adam, it's Kevin Crossman, the Pratt Scruncher from PrattPackPotCast.com.
You know, my head really, really hurts from the mindset you gave on the last DSE.
It's totally fucking shit.
Easy there.
All that consumer stuff.
I mean, speak about consumerism here in the holidays.
Jesus, age, Christ.
I have got a new perspective.
And I appreciate the, you know, the fact that the DSE is not just a little,
you know, promotional vehicle for Pratt Show.
Well, I hope it's that as well, obviously.
And, you know, some of your favorite mashups.
All right, that's stuff too.
And, and a way to solicit naked pictures.
Yeah, okay, it's that too.
Yeah, I do like the social agenda that has been put out.
With regards to Zack's invitation, you heard a little conversation with a man and a woman in there.
Yeah.
That was a cut-up clip from the movie Knocked Up.
Oh, it's just courses of the favorite of ours.
Okay.
Anyway, like once again, I guess thanks for the mind fuck.
And thank you very much, Adam Curry.
Sure.
Not a problem.
And a lot of people send similar messages in saying,
Wow, I never really thought about it that way.
I never thought that we have so much power as consumers
that we should actually learn to wield that power.
If we can just break free of the hypnotic forces at work,
which may finally come from television.
Because make no mistake.
When you're sitting there, you think you're relaxing in front of the tube.
No way, man.
It's like a filling station.
It's like a gas pump for consumers
and to be to flow into your brains.
And they do it in really nasty ways.
Like you ain't going to get laid if you don't buy this product.
Or you might die if you don't buy this product.
It's basically those two.
But it's all based on fear.
And people are waking up to it.
Hey, Adam.
This is old in from California.
Hey, man.
Just look at it into DSD-697.
And I got to tell you that you're wrong,
brand.
It's a little late.
My wife cornered the market on years ago.
Every time I put on a shirt, that's the wrong thing.
Every time I wear a pair of pants, it's the wrong thing.
So, you know, she hasn't trademarked it yet,
but she'd be really disappointed if you grabbed the brand.
Just kidding.
Look at Adam.
Oh, man.
No, I think my wife has part of her corner of the market
nail there as well on the,
no, that's the wrong thing, honey.
And this is catching on.
People really do get it.
And it's fighting fire with fire, you know?
It's like, let's slow down consumerists
by introducing a new product.
It's the product that will only change.
We could make a change once a year,
once a year instead of four times a year
for all four fashion seasons.
By the way, I'm not just picking on the fashion industry.
This is across the board.
This obviously has to do with consumer electronics,
with automobiles, with homes, with you name it,
with vacations.
I mean, all of this stuff is a part of the drive
to make the American consumer consume.
And I did receive also a lot of emails from people saying
that this was that after 9, 11, George Bush said,
please go shopping.
And I've been trying to corroborate that fact.
And although he does say something about,
and all the speeches I could find,
he talks about keeping the great American economy rolling.
It's not quite the same as go shopping.
So unless I'm mistaken, I don't think he actually said that.
But he did say that just recently in,
I think it was a rose garden press conference.
In fact, you want me to look that up for a second
because I should have prepared for that hold on.
Let's do a Google search.
Bush, go shopping.
Let's just see.
Let's see if we can get some actual video of that.
I love Google.
So efficient.
Here we go.
Dig video.
Okay.
With recession looming, Bush tells America to go shopping.
So this is the second link on Google.
And it's from a, from dig.com.
So it's only 17 digs and still number two on Google.
That's interesting.
Here we go.
Once listen what the press had to say.
Now this was,
um,
doesn't say.
Oh yeah.
Actually, I've seen this at the page that,
so there was an article in the Harold Tribune
on, um,
January 14, 2003 Bush did nothing to mobilize public opinion
to accept the sacrifices that war implies.
The first thing a leader would do.
Tax cuts could go ahead as planned.
Energy saving was dismissed out of hand.
Go shopping was the administration's message.
But see,
I don't actually think he said that.
Here's what he said in 2003.
As we work with Congress in the coming year to chart a new course
in Iraq and strengthen a military to meet the challenges of the 21st century.
Hmm.
We must also work together to achieve important goals for the American people here at home.
This work begins with keeping our economy growing.
And I encourage you all to go shopping more.
Yeah.
But that's,
that's the new one.
I don't think he said that in 2003.
Let's listen to see.
And work with Congress in the coming year.
Yeah.
See, that's, uh, this is from, uh,
just this path month I believe.
Challenges is the 21st century.
We must also work together to achieve important goals.
And listen to how he says it too.
Smug little twat.
This work begins with keeping our economy growing.
And I encourage you all to go shopping more.
All right.
So the message really is true, though.
We have to keep the economy growing.
So that's just the proof that we actually do have this power.
And if we slow everything down,
well, actually, I'd like to hear some economists weigh in on this.
If we stop shopping, if we keep the money in our pockets,
what happens to the value of the dollar?
Do we, uh,
hmm, it's got to hurt somebody.
That's for sure.
But will it hurt us?
I think not.
I think it'll just save us money.
And, uh, we can start making demands.
Think about it.
No, no.
I don't think we're going to shop.
I think we'll just keep our money in our pockets.
Thank you very much.
Oh, unless, uh, let's say you bring all of our troops home from Iraq right now.
Yeah.
You know what?
Okay, don't.
Don't go ahead.
Fine.
We won't watch television.
We won't shop.
We have plenty of other ways to entertain ourselves.
We've got webcams.
We've got astroglyde.
Oh, yeah.
Adam Jason from San Diego.
Two things.
Well, you know, I always start off with that.
Scatch that.
You know, uh, you're cracking me up with your speech on, uh,
perceived, uh, obsolescence or whatever it is about.
Don't get caught into buying the latest from the greatest.
Uh, Mr. How many MacBooks have you gone through?
And are all of them still working?
Did all of them need to be replaced?
Mr. Brand new iPhone?
Mr. Brandnew?
N-810?
This brand with that?
New car?
How many new cars have you gotten?
Uh, new plane?
And, uh, wanting to buy another new plane?
Please.
A little plane?
Maybe you're not getting this from TV.
And TV isn't telling you to go buy a new plane or new.
I don't know what else I'm not telling you, but whatever it is.
Point one finger at others.
Four point right back at you.
Ah.
It's really tires me.
I've got a lot of these messages too.
I'm not saying that, first, I'm not telling you to do anything.
I'm not saying that I'm not just his guilty,
or that I'm not a, I'm a great consumer.
I really help the economy. Are you kidding me?
Absolutely.
But we're just having a discussion here.
Okay. This is so typical of the internet.
Like me?
He said this.
Yeah.
So off to unproductive.
It's like all these flames that go back and forth and forearms.
Why?
It's painful, painful.
We're having a little discussion here.
Don't judge anyone yet.
I'm not judging you.
I'm just talking.
It's a discussion.
I make me crazy with that shit.
Listen to what I'm saying.
Okay.
I'm not telling you.
I'm not holding you then, though.
And of course, I'll participate.
I'm happy to participate.
My two girls aren't quite that happy.
Come home after two weeks in San Francisco.
And I'm talking about no more shopping.
I'm talking about clothes with the wrong brand.
And they're looking at me like, who the fuck is this guy?
What'd you do with our husband slash dad?
Could you please bring him back?
Yeah.
I was just listening to what was at 697.
And I love that thing you're playing from that website story.
That was really cool.
I was totally digging that.
Really, that's pretty much all my brain has been thinking about lately.
Glad you played that.
It really gets all of our mind going.
Red pills.
But you should check out the movie What would Jesus buy?
I don't think you mentioned it on the show yet.
But it's produced by the same guy that did it.
Super size me.
I haven't had a chance to check an out either yet.
I got to find where it's shown in my area.
But yeah, so check that out.
Check out the trailer.
It looks like it's pretty promising.
I love you.
I don't care.
Thank you.
Well, I did a little bit of homework for today's program.
And I found the trailer at apple.com.
It has a lot of.
A lot of words on the screen, which are factoids about how much money is being spent on shopping, etc.
So in order to fully enjoy this multimedia experience,
I shall read what is written on the screen while you listen to the audio of the trailer.
What would Jesus buy?
Which is a movie I've not seen yet.
But boy, do I want to?
Here we go.
From producer Morgan Spurlock.
There I'm so sorry to hear I have sinned.
Lots of Christmas pictures here.
Cash register, ringing up big bucks.
Last year, American spent 455 billion during the holidays.
With some brand new rims, you know, I just want to cruise around,
flossing my rims.
Consumer credit debt is now 2.4 trillion.
Yes.
We'll have about happen.
Because you and mommy they were doing.
This is a kid's room.
This has nothing in it.
Filled with boxes.
26 American million Americans are addicted to shopping.
Women who is about 60 years old,
cuss me out and spit on me for not having a PS3 for her.
Six year old grandson.
Who will save Christmas?
Reverend Billy Smith.
Reverend Billy, you call it the chocolate.
It's a chocolate shop.
Chocolate.
Chocolate shopping.
Drive the demons out of those cash register.
The church has stopped shopping around a cross country mission to save us
from our shopping since this holiday season.
Come on for the power to stop shopping.
Hey, baby.
Hey, who's brought out for drinking over our lives?
Ah, they're in the mall.
Time to exercise.
Let's go to that Walmart sign now.
Let's take a view, Billy, into our bodies.
Hey, lady.
It's taking the through an exercise amount of Walmart sign.
Main street here, USA.
It's made in China.
What?
You got that on them with different things.
What would Jesus buy?
This Christmas.
Well, that's something we all got to go and see.
That looks awesome.
Of course, it won't actually launch until after the 25th.
I'm sure.
I'm sure no studio as a part of the big machine would actually allow that movie to be
out in theaters while shopping was still taking place.
I'm proudly casting with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam.
Who are you?
Ready to be stumped?
Good.
He used them.
Left over from the toolbar with young pullback.
Hey, Adam.
This is hit this number 99.
And we're going to start right away with intro.
Okay.
Number one.
Around 93.
Okay.
They're in print R&B.
Shind your name, sign your name?
Yeah, sign your name.
They're in print R&B.
Number two.
Who?
Turn up there.
All the guys.
Next.
Design a…
I don't know the… I don't know the band.
That's an oldy.
And the final one is number three.
It's so good.
Uh, he's bad, your bad girls don't have summer.
I think I have at least two and a half stars out of three today.
And time's up.
And these are the answers to hit this number in 99.
Answer number one is from 1988.
This is Stairstone Darby and sign your name.
This is Anton number two from 81.
Future Will Augustus.
Future Will.
자...
And this is answer number three and he takes number nine be nine from 79 Donna summer
So at him how did you do hold you two and a half out of three right the ball bar always the answers to this
hit us and also the links to iTunes you can buy these trucks online can be found at hittest.potshow.com
Next week I won't be here oh if I'll go for it I'll be sitting on my ass or hiking through the mountains of one of the
Canary Islands. I'm going to La Palma for one week. Nice. So the next hittest number 100 has been three recorded
And I'm gonna stop with that right after I finish this one. Thanks for the info. All righty Adam. Thank you for listening in there for playing
Yeah, everyone else. Thanks for listening
Have a great week and be sure to join me next week for
It has number 101
I can't help but I just got a laugh every single time I hear all the the imaging and staging and the voiceovers and the in your face attitude of young pull out in the hittest
number 98
Vacationing in the Canary Islands. I've got to check and make sure to see we're we're not paying young too much
All right man. I'm looking forward to it. I can't wait to hear what you got lined up for us on the hittest number 100
Most awesome. Hey, you're something couple of people emailed me story came out. I guess last night or today
This is a prolific program or sent me this link
Major crude producer Iran has completely stopped carrying out its oil transactions in dollars oil minister
Golem Hussein Nossari sit on Saturday labeling the greenback as an unreliable currency
At the moment selling oil in dollars has been completely halted in line with the policy of selling crude in non-dollar currencies
Nossari was quoted as saying by the ISNA news agency
I don't know what ISNA is is that a rocky news agency
That's a doubt Jones a news wire report. So I would say they probably check that out
He added the dollar is an unreliable currency considering it's devaluation in the oil exporters losses. Okay, so this is
I'd say concerning and
Do you think it has anything to do with the fact that they were no weapons of mass destruction production facilities found and
Instead of saying hey cool guys. Thanks for complying
We said oh, you know what you're still dangerous. Do you think I'd had anything to do with it? What's so ever do you think maybe?
All right, you know that that could be a big problem, but there's other smaller problems in the world which to some
See just as big if not larger. Hi, this is Ron from the zip 71101 podcast
Imagine returning home after an evening out with your family only to find that your home had burned to the ground
Nothing left but memories
This happened recently to fellow podcaster Carmen Tyler sister Diane and her two daughters
Now I've never been in that situation and I can't even begin to imagine how they must have felt
Especially during this holiday season
Will you join me and my fellow podcasters restore some Christmas joy to this family you can do so
Simply going to www.carmentyler.com slash housefire.html
Click on the donate button and send your financial gift through PayPal
Your gift will be greatly appreciated and remember that's what Christmas is all about
Giving thank you and Merry Christmas
Yeah, that really took you know took a little bit of the wind out of me when I when I heard that this morning and
Preparing for the show that really sucks. I remember his little boy when we lived in Maryland
I was five or six years old a house around the corner burned down. I remember
You'd see a whole bunch of people stand and like really really burned down
You know where you could just see you know pieces of the structure still standing and just a huge smoloring mass of
Stuff and I remember how sad that felt
You know it's like wow man you know and was hurt
But all your stuff has gone and just everything your life is contained in this box and it's gone and that is
Really really messed up particularly this time of year when it's supposed to be a
a time of joy and family and
So yeah, please do I'll put a link in the show notes so you can help out to
Carment Tyler sister's family
I'm very sorry to hear that
Where you were talking about how you wanted to find a book on
On Dwight Eisenhower and life and all that well I just have to be in my local borders bookstores today and on the new nonfiction shelf
Is they book called Ike and American Hero by
Michael Corda K-O-R-D-A and it's a book on the life of Dwight Eisenhower
So I'm sure it's on Amazon. It's want to look it up. So I just wanted to give you a heads up on that and
I love you Adam and don't forget about I love you Adam Curry dot top later
Yeah
Before I forget
Yeah, it should be this week that the codes are coming in for the N-810
A lot of people
Waiting to buy it pent up demand and
It's funny because I wonder if this next story has anything to do with the delay in in these codes getting in and yes
It is you know for many countries worldwide
Including the United Kingdom
This came in three days ago 15,000 people at Nokia in Finland helps in Helsinki
became ill after drinking polluted water
The problem is I'm actually translating from a Dutch article into English on the fly here
but somehow the
the sewage
plant
somehow connected to the
to the waterworks facility
So basically shit was in the water
and they didn't discover it until after two days that you know that the basically they were
We're slushing all of this crud into the drinking water
And so a lot of people got really sick
And in fact Nokia has not had tap water for a week
and again this was three days ago and the army actually
has been called into to bring drinking water and I'm I'm wondering if if Candyman Luke is okay
or he certainly can tell us the ins and outs of the story and maybe he emailed me about it
And I didn't see it or didn't understand it and you know just thinking back I'm thinking did he was he like making
you know side mentions to being not feeling well or being sick and and now I'm kind of concerned
All of our friends and health sink you become definitely ill from poop in the water
Please Candyman let us know that you're okay and that all of our friends are on track there because you know
We need the codes
I'm curry Nick Jackson from the Bay Area here. I know I have called you
probably four times
This one you're really gonna like so I was clippin through
Through all the recorded shows I have on my TV and then then I saw my mom had an episode of do you record it and guess who is on it?
Dr. Ron Paul on the view
Okay, very very excited to see that. I think I think that really that's really saying something
That he's on you know
You of course you get him for five minutes on fox news every once in a while and then since he gets off
and all the all those morons start bashing and stuff and
Because it really sucks box news that they're all morons and we'll give him a fair time
Well, they'll give anyone air to
Saying something that that he's on this this big show that everybody watches the view
Everybody but a lot of people
Yeah
Oh, I don't know that's that's definitely good
That's definitely good and I know that lots of people are working these shows too. There's something called Ron Paul swarm
And it's a it's a site that you subscribe to and it gives you
Media outlets to contact when Ron Paul is gonna be in the area to try and get him on the show now this stuff is really working
It's not the mistake. It's I think it's by design and he's got traction for sure
I wish I had seen him on the view. I'm sure there's a YouTube link somewhere
You continue and I'll look for the link unfortunately though because you know the the panel's host
They're all they talk so much so so much so you couldn't really you could hardly get a word
And it wasn't like the way that see that that really showed me the the power of the interview
You with him where it was just here the questions give me the answers and that was it, but you know
They have to be occur in our units
But so he didn't get stress himself as well as he could have if they'd given him a chance to speak
But I think you know, he kept just bringing up the constitution constitution constitution
That's all the news friends with countries
Let's not be not the enemies. It was not the allies just let's just be friends with them
And so I hopefully hopefully some people
You're on a big hurrying up to actually here and if you can and I'll find them on YouTube or something
It was it was an interesting interview to see
One of the discussion a row of the way to um as you can
But yeah
non-Paul
Awesome. Yep. Don't forget December 16th is
The Boston Tea Party Tea Party 07 want to drop in on the money bar on Ron Paul
Tea party 07 dot com or
Ron Paul 2008 dot com donate your money to the campaign on that day. I think I found the yeah the piece from the view
Let's just take a look see if this is it and I put a link to it in the show now
It's a daily source code dot com
On the view on Thursday and joy you have something to say
Good night. I wasn't on the show. Let me move ahead. Oh, there he is. I did. We have a show. Oh
Okay
Well, I'm already three minutes into it and there's still them talking
Okay, I'll put a link to that in the show notes no time forced to go through it now
I'm using amazing characters. I just want to thank you for talking about them and that's about it
Love you Adam. No, I'm off
No, I'm on my friend
You know
This uh the idea of stop shopping that's something Ron Paul could actually use I think I I don't know if it would
If it would make any sense for the primaries, but wow if I
Excuse me
Let me have a sip of tea here
Still the PG tips haven't picked up the Yorkshire at the office
May love bringing home with me tonight. We have our London office Christmas party this evening till that should be fun
Yeah, I wasn't gonna say I don't know what the hell I was I was gonna say you know if only I'd known about the sooner
I could have started before Christmas or just not gonna make it the 455 billion dollars
Americans will spend on during Christmas. Is that really true is that really the number?
We're not rages amount. I'm sure we could do with a hundred billion less
much of thank
200 billion less we all could cut down just a little bit
But you know I've romp all uh it's on the Republican ticket if he wins the primaries and and he's the guy boy
He could he could use this as a part of the platform. Hey, let's just stop everything show Congress
Show Congress we need business. Let's just stop shopping screw you you know watch all the
All the lobbyists lining up trying to fix that that that would be a problem that that would slaughter wall street
Oh, man, it would be so much fun
Boy, I'm just a call from Salt Lake City. I was just listening to DSC
696 and boy the caller that called into uh I guess
convince you of the fallie of supporting on Paul is just
I don't even know what word to use for that guy socialist communist. I guess
blaming liberal maybe
To suggest that Ron Paul's ideas or platform which as you stay correctly is the Constitution of the United States
Which is the only platform Amy president so candidate should be running on considering that's the only oath they take when they get sworn into office right on
to suggest that that is somehow
Not the solution of the entire world as if it's the job of the president of the United States and I have to point out here that
I'm noticing more and more that people actually
Do kind of like the idea of a one-world government you know United nations
NATO
World trade organization, you know
I don't know if you'd lump that one in but you went for sure
You know
But that's just that's just places where people get together negotiate shit
Excuse me
That does remind me that if you want a fantastic deal on a domain name go to
DailySourceco.com is a link there to my go daddy codes page and
I want you to use a DSC one two or three the
Offers are right there so you can see which one is gonna work best for you
But if you just want a domain name for six ninety five it's DSC three is the code you use upon checkout
And I've been buying a couple of domains lately and I'm using my own code of course, and it's great. I love getting that discount myself
Let's see. Oh, let's get back to
So yeah, you know, I think that there's a two-step process there
You know in order to understand what Ron Paul is saying and and to become passionate
About what someone call
Isolationism, you know, you've got to understand the Constitution you've just a small document
You can go read it online. It's it's available almost everywhere in stores and theaters near you
And
When they make that a great movie about the Constitution how it came about
Yeah, that's another period piece I'd like to produce
Um
Yeah, so I think you need to evaluate it. That's what you really want people don't get kind of getting
Blue pill mode, you know, it's like, yeah, just take care of me. Well, yeah, everywhere
Government you all take care of it. Get along together and just make sure that I got a job and I can take a vacation and just have kind of an okay life
Just in a nice warm bed of productivity for the man
The problem solver for the entire world is absolutely ridiculous
I don't know, I guess this guy
He really should just move. He really should be living and maybe, you know, communist China
Yeah, okay, all right
Everyone has a different opinion dude, and that's okay. Don't go tell them people that go to go move to China
China might be great. I don't know. I don't know if China's horrible
Yeah, some parts of it probably are
But then again, some parts of the United States are horrible, so some parts of the United Kingdom are horrible
You know
All right, and I got to get out of here. Let's do this. Hi, Adam. It's Hermann. You know, she doesn't number one out
And I've got good news for all your listeners. We're busy making some very special toys
Rob good girls and boys around the world
Anything you got to bet this year? Charlie, I'm in the background. It helps us work a little harder
Well, such is the life of an elf? Well, I'm very good. Is the Senate on December 16th
It's gonna be live over the five lines that come
We're also excited. We've got all our computers ready to listen and maybe
Just maybe we'll be able to download onto a new iPod that's if we can make one
We don't want to be sued by Apple so
It may that happen
Well, I hope you and all your listeners can have a Merry Christmas and don't forget to go over at the
Super 16th to the five lines at eight thirty
Eastern time
They're here a special message from Santa Claus
It's a matter of fact, I think I hear Santa coming right now
Then he's been treating you a little bit
So he makes a little bit stomp
But I'm sure
Okay
It's Santa here
A very Merry Christmas and the happiest New Year
Bye for me
Whatever a gift is I hope someday
You're the greatest
All right, let's revert next time on the promo, okay
Nation's the podcast
I'm just been thinking about all of this fuck you I love you all of this confusion at the end of the comments
I think people were kind of digging the fuck you but the negativity it's it's kind of a little much I understand
Now though the I love you it's not catching on and it's not catching on everyone saying it is catching on
You know how it goes
But anyway, I think that I found a way for people to still say the fuck you and for you to even like it better
Okay, y'all m into that. Yeah, I'm ready. Yeah, I'm ready. Okay
How about I'd like to fuck you Adam Curry?
That caught me off guard. Yeah, I got to thought you might like that. Anyway just a thought
Doesn't catch on. I love you Adam Curry. All right. Send me negative pictures please
Adam ship from top of the pot says I've been listening to the last few shows of
Watch loose changes. I'd guys in the story of stuff and for some reason
It's a awakening appears to be new but I bet you were warm before
I know you remember those Frank Zapper for President bumper stickers that were around when we were back in our early 20s
You know like four or five years ago
Everyone thought this was a joke
But I think he was before his time and a viable option to run our country
I know it's not pot safe, but just listen to I and the slime and you know yet all this planned and perceived
Obsolessence bump bigger that a long time ago
PS what is it now? I love the fuck you Adam Curry yo
I'm close and I'm ready
I'm obsessed and I have a list of what you just have to make me lost change
I'm the two war of the government and in the street for I am just in the room
And regulate you I need you by a whole man punishes
But you can't look away I need you to think I'm delicious
With the stuff that I say
I'm the best you can get
Have you kissed me yet long this time
Who's an out of your TV set
You will obey me while I lead you
The garbage that I've lead you
Until the day that you know
You don't go for help no one will leave you
Your mind is totally control has been stopped into my mold
And you will do as you are told until the past is your soul
That's right folks don't touch that job
With the hands that come with me yo
Who's an out of your TV set
I am the side of your TV yo
Hands up and stand
Look at me girl
I am the side of your TV yo
He's an out of your TV yo
I'm the side of your TV yo
Yes
Almost perfect
Yup
He definitely was on to something wasn't
Fragrance aff or wrap an up
episode 69 or eighth of the daily stuff
source code tomorrow. Hopefully I'll be able to get one, I think I'll get one
show out before I get picked up for for the airport. It's an afternoon flight in New York.
And then I guess we'll speak to each other sometime from the big Apple.
Plane's trains automobiles. I will make it home for Christmas. That's for sure.
Adam at podshow.com. Deadlysourceco.com. Take care, everybody. Bye.
The best and the brightest. Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering
podshow and limelight.