Need new beats for your headphones?
Check out e-music.
Over 2 million jacks.
Log on and get to 25.
Headbanging.
Move, raise it.
Seeker's cracking.
Slow dance and hip, raise it.
Beat, slamming.
Trouble, tweaked.
Dooms.
That's 25.
Breathe.
And be free.
Get it at e-music.
Hotshow.com.
Don and Drew's show.
No, that was really bad.
And do that again.
Even for all of this, any other fucking.
Don and Drew's show is 646.
Get ready baby.
Yeah.
The Don and Drew's show.
Hey, everyone.
It's Don, Miss Ellie.
And Drew, Don and Chris.
And Adam Klee.
For the first time ever, somehow we have Adam Kuri on the show.
Somehow, well, you happen to be in my room.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Jowing the fruits of my friendships.
That sounds so hot.
You know, it is.
We were on the three year waiting list.
Yeah.
Yeah, people don't know that with Patrick,
you have to wait three years for me with Adam.
We haven't done a show together ever.
Have we done a Skype thing, never?
No.
Double-endor?
Never?
Well, we did the double-endor.
Yeah.
Not audio.
Yeah, all right.
That was just our private time.
So, well, thanks for letting me on you show.
Thanks for being with him.
Yeah.
Um, so we're at the portable media
the expo in the lovely butthole city of Ontario, California.
This is really the pits. It really is, you know what I'm talking about here.
Well, it's just like everything is completely wrong.
It's like take this room for instance, you know, it's like you get a sweet, but there's no
mini bar.
Right.
It gets a water.
It's the little things, the little things that irritate.
Got a huge flat screen TV, and then, you know, but like no electrical outlet, let's
have that anywhere.
It's like I can't plug anything in.
It's wrong.
It's just wrong.
But you are going to be able to plug in your USB lava lamp.
Well, yeah, but it plugs into the computer.
I know.
Let's skip G. That's the one thing I like about being here.
If you do, you meet some of the listeners. You guys do this all the time.
So, yeah, you meet all your minions.
Because we're of the people.
You are of the people.
Yeah.
Of course, I'm above the law.
Yeah, right.
So skip G. He's written in.
I think he's called an a comment.
Um, but that was it's really touching when someone gives you a gift that they really
thought about.
That's why I was asked for books.
It says, what do you want to give me a book?
Because you know, whatever you give me tells me more about you and what you think of me.
I'm going to send you such dirty books.
In Europe, we'd call you a dirty woman.
They call me that worldwide.
It's just a matter of time.
The dirty woman.
Yes, she's dirty.
Yeah.
So you gave me a butt plug.
There you go.
A glitter butt plug.
It's a, it's a lava lamp that runs on USB.
That's cool.
That's, he knows me.
He gets you.
Yeah, he does.
He knows that you need a little pizzazz.
Very nice.
Didn't we do, didn't we do a show?
Was that a blogger con?
Remember we sat in a room with Dave Weiner?
We didn't record it.
No, we should have.
I really busted Dave that time.
I walked in when he said, oh, we're totally fucked on.
What?
Yeah, Dave just said that.
And I was like, I don't remember that.
Oh, he told us that.
Yeah.
I was like, oh, what'd you write?
Yeah, it was like a slide right in.
Hello.
Busty.
What was he talking about?
Fucking me.
Like as insects or business.
No, sex.
You really?
I'm going to sign our dish.
Should contract.
No, it's like sugar over.
That's what I was saying.
I know.
I felt like you're shit.
I thought you were talking about sex.
No.
And now I'm doing this show for three years.
Oh.
Yeah.
Sign in blood.
I forget what happened after that though.
I was probably like, you wish.
Okay.
That was a long time ago.
That was actually the first time that we met you.
I decided that I liked you right away because you said you would totally go to the 3D
porn with us.
Well, I did.
I know.
But like you weren't like, hmm, should I?
No, I was right there.
No, I was always honest.
No hesitation.
And I'm like, this is a guy we can work with.
And I don't socialize with many people for anything.
But that was such a great combination.
You guys in 3D porn.
Remember that guy was doing like porn trivia.
Yeah.
It's beginning.
And I knew nothing.
Did it.
One of you win a prize?
Was it Sam?
Sam was with you.
I thought you wanted CD.
No.
Okay.
I thought somebody wanted a prize.
A thing of mince that no one could open.
It might have been Sam.
That's right.
The thing of mince.
Yeah.
So I didn't recall.
Did we all spend 20 minutes being like, this fucking mince.
Yeah.
No, in 2 months, that was 3 years.
Wow.
Did you guys still have them fun?
Yeah.
Can you tell?
I don't know.
Just check them.
You can sure.
So the expo is always kind of interesting.
This year it feels like they're not up.
They don't want any shenanigans here.
The hotels.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, more security.
It's the rowdy podcasters though.
Well, they probably thought we don't need any security for the other
thing.
I know that the pod show specifically has, you know, that the word is out within a three-mile
radius.
Don't let them do anything.
I don't give them hotel rooms.
Nothing.
You know.
So.
Yeah.
What kind of say?
That's your fault.
You're the riffrath.
That's funny because if you go to, like,
Comdex, you know, or any other trade show.
And I have to say Vegas.
You'll see when the show goes to Vegas.
Everyone's going to just be partying because that's what trade shows are.
Yeah.
You go party.
I'm sorry.
But, you know, the award show.
That wasn't a party to me.
That, you know, we went to the award show here.
Yeah.
And it was like, kind of, like a photo op.
It really was.
So it couldn't hear anything.
No.
The room was way too big.
Yeah.
The room was too big for the acoustics.
They weren't on stage.
I mean, that's good.
You couldn't see anything.
Right.
If anything, I would feel quite insulted if I had come here to receive an award.
I'm like, fuck that.
Yeah.
No red carpet.
It was fucking Joan Rivers.
I had to talk about my outfit.
There you go.
No, it's damn.
That's no good.
No.
This was, it seemed like just a little, you know, sight thought.
Like, oh, yeah.
We got to do the awards.
This took him in the corner.
Yeah.
Because I went, you know, for, for show girls.
Right.
I wanted to be like clapping and chair and in shape.
Nice.
Well, honestly, we went too late.
We missed the actual award.
But.
That was the restaurant's fall.
Yeah.
That's kind of disappointed.
So maybe in Vegas.
It'll be different.
Yeah.
I think it's going to be.
Uncontrollable in Vegas.
I don't know.
Because it's incredible.
I mean, what actually happens?
I mean, did you guys go to any, you didn't go to any of the keynotes or anything?
No.
Do a lot of people show up for that.
I mean, I went last year to one.
And it was a fall.
It was pretty full.
Yeah.
I think it was Jason Calcanas.
Right.
So I remember going there was the, with Michael actually going.
But it was a full room.
So.
Nice.
She's.
You don't like that?
I'm not sure.
Now you don't.
You're the like one of the girls that doesn't like first.
No.
I was expecting actually to do like the thing where you put your hand on your forehead in the last place.
No, it's first.
No.
I wasn't sure.
But that would've been really funny if I would've just totally punched you.
My girls do that.
Patricia.
That's like the thing on the forehead.
She does.
Yeah.
That's a table one night.
And Patricia can bounce like a fucking truck.
I see it.
But.
And I'm like.
See.
That's what I think.
Christina went like that.
Can you get the memo that this game was on here?
Did they find you?
It's.
They punched me all the time.
She's my mother-in-law punches me.
She really hits me hard.
And arm all the time.
That's like a Greek thing.
Maybe you're fun to punch.
No.
I don't have the meat your man does.
I don't.
He's like a fucking.
He's chisel.
He's got.
He didn't take me much, but I'm lazy.
Yeah.
No.
I mean, you've got it.
You can see that you don't have to.
He just happens.
Yeah.
He's like a few worker.
So we were at the zoo.
He does.
We were to do.
And they had this thing where you can test against.
Like the strength of an orangutan.
Uh-huh.
And so he beat the orangutan.
It was easy.
I was just like it would go right to the top.
I was squeezing it as hard as I could.
And I could not even get it 20%.
I really like it when you squeeze it.
Yeah.
So it's a man with extras.
So, um, are you having fun here at him?
You're having lots of friends, I see.
Making me get jealous left and right.
It is nice to see some women here.
Yeah.
It did.
The blooddress rushes away from my brain.
Yeah.
No, it's nice.
But, you know, first of all, I love all women.
You know that.
I really do.
I've had to learn to accept it.
You know, like so.
Yeah, but.
You have an open relationship.
Yeah.
It is awkward.
No, just any woman.
I love all women.
And particularly when the ratio is still got to be maybe 20%.
I mean, this is a lot less women here than the nerdy guys.
So you kind of like looking and seeing it, scoping out the room who's here.
And they all just look really beautiful.
Well, next to all these men, yes.
No.
bodies.
So, but, you know, and it's kind of, it goes a little bit deeper.
Because, you know, you hear these people.
You have kind of back and forth banter like with you or with Angie.
You know, so then hang out and hug each other.
Yeah.
I need that.
I'm tired.
I'm an old tired dude.
I need hugs.
A big time.
Angie swung by and grabbed me in the ass.
And that needs you.
But she, okay, so it's not like special.
I thought I was like the only one.
Sorry.
I think we're all.
I got that.
I was the only one.
Then I was going to hit Don.
It's Angie.
Does she live with Ryan?
I have no idea.
This is like.
I got to figure this out.
Are they on item?
I don't know.
I think so.
She was.
I've always thought so.
She saw.
So that's real talking to him.
And she went right over and busted it up.
Really?
I almost kneeled behind her.
No, she's going to put it up.
Did you do that?
Yeah.
Well, I've to ask her.
So I'll say, like, I'll make it really awkward for her.
I'll say, yeah, that was crazy when you pinch my bottom.
I'll make so are you with that guy?
Yeah.
It's just like, don't do it to those wingers.
And I'll say, you know, Adam loves tears.
And we're all really close.
Yeah.
It's been friends for three years.
Uh-huh.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Well, that's actually, you know.
Well, you know, that's how I got the contract.
People wonder.
Yeah.
That's what they all speculate.
So what have you seen?
Have you seen it?
Have you got a minion army?
Do you guys did a dinner in an outburger?
A little lunch thing.
Yeah.
It was really casual.
Everyone.
We didn't know what our schedule would be like.
Oh, excuse me.
We'll schedule this.
Well, you know, sometimes there's things to do.
But this year, it's really chill.
Well, I mean, yeah, there isn't much to do.
Right.
Are there any events?
So everyone's going to the pool party now.
That's what they're at right now.
Actually, there's a that culture catch.
They used to make the same room.
What is that?
It was putting who's sponsored.
I think extreme prizes part of that too.
There's a bunch of sponsors.
There's a ton of people.
And it's going to be, I'm kind of interested to see how they're going to do this.
Because it's also like a party that would be cool in San Francisco.
And I'm not sure if they'll be able to execute it in Ontario.
So what is it like performance arts?
There's going to be a, yeah, there's going to be a band.
There's going to be belly dancers and trepies with tissue.
I saw on the ceiling.
And it's going to be in that in that small room.
So they better have a lot of, because it's going to look really lame in that in the
size.
And you know how the bands are being too big.
Yeah.
And you got to have a lot of talent.
So that is not it.
It's probably his other girlfriend.
You think, let's speculate.
Did you say speculate?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Very much.
All right.
He's totally.
So peanut paper.
I'm like.
He's not smoking.
I don't know why they put me in a non smoking floor.
And it doesn't smell of pot or anything.
And the guy's like, actually, this makes a lot of sense.
So we're smoking pot in my room.
Guy knocks on the door and says, chocolate.
I mean, is this awesome hotel?
Why?
And here's that chocolate.
And I'm like, what the fuck is he saying?
He said, chocolate.
Help him up.
He says, chocolate.
It's really good.
Yeah.
What is this?
It's nice.
It's minty.
It's so refreshing.
Yeah.
Rottie.
There's candy here.
Right now, everyone's like, I wonder if Andy's on a new sponsor for this.
Yeah.
Totally man.
Those guys like ruin in the show was advertised.
Yeah.
It was somebody's like, it sounds good.
And this is what I have yours right here.
The fourth one is right here.
There's one more for you guys.
I'm going to take all that back.
That's it about the hotel.
No, right here.
Don't eat your chocolate.
Mm-hmm.
It's probably here to do turn down.
Yeah.
I guess for him, you know, he doesn't actually turn on the bed.
It just throws him chocolate on.
Any wake up, you think you should sit yourself.
I never happened to you in a hotel.
I thought she was like that.
Probably sleep on the fucking chocolate.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
That's really bad.
Right after you went to the Bean Burrito store.
Yeah.
I want to have to share because the mini bars.
Oh.
Thank you.
All right.
Chocolate ice cream.
That was pretty good.
Yeah.
Dark chocolate.
You guys didn't stop recording it, did you?
No.
How long did you frozen this?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
How long did you frozen this?
About 25 minutes.
Something like that.
Yeah.
It goes with the flow.
Sometimes I feel like it can go longer.
Sometimes you can't.
Sometimes you have to cut the show short.
No, not often.
Very rarely.
Yeah.
Nice.
So, okay.
You've been podcasting longer than mostly everybody here.
Although you're catching up to me 6.46.
I know.
Yeah.
I just can't.
This really bumps me out.
That's the one thing I really hate.
I just don't have the time.
And really the energy after the number hours to do a show.
Right.
Really pisses me off.
But I mean, you're building the company.
So the other people can do it.
Agreed.
But you just finished 6.6 right?
Yeah.
But even for that, you know, I would have loved to know a lot more production and stuff like that.
I just don't have the time.
I want to do something.
Yeah.
We're 20 away from you.
We should get on that now.
Let's have videos.
We don't count the numbers on the videos.
Yeah.
I heard you did really nice on the San Francisco office.
I haven't seen it yet.
I want some people mention that.
You were in it.
But you had your back to us.
Yeah.
You were with Moody.
Oh, really?
In Wisconsin.
Yeah.
I'm like, I'm Rock Moody.
After I saw that, I thought, why didn't I just bang on the door and be like,
I love you.
I'm angry.
Really?
Because I would have tunged you.
Yeah.
No, totally.
But you know, I get to the office.
And I get kind of intimidated because it's so professional and so business-like.
Really?
You think so?
I mean, everyone's working.
Not stuffy.
No.
Everyone's working.
Yeah.
I mean, they're busy.
But everyone's excited when you guys come.
I mean, that's like two days ahead of time.
I want to run it around like you don't do a cop.
I'm not kidding.
It was really exciting.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It means to like engineers.
They're building shit that, you know, we don't want to think about.
You know, shit just kind of works.
Kind of.
Right.
And you see a lot of people that do that.
Yeah.
But we've seen the demo of the what the stuff they're working on.
So it's like a new stuff.
Yeah.
So for you guys, for them to present that.
That's a big deal.
You know?
That's a good connection.
I wish I could get more.
And more of the talent and stuff like that together with the company.
And it's just geographically challenging.
Sure.
And just the time that goes into it.
But there's a lot of people at work trying to.
Trying to make it easier for us.
Better.
Don, you're looking at me like.
Fuck this.
No.
I'm just like listening.
Good.
Give me a look.
No.
Everyone who don't totally was awesome.
Going this award show because I felt so unhappy about walking.
It's not.
Yeah.
I know everyone wants to say something.
And you know what's the talk.
And then someone else interrupts.
And then, you know, just feel, you know what it is.
Yeah.
It's weird.
It's very difficult.
But then we kind of walked in arm and arm.
And that was like that.
Just let us alone.
It's nice.
You know, I'm like Adam.
It's like we're at prom.
Yeah.
Totally.
Just strange.
So do you.
So when we're at the expo.
Like tang out with you.
We usually have to hang out in small groups.
Yeah.
I don't usually see them big like clusters and stuff.
Because it just disappoints everyone.
And tires me out.
Sure.
Totally.
Yeah.
You can't just everyone wants to say something.
They'll be waiting and hovering.
And you know.
And then people are recording your conversations.
These.
Yeah.
This is pretty weird.
The video like two.
Five video cameras.
Well, I just talk into someone.
That's really uncomfortable.
Right.
Yeah.
I'm not having a real conversation.
I'm totally posing for the camera.
I'm looking like the pod father.
You know, I'm not actually listening about the fuck you say it.
So that's hard.
Yeah.
But some people even have their rigs.
Like that justine girl.
Mm-hmm.
He's like sending it right there.
Yeah.
She's live all the chicken.
What's your purse?
She got a fucking backpack.
Yeah.
Like a whole wife.
I know she's like transmitting it.
And I'm thinking like.
Yeah.
I want to be though because it was like she's shooting from the worst angle.
First of all.
Yeah.
She's not very tall.
And then.
She's shooting it from like so low.
Yeah.
And I thought.
Oh, that's going to look fucking at you.
That's a little light situation.
Yeah.
I don't know if that was going to work at all.
But she's cute, right?
She wants everybody to look worse.
No.
She's, I don't think it was light there.
True.
Well, the other guy wears it on his hat.
Yeah.
So it's like eye level.
Just like girls.
I bet girls wouldn't do that.
She, I think, had it on a half a while.
But you're right.
I mean, it's a very shy morgue.
Yeah.
And I think it's like a real blue tooth head set.
And it actually exists.
And we're actually kind of getting that way.
I mean, we live in science fiction.
Sure.
For real.
Yeah.
Totally.
or just D&TV?
I don't.
No.
I've looked a few times, you know.
I'll watch it for a while, but I mean, it's been a while.
I don't think anyone's ever, whenever I see it.
No one's doing anything that's that interesting.
They're just sitting in front of the computer.
Right.
Or even at a party to take your kid off at least.
Do something.
Yeah.
I don't know.
They wanted us to do something.
You know?
One of us that run a camera.
I don't want to, I don't want to do video all the time like that.
No.
It's just two.
It's, I barely have privacy as it is.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, like, I'm talking about my life all the time.
Everyone knows, like, I was sick for a while.
I don't know how many people I've come up to say, like,
How's the hepatitis A?
And I'm like, oh, what?
I'm like, yeah.
I eat like a sick thing.
Really?
You ate that?
I was so sick.
But it's so good.
What did you call it?
Hepalomode.
That's what the A's for.
Hepalvan.
You're probably getting it.
You're getting it.
I got it from butt-munching, Drew.
Yeah.
Nice.
Have you ever given him the BJ all the way?
Yeah.
Okay.
I thought it was, yeah.
I remember him begging for it.
He always does it.
Exactly.
If he had ten floor jobs a day, he'd still be like,
Can I have another?
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, sir.
Oh, you guys killed me.
You wacky kids.
All right.
I'm sure that you're always saying that.
Like, oh, why if I'm back from San Francisco?
I'm too tired.
Are you ever home?
Yeah.
How was home last week?
No.
Oh, well.
But, you know, look.
Now is a good time to do this.
You know, because Christina's 17, you know,
Yeah, I'm home and like, you know, she has, she lives in an apartment in her house.
Basically, you know, so she's got her own life.
And Patricia has, you know, she got all kinds of shit.
She's traveling.
She's doing her.
She's putting together a big band, like a 17 piece.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
She has a whole show in mind.
We've married for 21 years, you know.
It's like, she's okay if I fuck off for a while.
I was home for three months.
I was home for a long time.
Okay.
But, you know, every single day in the London office,
we really had to get that going.
And you come home at four o'clock.
San Francisco wakes up.
So you're still on the phone until midnight.
Yeah.
But, uh, out the fuck.
I'm saying to come check that off.
Is that, you know, she got a car.
She totally come.
We're going to.
Get, we have a plan for that, yeah.
We're making a calendar up.
I'm going to write a book.
Yeah.
I'm a pageal press.
For a pageal press?
Yep.
Excellent.
That's, I really believe in that.
And that's going to be incredibly successful.
I want your story, actually.
Would you write my story?
Well, you have to tell me what you say.
Are you serious?
You just, I just-
No, let's say it.
No, this book is about losing your virginity.
And I'm-
Oh, I got a great deal of losing your virginity story.
Oh, I'm so awesome.
Well, then we'll have to put in the book.
Great idea.
Yeah.
And so, hi.
So, we're going to do audio version.
We're going to do a podcast that builds up to it.
And we had a meeting today with Mark.
You took a meeting.
I took a meeting.
We took a meeting with Mark.
Yeah.
And, uh, we're talking about the release and stuff.
And I was like, I had to get out of the story in the book.
Mm-hmm.
So.
I was 15.
Does it now?
Yeah.
Okay.
I just remembered that.
I remember her name, too.
Okay.
Before we write the book.
We need submissions.
Yeah.
But we'll be talking about that.
This was actually-
I mean, I got to tell a little about story.
All right.
Give me a little bit.
Just the tip.
But it was-
I think-
The tip is pretty broad.
I like to hear that.
Yeah.
I'm trying-
Without giving it all away, it was one of these.
Uh, I had a buddy and-
And he was older than I was.
And he had a, um, a girlfriend.
And he set me up.
So that could, you know.
Have sex with his girlfriend.
Uh, but I had never told him that I'd never done it.
But she figured it out pretty quickly.
Yeah.
Women have that intuition.
You're fucking the mattress.
Hey, don't-
It was not that bad.
That's my knee.
But-
But one thing I will say.
Did you read that?
It was a girl who writes for new New Yorker magazine, I think.
And it was-
It kind of flowed through the internet a week or two or so ago.
She wrote this thing that nerds make the best lovers.
Yeah.
And it was a line in there that really agree with, you know,
was it one of the reasons why nerds make really great lovers is because they don't mind reading the manual.
That's so true.
Boy, did I study that shit?
I got really good at it.
Well, we're going to have to find out all the details.
Oh, yeah.
For the book.
I'm all for that.
Very good.
I think that'll be extremely successful.
I think so too.
I'm excited.
My meeting was very productive.
We should also do a masturbation book.
Oh, totally.
I mean, it's like it's endless.
For really, yeah.
Yeah.
And that's really-
There it goes.
It's in the works.
Cool.
I think Mark's trying to get it done for June.
Really?
The book has to be done by June?
Yeah.
More than it all winter.
Okay.
Nice.
Who else are you going to talk to?
A lot.
I'm just going to talk to tons of people.
I want to make sure that I even get a good generation gap too.
Like I would like to talk to you.
Just again.
Yeah.
I want to get into the slash of the elders.
This is wrong.
Nice.
True.
See, Drew can't take my words.
See, you want some celebrities too?
Yeah.
I mean, well, I just want interesting stories.
We just got one.
What are you talking about?
No.
And I'm curious.
Let me think.
Yeah.
We work on it.
What's going to be right in the celebrities kind of less important.
This is the good story is really what you want.
Right.
I wonder how many different stories there are.
I must be tons.
Everybody's got one.
Yeah.
How about you?
Me.
Yeah.
I got sorry for the book.
Thank you.
All right.
Well, we got to get out of here.
We got to get out of here.
We got to let Adam get back to making the way source code.
Yeah.
That was a slight point.
This has been awkward since you didn't have pants on.
And you're dripping the whole time.
Oh.
You're dripping the whole time.
Well, thank you for the chocolate.
Sure.
And the water.
Great.
That's pod shows.
Maybe we have a chocolate.
It's a water.
If you're a pod guest, you're in your thinking about signing with pod gel.
Just think about the water and chocolate.
You'll get.
And you can be best friends with Adam Curry, which comes with every single contract.
Right.
We had to add that, remember.
Oh, that was our clause.
Yeah.
We got to be best friends.
You guys are great.
And I appreciate it.
What you've done.
Seriously.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Did that sounds interesting?
Okay.
Not too.
Just somewhat sincere.
All right.
You guys.
Well, thanks for listening.
Adam, thank you so much for being on the show.
Thank you guys.
We have to promote anything.
Do you want to promote your show?
Yeah.
Do you have a podcast?
Don't we have a sponsor?
No.
We don't have any sponsors.
We have a sponsor?
No.
I can't believe you paid you guys.
I know.
That's what we're always saying.
Please.
We have some tequila thing coming up.
Yeah.
Oh, that's going to be cool.
I heard the sponsor that today.
It's going to be pretty cool.
Don't we have some...
There's some other...
There's a lot coming down.
You know, we...
Now we have 8 to the B.
And we've got...
Yeah, we're...
Our shit's kind of squaring up a little bit.
You know, we've...
There's...
It's not as painful.
It's the square peg in the round ball thing.
I see more like the star hole.
I see the star.
Can I see that?
I did a hypoxia test.
Do you know what that is?
No.
What a hypoxia is.
Is if you fly above 10,000 feet for...
I don't know if you go even higher than it happens quicker.
It's one that's just no oxygen.
And you eventually you die.
See, it's no big deal.
I mean, that's...
That's why your...
Your plane is pressurized and everything.
And if you're above 10,000 feet or like a 10 or 12,000,
you shouldn't do it for more than 30 minutes.
Legally, I think, and you have to go back down to 7 or 8.
Okay.
Because there's less...
You know, the air is thinner.
So there's less actual oxygen.
And what happens is you start to get really stupid.
And it's really dangerous because, you know,
you can be in flying in there's a situation.
It's like being stone.
You kind of sit there and like...
Okay.
You know, so they give you the...
the square in the peg game.
We'll have to like, three minutes, right?
Okay.
Now put the pegs in the right hole.
You're like...
Like, yeah, I could totally not fly.
No, I could fly.
I know I could fly.
You know, so...
Anyway.
So how'd you do in the test?
Well, no, it's three minutes and then you're stupid.
Then they put you back on oxygen.
Otherwise, you're just, you know, you'll pass out.
Yeah.
You know, that's happened.
That happens to me when I fly.
No.
Every time I wake up, what's it called?
Well, even just take off.
I just have to...
Any kind of bank.
You pass out of it.
Really?
I'm always like this whole catcher from hitting the head of the side.
Every time.
Every time we fly.
As soon as I feel the bank, I got a really...
I just lack of...
You're not afraid of flying the world yet.
No, no.
No, it's not either the panic thing.
No, just...
I just can't...
Stay awake.
No.
I just said the blood to the other bank.
Really?
My doctors are perplexed.
Oh.
But they're like, well, just don't become a pilot.
Yeah.
I'm like, okay.
No worries then.
All right.
So...
We'll let you get back to...
So, six, six, six.
We tried.
We shoot for London.
Okay.
Don't tease me like that.
Oh.
We're in 20 shows.
That's four weeks.
Okay.
Something like that.
I don't think we can...
You'll like back...
Five, six hundred.
Okay.
Six, nine, do nine.
We'll shoot for London.
All right.
Well, that would be cool.
Or we're in.
Because it's right around Halloween, actually.
Six, six.
We're trying to make it Halloween.
All right.
We'll...
We'll make it happen somehow.
For that show.
All right, sweetie.
Thanks for being the show.
I love you too.
Me, Nick.
I love you, Andy.
You guys are okay.
I-
This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery.
Mojo!