This podcast is brought to you by Paancho and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
Adam Curry's Daily source code is the program that started the new media revolution,
where listeners and producers party together.
Adam is getting from the Zedeshon Keptown, South Africa.
Good morning, Adam.
Happy Thursday, Adam.
How you doing?
Adam Curry.
How are you doing?
I'm here.
Adam, it's all again from Kurt The Washington.
With a cast of contributors from around the globe,
and a passion at worldwide audience,
it's no wonder that the Daily Source Code was featured in Time magazine
and made cover story news in Wired.
The Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
It's my arm.
Being able to choose the music that I want to play for you is
virtually Nirvana.
It's low.
You're supposed to be my trophy wife.
And I can just see it now.
It's sweaty.
You really want to look that leg?
It's me the butt.
Good.
It's geeky goodness.
I mean, just start this thing up on a command line
and lock that puppy down.
You know, that's about all that's needed in it's all for you.
It's my job to entertain you.
And if that means going to jail,
so be it.
Delta share a Charlie 5-6-2.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
On the casting, it's out of curry.
Payman and Paris in 94.
I wasn't 95.
She was there studying abroad.
He was on tour.
Playing in another dive.
They partied hard in the pocketweights.
A little north of the sand.
He dreamed about her in so many ways.
She dreamed about her in French.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
And he's the one.
He's the mother son.
Not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
They met in New York a few months later.
He was still living alone.
Hugging the ball and masturbating.
Never answered his phone.
The first date was a movie together.
Outside it Brian Pock.
We're the spirit of St. Louis.
Just went on forever until they drank wine.
Until they saw us cause.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That he's the one.
He's the mother son.
Not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
They finally hooked up for the first time.
The night before the Fourth of July.
He felt so awkward saying goodbye to the girl who just changed his life.
Now my friend, they are inseparable.
She even gets that boy to go to the gym.
Now if you don't think that's love, you must be cynical.
Oh, maybe man, you're just dreaming in French.
Yeah, because she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That he's the one.
He's the mother son.
He just needs time to heal.
Oh, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That he's the one.
He's the mother son.
Not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
Yeah, he's the one.
He's the mother son.
Not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
What to do with Michael?
It's daily source code episode five, six, two coming to you.
Almost live from New York.
Everybody, you're doing it.
What are we now?
Wednesday, the 14th.
Technically, of course, it's Wednesday, although from me it's Tuesday nights.
Still on that night.
We schedule even though I'm on the on the East Coast.
But it's only actually the only time I can do the show.
It's been another crazy day in New York.
But I love this city, the energy.
And you know, it's so easy to get around from from office to office.
And from meeting to meeting, you know, it's just it's, it's a town made for business.
I got to tell you.
I love it.
And what a fantastic day.
It started way too early.
Of course.
I was embedded.
See after the show last night.
I don't know.
I started to want or something like that in the alarm when it's 630.
That's just not enough sleep for a growing boy.
But of course, I, when I'm in the hotel here, I do really literally go to sleep.
When I get in bed because the porn is horrible.
It's really no good.
And they have, yeah.
It's just like the standard service porn service and all the hotels in New York.
Isn't it good?
Just no good porn.
Anyway, not the you care.
So breakfast at like 715, you know, off to the first meetings it ate.
Oh, yes, pounding the pavement.
Let me see, um, or some of the fun things that happened today.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yes.
I had a, had a meeting over at Marie Claire at the, at the Hearst,
Hearst Publishing Building.
Marie Claire, of course, we produce the mast head,
which is behind the scenes at Mary.
Do we, I don't know if it's Marie Claire or Mary Claire.
Well, Joanna, who's the editor and chief and also star of the, star of the show.
It says Marie Claire.
So I met her.
I met the publisher.
Uh, our main contact who is, you know, basically our,
our counterpart.
Oh, well, can you tell I'm tired.
Our counterpoint for production.
Uh, let me tell you.
Sorry.
Up in those offices.
Man, it's like,
Oh, estrogen spill on 105.
Man, oh, man.
It's some powerful women.
And they know what they want.
Oh, boy.
That was a lot of fun.
Actually, I, and it was really great meeting Joanna, man.
She's a, she's just as dynamic in person.
She, yeah, she's on the show.
And I understand why she's kicking ass on that magazine.
But here is something incredibly cool.
So I was, we're planning out the next couple of episodes.
Um, there's an interview planned both for the magazine,
but also for the show with Angelina Jolie.
Yeah.
Yes, who's going to be doing special executive producing on the set that day, huh?
Yes.
I, it's either April 4th or May 4th.
I don't care which one.
I'm, I'm, I'm caching in my virgin Atlantic miles.
And, uh, I'll be there.
So that was, uh, without a doubt, highlight of the day.
And, uh, I was actually, um,
I'll check in my email on the, uh, on the good old Nokia tablet.
Um, in the back of the cab on the way to an appointment.
And I saw an email come in from Eric Bergen's mom.
Now, you remember Eric is, uh,
uh, the a podcaster, or I know him as a podcaster from Green Room Radio.
Come, sorry.
I'm just so tired.
Um, and he invited me to come see the Jersey Boys as the production was in San Francisco.
And it turns out he's one of the leading as one of the leading roles.
And it was really good.
And I enjoyed it immensely.
And, uh, his mom has a podcaster.
And, uh, I think at one point probably in the back and forth conversation,
I asked if his mom was hot.
And I got a, uh, I got a voicemail comment from Eric's mom today.
And I was listening to this on my, on my tablet.
And I was cracking up.
It's fantastic.
Check it out.
Mr. Adam Curry.
I thought I needed to leave you a little voicemail.
This is Alison Lee, the host of CraftCast www.craftcast.com.
Also better known as Eric Bergen's mother.
I guess that makes me a Jersey mother.
Yeah.
Something along those lines.
Yeah, baby.
Anyway, I listened to my son's call in comment.
And as much as I appreciate, obviously, my son giving me a big play on air.
He sort of played up that whole domesticated thing in a way that made me feel.
Hmm.
Now, what do you think so far?
Does she sound hot or what?
Eric, I called you here, Eric.
This is not for you, okay?
Pretty cool voice, huh?
Not so hot, actually.
I'm not that a son should really think of their mother as hot.
Frankly, I had to call in and set the record straight.
So, you know, even when you do crafts and are domesticated,
you can be sort of hot.
I think you should check us out.
And guess what, Adam?
What, baby?
You're really hot.
Bye.
Thanks for your show.
Oh, man.
What kind of hum did you have?
You had a hum or Eric's mom?
You've got to fix your mic.
Get Eric to fix your mic.
You sound hot.
Definitely.
Hmm.
Well, I don't know what to say.
I'm kind of flabbergasted.
But, you know, I knew that your mom was hot.
Yeah, you know, as a wise man once said,
you only really have to look at the branch to know what the beauty of the tree will be.
Adam, check this out.
More evidence that DSC listeners love to spank it.
And no, no, no, calm down, calm down.
Don't want to get you all excited.
Like that time, the John Norris showed up to work.
We're in that t-shirt that said mustache rides 25 cents.
No, what I mean is that there are DSC listeners out there who can play
some mean mother fucking guitar right on.
This one comes to us courtesy of John Walker,
who sent in the solo section from a song from his band,
Logan Var.
I believe it's pronounced.
Logan Var could be lock and var.
Isn't that what the deft leopard say on Rock of Ages?
Definitely.
You go and flip.
Logan Var.
The way it sounds like some kind of medical instrument they use during surgery.
What I like is he says in his email.
It was recorded in his home studio in one take between conference calls.
Take that corporate America.
And if you listen to a close, you can hear how he uses the wall up pedal.
And like that kind of like halfway down position and get like a really cool,
like semi-wall tone in there.
Yeah, you know, all about to halfway down and semi-mark.
Really kind of nice.
So Adam get ready.
Rock out with your cock out.
Spring notes all over the place with his band lock and var.
This is John Walker.
I'll tell you, take some of that blue scale stuff and crank it up.
It always sounds good to me.
Hey, John says the gear used in this solo is a THD Univalve.
And I've been as tube screamer a cry baby.
And his blaze strat.
I know to those of you out there don't care anything about musical gear.
I might as well just to say.
So thank you, John Walker.
And you can find lock and var at the pot safe music network at music.potcho.com.
Or you can find their CD fire eyes at CDbaby.com.
Hey, if any other DSC listeners out there have a guitar solo that they want to share.
I don't care if it's rock or it's blues or it's jazz or blue grass or, you know,
you just picking away on an acoustic guitar send it to me at house of tone house of tone.
All one word at gmail.com.
Adam, thank you again for playing this.
My brother and just want to let you know that every day we keep the guitar solo alive
is another day that we strike tyranny in the hearts of boy bands everywhere.
I don't know idea what I'm saying.
But anyway, thanks again.
And I'll catch you next week with another guitar solo on house of tone.
Later, keep in the axe.
Wank alive.
Mark Hiroshima to name cough.
All right.
Mark, thank you.
Hey, gmail update.
You know, I was popping my mail.
So literally using the pop 3 protocol to get mail from one gmail account to the other.
Which, of course, is kind of ridiculous because, you know, with like a couple of keystrokes.
All that mail should be able to point it to to be pointed to a different account.
When did I start this?
When did I leave Friday?
Because it does like 200 mails at a time.
And it only will do this a couple times an hour.
So far, I've gotten about 8%.
And it's just an ongoing process.
It just keeps popping this mail over.
8% of my old Gmail account is now in my new Google apps 10 gigabyte account.
Now, here's what really slays me.
So in the middle of all this yesterday, I noticed that my standard Gmail account, all of a sudden, went to 10 gigs.
Can you believe that?
So I don't know if that's a part of having gotten Google apps.
I mean, I don't recall ever saying, you know, add this old account to it or something.
I have no idea what happened.
But now I have 10 gigs on the old account.
10 gigs on the new account.
And I guess basically I'm just going to leave the pop process going.
Because now it's just fun to watch how long it takes to move.
How long it takes Google to make you move four gigs of data.
You know, it's we're moving on four to five days now.
That's nuts.
Hey, Adam writes Bart Floohles.
It's just from the Oklahoma Department of Transportation.
The Oakland Department of Transportation.
Interesting.
Adam, I'm shopping around for a Mike preamp and heard on the Daily Source Code.
You're using a personas for your New York setup.
Can you tell me what kind?
Sounded really sweet.
Yeah, this is that new box that I got.
Let me see.
The hotel phone is on top of it.
Let me just.
The hotel phone has a core that is just too short to move it anywhere except where they put it on the desk, which is dumb.
Yeah.
I don't know if they make these anymore.
I actually picked it up second hand at Anderton's music in Guilford.
It's the, and it is pre-son as PRA pop aroma echoes Sierra Oscar November, uniform Sierra.
It's called the smart.
It's the blue max smart compressor.
And it says a little stereo compressor.
It doesn't even, there's no limiter in it.
So you can overmodulate it.
But very simple.
It's got some presets on there.
I'm, right now, I'm using preset stereo one preset.
You can set it manually, but I kind of like the way this sounded.
And you have got your input, your ratio, and your attack, and your release.
And it's beautiful.
And the nice thing about it doesn't have an external power supply.
You plug, you know, a cord, an AC cord right into the back of it.
Because the power supply is what kills me, man.
I have a bag that is literally just for power supplies.
You know what, I haven't suggested anything.
I haven't endorsed anything.
All I did was I said, look, when I saw an inconvenience,
I talked about that.
And now I saw this movie.
There was a channel for movie.
And it's called The Great Global Warming Swing.
Don't let it refutes everything that we, that is common,
I guess common knowledge about global warming,
and the cause of it being CO2 emissions.
And how are all going to die?
Die, I tell you.
We're going to die.
I guarantee you, 100% you're going to die.
It's just maybe not during the global warming.
And I haven't gotten a lot of hate mail, actually.
You know, I've gotten mail people saying you don't know what to tell you talking about,
but I'm not talking, I don't know what I'm talking about.
I'm just a messenger.
A messenger that's used to getting shot, by the way.
When you have these sort of polarizing arguments,
one of the things I like to look at is sort of the solitary,
with which people will, you know, kind of defend their stance
without really addressing the counter bailing evidence,
for instance, with this global warming swindle documentary.
It seems, on my end, it seems like a very compelling data
that, you know, hey, maybe this big hot,
sphere called the Sun, which is many thousand times
the size of the Earth might actually, you know,
have a little bit to do with how hot our planet is,
rather than, you know, carbon dioxide emissions from man.
So, you know, I think rather than jumping on either side of the data,
I think what we need to do is look at the data,
and, you know, I have to be in truth,
and I have watched this great global warming swindle,
you know, I would say that the BBC show,
so, you know, very compelling evidence,
and I think that people want to say that global warming does exist
that they do need to discount some of this evidence,
such that, you know, solar activity may have something
to do with the temperature here on Earth.
So, do I want to go on too long?
Yes.
All right, perfect time to stop.
Folder scruncher? No, none of that.
Yeah, exactly.
It's, and it wasn't a BBC documentary,
it was Channel 4, and in show notes from,
or was it yesterday, the day or Friday, from football Friday,
you can, or just uncurry.com, I think,
is where I put it.
You can find a link to see to watch this on a YouTube,
or Google video.
That's actually, I wonder.
Is it still on Google video?
Now that Viacom has, I love that story.
Viacom suing YouTube slash Google for $1 billion.
Yeah, that is a negotiating tactic.
Okay, that's, that's the way the big boys do business,
and believe me, Google is not going to pay
I'm going to pay out of billion dollars.
They're going to work something out.
But, of course, the real losers in all of this are us.
You know, we now figure it out already, guys.
Will you please?
But, wow, you know, that when, when Google and public
and in their perspectives, Larry and Sarah, Sarah Gay,
Sarah Gay, Sarah Gay, Sarah Gay, Sarah Gay.
I said that they would do no evil.
It wasn't dope be evil, by the way.
It was do no evil.
Big difference.
I see it even the New York Times is quoting that one.
That's just going to come flying back in their face.
Now, you, you can almost predict it's going to happen.
But, fun story to follow.
That's for sure.
Fun to see, as actually, I haven't, I've looked,
I've watched a little bit of news that watched
American Idol tonight, which I thought was an all-time low.
What a horrible show.
And, you know, I don't know if you saw this one with, with
a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a
little bit of a bit of confusion about a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of. Okay. Oh yeah. Nice. You got to do this. got to do this now. You didn't have to do it up yet too. So first thing about the huge open space. So one thing I do to suggest you have to be kind of enjoyable moments. Yeah. That is atenium wondering if you didn't have to do it up in a little bit outside or something or a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of some food that I always forget is did didる at your end. hurts for later hardly everything.
1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
Sorry about that.
Man, it's good to have been talking all day.
I haven't saved any for you, honey, I'm so sorry.
Hey Adam, it's the New Yorker in London, the nylon and momentan.
I just wanted to get a look for your heads up.
Current TV, UK, something that new to USV was,
but it's starting here today, Monday on Channel 229 on Sky TV.
And it's kind of you to meet mainstream media
with user-generated content on the television set.
Now you can go to their website and figure out
how you do it, because you put it on the site,
people vote on it, and they put it on the TV.
But it's very interesting, because convergence is not just technology,
but media.
And it'll be curious to see just how this takes off
and the impact on podcasting, for example.
And video casting, as well as the YouTube generation,
as it hits mainstream.
So just to learn to do that, if you haven't been aware,
and your listeners, if they haven't been aware,
and it'll be interesting trend,
that's current TV on Sky 2-2-9.
Yep, bye.
All right, nylon, thank you.
It's a guy from New York and London, nylon.
We're just gonna call you nylon from nylon, okay?
Nylon.
Yeah, I've seen previews of this.
I was not very impressed.
You know, it feels forced to me,
and this whole voting thing,
why does everything that is generated by independence
have to be denigrated to contests
of American idol like format.
You know, it's boring.
I had a conversation with,
I'm not gonna tell you who that was,
but with a media buyer.
And that's what I'll tell you,
was for the, for Doritos.
And it's a big ass brand, Doritos is huge,
and I would love to have them on the network.
But you know, the first idea,
now maybe we could do a contest,
and I'm so sick and tired of contest.
Let's not do a contest.
Why don't you just sponsor some damn good media?
That's exactly the way I've been talking
this week in New York.
It's been a very liberating
and I've gotten good responses.
So yeah, everything seems to have to be a contest
when it's not mainstream.
It's like such a separation.
And we've done it too,
but I'm a little tired of it at this point.
Just everything is like,
create the commercial, you know,
where were you?
In the 2005, man, we've been there done that.
Oh, before I forget, let me thank my sponsors for this show
that being folders.
I have been drinking a lot of folders coffee
because I don't like waiting for room service.
So I've got, well, it's not the gourmet stuff.
It's instant.
So I have that here in my hotel room.
And of course, whenever I see it on the table,
I always reach for the splendor,
because, you know, those two,
it just makes for a perfect combination
and a perfect taste.
Yes.
A serious satellite star is one or two listeners.
That's it for you for today.
Those of you still hang around.
Thank you.
Listen to this.
It's not often we get a comment from France.
France, of course, is a very interesting country
when it comes to media.
And their nationalistic view and a way protectionistic view
or stance on media, you know,
there are rules about how much foreign versus national content
is portrayed, displayed, and played on any form of mainstream media.
And the French, right?
OK, so listen to this.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Good afternoon, from France.
I'm listening to the G.S.C.
5, 6, oh, it's talking out there in the morning.
You see, on Clarison, about the global war,
I think you might try to get your hands on a book.
I think it came out two years ago.
It's called State of Fear.
It's a book written by Michael Christon,
not guy who wrote Jurassic Park on goal.
All those great books.
It's something like science.
It's a fiction, science fiction.
It's quite interesting.
Try to read that book.
Hey, it got an R.U.A. scrunched or a full day.
So I'm listening to that.
And by the way, I appreciate it, Edgar,
because I have seen state of fear.
People have told me about it.
And I would, of course, that's going to be fiction.
And I'm really a little bit into the nonfiction these days.
But anytime you've got a book,
you want to recommend to me.
I really appreciate that.
And of course, I do the same when I read a good book for you guys.
But listening to Edgar's voice, I'm like,
I know this guy.
I know him from somewhere.
So I hunted around on my first gen iPod.
And I found it.
It's him.
It's Edgar.
Check it out.
I don't like Edgar.
Edgar, come on in my friend.
My friend from France.
I got a caption for you quantities.
No what?
That makes you uncomfortable.
Fuck you.
I'm the re-endrover, you're driving on.
Yeah.
Oh, my man.
Fuck your sub convertible.
And the fuck get twice weekly trips to the analyst.
Still with a lot of fuck.
Fuck the harm done.
Me, no.
I'm blind festin' south of France.
I'm here to ask for God, more cash done, God, I can't come.
So I don't do just a thing.
That's just right.
I'm sure the death on your damn design of David from my doucheys.
No cholesterol, naturally.
You're a big old son that knew we are times.
Fuck no odds, keep turning up.
And newsweek.
And a lot, including nation, village voice, radiate, and the rest.
To be set up, religion, motherfuckers.
Take this passion over to have one of Tarleton movies.
One of Tarleton movies.
And fuck, if you can.
You're a pencil thin, deviant drinking, calorie counting, caffeine limiting.
So the I'm sparing, new dress sweet, sweetening, rear view mirror of a preening.
Cara, nibbling, body.
So the drone in a leg comes like, cool, fucker.
I got cash.
What else matters?
Slavery.
Fuck your fencing school, yes, fuck yo.
It's on your fullo, onion, a variety.
Oh fuck, all that shit to call me, the content to enjoy.
Got cash.
And I got cash.
I'm gonna have you with that.
Oh, go sit down, yes, cure.
On the Tarleton, of course.
We let your political correct, as you.
But I think you're at big also.
And you don't ask for it.
And you're idea of multiculturalism.
Japanese restaurant on Monday.
In the untaused day.
And I'm Wednesday, Caribbean.
Not too spicy, please.
Well, I got cash.
I got cash.
One is in the family for generations.
I'm afraid to break.
I'm trying to find the need to buy.
Telling you, it's the unpleasant.
You're not forgot.
I got cash, motherfucker.
And you can't tell whether or not I'm joking.
Can you?
Don't fuck.
What's playing on?
At least first.
Oh, man, I got cash.
Fuck you.
Quantities.
It's got to be Edgar from France.
Thank you for calling in my friend.
And of course, that's another track of Adam's first gen.
I bought.
It's been on there for something like five years.
Tom's hooting.
Send me actually a copy.
Two weeks ago.
And it was just so coincidental.
But there you go.
Completely our friend from France.
Edgar, feel free to call on any time, buddy.
I'll play it on.
Adam's first gen.
I bought.
Hello, Adam.
It's Mike Turner here from Bristol.
In the UK.
Just third year or two by Friday's podcast.
You're talking about a portable rig for cashblaster.
I've just been listening to audio courses.
57 podcasts.
It's came out this weekend.
These uses cashblasters.
I'll let's Chris Hamley and he's from the UK as well.
The audio courses.com.
Please talk about the ST software plugins for cashblaster.
I don't think cashblaster has got any facility here.
The moment I saw that plugin.
So I'm presumably the cashblaster.
Mike, listen to the daily source code as well.
I guess he does.
My deal solution for a mobile rig for a portable cashblaster.
Especially if you're off to a New York safe car and two lamps.
You know he's gay and whatever you can't run.
And we've given the facilities of modern processes.
There's only this sort of stuff coming handled in real time.
In software it is handled in stuff like.
Potholes and other record and few base and other recording devices.
Which actually does handling real time.
There's only this would be an option for cashblaster.
That's all that I'm just about to do this.
Cheers.
I really like that comment.
Of course that was about cashblaster.
It's the software that I use to create the daily source code.
You can find it at cashblaster.com.
And this is the VST plugin architecture.
It's very interesting indeed because there are some great plugins.
And you could literally before the Mike channel and for the music and effects channel.
You could put on reverb or compression or whatever you want.
And it would be a perfect thing for for cashblaster pro.
But I hope Mike still listens.
I think he does.
I think the problem though is that you're going to build in a delay.
Because it's still you know it's a digital process.
The audio is being processed.
And for me the way I work I want to be able to hear the ends.
You know it's like I think the computer fan is on or something.
It's making a horrible hum.
I got a hum.
See is that any better?
Not much.
Whenever you introduce something into the chain essentially that is software.
Not hardware based and VST plugins are software based.
It's going to give you a delay.
And then it's you start to talk funny because you hear yourself.
Like a couple milliseconds later than the words are coming out of your mouth.
So I don't think it's technically possible.
At least not in the way that the cashblaster was designed to be used.
Hey Adam this is Blake Morgan in New York City.
I just want to drop you a quick thank you for the tremendous support you've given me.
And the other artists on my label engine company records.
Every time you've played any of our material whether it's my stuff or Leslie Gores or Mike Aracos.
We've immediately seen a major bump in our sales on iTunes off of our artists websites and off of the record company website.
It's not an accident when it happens.
It's completely clear that it's a direct result of daily source code spinning our music.
So I'm here to tell you that podcasts, pod safe music network.
It's making a direct impact on the success of our music and independent music in general.
I came from a major record label that I ditched to start my own national record company.
So believe me when I tell you I know what I'm talking about.
So please keep doing what you're doing.
Spread the word about great new music. We truly appreciate what you're trying to do.
And I think that not only are you refusing to appeal to the lowest common denominator.
You've become a major factor in raising it.
So keep the music coming. I'm a big fan and I hope to talk to you soon.
Take care Adam. Thank you Blake. I really appreciate that.
In the old days and if you've seen pictures of Adam's attic at the curry manner.
You would get like a gold record. You know, that was kind of the thing.
That was the way the record companies and the artists would say thanks for helping out.
Of course, because you're not really on the real, on the real goods, you know, with the real money's flowing.
As a VJ or DJ, you don't see any in that.
So you get a gold record, which of course it's nice. You know, it's cool. It really is.
Although I must say somewhere in the mid 90s, the gold records were the qualities complete crap.
You know, I've taken these records out and they don't play.
You know, the old ones that Patricia has are really gold plated and if you play him, you can actually hear that the song is on him.
I'm not allowed to demonstrate that anymore because the last time I did that, we couldn't get the frame back together perfectly.
And so it's kind of like that gold record of hers is always kind of crooked and she's really pissed off about it.
But it's cool because it literally is, what's not really, you know, a goal. It's um, it's guess it's to think the call it the mother master is that what it is.
So you actually have to play it backwards on a turntable in order to hear the song.
But it really was the song.
And then after a while that it just became kind of a joke and you know, they put the stick cassettes in there before CDs and the cassette, you know, they're like the little gold spray painted cassette would, you know, the glue would come undone and then, you know, that would kind of like one end would like tilt down and, you know, or completely fall to the bottom of the frame.
But for you to say that, that means a lot to me and it means a lot to me that it's working because it's kind of we, we set out to do, you know.
A Blake's also a musician, by the way.
The perfect splendor sponsorship, saccharine.
Whatever, I'm not supposed to be so clever, I'm not supposed to be together.
And the anger in my second skill feels real.
And the cancer in my second skill feels real.
It feels real.
For give me fever, I'm not sick enough.
For give me weather, I'm not well enough.
Whatever, I'm not supposed to be so clever, I'm not supposed to be together.
And the anger in my second skill feels real.
And the cancer in my second skill feels real.
It feels real.
Whatever, I'm not supposed to be so clever, I'm not supposed to be together.
And the anger in my second skill feels real.
And the cancer in my second skill feels real.
It feels real.
And the anger in my second skill feels real.
Awesome.
Great pipes, Blake, awesome dude, I really like that.
Let me see if I have that right, hold on.
The Brian Leslie Gore, who is performing in Chicago at the American Airlines concert hall in Illinois Chicago 7 p.m.
On the 17th, just so you know, let's see, I'm really bummed because PD loves sent me an opener for the show.
And he sent the email and he sent the link to Jersey Jung, he said, you know, play some Jersey Jung on the show, man.
But then he forgot to attach the opener, which is a real bummer because I hate it when he puts a work into stuff and I can't use it.
So I'm like just sitting here clicking refresh on my Gmail and see if it comes in.
Okay, I'm sorry. Oh, look at this.
This is interesting.
Time sensitive PSA for families united against hate.
Play this on your podcast playing this on your podcast will be very helpful.
Oh, it's from Rebecca from Trini Recradio.
I think, yeah, Trini Recradio, right?
Trini Rec.com, shall we listen?
I've had bad experiences while on the road and just playing stuff without pre-listening.
Let's live dangerously shall we? Let me see what this is, hold on.
Sounds like shit.
Hi folks. My name is Ethan St. Pierre and I am working with an LGBT organization called Family United Against Hate.
You can go to their website at www.fuah.org.
That's fuah.org.
Family United Against Hate offers support guidance and assistance to families and individuals dealing with incidents based on bias
and to the people organizations and agencies who serve and support them.
We are getting a group of LGBT hate crimes survivors to stand side by side and lobby Congress and support of an explicitly inclusive hate crimes bill
and to send the message that anything less is unacceptable.
We do not want to leave anyone out of this event.
If you, as someone you know, has either suffered a loss or experienced anti LGBT violence
and would like to be a part of this lobby event, please contact me at radical guy at gmail.com.
Families united against hate and the trans FM internet broadcasting network will be sponsoring a fundraising event
to help to fray the cost of the travel and or hotel expense to those who cannot afford to make the trip on their own.
Fundraising event will begin at 10 p.m. on Friday night.
Oh man, look, this is not the way to do this public service announcement. It's just only not even halfway through yet.
No, no, no, no, no. You got to get people to go to web page that will, you know, with all the details who gives us shit about what time.
That sounds like like you're like you're on to something though.
The hate crime in general, it doesn't even have to be against gay lesbian by transgender, whatever GLBT stands for.
That doesn't have to be. It can be any hate crime in general.
Do we not have a log in hate crime? Come on. Is that, do we not?
Do we not have a log in hate crime? That's that doesn't sound right to me.
All right. Okay. It's time for me to go to bed. I've had it.
No, open it from PD love. Unfortunately.
Daily source code dot com, add them to podshow dot com if you want to email me something.
And of course, although I don't really want to say it, you can obviously attach something these days.
Because, you know, I've got that wonderful 10 gig limit now, my Gmail.
And if I could just find, where is it? A crap. Oh, man. Oh, here it is.
Very important before I say goodbye. Talk to you tomorrow. Take care.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.