This podcast is brought to you by Ponsho and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
You're going to break that baby and PWB up my ass.
Don't you get the crane and move the jersey tied piece over there.
Phil, Phil.
Get another load of Trinity feedback and mix them just Smith jingles.
No, no, not there.
Move the ass or size the third day.
Sally, Sally, come in, Sally.
Order me up more food bar and need more food bar.
Hey, what are you building?
What?
What are you building?
What are you some wise guy?
We're building the DSC551.
Actually, there's a lot of food bar.
Of course, that's a lot of food bars.
Food bar Friday.
Yo, yo, AC.
Start up the Charlie.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hello!
Hey, don!
Beat-
Yeah!
Drop the unknown river,
Down down baby, down down the roller coaster, sweet, sweet, sweet,
Baby, never gonna let you else,
Jimmy, Jimmy, go the box, Jimmy, shimmie, shimmie,
But, Jimmy, shimmie, go the box, Jimmy, shimmie,
Pau, rocket to the sunlight.
Rock it to the moonline.
Jerry, Jerry, cook it up, cook it up, just try.
I'm milkshake, keep the running to the yard.
If I'm gonna give you something, you know, I got a chance.
Don't be
浩谑, well, yeah, misery goes on snake.
Don't can't eat, No candy for you.
Down down baby, I know karate, looks so sorry.
What should we do to find it by Jimmy, Jimmy,
Cover basket, Jimmy, Shimmie, Pat.
Jimmy, Shimie, go the box, Jimmy, swimming in the hay.
Straight rock football, bench, your heart's跟大家.
I'll play Kuku, we got a good thing
To the front to the back, gonna take a lunch
Get in at the ring by and get ready for the pub
Cool!
No candy, no candy
We're going out to America and actually
No candy, no candy for you
No candy, no candy
We're going out to America and actually
No candy, no candy for you
No candy, no candy
Oh, you got up
The fighting cocks
We got no candy for you
New world where TV networks, movie studios
And record labels
Still think they can govern what you see in here
One man has the power to return control of entertainment
To the masses and make big media corporations
Wet their tiny little pants
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content
Comes the Daily Source Code
With Adam Curry
Hell yeah
That's how we roll with it
Hey everybody, how you doing it is
Food Bar Friday
We are officially fucked up beyond repair
It is the end of the week
And we celebrate that here on the Daily Source Code
With all kinds of stuff
And today it's going to be lots of music
Great music, thank you
Surgeersy Todd, the official musicologist of the Charlie
For a tournament on to the fighting cocks
With no candy, that was twisted
But it was, I don't know, it was interesting
And it had that
What is it, it's a Glen Millenir
That it started off with very, very nice
Hey, I had a, just a funky ass day
To wind up the week
Well, of course, I'm kind of kind of
Fibbing a little bit because it's Thursday night
Late to 1130
And by the time you're hearing this
In Los Angeles
Meeting with lots of powerful people
But it is, forget it, it's food bar
So I had a really interesting day today
I got up at 730
Because I had a nine o'clock meeting at HQ
Of course, I had no production work to do
So doing that none of the evening schedule now
And I looked outside
It was pouring right
And so, you know, wait a little, I don't think
Okay, I got a time this because
He's driving Trinity to keep it rolling
So we can get it on the road pretty soon
And make, you know, and
Clearly, it's a kind of QA that Rosie is doing
It's like bug testing, you know, and so what if we replace now
The transmission, we've replaced that we fixed the gas tank
We've replaced the brakes
We've had two new fuel pumps installed
This behatch is ready to roll
For sure
So anyway, so you know me, I'm a hair guy
So I got, yeah, I do my hair
I take 20 minutes every day
Nice and poofy
And I was like, okay, it's stop raining
I can't really see if it's stop raining
But I can see that the windshield wipers
Of the cars down on the Harrison
Which is part of what I, I have 180 degree view
So Harrison is just one of the streets I see here
And I see the windshield wipers
Either on intermittent or not on to like, okay, I'm making my move
I go outside within seconds it starts
So it's almost like hail
I'm like, oh man, and I have a ten minute, you know, eight or ten minute walk
Like this is not gonna, this is not gonna fly
So I stop underneath the overpass
Where many of my friends live
And open up my bag
And I had in there a plastic bag
From a Heathrow airport
From the new stand
It's what they put my magazines
I was by the pilot magazines at the airport
They always seem to have them at airports
And sure enough, it fit perfectly over
If it perfectly over my head
It was the perfect circumference, it wasn't a huge bag
And so it protected my head
It was like a clear plastic bag with some writing on like WH Smith or something
And it just got all poof beyond top
And no matter how I try to push it down
To make it like a shower cap
We're kind of poof up
So I said fuck it
And I just walking down second street here in San Francisco
Like a six foot three smurf
And I'm looking at him window
He's going like, man, I look like a ridiculous retard
I'm sorry
Nothing against retards
But it's just like, that's what you would call it
Total fucking idiot
Just pardon my French, but hey, it's football
And I notice that people don't even look at me
Or they look at me
Nothing, nothing, no surprise
But I do think I should invest in an umbrella
That might not be a bad idea
I'm in DSC listeners around the globe
This is Robert and Toronto
Post of the mobile movie podcast at mobilemovie.podshow.com
Who doesn't like Jeff Smith
I think his stuff is fantastic
I asked Jeff to do a jingle for the mobile movie podcast
We review movies right from our hot rod
Many in and around the streets of Toronto
Right after we've seen the movie
Jeff said, what do you like?
I said, I like movies
I like driving music
What can you do?
Just said, I've got just the idea for you
Here it is, the Jeff Smith jingle
For the mobile movie podcast
Again, mobile movie.podshow.com
Bring it on Jeff, you rock man
It's the best way to go
Have to remove it
And we're going mobile and everywhere
Go to flag out the highway
All the way down
I can bring it along
I say you there
We have to take it
Not for a mission
And the mission is making it more or less
Take it right
After the movie
Driving on over to the right
Holy crap, that's awesome
Jeff Smith, once again
Man, I love that
And while I heard that play and hold on a second
I was listening to that
And I'm like, oh man
I know what this is inspired on
I love Jeff Smith
He makes such catchy, hokey stuff
And always sounds like something else
But it isn't exactly the same
But that jingle sounded so much
Like one of my favorite songs of all time
I just got to break my own format once again
I'm sorry
You will never learn anything about music
If we don't actually
You know, crap, almost
Like I was so in tune with everything there
Is that not mute?
No, okay
It was just a long intro
Let me see if it's working
Do I have a plug in the right place here?
The hell was that?
Why is it so soft?
Oh, that's lame
That's working
Oh, man
Oh, I see, I see the problem, okay
If you have
It's really sucks
If you have your earbuds really jammed in
Tight then you already hurt
Let's listen to the piece of that Jeff
The Jeff Smith jingle again
Okay, now listen to this
This is what I want to do
Originally like five minutes ago
My friend Dan Hartman with the
And going to grow
You want to perform music
Come on, let me take you on a plane ride
The mountain is high
The valley is normal
And you are confused
But this way
So I can repeat
Give you a hand
And lead you into
The promise plans
Come on and take a free ride
Come on
All over the country
Same in the same
Nobody's waiting
This kind of game
We got a little dinner
It's time to be here
But you know all the answers
Let's know about it
Come on and take a free ride
Come on
All right
All right, it's enough of that
I love that song
I really really really miss Dan Hartman
Oh man, he was so awesome
Dan Hartman
You know, remember him from I can dream about you
And re-light my fire
And ah shit
I get on those Napster kicks man
And then you just you just can't help yourself
But look up
Artists and shit you can play
Because you can play as much as you want
Of course, it is easy for button to share that with you
Let me say instant replay
We are the young
I can dream about you free ride
Live it in America
He wrote for James Brown with another body of mine
Charlie Midnight
Keep the fire burning with a letter
Halloway
Cranky
And the loving your eyes
Unfortunately, Dan passed away
Of AIDS
I think in 1996
Maybe
Yeah
No, there was a little bit later than that
Anyway, thank god as music lives on
And if you would be so kind
Is to go purchase a Dan Hartman song
At the music
Music store of your choice
I would really appreciate it
Because
I believe that his estate
All proceeds from his from record sales
Go through his estate
And they go towards AIDS research
A speaking of buying stuff on iTunes
Hello
I'm just in the DSC
And I heard you mention
The drummer's the child thing
I was thinking
Will they count if people from different countries
By the actual album
Would it be better real?
Can we all buy from the US still without a US credit card?
I'm not sure
I just wonder how it would affect the child
If people were buying from different countries
Or how we could go about buying from the single countries
Are you not to say anything
Anyway, as recent you tag it
Now we're Wales investing
All right, thank you
All right, man, thanks
Yeah, that's he's referring to bum rush the charts
You can find more information about it
bum rush the charts.blogspot.com
And it's kind of a cool idea
We're going to show the power of podcasting and pod safe music
And as many more pieces
I can plop through my microphone
We're going to do that on March 22nd
And just a plethora of podcasters
And independent audio producers, I'm my dad
We'll be placing links
And playing
I guess I'll be playing this song
That song by Black Lab
And the links will be to the iTunes music store
What we're going to do is try and get the song
To number one
March 22nd
Very strategically chosen date
We don't believe there are any other releases
But we think it would be pretty interesting
If we could drive a song to number one
That that shows a pretty awesome power
So if you want to join that
I don't know where to
bum rush the charts.blogspot.com
Link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
So the question
Yes, you have a different iTunes music store
For each country
Do the same thing in your country
Let's see if we can do this by country
Maybe we'll see that Germany is
An example is really strong
And that Germany kicks ass
Doing that
I think the song is available on all music stores
I'll have to check on it
Not entirely sure
But it's going to be a lot of fun
So the rest of the day
Busy
And of course around 3 o'clock
I've got the big dip
The jet lag hits
But it was a day filled with beautiful women
For me
Which is always enjoyable
The lovely Natalie Delcante
She came to the...
We have two offices
And one we're using is a studio for texture
If you have not seen her show
Please check out textra.podshow.com
T-E-X-T-R-A
It's good show
I like what I like the most about
She'll sit there
And she writes everything herself
And she does all the research
But she also gives her own opinion
Which is nice
And I often find myself yelling
Back at the screen
I disagree
Anyway
So it's so frazzled and so busy
Didn't really have a chance to talk to her
But it's just nice
You know, smiling women around you
And Cali Lewis was from Dallas
Visiting Podshow HQ
And Cali, Cali looking so good
Let me tell you
You know how people look good on television
Or on video
And then you see them in real life
And it's kind of a disappointment
They're really short
Or the head's really big
Then a white has an enormous head
I'll let you know
So does Pat Say Jack
But anyway
When you see Cali
You know, you already
Love her when you see her on Geek Brief
But in real life, man
It's just that there's an energy
There's a life force that emanates from her
That is quite enchanting
And I had dinner with her
And with Neil and with Richard
And the best part about it is
We made Richard pay
If you're tired of all those uptight award shows
Then head on over to earmuffawards.com
And listen to the second annual
Frat Packure Muffawards
This is the award show for fans of movies
Like Caldiganites
The breakup
Or you mean to pre
Who will win the coveted awards for categories
Such as best sex scene
Best celebrity cameo
Or the cheese
A award
For dubious distinction
Featuring podcast personalities
From shows such as
Five Honey by Midnight
Podcast 411
Film Spotting
The amateur traveler
The office alliance
Big Barry
The metcast
That's what she said
And the Frat Pack tribute
The ceremony is broadcasting now at earmuffawards.com
I'm in
I love it
Earmuffawards.com
Great
Yeah, Oscars this weekend
I'm definitely going to watch
I'm excited about it
Because
Normally I wouldn't be able to watch that
Because it'd be on way too late
In the UK and then you see it the next day
And you already know who won everything
Because you know it's all over the radio and the newspapers
And you know
So I'm going to make my own little party here
My own little Oscars party
For sure
Hey, let me see
What else?
Oh, yeah
Let's talk
What should I talk?
Do you want to talk about my Wi-Fi?
Because I have some theories about this now
I had some problems with the
The condo is not small
Certainly not small
But it's not
It's not palatial
So the Wi-Fi router
Which has always been in the same place
Behind the
Behind the big devol
That's a French for couch
My devol
And all of a sudden
There's a whole bunch of spots
Within the living area
That it just won't connect
It won't even see the network
I see other networks
Really strong signals I might add
Which of course is probably part of the problem
I've tried everything
I've tried switching all the channels
There's a huge amount of configuration options
You can set in these
And these de-link
Wireless routers
I want them in bed
It works fine
And then the other weird problem
It'll connect to the network
But then it won't get signed
So for some reason now the DHCP
Doesn't seem to work
But that's also dependent on where you're standing
So
I'm fairly convinced that there's just so much
Wireless activity in this city
And maybe even in this building
And maybe because of the height
That there's just too many signals
And it's got completely food bar
And here's an interesting thing
You might want to try this
I'd love to hear
I'd love
I don't know if you have a lot of signals where you live
Continuously
It's almost like the wind is blowing the signals in
And you see all these names show up
And it's kind of kind of interesting
Even though it's very very frustrating
Not being able to connect right off the bat
And I have found by the way that if you let it sit long enough
Eventually it will connect
I don't understand what's going on
But let me just read off some of the names
Of these wireless access points
It's pretty interesting
We have two offices one I see here
Benbo 7
Barney
He's Ms. Magda
This is my favorite brown town
I wonder what that is
Winston
What kind of wireless networks are you seeing
Where you live
That's an audio comment I wouldn't mind having
In fact
Would you mind dialing it in?
Here's a reminder of our phone number
Us one two one six two five six three five seven
Your honor
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
Your honor
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work
And law here
He's jerseys
Oh yeah
Yo
What's up AC?
It's Jersey Todd
The official music college stuff
The shot shot
And one of the criticisms that I hear
About the positive music network
Is that people say
I don't know who this guy is
I don't know if I should play
Well that's not going to happen this week
Because somebody posted about five or six amazing
Amazing songs
His name is Jeff Malon at a Philadelphia
And well he also posted
His resume
Check this out
This is Jeff Malon by Jeff Malon on your football Friday
I think I'm tracks like they leave a bit in my added
I play guitar so fast
Just like I've got my civics
I give my songs away
Cause I steal songs like crazy
I have 5,000 friends in the STEM most ladies
I just shit
Shout out
I'm Jeff Malon on the King and I'm a bass cow
They're not telling me why
Cause I'm crazy
I'm a joke
It's not easy to watch
Stop
I'm in my scooter
Just to see if it will go forward
I'm up at 3am
And lines and chillin with my lead
I just shit
Shout out
I'm Jeff Malon on the King and I'm a bass cow
They're not telling me why
Cause I'm crazy
I'm a joke
It's not easy to watch
Stop
I'm a joke
I go to Target once a week and never get nothing
I bought a crackpot now, I never used my oven
I just shake it out
I'm kept mad
I'm the king and I'm the best
I'm the best
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Thank you again, Sir Jersey Todd, official musicologist of the Charlie for Jeff Malen, that is interesting guys from Philly, of course, makes sense, hey, the satellite window closed during that during that song, so we're all alone now
comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip
comic strip, comic strip, comic strip and comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comics strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic
me side or rocket that is dude. I don't think I ever talked about anyone having the right
to shoot down anything but okay I'm glad you agree with me.
Coming from Iran towards USA. Here is a quote I'm quoting.
Poland and Czech Republic are situated directly along the shortest line between Iran and the
United States. If Iran were to develop and fire an intercontinental missile at
America. If you're going to shoot a missile, it should be an intercontinental one because we're all
part of the jet set these days. The two countries would be ideal locations for heating the
missile in mid-flight and quote. So you see that USA, USA wants to build installations with
interceptor missiles, missiles intercepting in these two countries. However, Russia says that it is
wrong because this interceptor missiles could hit Russia also. So Adam, you as American
could you tell Russians to calm down Spakoynoski and to allow USA to defend itself. I defend.
Otherwise, if Russians will not calm down, then a new arms race is cooking and then you can
forget about sucked up beyond repair Fridays and get ready for the workware.
That's it. Oh, you know. Always a high positive note for the end of the week there from
comic strip blogger. Yeah, no, I agree. Hey Vladimir Putin, chill dude. Although I can totally
understand. I mean, remember when Russia put missiles in Cuba, was there a minor freak out in
the United States? Yeah, I think so. Oh boy, the world is a bit foward. Anyway, when you see that video
and I do think I do hope you take a look at it. From, was it from video leak or something like that?
I can't remember what it was from. Anyway, it's an embedded video. When you look at that, you know,
and just reverse the roll for a second. Because these are clearly very with it.
Some very attractive, by the way, young people. And so if they're here in, you know, all this crap
about what America wants to do to them, just reverse the roll for a second. You'd be sitting there
having a drink saying, fuck that shit. Man, oh man, oh man. Hey, anyone out there in Iran,
give me a call. Let's talk about shit. Okay. I want a second. Here's what we should do.
Where is it? Oh boy, I'm so tired. Here it is. If you're from Iran, this is the closest number I have to your location.
Please give me a call. Plus four four, two, oh seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three,
plus four, four, two, oh seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
I don't know, Jim, I'm using fused stuff. I've just got an invite this morning and I've just installed it.
Me, this is the future, this, this is definitely the future of television.
Oh, I haven't gotten the invite to the minute, but if you don't already have one, give us a certain,
if I do get one, I'll certainly send you a link about the help. This is fantastic.
Hi, man. You know, I do not have an invite for the beta. I did send off my email address to get one,
but I got no juice. I did see the interface briefly today on texture. Natalie Delcante has an
invite and she showed some of the interface. Looks really slick, man. Definitely. Would you mind sending
one to me? I'd appreciate it. And my prayers have indeed been answered. The news is official.
And of course, all the technology presses picking this up is what is the headline I read?
Oh, Google takes a swipe at Microsoft because they have the Google Premiere edition.
Yeah. That means for your own domain, you can get Gmail, multiple accounts, all the apps like
a docs, calendars, scheduling software, all as web service. Brilliant, brilliant, brilliant.
If the stock was not already, like 4,500 bucks, I'd buy more. So expensive.
50 bucks gives you, um, it doesn't say how many accounts you can create for that,
but you do get 10 gigabytes per account. Hey, finally, for only 50 bucks a year, fantastic. So Sunday,
before I get ready for the, for the Oscars, I'm going to have a Google Premiere edition
party for myself. I'm going to set up Curry.com with Google Premiere edition. And the reason why I
really have to take some time is because, you know, besides all these MX records and shit,
you got to set up. I have a lot of email accounts that, you know, like Patricia's, my sister,
you know, there's a lot of stuff that I have to make sure it works. This one guy, um, whose name is, I think,
Tom Curry. I think it's Tom. And, uh, geez, I've known this guy virtually for,
I'm going to say, since 1993, something like that when I got Curry.com. And, uh,
he, I remember sending him an email and he said, hey, you know, my name's Tom Curry. I would
really love to have Curry.com email address. And, uh, would you hook me up? Can you hook a brother up?
I said, yeah, absolutely. And, uh, so once, you know, once every couple of years will send me a note
and say, hey, man, is, is the server okay? Because I haven't been receiving anything and
a couple times something has been broken. Um, but, uh, I'm, I'm looking forward to putting all that
together. That's going to be cool. Very, very cool. All right. Let's see, Fubar Friday on the daily
source code continues. Uh, only one more, uh, one more, um, comment here and another kick-ass song.
So let's get ready for that weekend. Hello, Adam. It's Martin, aka GD from GD's by size bonus.
As you know, I do a music podcast for five days a week. And I'd like to keep my finger on the
pulse of what's happening in the music scene. One of the bands that really is ripping up the
polysphere of the moment, the band called Bella Donna. Now, they've done great things on my space,
um, they have a blog on there, molest every day. They always communicate with the fans. Like I said,
they're on the PLM as well. They're very crafty on there. They put songs up there and they'll even
they're a couple of months taking down, put some fresh ones up. Now, the good news is they're
coincidentally UK. Now, come all the way from Italy to the UK on March the 5th.
If we down in Camden at the Underworld, the legendary Underworld, uh, let's see, such big
names as Radiohead Smashing Pumpkins, placebo, sound garden, crambles, food fighter,
squid and stone age, out the list just goes on and on. They've been invited over by a US
rock band hydrogen to play this date as special guests. Now then, I've been looking down
at Bella Donna on the PLN to see who's played them and you know something there's one
name missing. Yours, so come on Adam, get your finger out and play some Bella Donna,
and also just the side thing, think B.T. Potio, pay for me to go and see them. Okay, take care, Adam.
This is sound of Bella Donna, and so he called Black Swan.
I'll let you for my departure, record for my broken dreams. I will survive.
That's why I owe you all the soul of the ladies. That's why I owe you all the spirit of
play. Free will be so much so high. That's why I owe you all the right.
It's like your fuzz and whirling victim. There's a feather lamp of God.
Oh my God, and none. All the spectacles of my reaction. My revenge was soon enough for
my war return. That's all. We're tough to still fight. That's all.
Oh my God, I'll survive. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna hold somebody. That's all.
Oh my God, I'm gonna die.
That's all. I owe you all the soul of the ladies. That's all.
Free will be so much I have no idea how I miss that one. Bella Donna Black Swan
at the end of another week of the Charlie it's Friday.
You know, I had this whole final thought of the week thing. I'll set up and then
I'm just in a whack-down mood today, man. I haven't gotten my fix of old school music. I must be
something like that. I was just thinking, what is my final thought of the week?
I was gonna say something really philosophical, but I'm an old guy now.
Remember when you when your parents turn 40 and you were like crap, my parents are old. Okay,
so now I'm 40, 40, 42 actually. And I guess that since I was surrounded by women today,
I just want to say that you can find something beautiful in every single woman in the world.
Aren't women fantastic creatures? I mean, and it's, and it's not about how they, you know,
it's not if someone's pretty or ugly or that's not what I'm talking about. There's just something
about the creature that is woman that fascinates me. And I just want to dedicate today's
football Friday to all the women in the world. Oh, you know, that reminds me of another song,
a second. I'm so out of control. Hold on a second. So, as I was doing that,
that final thought of the week. Yeah, baby. Oh, I'd like to have a good one.
And I love all the paintings of the world.
And my name is Ralph, now I like a woman who loves her freedom. And I like a woman who can hold her on.
And if you feel that description being, come with me. I know all the lyrics of this song.
Take my hand. Come with me, baby. To love, man.
Let me show you how sweet it could be.
She and I that will me. I want you to love, throw it on. Come with, come with, come with, throw it on.
Aquarius or Libra, Libra?
And my name is Charles. Hey, Charles.
Now I like a woman that's quiet. A woman who carries a stuff like Miss Universe. Miss Universe.
And let me show you how sweet it could be. She and I that will me.
I want you to love, throw it on. All that, a boy band should show cover the song.
Interhead, I guarantee it.
Okay, I'll leave.
My name is Paul. Paul's Paul. I said, I like all the women of the world. That's right, Paul. I'm with you, my brother.
If you have a stand where I'm saying, I'll taste it.
Here I come.
Okay, let's do the chorus one more time.
Cancer. And my name is Larry. Yeah. And I like a woman that loves everything.
And everybody in everybody. Yeah, Larry. And you know what, ladies, if you feel that this is you,
then this was what I want you to do.
Yeah.
Take my hand. Let me take you to the land.
All right, I'm not officially sick of myself singing.
Did you fast forward that bit? I'm sorry. I don't blame you. All right, everybody. That's it.
That's the final thought of the week. And that's it for the Daily Source Code for this week.
Of course, I'm going to be here throughout the weekend. And I shall also be here up until
Thursday. Yeah, Thursday of next week. And then we go back to the Currie Manor, which will be nice again,
because I got to love the lady there as well. So let me, what the hell was that?
Man, someone in Europe is up really, really early.
Let me just get this. I want to do it right.
Okay, here we go. Thank you, PD Love, by the way, for all the fantastic openings.
Thank you, Brian. No, for what I'm about to say.
DailySortsco.com for all the links for songs and other things mentioned at the show notes for today's show.
Adam at podshow.com. There's the signature lighter click until next time.
May your heart have wings and may all its flights be full bar.
The best and the brightest served of daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery, podshow and
lightweight.