As the world anxiously awaits, the CSD files prepare yourself for.
Food bar Friday, food bar Friday, it's food bar Friday.
Demi Craig, I was trying to do the radio voice you ruined it.
But it's food bar Friday, it's the DSC 543, Qosm Jersey Todd, Qosm Jeff Smith, AC hit the button.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding, it's a matter of theory.
One hit, bring me out of the planet.
There's a lot of time.
Hell oh, hello, halo, halo, that a roaring wing has been spitting the club.
Hell oh it all.
Hell oh, yellow.
Hell oh, hey nooo, it all.
Hell, it all, hey nooo.
Deep Ive untie quality.
Deary Queen Community.
And used butt circuit-fiat-deak-faj-stay-alop.
Tamara Skull carries his float deep, though.
Cloudnuts fill it away throw awaylag.
Time is back my life to wreck down a dagegen-bound 10, man.
Complete the list and start again
The greatest guy is a blue-er when I'm on my way
Ooh, just a black, black-dick taxi cap for you
Ooh, just a black, black, black, black
I shot his horns and walked the cross, I was around modern
Makes it up and safety end, do not trust the night, it's creaming
Pull you up to you down again, like the lay, you life decay
Wouldn't have any other way, yellow beige and bow tip
And a pleat the list and start again
The greatest guy is a blue-er when I'm on my way
Ooh, just a black, black dick, taxi cab new
Ooh, come back, taxi cab, quick, let's back for you
Ooh, shoot him back, you have what gotta do
Ooh, just a black, galactic taxi cab from you
Yeah, hey, yellow page and fountain pen
Complete the list and start again
The greatest guys of blue are when I'm on my way
Ooh, just a black, galactic taxi cab from you
Ooh, come back, taxi cab, quick, let's back for you
Ooh, shoot him back, you have what gotta do
Ooh, just a black, galactic taxi cab from you
Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Come in back, come in back, maybe a half, quick, let's back for you
Nothing like grabbing a black, galactic taxi cab on a super bright morning
Ooh, just a black, galactic taxi cab from you
Alex Brummel, from Jersey, of course, thank you, sir, Jersey Todd, for turning me on to him
Link links to Alex Brummel's page at dailysourcecode.com in the show notes
Coming to you from the curry manner, it is a daily source code episode five
Was it five or five already, is that, is that we're up to?
Five, five, four, oh man, what are we up to now?
Five, four, three, what are we here in the background?
Everything's completely food bar, okay, do you hear that?
Here's something really weird going on
Well, that makes it par for the course because
The more actually last night started off completely food bar
I told you I was feeling this cold coming on
Both Patricia and I are pretty sick
And looked at each other this morning and said, well, you know, it's, yeah, it's flyable
But I feel like shit, I'm just not gonna be comfortable doing anything today
And so I, I've postponed everything
Hoping to go tomorrow, of course, whether and body fluids and temperatures premiering
And so, you know, I might have gone into London to visit comic strip blogger
Because he did fly in today, he texted me
But I'm just not feeling well, I'm really sorry
And in fact, I had my finger on the button to roll out a best of Charlie
Still have a couple of best of Charlie's sitting in the vault
And I was like, okay, I'm just gonna do an intro
And then I'll just roll out the best of Charlie
And then I'll go back to bed or whatever, just chill out, lay down
You know, when both mommy and daddy are sick
And you've got the teenager walking around, you know, there's a lot to do
So we're taking turns doing shit
And then I started to hear all the fantastic things that we're sending
Because, you know, I have to clear out my Gmail inbox every single morning
Oh, yeah, I've been doing this for over a year now
You know, I have one of those secret four gigabyte accounts
I've been, you know, deleting attachments for at least 14, 15 months
This will, I would gladly pay to have real unlimited storage
It's always funny when you enter empty out your Gmail trash
And you delete the things forever in there
Ugh, full of your coffee
There's always a little note that says
Your trash is no empty, but who needs to delete things
When you have unlimited storage, I'm like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Who's world you live in in Google?
Alright, it's through bar Friday
So, properly titled today
I am fucked up beyond all repair
Hey Adam, it's the divas from TheDivaCast.com
Happy Valentine's Day
The milk cast is what I call that
I like it though, I listen to TheDivaCast
You got to kind of listen through some of the clutter of what it's interesting
It's like sex in the city, only without the city, without the sex
But you know, a lot of the issues are there
And it's interesting to get to know a little bit more about
The female side of the species
Lots of people calling in to the voicemail line
Using it for different reasons
Apparently also to contact me directly
Oh yeah
In the new edition of that same gossip rag in the Netherlands
They now have pictures of the curry manner
Apparently they stood outside with a telephoto lens
In the woods across the way
It took pictures of us
I can't remember the stories like, you know, while they may be
They may be wanted and on the run or on the lamb
He's on the lamb
But look at this nice, nice crib they got
That was basically the story
That the first thing Patricia and I said, are the pictures any good?
Yeah, pictures are great
I haven't seen it, but if you're in Holland
But don't buy it, just go buy the magazine rack
Take a look at the pictures and then just leave it there
And crumple the edges a little bit, will you?
So anyway, so I'm getting personal phone calls now on the voicemail line
Which actually it's time to, I think it's time to play the US voicemail number again
We're here for the 37
Man, that thing's irritating, if you're not feeling well
Okay, this is a message in Dutch from a production company
And I'm going to play it for even though it's in Dutch
Because you're going to recognize those of you in the UK
Well, definitely recognize a few words
It's one of these typical
We call them producer, I'll just call it production pussy
That doesn't sound right, does it
You know, one of these associate producers
who's job it is is to go find people to be on shows and so they call celebrities and they're always
perky and they have the minute you pick up the phone and they start talking you know exactly
what kind of beast is on the other line. So listen as a she invites me to a show
and see if you UK folks if you can pick up the title of the show.
Yeah okay then she gives that her phone number okay so you heard the voice right? The name of the program she's invited
me to participate in is a program called Dragon's Den. I have very successful format in the UK
so the시는c
is a program called Dragons Den.
A very successful format in the UK.
I think the new season premiered just the other night.
I have it on the on the skybox and we watched it.
And essentially, it's five wealthy entrepreneurs
success people who are investors.
And they sit on a panel and people come in and pitch ideas.
I mean, it's kind of an old, it's not a new format.
There are lots of derivatives of the format.
But it's these people are interesting to start off with.
And they do a lot of good screening on the ideas.
And so essentially, they're asking me to do the Dutch version
of the show and be one of the investors.
Which I find a very, very interesting question
because of all people, why come to me, I have not
been successful with my adventures in the Netherlands.
And I, of course, blame it on all the rules the Netherlands has.
You can't be successful.
The country is not set up to be successful.
It's set up to be a fantastic tax haven if you make money
on royalties of creative works.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
But if you want to be an entrepreneur, no.
So be interesting to see how the program goes.
So I said, no, I'm beside, I got no time to do that shit
between here and the condo.
But it was flattered flattering.
Flattered, Michael Flattery wasn't flattering to hear it.
Oh, please, someone save me.
Save me.
So Jersey Todd, hey, 10 to rub.
But I got to be honest, last week after my parents
on food were Friday, I really wasn't feeling
a love like I usually do.
So I'm thinking and thinking, what exactly do I need
to make my appearances more special on the Fubar Friday
edition?
And then it came to me.
Actually, it came to me in an email from Jeremy Row.
Check this out.
I need the new theme song.
I'd like to make a motion to work this further around,
and then the orange on top to turn its roll around.
It's a football Friday, with Jesse Todd on the Charlie.
Ah, that's exactly what I needed, a new theme song from Jeremy Row.
Awesome, dude.
Listen, it's been a very, very busy week here as your official
musical.
Yeah, it's not about all the glory dude.
It's about doing the hard work that comes with the office.
And I've been taking all these emails, taking all these phone calls, all about your musical
selection for this week.
And I think that really nobody's summed it up better than Paul Durham from Black
Lab.
Check this out.
Hey Adam, it's Paul Durham from Black Lab.
So if Todd is the official musicologist, then I'm claiming the title of
official rock and rollologist of the Daily Source Code.
I got to say I took your playing the Beatles as a cry for help, a kind of desperate plea
for new music.
And I'm here to help.
We have a brand new record called Passion Leaves of Trace, 12 new songs to keep
curry manner rocking for another year.
Valentine's Day is right around the corner, but there's no place for ballots on
football, Friday.
Here's an evil little tune off our new album called Broken Heart.
Check out the new album on iTunes and Blacklabworld.com.
And of course, you're a pod safe music network.
Thank you Adam.
She looks clear with a broken heart.
She looks an easy mark.
I hate to be rough.
I like her so much.
I don't know where to start.
She looks clear with her eyes red.
But I just don't know where to dress.
I don't think where she walks.
And the way the shit talks, no matter what she says.
Then you know I know my shit is no one's feeling you.
Then you know I know my shit is no one else ever will do.
Then she knows I need it.
But I've had enough of it all she's got.
With a broken heart.
I don't know where to start.
But I just don't know where to start.
And I just just don't know where to start.
And I just don't know where to start.
But I just don't know where to start.
Broken heart!
She's the best.
She's my sister, my only sister.
She shows me a good son.
I show her my worst son.
And you know I know my share is no one's feeling you.
And you know I know my share is no one else I will tell you.
Yes, you know I need it.
I've had enough for now.
But I see nothing else in the sky of a broken heart.
Black Lab.
Just thinking about how interesting all that.
That's a real social network for you right there.
I've got Jersey Todd who I've never met in my life,
only on email and through the...
His contribution as the official musicologist of the Charlie of the Friday,
Fubar Friday.
I met Paul, but only briefly when he was at the office.
They did that Black Lab, did that acoustic set for us on a Fubar Friday.
So he sent a comment to Todd.
And then Todd puts it together, send us to me.
And then I'm playing it.
And there's a lot of use out there listening to the Charlie.
It's interesting when there's really just two types of movements in music.
Isn't there?
If you look at the whole iTunes,
big four record company DRM debate.
And then what we're doing?
You know, and look, you can't just be a musician and have a record company go out and sit
and sit around and have the record company do everything for you.
Because it just doesn't work that way anymore.
You've got to move it.
You've got to make it happen, baby.
You've got to press the flash.
Think of pressing the flash.
Still plenty of time.
I'm going to keep the submissions open.
Plenty of time for you to send in your preference.
Whether you're a folder or a scruncher.
I'm testing out some new software.
It's pretty cool.
I posted a pie chart of the Daily Source Code audience.
Bathroom preference makeup.
Folder or scruncher at dailysourcecode.com as well as in curry.com.
It does work.
I don't know what we mean.
The software is great, but it would only really be cool for pod show.
I think if it were server based.
You could just set up a number.
So anyway, if you want to, if you want to participate.
The number just put it near mobile phone right now.
You're mobile plus four four seven eight one four three three eight five nine zero.
It will cost you whatever an international SMS text message cost.
And if you want to check that number again, of course, you can find it in the show notes at
dailysourcecode.com.
Oh, you're something else I wanted to say about.
So it's just, you know, just isn't with music, a whole new different approach has to be taken with the marketing and the packaging.
It's the same with new shows.
You know, we've got a couple of new shows, new episodes coming out with all new shows.
You can't just put it on the channel.
And because you have 24 as a lead in or American idol or whatever that you're guaranteed to get audience.
You know, it's like a tree in a forest.
So I got to help promote some stuff.
Marie Claire dot pod show dot com.
This is awesome.
I wasn't a big fan of episode three.
Now, this is it's called the mast head.
And it's a reality based episodic show around the making of the magazine.
Marie Claire, which is, you know, guys, you're not going to give a shit.
Okay, don't even go look.
But girls, let me tell you.
I've made a study of this.
I live with fashion divas.
They've been all around me.
And this type of show, I consider to be female pornography.
It's just porn.
The money shots?
I know exactly what they have to be.
You know it, too.
You know what you'd like.
Look at that when it comes to fashion and style.
And that make believe world.
And the world of devil wears product.
Well, we've got an, I don't know if it's up yet.
I think it is episode number four, which was shot, of course, at Marie Claire,
but also around the photo shoot they did at the United Nations.
First time a fashion photo shoot is over there.
You've got to see this show.
It's like eight or ten minutes long.
And I think you will enjoy it because again, it really is just pure porn.
porn for women.
Adam Curry proud to be a pornographer.
Our posh people big smile.
God, they got shit.
It's a fine question.
Yes, it is.
Our posh people pigs.
Alright, whether I'm football or not, we got to wind up the week with, uh,
with at least one more look at, uh, our quest for the answer.
Our posh people potty pigs.
Well, there's some questions about some of the findings that our survey has, uh, delivered.
Our hire.
David's first calling.
How you doing?
Good.
And just listening to, I think it's five, three, nine.
We have a gentleman's talking about the movement in Germany,
set to the team club.
Um, I want to know.
How about hell?
To sitting.
And they get different to whether the pipes are right and right.
Yeah, that's a very good question.
It's, and by the way, I've been corrected by, uh, my many German listeners.
It's, it's in,
Pinklyn with a pee for pinkle.
It's in,
Pinklyn.
Pinklyn while sitting down.
Uh, I think the point of that, uh, of, you know, that whole story about the apartment building
that torn down and, uh, apartments that had been used by men.
They had to basically remove all this corroded piping.
I think it's because it goes down the outside.
The outside of the pipe and, you know, or the outside of the bowl,
it drips down.
It's just, it's a mess.
It really is.
And it's, you know, you don't have to be a, a bad aim.
You know, if you're tall like me,
you're just basically creating velocity that got to go somewhere.
And it is quite disgusting for other people living in the house with you.
So, I've, uh, I still find, you know, I catch myself once in a while thinking,
you know, they'll just be, I'll just be really quick.
I'll be really fast.
I won't sit down, but really, it makes no difference
whether you sit down or whether you stand,
particularly with the buttonfly jeans.
It's kind of like a lot of bullshit to me. I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
And further to the, uh, post people, post Pete.
Um, I don't know about many post places, but, uh,
with my girlfriend and her kids, we visit terms,
places for McDonalds and, uh,
Hungry Jacks. Sorry to be very keen.
Oh, wait a minute.
Burger King is hungry jacks down on it.
That's interesting.
Why not just Burger King?
It's like a, like a Paul fiction thing.
The Royale with cheese.
You know what, I've already listened to this,
and he's just going to go into this whole thing about more,
like, tampon stories.
And can I just say something as a species, as a human race?
So far from coast to coast around this blue marble,
the glow we call Mother Earth.
We are all potty pigs.
We're fucking disgusting.
And it is, and Demic to our youth because we know,
we know that someone is going to clean that shit up,
so finally we don't have to.
I'd like to make a solemn vow here that I'm going to, uh,
not be a potty pig and certainly not a posh one.
And I'd like all of you Charlie listeners to join in this movement.
And by the way, if you see something nasty, pick it up.
It's okay, clean it up, pick it up.
You can always wash your hands.
And maybe just maybe.
We'll start something that will be better for all of mine can.
Lounge, down tempo, chill out time.
Electronic and acoustic music from all over the world.
Space music.nl presents the fresh air series.
Fly at the Space Music Podcast.
Right on, Space Music Podcast.
Uh, like that.
Hey, folks on serious stars, uh,
102 great lineup for you, uh,
this evening on the, on the stars channel.
If you want to hear the rest of this podcast go to daily source code.com.
And for those of you still hanging around,
because you downloaded like a normal human being.
And you're in the UK, give us a call, mate.
And it's our friend Charles the Drunken Londoner.
No long, you know, he needs a jingle.
Yeah, no longer drunk, I fear.
Hello, Adam.
It's Charles your Hangout the Londoner.
First of all, I want to apologize for, uh,
that Drunken message.
Um, I really need some apologizing is that, um,
I rambled on and on and on.
And that was just all thing to do.
To be honest, I don't actually recall leaving that message.
And it was a bit of a shock listening to.
I think it's five, first and nine I was listening to.
That you see.
Doing good work here, doing good social services.
It's, it's interesting when you hear yourself drunk isn't a Charles.
Ah, my friend.
If you can't even remember calling in maybe it's time to lighten up
just a little bit on the paints.
And, uh, you played that comment.
Uh, I also want to apologize for Malcolm and, uh,
Abu Dhabi.
My friend, you rock, you have me best voice.
And, um, I love the fact that you think about what you're going to say before you
record your comment.
Um, and phone them in.
And that must be really appreciated by Adam and it certainly appreciated
to, uh, by us, the listeners.
Now, I wanted to now go on to, uh, the, um, posh people for what he's
do does.
Um, I once worked for a large media company.
They had a problem that was excluded to the latest toilets.
And, uh, all the women were taken into a meeting.
And, um, we're given a, a talking to, and it continues for a little while
and then, and then it stopped shortly after someone left the company,
which I, I think was probably just a set up to be honest.
You know, it's a quite a good room.
And it's something you don't look like, leave the company.
Then you stop doing the thing that you've been doing.
Anyway, that's just my mind.
What's like your idea was, uh, and me rambling on again.
Um, oh, the other thing, they knew that it was a woman that was doing this because, uh,
uh, another man speaking, you know what?
I'm not going to go there.
Anyway, because I was, what a lovely snow day we've had today.
Yeah, I was there.
This is a junior.
You know, yeah, bye.
All right, Charles.
Amen.
You sound like a human almost when you're not drunk.
Just something to consider.
I'm just saying, you know what I mean?
Uh, okay.
Should we close that topic?
I'm kind of done with it.
I do want us all to, to practice sanitary bathroom habits.
So that will be nice.
Grammys coming up this weekend that, of course, pod shows paying attention to it.
It's not life.
It's not backstage.
And it's so not LA.
It's Carolina and Michael.
Dishon, the Grammys.
Get the real dish on who's wearing who, who is doing who,
and who's going to be wearing the winning and losing shoes.
Who's doing the dishes at this year's Grammy Awards?
It's Carolina and Michael.
Dishon, the Grammys.
And it's only a dish of the Grammys dot hot show with hot cow.
That's Michael Butler.
I'm very own rock and roll geek.
And we have Carolina who is the receptionist at Pod Show.
And I got to tell you, I've heard, I've heard these episodes.
You're going to love it.
Why not down the week?
That means one more update on our old girl.
Sing along if you're sick, okay?
More email coming in from the mistress of the project.
Folders.
With nice, splendid flavor blends.
Eh, what a comment.
Hey, how come no one's called me and it's tried those two together, huh?
Please.
Barbara the Palo Alto podcaster who is now managing the group at free Trinity,
the Google Group for free Trinity.
You can find the link to that in the show notes at DennySourceco.com.
It's starting to collect some interesting statistics and very interesting
invitations for Trinity to stop by.
And I'll try to see Tim from Eugene Oregon, not a podcast or a
biodieselike expert.
However, I could likely range any or all of the following.
I meet up with some people from the Eugene BioCare share.
Interesting.
Or meeting interview or whatever people from sequential biofuels.
They opened up the Pacific Northwest First Commercial Biofuel Station.
Nice.
Texas.
We have Charlie in Texas who's running biodiesel in his kaboda
tractor.
The horse is love it.
Is that a Japanese tractor?
They're pretty good.
A Christian daily, of course, from Houston.
Love to drive a leg through the Lone Star State.
This video, of course, is a professional video montage artist.
Doug Moore from Georgia, helped Trinity across North Georgia.
Could drive anywhere from North Georgia mountains and metroid land on
Athens.
Just a realtor.
Good old Doug.
Mike from Portland, my wife and I do a podcast.
The Portland Oregon love to take our kids for a ride in the car that runs in French,
Fryoil.
There's a biodiesel station down the street for my office, which needs to fill up.
Interesting.
Just Smith, of course, from Nashville, Tennessee is a biofuel place in
Murphy'sboro, town just outside Nashville.
Kevin Reeves pops in.
Hey, you don't want my blind ass drive and Trinity around town, but
damn it.
I'd love to take a ride.
Let Jeff Smith are evil at the wheel.
Fuck no, man.
I think we put Kevin Reeves behind the wheel.
I'll be funny.
You're definitely on the map.
I'll be awesome.
Michael Pilly and Baker's Field California.
Jack of all trades when it comes to technology.
I'm available as a podcaster.
I produce a weekly NASCAR podcast, local DJ here in town.
Videographer mapping, making local contacts to events.
Video of refueling station in San Diego.
Tell you, it's all over the place.
Jack Elias is a friend of the Charlie from Washington.
There's a march on the Pentagon to end the war.
March 17th since Patrick's day, drink green beer and end the war.
It'd be great if Trinity could be there then.
March 17th.
I don't know if we can make it.
We don't even have a start date yet, but.
And the list just goes on and on and on.
It's fascinating.
So if you want to join up and if you want to give Trinity a
world.
As you can see, I mean, you don't have to be able to have vision.
You can participate in the project.
Let me see, was anything else I had to do.
Okay, so.
All right, so Barbara's going to do a push pin version of this, I guess.
Excellent.
Free Trinity.
Win viable prizes.
Trinity.
The greater central luxury.
Let the bio diesel set your brain.
Trinity.
Free Trinity.
Save the world.
Win valuable prizes.
Trinity.
Twice a long, long time ago, my friends.
When little podcasters used to climb, well, you don't come climb up on my knee right now.
And would ask me questions about how to do their show.
Yeah, how to manage data and climb some campuses going.
I'm going to inspiring podcasters.
And of course, I use the podshow plus page.
And I get all these great stats and numbers.
My question is simple.
How do I know if my podcasters success?
I mean, I talked to other podcasters, and they're all tightly-picked.
Like the number of uploads and downloads is some secret formula or top secret information.
So I wanted to want to tell them my stats.
I like that my stats.
Do they sit around and laugh?
That means if you haven't had so many downloads or are they going to laugh?
That's really good.
That's considered success.
Hope you can give me some insight on that.
That's it.
Thanks very much.
Folder with a slight twist.
Alright.
Well, okay.
So I appreciate you asking the question.
I would say for a show.
The number you're looking for is at least two.
Because you probably download your own show just to check it out and maybe listen to it again.
And if at least one other person is listening, that's success.
I got to tell you, I do not look at my stats.
Once a month at the roll over period more or less, I want to see if I went up.
And I have to say that's pretty much been a 30% increase month over month.
Since, well, I mean, the early days, the increases were much larger.
Certainly for the past six months.
It's been a 30% month over month increase.
It's all look at that.
But I don't even look at the absolute number.
It's big though.
And it doesn't matter because I still feel like I'm talking to the same 20 people for some reason.
It's really funny that way.
And maybe it's only the people who contribute to the show.
And that doesn't, you know, that's fine because I know that there's a lot more people listening that are contributing to the show.
But I know that they're enjoying it in their own way.
And they don't have to contribute.
That's not a problem.
And maybe one day they will, which is another part of the magic of it all.
But really, it feels like, you know, just the people who call in, then I'm just talking to you guys.
And that's just the way that's the way I do my show.
You know, if you do a PW event like production.
You know, it's, it's much more of storytelling and less of an ongoing dialogue with the audience.
You know, that may be different.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
I find it very hard to say.
But yeah, for me, the fulfillment does not come from how high the number is.
It just comes from the loop, the immediate feedback loop.
So again, if at least one other person is listening.
And if that person is actually or watching.
And if that person is is feeding back to you even with comments.
That's the justice valid is sending in an audio comment or dialing the voice mail line or sending in an SMS text message,
whether you're a folder or scruncher.
Yeah, it's, it's all, it's all good.
That's my feeling.
Now, of course, when it comes to commercializing podcasting,
Well, then you have to have a certain audience.
But even though, even though, you know, we're finding that.
There are sponsors who are understanding advertisers who are understanding the value of this exact link that I'm talking about.
And that, you know, you shouldn't be buying based upon an absolute number of people hearing a commercial.
In the hopes that something will stick.
And as a part of an overall strategy and overall media buying plan that, you know,
you'll, the message will hate you at least a couple of times until you remember it.
I saw this last night with the, with the mastide with Marie Claire, because I show Patricia this stuff, you know,
and I say, huh, I got some more porn.
And let's take a look at it.
And there's some clever advertising in that.
And product placement, I got to tell you right up front.
And it was so funny because at one point, one of the stylists for this photo shoot is a,
a steaming down address and saying, you know, we have to bring this stuff back.
So we want to make sure that it's absolutely flawless that the girls don't mess it up.
We make sure they wear deodorant so they're not sweating in it, especially not deodorant that has white marks that, you know,
this sounds like a logical story.
And she shows a, a, a, a swath deodorant swath is one of the, one of the sponsors of the show.
And it's just, and she actually, she just picks it up.
It's there.
I mean, I don't know if it was placed there or not, doesn't matter.
And I saw Patricia lean into the screen.
And I said, what are you doing?
And she said, well, I'm trying to, I'm trying to see which one she was recommending.
I thought that was really interesting.
And then right after right after that segment, there's a short, a swath commercial.
And she said, oh, okay, now I know what it is.
And I was like, wow, she wasn't offended by it.
She was actually interested in it.
It gave her porn and information at the same time.
But with the hell that I get off talking about this about who cares?
Anyway, uh, fuck it, have fun.
That's what it's all about.
Hey, hi, you doing everybody?
It is Marcus couch from the scene scene and pod show music rewind.
You can find me at Marcus couch. podshow.com.
But, you know, this weekend, you can find me moving into my couch condo, the sea side villa.
And Laguna Beach, California, I've got a lot of boxes to move.
And I'm going to need some superhero strength.
Here's powder with Sonic Machina.
Higher than high, high, high, high, high.
Forever, forever.
And like a diamond in the sky.
I need my bright light.
And I'm super sweet.
And I'm super strong.
And I'm super cute.
I'm everything in my heart.
I'm the type of shit you know about me.
And I'm the type of shit you know about me.
With your friends in the street, all you know about me.
I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it
I don't feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I want it out to be so true, I feel it,
I don't do, I don't support you
I am where you are
I don't support you
Darling, is that perfect for a football or Friday or what?
Marcus Kai So çok
Thank you very much for powder
heroes. And that concludes our podcast week here at the Daily Source Code in Adam's
attic at the Corey Manor on the west side of G-town in the affluence Sourbove
Surrey. Okay apologies to the cast blaster Mike. So I hope to see you tomorrow.
Buddy. And everybody, thanks for contributing. Thanks for helping me get through the
show. I'm going to see if I can help Patricia make some of that chicken soup with
ginger because man who I need it. DailySourceCode.com, Adam at podshow.com.
Be footballer.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.