Ladies and gentlemen, I present Padshal's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Roses are ready. My sweater is beige. For your domain name needs, you should go to this page. GoDaddy.com.
Hey everybody, how you doing? It's episode 524 of the Daily Source Code. From almost empty, you can hear it.
Can you just hear the echo? Oh wait a minute, that's my mixer board. Yeah, all that's left. Actually, the Shandeliers are even gone at this point.
All the boxes are gone. It is the big move of 2007, we're moving from Cottage A to Cottage B on the other side of town, the other side of the tracks.
It's been nice, I've been going through all, it's so hard doing this. You find stuff and it takes you on an instantaneous trip down memory lane, pictures, recordings, of course.
You know, I packed away my archive of audio and video stuff. I actually have seven boxes of mini DV tapes, all 60 minutes in length. So, there's probably several hundred.
Probably like 200 hours of video from our reality show, Adam's family. I uncovered those, man. That's gonna be great to look at one day.
And tomorrow, the podcast console actually will be dismantled. There's good news because it appears that the big green thing, the ugly green chair that we can actually dismantle that and we'll be able to get it up into the third floor.
My domain in the new Cottage shows a lot going on here. Of course, there's a lot going on around the world and Cali Lewis is pretty busy yourself.
Adam, it's Cali from Geek Brief TV. As you know, this week is C. Yes, the biggest consumer electronics show. So, if anyone's interested in gadgets, I just wanted to let everybody know we're putting out two to three shows a day.
It's gonna be fun.
Is she not Cali, are you not doing anything at Mac world? That's what a difficult choice that must have been for her, man.
I know she's such a major Mac head to not to not go to Mac Mac and must have been very, very hard. Maybe she will be doing some stuff there.
I'll look forward to updates from CES at GeekBreef.tv or GeekBreef.GeekBreefTV.podshow.com.
This morning, the BBC aired my interview about what they call user-generated content in regards to news reporting and the Saddam Hussein video, which I posted about before the new year.
And it was, and that's kind of cool. You know, I'd promise myself that I was going to be posting more of my weblog and immediately I strike. I get a hit.
And I was able to explain that in a little bit more detail in the interview. I put a link to the interview on Curry.com.
And of course, I'll put a link to that interview in today's show notes as well.
A reminder that the Marie Claire show, the mast head, has launched.
It's very much the Delaware's product. Only it's, well, it's real. And it's about a real magazine. It's about real fashion. It's a part of our forthcoming fashion channel, which will be launching very soon.
You can find it Marie Claire.podshow.com. I think it's also the masthead.podshow.com is where the actual show lives.
So that's kind of just a quick update for me for today.
I'll be able to do a show, or at least the best of Charlie every single day, because it's funny how after you do a week or the best of Charlie's and after several weeks of asking for them. Now all of a sudden, all these people are saying, hey, can I still fit one in?
So we might even have to run through the weekend to fit them all in, but Julian Smith and over your head will do one.
There's only a couple more to go for this week. And then, of course, next week will be a little bit sporadic because I have to travel a San Francisco.
I will have the the broadband dog dongle adapter from from vote of phone, although it's been sitting at the post office for two days. I keep calling for redelivery. I get an answering machine.
And you're supposed to give your your name, your address and your item number and they just haven't redeliberted it yet. So I haven't been able to test it.
And otherwise, everything else is fine. So I want to thank you all so much for attending the notes of encouragement. Those of you who know what a big move is like. It is the big move of 2007 rolling up best of Charlie's.
Partially brought to you by Stomp the yard brand new movie, which is coming out on the 12th of January to find out more about it. Go to stompthepodcast.com.
Tony Costas will tell you all about that as a podcast. You can subscribe to multiple episodes, in fact.
And also brought to you by Splenda and by GoDaddy. Use check out code dsc three for an excellent discount on any domain name that you buy at godaddy.com.
And my love my true cyber love. Angie B delivered a best of Charlie for me to play for you today. I'm so happy. It has a subtitle. Adam loves the ladies. Oh, yes, I do baby.
Get ready for another best of Charlie edition of the daily source code with your guest hostess Angie B.
Now we all know that Adam loves ladies and ladies of Adam. So for his listening pleasure, I thought it compiles some of my favorite female front and songs that he's played on the DSC of the past four or five months.
Moving could be so stressful. I'm sure he's ready for a little downtime right about now. Let's hope this does the trick.
And welcome watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine.
Oh, don't worry. I've made a way and got my life inside, waiting for the moment when it will look longer high.
This deep inside me is a spark and when I feel this time, I will release it from the heart. Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine.
Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine. I am everything and I am nothing. I am yours and you are mine.
I am everything and I am everything and I am everything and I am everything and I am everything and I am everything and I am everything and I am everything and I am everything.
Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine.
This deep inside me is a spark and when I feel this time, I will release it from the heart.
Just stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine.
Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine.
Stand back and watch me shine. Stand back and watch me shine.
I'm so wish I could say it was pot safe, but we're not quite there yet.
This is a song that's been stuck in my head for the past couple of weeks, because it's
the theme tune to In the Attic, that's the show we have going on now with the P-Tounsend
is a better half, Rachel Fuller, Pete's brother, Simon Townsend, if you find it in the
Attic.com.
Of course, Pete and Rachel and Simon also have profiles on Potcha Plus, BT Potcha.com to be
exact.
You can get to it from Potcha.com or from BT Potcha, Rachel Fuller. Potcha.com, Pete Townsend.potcha.com.
That song has just been haunting me, and I sent an email to Rachel and I said, I really
want to play that on my show, knowing, by the way, that Michael Butler is hot on her
trail to get some of her stuff up on the P-M-N, as well as of course he's going to go
after some of the new stuff.
And it was a really catchy track out of good choice.
Two band Rachel hasn't put that on the Potcha music network yet, I don't get back to her
on that one.
So let's see that hailed from DSC 502, from November 22nd 2006.
This next track that I selected came from DSC 405, from October 25th 2006, excellent choice
at him.
It's guaranteed that we'll all have us in the mood, and you know what, he turned me
on too, baby.
Like a flower waiting to bloom, like a light bulb in a dark room, I'm here waiting
for you to come home and turn me on, like a desert waiting for rain, like a school
here waiting for spring, I'm sitting here waiting for you to come home and turn me on
like a flower waiting to bloom, like a light bulb in a dark room, I'm here waiting
for you to come home and turn me on, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in
a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in
a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like a light bulb in a dark room, like
gimme some m Meghan, mais, mais, mais.
And I have eyes waiting for a new tune, and my glass is waiting for some fresh ice cubes.
I'm just sitting here waiting for you to come home
And tell me
Perfect
Very lazy Wednesday
Grace-guys outside, key-drawn inside
feeling like crap, my friends, I think the flu is still with me. I've carried it back.
Maybe it's the second day of jet lag, but I just woke up, I just feel, you know what I mean?
It could care as hell, I feel. You've got your own problems, right? This is from the pod
safe music network and Jersey Todd, I learned me to the fact that it was, of course,
nothing special there. This is job as the official music college at the Charlie. Nina Simone
turned me on to Tony Humphrey's vocal mix Nina Simone, of course, a superstar in her own right.
The helm straight on him. You might want to check out her Wikipedia entry for a little bit more
enlightenment on that subject. If you dare. So you know Adam, you could feel free to cry,
my shoulder anytime you like, I'm always there for your baby. So let's get back into some more music.
I love the ladies. That's right, and my name is Leroy. I guess I'm not in on that
This is Rebecca Havelin, also from New York. You'll love her voice man. She plays, she writes, she sings,
and she's pod safe. I found you.
But when you found me that night and you held me tight, I knew I'd never run from love again.
I've been down this road, one, two, many times, I teach, day it just feels like a blind in the blind.
But you had the same. I've been searching for all my life, and I'll never stumble again.
Girls, when I didn't think that I would ever find love again, I felt you, oh yes, I did.
And when I didn't think that I would ever find love again, oh I felt you, oh yes, I did.
I found you. You held me here when I was weary, and you held me down when I was afraid to jump.
Did I still push you away? Only because I was afraid, who's in the game once again?
Oh, I didn't realize all the COVID-19. Until I didn't have it, I don't know. So, won't you accept my plea?
And come back to me, and I'll stay right here to me, because when I didn't think that I would ever find love again, I felt you, oh yes, I did.
And I didn't think that I would ever find love again, oh I felt you, oh yes, I did. I found you.
Rebecca Havilland, I found you on the plot-safe music network, that's exactly where I found you.
I love Rebecca Havilland's voice, so great. And by the way, the New York comment did not pertain to Nina Simone.
So this next band, it was tough to choose which track to play, but the clip I selected has such a great story that it was just a no-brainer.
So here we go. And I want to wind up today's celebratory episode with song from, actually it is the song I have to say,
that really got my juices flowing two years ago, over two years ago,
when we, well, I guess when we started numbering the shows, it was all talk back in the time.
I think that we smartly had all kind of figured out, hey, wait a minute, maybe we should not be playing any
music, because this music licensing thing is very complicated. This is before the podcast,
music network as well. The music licensing is complicated, and we got something really interesting going here.
Why don't we just stay away from playing music all together? Because the last thing we needed,
over two and a half years ago, is to have the RIA brand podcasting as some type of illicit pirate activity.
And so that's literally what it was. They were very, they were celiloquies.
Remember that? We used to talk about, who was it? Who said that, celiloquy?
Podcasting is nothing more than celiloquy. So which, of course, is partially true, but it's
become so much more. But I do recall, bumping into a band, online, who had their, their songs online,
available for, I think was a preview, listen, or whatever. I had one song, you could actually download,
and they were selling their CDs on CD-Babe, completely independent, four girls from New York,
and I really, really thought the song that I had found, which is for off of their CD, was so appropriate.
In so many twisted ways, is to what was happening with, with this thing that, at the time,
wasn't even called podcasting. We didn't really have a name for it.
That I, you know, I sent the singer of the band, the new mail and said, hey, would you mind if I,
if I played this song on my, on my show over here, and I sent you a given example, she said,
yeah, absolutely knock yourself out. And so I put a link back to their site, and where they sell their CD,
and as I said, you know, iTunes, even, and no, I'm sorry, not iTunes. What they selling it on iTunes?
I think they might have had it on iTunes at that point, but definitely CD-Babe. And I played it,
and then a couple of the people who were experimenting along with this in those early days,
played it, and then a few weeks later, I got to an email back that said, hey, you know, we're actually
selling CDs because of this. And that's when I got, that's really when Ron and I started to work on
the podcast and music network. You know, how can we make that? Obviously, it's working.
There's, I can now legally use content to fill up my show, which I love doing. It's,
it's, you know, to me, it's the same as someone sending an audio comment. It's, you know,
it's someone's passion. There are their their soul. And, you know, they want to get credited for it,
and, and if possible, they, you know, they have a business model. They want to make some money. So,
we came up with the idea for the podcast, music license. And so, really was, in those early days,
this song, that band that got my juices flowing, and they have not stopped. In fact, they're
the pumping quite, quite fast at this very moment. Of course, I'm talking about the
listidious bitis. And I want to be famous. I want to be famous. I want to wear minks and
satins and pearls. I want to be famous more than just any old girl. I want to have eyes as blue as the
sea. I want all the people to look at me. I want my own show on TV. I want to be that girl.
I want to be famous. He got it's art, his heart is at spy. I want to be famous.
Got a Paris on private flights. I want to have lovers buy the score.
When we produce is knocking down my door, this is the faith that is in store for me.
Oh, when I famous, I will wear a great trench coat and fake red hair. So, they all will know
that it is me. When they see me, how they'll smile. And they fold a grass to sign.
I will say sorry babe. Talk to my assistant. I want to be famous.
The tabloids will bring what I eat. I want to be famous. Who I do will be news on the street.
Then when I'm old, I'll have a ball. There'll be shocked that I'm living at home.
When I enter the gas, we'll fall to the knees. And then I'll slip the throat so my enemies met.
Oh, I don't want wine and cheese. When I'm famous, famous, famous, famous, so exhausting.
I want to be famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous
famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous
famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous
famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous, famous別vasam Historians!
I suspect I do add them.
Well, it looks like we've reached the end
of this special Adam Loves the Lady's Edition
of the best of Charlie.
I want to thank you for having me as your guest host today.
I wish I had just a little bit more time with you
because he played a lot more great tracks.
But if you'd like to hear more from me,
you can always tune into the Chillcast with Angie B,
Tuesday night, some serious stars 102,
or just subscribe to the podcast directly
through the Chillcast.podshow.com,
or check out my site, AngieB.com.
All right, well, it's been a blast, see you around.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest,
served up daily by the sharpest minds
and content delivery, podshow and line light.