It's very cold here in Siberia, but when I need to warm up I listen to the DSC-692.
It's like a good barrel of vodka, very smooth, warm you from the inside out, and even drink the old thing you need to eat.
It's very cold here in Siberia, but when I need to warm up, I listen to the DSC-692.
It's very smooth here in Siberia, but when I need to warm up, I listen to the DSC-692.
We can get closer to one and down the whole year.
Let's snoop a little bit.
Keep it off for brand new week of shows.
If you're from the Curry Condo and Georgia, California,
come to you from San Francisco.
There's a very source code episode number 692.
Nothing like some party bend to get things rocking.
What do you say?
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's Adam coming to you from the Curry Condo.
Seems like I was just here.
In fact, my cleaner, her name is Christina, has not even been here.
It's that last left.
Which kind of sucked, because I walked in, like,
doesn't smell very fresh.
Of course, you recall I had a power outage last time I left,
and I couldn't turn the dishwasher on.
I thought that she would have been here by now, but apparently not.
So it's a little bit messy.
Got everything set up here in the studio.
And of course, my microphone stands snapped.
I have a, I carry around this really heavy Mike stand base
and a little, you know, little attachment,
just a little piece of metal, so that it sticks up a bit.
Probably about, what is that?
Like, ten centimeters, something like that.
Well, maybe even last, maybe even, like, seven or eight, seven probably.
And on top of that is a plastic.
My holder.
Well, that snapped off.
So I've just parked the microphone in a towel here on the Baker's rack.
So aesthetically, the studio looks like shit.
But otherwise, doing okay.
Hey, really rough travel.
We started off with a problem with the oil cooling
in engine number one, I believe, on our 747.
So we spent almost four hours on the tarmac at London Heathrow.
After, actually, I was, I was running a little bit late this morning.
So I wasn't able to pick up my magazines.
You know, I rushed into the, into the lounge, had a,
full English as we call it.
So that's the big English breakfast with scrambled eggs, toast,
beans, a big ass shataki mushroom, a sausage, you know, full English, right?
My cappuccino had my, my orange juice, but really had to wolf it down
because I only had about 15 minutes before I had to get on the plane.
And then I walked the wrong way because I was, of course,
in the days, it being Sunday morning early.
And then I walked back the other way.
I didn't run. I don't run for airplanes anymore.
I know they got my bag on board.
They're not taken off with that bag on board.
And, you know, got there.
And then there was still a huge queue.
So it took another half hour before it was actually on the plane.
And then another three and a half, almost four hours sitting on the tarmac.
Just a rough flight in general.
I'd say a lot of, a lot of turbulence.
And I did see a couple of good movies.
Finally saw a hairspray.
Now it was fun.
John Travolta.
I didn't, I'd never even, I'd never seen that any of John Waters work
previously.
I haven't seen the play.
So I didn't know what the story was about.
Great story.
If you haven't seen it, then I won't, I won't tell you because you just had, you just have to go and see it.
Of course, upon arrival, I have to admit right up front.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm a bit of a chicken shit.
I didn't dare strap on the wireless microphone.
Because I just, you know, I was like, am I going to get harassed again?
You know, I just didn't want to, no, I just didn't want to deal with it.
Because, you know, after today's experience, I will.
Because now I know at least, you know, I'm starting to understand a little bit more what's going on.
Once again, went through passport control.
Now, this is actually not the TSA.
This is the, um,
Customs and border protection agency, I guess it is.
CBP.
And, um, yeah, a lot of typing on the terminal there.
And, uh, how long have you been in the UK?
Well, actually, I live there.
Uh, I was just, uh, just here a couple weeks ago.
I got a company here and I go back and forth.
Ah, what are you doing the UK?
I just live there.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
I got a big M on my Customs form.
I said, what's that for?
Many.
So, what do you mean many?
I don't know.
So, there wouldn't tell me.
I get my bag.
And, uh, of course, you know, I handed it to the CBP officer.
And, I knew that I was, actually, it's interesting.
He puts it in a, I've seen this, this happened last time.
It was, well, he put it in there like a blue, um, a plastic envelope.
My Customs form.
So, it's clear on one side and blue on the other and it's plastic and just kind of like a
Sheath and he puts it in there.
And, they have yellow ones, too.
But, I get a blue one.
I'm blue.
And, uh, I had a nice chat with Officer Williams who, uh, was very confused.
Um, but kind of the same procedure's last time.
Do you have a business card?
Do you have any other proof of ID?
You know, I showed him my pilot slice since this time.
Like here.
How about this?
And, uh, didn't want to see my bags.
And then he went to go talk to a supervisor and he came back and he took his time.
You know, and, uh, do you have any cash with you?
So, yeah, sure.
Here.
Take a look.
No, no, I mean, do you have more than $10,000?
No.
Although, if, uh, if the dollar keeps dropping like that,
I probably will have to just for, for tips along the way.
And, uh, so this took about 45 minutes to an hour as usual.
And I said, you know, Officer Williams, could you please tell me what's going on?
He says, oh, this is just random.
What do you mean, random?
Three times in a row.
Chicago, twice in San Francisco.
The last three trips I've made to the US.
Yeah.
And, you know, he's just random.
Three times in a row.
That's random.
Yep.
You're just, uh, one of the ones on the list.
What list?
Oh, I don't know.
Uh, this is information that we don't control.
Well, who puts it in there?
No.
And then I say, uh, but it says right here, um, that the seat on this little sign, you know,
it says where you'll treat me with curdy.
You'll treat me curduously, what you have.
It says you'll explain the CBP procedure.
Oh, yes.
I'm explaining it to you.
I just did.
He said.
Which is just routine.
And it's just random.
I call bullshit on that.
So anyway, we know it's not the TSA.
I'm on some other list.
And there's something in the terminal.
Something flopping around that is very confusing.
And I'm not like in it.
So next time I'll record it.
Well, four, four, two, seven, six, eight, well, three, seven, three, did it.
Bloody hell.
If you change that number, I'm going to have to forget it.
Um, let alone the jingle.
That's annoying.
Anyway, um, what I want to say here.
Alan, put in the bottle.
Um, where all bricks or all piping faces in shame have been kicked out of your own
two days late.
Um, ironically, Swiss police really happy.
So then I have to deal with lots of things with you.
We're getting this year.
Yeah.
I noticed that.
I actually talked about it.
I know agenda.
The show I do with John C.
Tovorek, uh, which went up Saturday.
And people are so depressed in the UK.
This is really.
It's not good.
You know, we were surprisingly good in the rugby finals.
Didn't win.
Came in second.
Which, of course, is the first loser.
It depends on how you look at it.
But not even qualifying for the full, uh, Euro 2008.
That's, that's really sad.
And of course, it's the manager's fault.
That's why he got sacked immediately.
David, right the day after.
But wow.
People, you see grown men walking around just a little bit hunched over.
Just a little bit depressed about not being in the competition.
But you're right.
I bet they're really happy.
They're the who looking to be showing up at the finals.
But the final.
Nothing like I want to San Francisco with a message from my friend, the prolific programmer.
Hi, I'm prolific programmer here from Miami Florida for the week.
I just wanted to, I was just thinking here episode 69 when we're guiding you in day to day,
with seems like a very nice device. To synchronize with your 800 you'll need to use our
sync with including both. I believe the all command line options are dash ABZ and just back up the
whatever the SD card is called to the to the MN to the Emini and micro SD card over the internet.
It takes two IP addresses and you should be done. I will post instruction for the instruction.
I blog at log.prolificprogrammer.com. Many thanks kids.
Yo, prolific programmer. Thank you. Yeah, I hadn't even thought about that. Of course, these are
unique devices. Linux. So you can easily use all those kinds of commands. Like I don't
know if it has our sync actually. I'll have to check. I'm sure it does. That's such a basic
command. I'd forgotten all about that. Sometimes, you know, there's just so many beautiful,
beautiful little things you can do with the command line, which is really what I like about my
Mac as well. I always have a command line window open. It was just to look at, you know, do a top
minus you to see what the processor doing processes. I can ping something to see my network connection
is alive. Oh, and the the 810 by the way comes with the terminal window built in. And of course,
now the actually have a keyboard attached to this thing, unlike the N800. You can actually kind of,
you know, do like unique stuff. Command line. It's it's freaky. The more modern we get, the more I
I earn for G-Max. Hello. Hi, Adam. It's John Clark. You know, John? Yes. Not here.
Somebody's from the funny direction. I used to have a pair of Nokia tyres. I'm a van that I ran many
years ago. Let's see. I told you it was a cookie company. They used to make rubber boots and tires
apparently. Why I heard them as a cell phone company? I'm glad you got the 810. Didn't think it would
take you long. And I'm just curious because I've been looking at the 800. Okay. And they've moved
the 5 way navigator off the front panel on for the keyboard level, which means you can't use the
5 way navigator without sliding the keyboard out. I just wonder whether you think that's a good idea
or not. Because it did occur to me that if you were using the keyboard, you might use it closed up.
If the navigator was on the front panel where I used to be, just curious by the way. Oh, and
fuck you. Hey, that's our Britain Basel. Yeah, you know, I'm sorry, not a Britain Basel. Who was
that? That wasn't my Britain Basel. That was who? I Adam is John Clark. John, that's what I meant.
Yeah, John, you know, interestingly enough, that is the first thing I noticed.
Even when I was looking at the pictures of the N800 and 10. And by the way, there's a link that
you can buy one. It's not the super duper price yet, but it's through Amazon and they're pretty
reliable. In fact, I've never had a problem with Amazon. So if you want to get one, you'll probably
wind up, you know, just like the iPhone, you know, and you'll wind up paying more. More than I
can offer to you in the future, at least. Yeah, the 5 way navigator. That's the
up-down left right. And then it's kind of like a, like a poor man's mouse button. I have to admit,
I really like using that. I like it more than using the touch screen because, you know, don't forget
that it has a complete touch screen system. So you can put your finger on the screen and you can
basically move the page around up-down left right. You can click on stuff. So I kind of switch
back and forth. It depends on what kind of page I'm on. For instance, the Google News page,
news.google.com. There I'll use the the 5 way navigator versus maybe if I'm going to check
some comments at curie.com. In that case, I'll just use the touch screen email. I don't use the
navigator at all because it does Gmail. So beautifully, I use the Gmail shortcuts. But really,
sliding the keyboard open is actually a little more comfortable for me. It's easier to hold the
device because it's not just one flat thing. You know, when you slide it open, then you have something
to hold on to and your thumbs really can rest comfortably on it. So I kind of enjoy it using it
with the keyboard open. Man, the battery life is just unbelievable. I think I listened to five
different shows on the way over. It was still only, you know, like it still had six days stand by
two hours full use. Now, I did have it in an offline mode. Also, I forgot to tell you Friday,
it has a GPS built in. It has whatever the map is that the N800 also had the same program,
which is not my favorite. I really like the maybe it is a way finder. But it's not the same,
it's the one I have on the E61I, which I really like. Maybe that one is the one that's becoming
available in I think December. Along with Skype, I did the whole upgrade. There was a new version
of the software that came out. So I flashed my device, did the backup restore all of that work
almost flawlessly. I think the only thing I had to reset was my phone, my Bluetooth connection
to my phone, so I can use the 3G data connection. But yeah. I don't know what I'm saying anymore.
Please, someone save me. Save me. Hold on. I'm playing another comment here.
Well, you have to understand something that as far as mask media concerns, this is not like a pin
up for the internet, I think that, but pre-press doesn't make that. Yeah, I know where this is going.
And of course you're right. Of course. And I'm seeing it too, man. I'm seeing that Ron Paul is just,
you know, he's barely taken seriously. And you can sit there and say, why is that? But it's pretty
clear. You know, this is a race between Hillary and Obama and then maybe Giuliani or someone on
the on the Republican side. And we'll see if it is just us cooks out here who are who raised five
million dollars. You know, if it is just, you know, a handful of people, then it really won't work.
Will it? Of course, when I'm hoping, is that we're millions strong, millions, millions who have
heard the message. And we'll vote for Ron Paul. There are corporations and corporations are going to
do what is in the best interest of corporations. I don't necessarily fault them for that,
but the reality is they're not going to push around all because they don't want to support Ron Paul.
They don't think that's where the money is. To get a clue on this, all you have to do is go to
YouTube, listen to some of the interviews they have with Ron Paul. Yeah, I agree. Very condescending.
The other thing I don't agree with there was what you're saying is that that's not where the money is
clearly. It is where some money is because, you know, we raise almost like four and a half million
bucks in one day. Hey, does anyone else December 16th is happening? Is the Boston Tea Party the next
the money bomb? We're going to drop on Ron Paul. Let me know, will you please?
You'll hear, you know, he's trying to say, hey, I like their audience. You know, they're doing so good in the
text polls. And they try to struggle off like that. That the poll was nothing. Like it's interesting
to get it's not valid. Yeah, so we get the support like their lives. They're looking, you know,
taking it from people. And while when you look at how they try to belittle him, trying to make
his efforts in his accomplishments as small as possible, you'll understand that this is a
corporate minute about a freshman over. Yeah, I agree. And that was kind of cool that it was the
Fox News poll I think. And Ron Paul was at the top of the poll. Ron Paul was at the top of the poll.
And he said, he said, hey, you got a really smart audience. Those Yahoo's over there. I was pretty funny.
And they tried to downplay it. So maybe that maybe, you know, I'm sure there's only so many people
watching, uh, was that Fox News Fox, yeah, the Fox News channel. I mean, they don't have millions of
people watching. I don't think. But maybe it's a representative sample. The internet, however, is the
ultimate form of free press because all of the things free. Because anybody can post anything. And
I have, and you have, and everybody else has equal footing as a major corporation. They can't buy a
stage and lock me out of it. We all have an equal opportunity access to that stage. So that's why
you're seeing a fake difference online. Well, we got a whole piece we can transfer that action that
energy from online to the real world. And two happens. Fuck you out. I'm going to fucking media.
Yeah, right on. Hey, if you want to get a great deal on a domain name,
I have a page at curie.com. You can find it in the show. No, it's a daily source code.com as well.
Where you can use one of my three codes. They used each code for a different reason for a different
type of discount. It's real simple. Easy to remember. DSC one, DSC two, a DSC three. And I think DSC
one is if you just want to get a domain name for six. Wait, did DSC three is domain name for 60,
65. Can't get a cheaper anywhere else. And also, I believe, um, I'm not supposed to,
isn't it Sony headphones? I think are sponsoring the network. They've got this new line of
headphones out. And I asked, uh, you know, really, what I really want is I want everyone who's doing
the campaign to have a pair, uh, but Sony wouldn't spring for them or the agency wouldn't spring for them.
Understandably so because, you know, that could get pretty costly. If you look at how many
shows are running the commercials. Um, but apparently they got some really, really good ones now.
Go to Sony.com slash headphones. Uh, I think they're great for, uh, probably, uh, really good,
knowing Sony because I use Sony headphones, professional headphones. I've used them almost all my life.
I think I started out with pioneers in the very beginning, uh, but quickly moved to, uh, move to Sony.
And I've tried all kinds of headphones. Sony really knows what they're doing when it comes to sound.
So, um, I'll see if I can get it at my hands on a pair and I'll let you know how they are.
Interested in the wireless ones. The, uh, yeah, they have wireless, right? I think it's Bluetooth.
Now I'll check those out. Maybe I should be able to hook them up to the N8010. Oh boy.
Okay, one more song, um, from the pod safe music. Holy crap. It's not my favorite performance
but whenever comment Tyler comes out with a new song on the pod save music network, I just got to play.
I think about my kiss you, oh my world is around. Now we're all getting hands in hand.
It was crazy world, uh, I'm so into you and don't you? Maybe you're driving wild.
Well, I love you so, and I just got to let you know to find me, oh, down in my soul.
Oh, we're looking at everything, please. I like that funny way you smile.
Oh, now let's go to you, baby, you're just my style.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I love you everything but here
I like that money away you smile
Oh darling, don't you know
I don't just say more or less
I love you everything but here
I like that money away you smile
Oh now they're talking to me
Baby, you're just lying
Carmen Tyler, you are just my smile
On the pontiff music network
A live I presume
Yeah, sounds like
Now I've been watching dancing with the stars so much
That I would have to easily be able to identify that as a jive
Ladies and gentlemen
Next time we'll do the American sway
All right, I'm pretty useless
A 24 25 minutes
Almost like the old days
I'll leave it at that
And I'll be back tomorrow
We'll do a full week
I'm pretty sure of it
Looking forward to it
Keep your phone calls coming
Of course you can find
Learn out to dailysourcecode.com
And send me an email at podjio.com
I'll talk to you tomorrow
Bye
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear