There, bro.
Delta.
Seerator.
Episode five, nine or eight.
The $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm guessing it's a battle curry.
In their eyes, it's a place that you find you discover.
Like you love it.
You cut this day on this rock, not so rock.
The night and on which you found a lover.
Then you switch and you feel that it's in your pesky cup.
Your pesky pesky pesky cup.
Then you smile, he goes wild.
Didn't understand.
That was money to be made.
You see this car, the Muscat played.
By organising.
Say.
Sense.
But you're not.
She was set to kick and save me.
You're not.
You're just suing her smile.
I'm sorry.
She was set to kick and save me.
Yeah.
You're not.
We're long, we're just shooting, oh, we spot her out
We're gonna be a very big place, so be yourself, don't fill out some place
I love your mind, I love him twice, twice if all you would
You pay the price, don't go too high with it
And don't be a star, it's such a drag and take care of yourself
Don't begin to lie, it's a hard life to live, so live it
Well, I should be a friend, I'll never pretend to you
You know that I love you girl, and I'll send you away
But you're not, she was such a kick, girl, she made
You're not, you're not, she's a cheater, no, star, it's a real
She was such a kick, girl, she made
Don't begin to lie, it's a hard life to live, so live
So be yourself, don't go too high with it
She was such a kick, girl, she made
The punch you're exclusive, the cooks.
And Pete Townsend, Urla from the in the attic CD release party that was held in London just a couple
of weeks ago.
You can find that there's a video for it in the attic.podshow.com.
It's not on the pod save music network for obvious reasons, but we do have the exclusive
for the website and you can play the video.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It is the daily source code episode number five, nine or eight coming to you from the curry
manner in the affluent suburb of Surinone is Gilford on the west side of G-town.
A nice day today, or at least by my terms now.
Now that I had that life-changing experience of flying home in the severe wind share conditions,
any kind of weather is kind of looking beautiful to me.
And it sounded kind of breaking through just a bit.
Wouldn't be a bad day for flying.
I got so many responses about that was it about Tuesday evenings episode.
And the next time I fly, I am definitely going to take a longer recording equipment.
I've done it before, and it does work out quite well, particularly because you really can
feel the sound of the engine.
I've been able to perfect the mic technique just the right way so you get the perfect balance
of the radio, the intercom, and then the ambient sound.
And it takes a little bit of work, though, because I got it at its stuff down.
And it just takes a little more work than usual, but I will do it.
If not for you, I'm going to do it for myself.
I'm tired, I got to tell you.
Yesterday, full day in London at the UK crash pad, but I don't know, there's the BT pod show
offices in Swanky's shortage.
Signed up two new shows, which I'm really excited about.
One is a games weasel.
This is going to be great.
This guy named Matt, who's a games expert.
He's going to do a daily audio show.
I'm sorry, he's going to do a weekly audio show.
And I hope moving towards video, but he's got some pretty cool concepts.
He's got great contacts, and he knows all the latest shit about all the latest games
coming out.
So that's a show that's coming out.
And then we have UK listeners.
May have heard of Barry from Wattford.
I think he does a kind of a semi-regular calling on LBC.
Is it the London Broadcasting Corporation?
It's London Radio Station.
I haven't feeling he calls a couple other stations around the UK as well.
But he's going to be doing a daily show for us.
It's audio again to start with Barry from Wattford.
It's just the most opinionated old fuck you've ever heard.
It's kind of like a combination of was a geriatric 1897 or whatever the hell.
And a little bit of Sam Kinnison thrown in there.
It's hard to explain.
So signed some shows.
We did some meetings.
It was always good to hang out.
I went to British telecom.
I sat with Gavin Patterson for our quarterly update.
It's fun because things are going well.
So things are very nice.
What do you do?
I had a late dinner at the Great Eastern lunchroom.
I think it is or dining room.
And I wasn't home until like 1130, man.
It was just a full last day.
And I got another one of those days today coming up.
Of course, don't forget we've got all the San Francisco calls.
I'm looking at it and out starting it around 430 San Francisco awakens.
So it's just a busy day.
I've been collecting lots of stuff for tomorrows.
Football Friday the maximum music edition of course and no
Sevant for you today.
Although I do have Sevant calling in and providing appropriate feedback.
And of course we did have the Lady Patricia on yesterday, which I don't know about you.
But I always love having my wife on.
And we kind of got it open up about the lesbian kissing experiences.
I think I need to delve a little bit deeper into that though.
Hey Adam, long time listening to the show here. This is Eric Skiff.
It worked.
I started a company called Cliff Marks a couple months ago and since starting there I've just been amazed at what I've learned on the site.
So we started a podcast called Cliff of Earth City where we share a bunch of things that we learned every day.
But I had one today that just made me think of you and I was listening to you in Lady Patricia yesterday and thought you know what Adam might get a kick out of this.
So one of the clips we featured yesterday is compared to things.
Getting a raise of $50,000 or having sex once a week instead of once a month.
Wait a minute. What are you supposing there my friend?
Now I got to put myself in that situation first and that does not seem like a very happy one.
And then talked about which made people happier.
So which would you assume?
Well, $50,000 extra dollars or...
Let me think about it for a second.
$50,000 extra dollars.
And I don't care how rich you are.
There's always room for extra money.
Or having sex once a week instead of once a month.
Hmm.
Well, I guess with $50,000 you could essentially...
And you didn't say love or having a loving relationship or making love.
You said having sex.
I think the 50 grand will get me a hell of a lot more than once a week.
Well, the answers at clippaversity.com.
But I'm definitely interested to hear what you're thinking is.
That's clipped like a paperclip and a versity like university.
Clippaversity.
What we learn every day from clippmark.com.
Got all right? Well, I'll go and check it out, but you've got my answer there.
By the way, no phone calls at all today. What's going on with you guys?
Come on. Here's the UK number to call.
Plus four, four, two, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
As I said plenty of comments coming in.
This is a rather long one, but it was kind of nice to just as a personal feedback to me.
And you know, so I thought the sound quality really wanted a little bit of extra length.
Let's check this out.
Hi Adam. This is Paul Smith.
Gotta hope you can hear me, okay?
He calls doing like a sound seeing tour here.
I don't know what his setup is, but it sounded pretty good.
Despite a bit of wind.
In fact, I'm going to back off the mic a little bit.
Back off, brother.
So I just heard DSC 596.
And, uh, man, and I'm glad you're alive, too.
That sounded very cool.
I just wanted to tell you where it was.
I am, uh, this is again, Paul Smith, uh, from Gainesville, Florida.
And, um, I'm on, um, on a trip, a business trip down to Marco Island in South West, Florida.
And I'm sitting on the 7th floor of the Marriott.
And, um, this one just went down.
I was sitting on the balcony, uh, drinking hide-it-in.
Oh, yeah, listen into, uh, the DSC.
Gotta drink the hide-it.
Yeah, as I'm shit, man.
I'm going to rip off an audio comment to him.
And, so we don't expect you to play this.
Don't want you to play this, it's just, uh, just a dude.
If your life is worth living, it's worth documenting, and it's worth podcasting.
You know, trying out the, actually, this is a, uh, Sony IC recorder.
There you go.
MP3 player recorder and, uh, never really recorder.
And I'm just, um, a little bit of voice for business, but nothing for my podcast.
It's kicking ass.
I love this sound.
I thought, heck, I'll just try it out.
Yeah, so I plugged my mic in in, plugged my headphones in it.
And I'm sitting in the balcony, basically chillin.
Such a thrill-see.
Um, but that's awesome, man.
I, I heard, uh, Friday show.
And, um, maybe Thursday, Thursday or Friday.
Whenever you posted the, uh, the thing about Patricia,
on the Dutch TV, I went to your website, and I saw it, and I played it.
If you know, this is almost like, uh, a little recap of, uh, the past couple days.
I, it's, it's, it's, it's even taking me back now.
And once again, I'm so happy to be alive.
And the comments, and damn man, you're right, I didn't understand anything.
It was pretty wild, pretty surreal being, uh, America.
And, uh, and seeing, uh, Dutch TV, and just seeing the mannerisms and, and how they talk, and how they walk out.
Don't you think they, it sounds like they're gonna throw up at any moment, but all the sounds,
they're gonna throw up at any moment.
Hey, um, you know, it's very, it's sort of like watching Lano kind of, or Carson, but, uh, in Dutch, um,
very awesome. And, uh, I've been listening Patricia on your show,
I guess, from the beginning, and uh, I've always had this image over.
I've seen a couple pictures over, but I, I don't know any of her history other than through you.
And, um, man, what a woman, huh?
But, uh, no, no, you mean, or what?
Oh, you mean, uh, you mean, uh, what, uh...
What a woman, a half, I think is what you mean.
Oh, yeah!
Nothing gets more excited than talking about my wife.
She is in The Secret House!
You call it my friend, woman of hell!
Owls.
She's right to my turn.
I'm just letting it all in.
Owls.
She's right to my turn.
I like names that mess up back.
I ain't holding up in back.
Owls.
She's right to my turn.
All right.
I shouldn't play anymore than that.
I'm going to get in trouble for her.
Oh, hold on a second.
I screwed that up.
Shit.
Polynesians.
Oh, sorry.
My name's Darren.
I'm a boxer in the UK.
Although at the moment, I'm out in sunny San Diego on a business trip.
Oh, man.
The audience is traveling this week.
And of course, with time on my hands.
I've been listening to the daily source code.
Okay.
What do you mean time on your hands?
Excuse me.
This should be planned in your schedule.
Question for you.
Now, when radio back in the old days,
had to be licensed.
And there were a lot of people who are against the man.
They would get on to a boat,
sail the boat out into international waters
and broadcast from out there.
Now, using AM.
Of course, the signal travel a lot further than FM receivers did.
And they were able to be listened to by a lot of the country.
Despite the fact they're running out of a boat in the country.
A boat in the middle of the sea.
Okay.
So I know exactly what's coming because this comparison has been made many times.
I think I can think I can address it.
So yeah, the pirate ships that you're the pirate radio ships you're referring to.
Like me, me go Caroline, radio Veronica, radio and North Sea.
Their whole deal was, look, the spectrum that is being used in international waters
belongs to no one.
So we can just use that spectrum.
And indeed, as long as they stayed out of the territorial waters,
which of course didn't happen because they broke anchor
and they would wash ashore and all kinds of shit like that would happen.
But if we're all in tens and purposes,
they were operating legally within the limits of all of the international countries
that were surrounding this broadcast.
So yeah, you know, no other laws applied, I guess.
Now, how does international positioning affect
these ASCAP BMI requests with regards to the streaming internet radio?
I'm sure that, like BBC, they stream a lot of their radio stations over the internet.
Are they going to be exempt from this?
Or was to stop people from putting their server in Mexico?
Does it matter where the server is based as to where the,
the licensing fees need to be collected?
I'm sure that there's some kind of a technical rule about it somewhere,
but I just wonder what it is.
Yeah, thank you very much.
Yeah, sure. So this refers to the web radio streaming fees for playing licensed music.
Well, yes, that only applies to the United States as such.
Sound exchange, I believe it's just a US organization that is collecting fees.
So if something is played on a web stream,
even if you have a web stream, you have to pay a default of $500.
Regardless of whether you even put anything on it, mind you.
And that is a statutory copyright.
So you have to pay for it.
Now, to get to your question, yeah, sure.
If the server is in a different country, that's one thing,
but it's not just about the server.
It's really about the business.
So if you're running a business in the US and you have your servers somewhere else,
it's just not, it's not going to work.
They're going to come and collect anyway because that's pretty ubiquitous,
because you can get to the stream from anywhere.
If the company is actually set up in a different country,
then I think you're going to adhere to the local laws.
By the way, it's the same with ASCAP BMI.
There's the Buma STEM Rine in the Netherlands.
There's Gemma in Germany.
There's, uh, I keep forgetting what it is.
RPCSA.
The UK RSPCA.
And they have their own set of rules.
And I think you've been probably just compared to, well,
so lots of porn sites are set up in Amsterdam,
and the businesses are also set up in Amsterdam.
And look at it like all the poker websites.
Sure, they're operating legally by operating offshore,
but the minute one of the executive sets foot on the US soil,
boom, he's arrested.
Uh, so that's not going to work.
There's no way around it.
Look, this is life.
This is the way it goes.
Both Brian Longa said are some on from Pod Show,
and Sir Jersey Todd are, um,
Ambulance Chaser.
But also a fine and very competent attorney.
He said the same thing.
Look, this is just the beginning.
All this shit is it's going to be changing more things.
It's going to be fights that's going to be all kinds of stuff
going on to, to come up with some proper jurisprudence.
And I think this one, uh, we just kind of lost.
We can fight for a change in the fees.
Um, I'm happy that you can still always license your music.
To any other individual organization, um,
for a certain uses such as Pod Safe Music.
Uh, but we're pretty much stuck with it the way it is.
And I thanks for the audio comment too.
Hey, come on, come on, guys.
I need more phone calls.
I need more advanced calling in.
What nylon?
Where the hell are you?
I've sworn to a one six to five six three five seven
Last one to a one six to five six three five seven.
I don't know.
This is Alice there from the Eclipse podcast.
Proud member of the BET pod show network.
We've got a bit of a crisis and I'm asking for your help.
Now I don't know if you've seen on the UK and use this week.
Literally, just in the last couple of days or so.
A three year old called Madeline McCann has disappeared.
Whilst the family were on holiday in Portugal.
Now, another Charlie's got an amazing audience.
Very interactive.
Very keen to get involved.
And I'm hoping you've got a bunch of listeners in Portugal itself.
So what I'm doing is I'm emailing all the podcasters on her.
Sending on picture of Madeline.
And asking if they could make reference to the case.
And perhaps link to the BBC news article to show people this is a genuine
Emergency appeal.
If people would be prepared to replace the normal album art that they put out
this show with the photograph of Madeline, that would spread the photograph
far and wide as well.
I want you to use the power of new media social networking.
It doesn't matter if you pod show a BET pod show.
Forget about young versus the Brits.
Let's have young working with Brits to try and look at this lost child.
Yes, the local place will be working with the European.
Trying to track this child down.
But let's show them the power of podcasting.
Let's make it a change in someone's life.
This family must be going through absolute living health.
A broad with one of their own missing.
Thanks very much Adam.
I hope you've got the chance to play this.
And that you can replace your album art just for one day.
That's what we'll be doing at the Eclipse podcast.
Yeah, of course.
Excellent idea.
And you know, even though you're, I'm almost immediately inclined to think
what what difference is that going to make?
It could just make the difference.
So I'm happy to oblige our place.
The beautiful picture of myself with the picture of Madeline.
Yeah, it's, it's interesting.
This story has been alive for three or four days.
And it has pretty much dominated a lot of the, of the British medium.
Not quite sure why.
Of course, you know, maybe it's just a slow newsweek.
But obviously, whenever a child is gone missing and it is every parent's nightmare
for this to happen while you're on holiday and they're in Portugal.
And, you know, they only had her out of her sight for a minute.
I mean, you know, all, it's all the memes that every single parent gets freaked out
by.
So I'm sure that's why, you know, particularly on a quote, slow newsweek.
It's dominating the media.
But obviously, that's great for the, for the family.
So that they have more chance of finding their child.
It's, it's messed up, man.
That's really messed up.
So yeah, oh, of course I'll put the, the album, Martin.
And if you're in Portugal and you're listening, I know we have a couple listeners
there.
Let me know if, if it's bigger than news in Portugal as well, if people are really into it.
You know, if there's, if there's pictures post that all over the place.
Um, if not, if you're in Portugal, please try and pass on the word.
Uh, doing as much as I can to help, of course.
Jim Funfain and Dale sent me an email.
Said, hey, you know, I love the fact that you played Venus on the football Friday.
Let me just play a little bit of that for you again.
To remind you what it sounds like.
Did you know that that song was inspired by the banjo song of the big three.
And he sent a link.
Oh, I love that part.
Um, and let's see, this is a link that of course I'll put in the show notes.
And let's see, uh, so late, uh, Mariska Ferris on vocals.
Roby Funlay with the band's league guitars.
We're seeing the writing credit for the song.
You know the tune right.
You've heard it a million times.
Me the first time was the 1980s cover version by banana ramma.
But have you heard this?
Based upon the traditional Osuzana, the writing credit goes to Tim Rose,
who released it in 1963 on the roulette record label.
It's called the banjo song.
You got to hear this.
This is unbelievable.
Let me just play the intro again.
And then I'll go straight into this banjo song here.
So this is the shocking blue.
All right, we recognize that, right?
Okay.
Now check out the, uh, the big three with the banjo song.
Oh, man.
He's got it.
Yeah, baby.
She's got it.
We need to do a mashup of this.
Well, I come from Alabama top.
Pull it up and chew on honey.
Oh, well, I'm hit on it.
That Ole Miss is safe.
Got it.
Oh, man.
Waiting for me.
Oh, Oh, oh! She's got it.
Oh, she doesn't.
Yes, baby.
She's got it.
That's awesome.
Awesome.
I'll be with the B&G and jail on my desire.
Crap, let's go in, I'll eat her ain't so hot and not I left
No end to a table stall
So I'm hit on a bed, oh my dear river, where the sun gonna keep me from on a wall
Oh, oh, she's got it
Don't cry for me
Cause I'm gonna see you and I'll eat the beach
Oh, I know it's fine
Wait
I wonder could I just sink those two up? What would happen?
Let me say
Almost like only 20, yeah, I'll queue it up here
Okay, let's try it again, let's see if it works
It is a different tempo, I don't think it's gonna work very well
Okay, it's time for our savonth from our series of the circle of savonth
I'm the Sultan of savonth
I think I'm gonna be able to get at least one savonth in episode
There's a fast forward button on there for a reason
And I hope to be able to talk to savonth every single day
So long
And by the way, I want you to know that this format changed
Doesn't mean that I don't stand one to make a picture
Make a picture, make a picture, make a picture and the salt in a sense of on savonth
Atomic Rod Jackson with an update
I had a atomic rod at him's here with an update on the atomic controversy
Apparently our last discussion took place on an anniversary for the anti nuclear industry
nuclear industry. On May 1st, 1977, an army of protesters calling themselves a clamshell
alliance sat down on the site of the Seabook nuclear power plant in New Hampshire, eventually
more than 1,400 people were arrested for trespassing. At least one person who was there,
Paul Gunter, liked the event so much they made anti-nuclear activism his career. According to
an article published in the Toronto Star on the 7th of May, Gunter says he has been trying to drive
a state through the heart of the nuclear industry since 1975. Gunter's position is becoming
more isolated every day. Last week the intergovernmental panel on climate change, the IPCC stated
that nuclear power was one of the technologies that should be used to combat global warming.
The third way a progressive think tank aligned to the Democratic Party recently issued a
policy memorandum asking environmentalists to support nuclear energy as a means of reducing
pollution and providing secure energy supplies. In the 30 years since 1977 we have developed ways
to address the remaining issues associated with atomic energy. Charlie listeners even know
the Al Gore's recent comment to the U.S. Senate that reactors quote come in only one size,
extra large, and quote, his bogus since they understand that there are small and even extra
small reactors on the drawing boards at Adam's atomic engines incorporated. I've given a quote
that old fashioned people like Paul Gunter will open their minds to new information,
but at least I know that there are some charter listeners that are getting the message that
atomic energy provides some hope for a better future. If they want more than snippets,
they can listen to the atomic show at atomic.thepodcastnetwork.com
So we were planning on launching the suckless zone. I believe yesterday and of course as always
there's a couple of snags and we've been through it a million times. You go and check the verification
email and then it looks like shit and you got to fix all the words and the from line and everything.
So I'm still hoping it's going to launch this week because I do want you guys to participate.
Not already people are standing in comments and ways for us to, well quite frankly, the suck
last and it's much appreciated. Candy Man looked with an idea next.
Help us suckless, help us suckless, help us suckless, help us suckless, help us suckless, help us suckless
, help us suckless, help us suckless, help us suckless, help us suckless.
Hi Adam, it's the candy man speaking listen, I think I may have a solution to bring
bring up what shows you what design to the next level. A couple of researchers of the University
of Oxford have devised mathematical formula for describing the ultimate perfect website.
And as you grab a piece of paper and a pen, I'll give it to you now.
All right, all right. I'm ready. I'm ready.
Go. B website equals 14.14 times E's nerve plus 13.56 times speed plus 13.11 times 3.
this plus 10.89 times funk plus 10.89 times up minus 12.63 times folks plus 10.32 times
ads plus 5.21 times multi m and then you divide the whole thing by 6.26.
I think that's pretty clear and then there are a couple of other data points here in this research also about the infinite users.
18% of people find that easy navigation should be the most important feature of website.
62% think that fast or quickly loading the page would be very important and 49% think that the functionality is very important.
80% actually said that simple and clear design is the most important feature of website and only 6% of the interviewed people said that multi-media and fresh content is important.
So I suggest you just put this into your product development pipe and we all look forward to seeing the results in a couple of four months fine.
Thanks.
But spoken like a true sales guy.
That is interesting.
Luke, you should tell me a link to that formula.
And it sounds like it kind of makes sense.
What parts are important?
Navigation, speed, cleanliness, functionality, only 49%.
I'd like to know who the respondents were or the survey takers or how they came up with that so please send me a link.
I'm very open listening to all that stuff and of course I agree in general with most of it.
Although I'm surprised by the functionality.
So that sounds like a very lean back crowd.
You just want to be entertained and don't really want to do anything.
I don't know if that's what we're looking forward.
We're very happy with the creators and I'd have to say the like, what's the word?
Contributors.
That I don't register the pod show because we do have a nice little nucleus.
By the way, did you find the videos?
There's like a soft, soft core porn group.
And they've uploaded videos like 300 of them to their profile pages.
I'm not even going to tell you because if you find one, you'll find them all because they all have each other in their entourage and stuff.
I got to tell you.
We're going to put, of course, an explicit and 18 viewing thing, whatever we have to do legally.
We're going to put that on there, but it's hot, man.
It's really, really cute girls walking around in short skirts, walking in bathrooms and flashing in hotel rooms, trying on lingerie.
It makes no man smile.
Jucks and orbs and darts and gourds.
Elmer futs and bouncing booters.
Sweater stretchers, long protectors.
Beach umbrellas, frost detectors.
Scooby Snacks and snake eyes dice.
Jello molds and hyping lights.
Every day I probably use 99 words for boobs.
We're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we're going to put that on there, but we
bring it up there.
Magic ear muffs, warming clothes, strobes and probes and frontal lobes, knockers, bonkers,
nigger bonkers, smurf sand screaming, yellow zongers, tanning cannons, Mr. Viggs, Big Bad Wolfs and
Forty Pigs, jogging partners sailing youths, 99 words for boobs.
Two point jumpers, bambies, thumpers, rubber, baby buggy bumpers, root up Vegas, Kyle Miggas,
Kongo bambos bowling pins, fast pitch soft balls, signage twins,
your claims I'm breast obsessed are true.
We're quite a pair because I'm a boob.
I love that.
Robert Lund, 99 words for boobs, it is pod safe and as far as we can see,
because it's parody, it is completely clear.
I've never heard of Picasso's cubes.
Nor do I think I've heard of ear muffs for midgets.
Definitely two new ones for you.
You've got any send them along.
Adam at podshow.com.
DailySourceco.com for links everything in the show notes.
Hey tomorrow, Maximum Music, Fubar Friday.
See you there.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Subdupt daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.