Time shifting is so cool, you right now are listening to the DSC 566.
The show may be recorded at night, in the morning, in the afternoon, it doesn't matter.
It could be recorded in San Francisco, New York, the UK, anywhere across Europe, even
in a plane going across the Atlantic, doesn't matter to you, you're consuming it in
your present.
It's recorded live, it's a live person talking live into a mic and you're listening
to it live.
So it's pretty live.
But you know, it's just time shifting is cool, podcasting is cool.
So enjoy the DSC 566 and if you are listening to this honor before March 22nd, bum
rush the charts.
By the black lab song on iTunes, make a go to number one and show what podcast you can
do.
Again, enjoy your time shifting.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You're hanging around the club, baby, every night.
She was thinking a little bite, got you knowing right, you're like a baby, you're
all around.
You know, if I can hear it, you're like put you down.
I teach you real life, I can keep you flat as fast, but you do, you're chasing all
the outside.
Where the fuck are babies they can't see, you'll see the teacher, mama, oh, you're cheating
on me.
Oh, baby, oh, we're gonna keep you, we're gonna keep you, we're gonna keep slow, you're
got a repaid and a broken heart, you're looking a little mama, but you're
ain't you smart, you're like a house, you're like a little woman, I know, you're
like put me up in the future, get your best show.
Oh, easy, easy.
You're gonna be my joke and you're sweet, you're you mama, oh, you're cheating on me.
Oh, I make a cheating game.
Oh, baby, oh, we're gonna keep you.
Oh, baby, oh, we're gonna keep you, we're gonna keep you, we're gonna keep you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
You, yeah, you always stay, you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love love you, I love you, I love you, I love your
You know, you just don't hear enough of that kind of music on the radio.
That's why I played for you.
Mark LaFourmei, I'm going to guess.
Two true mama from the Pod Save Music Network.
You know, I'm just scouring around, looking at the top 10 most pod plays of the week,
and that showed up, I'm like, okay, okay, off to the playing it is then.
Everybody, how you doing?
It's a daily source code 566 for Wednesday, the 21st of March 2007.
Technically, we're into Wednesday, the 21st, although it's actually still Tuesday night.
I was in the city all day.
If you remember from yesterday's show, I kind of hurried the lady Patricia along.
So I could run off to my meeting with Gavin.
So it's still Tuesday in the US when I'm doing this.
It's Wednesday in the UK, and I think it's April 18th in Australia.
Something like that.
It's guys are always ahead.
I can never figure it out.
So anyway, rushed off to the city, do my meeting, which was great.
It's always fun to catch up with Gavin.
It's kind of weird though, you know, and now I've been to his house, so I have like a personal
relationship with the same time and professional relationship.
Whoa.
Oh, man.
It was, you know what I mean?
It's like one of those things.
I shit he's younger than I am with the hell of my talking about.
So that was, you know, actually, there's something that we haven't talked about.
Have I ever talked about Pod Show TV because that's something that is really ramping
up pretty quickly.
And it's a whole new way of looking at Pod Show and how you interact with media, how
you collect things.
Of course, it's all done through a remote control.
And the cool thing about this is, you know what, IP, IP TV, you hear about it all over
the place.
It's kind of like, it's almost a ubiquitous name for watching television coming over
tubes, a series of tubes, better known as the interwebs.
Now British telecom actually has an IP TV product in the market.
I think they've got, you know, a couple thousand people now in the first stages of the test.
And it really is a set top box is what it is, except instead of the television signals
coming through the cable, it's literally coming through the other wire that comes into
your house.
Pretty interesting stuff is now you see companies like British telecom competing with
companies like Comcast or in the UK, we'd say NTL, which of course is NTL, but it's
kind of a joke because they suck so bad.
Actually, that's virgin media now, I should say.
Oh, man, I don't want to go off on that.
We'll talk about that tomorrow, but virgin media.
Anyway, so this poncho TV, it works on a couple different platforms.
So the set top boxes, they run, I think, a version of Windows CE, but the interface
is very similar, if not almost precisely the same as the basic interface on Windows Media
Center Edition.
You may have a PC that already has media center edition.
It's very much like the iTunes 10-foot interface, what are they called front row?
Where you have a menu system and here's the stuff you can choose from, you know, pictures,
music, bloody, bloody, bloody, bloody, and you hook it up to your TV and you have some kind
of Microsoft version of an experience.
So we built an interface that goes right on top of that.
And so this fits not just on the CE-based IPTV platform, but we're probably going to roll
it out first as something that you actually download and install and then works right with
your Windows Media Center Edition.
It's extremely cool shit because you can essentially be programming your channels from
anywhere, you know, from the office or anywhere you are that you have a web browser so
that could be in a mobile as well.
I've got to verb something awesome, but it's still not happening at the wrong time.
I kind of like doing this stuff at a different time.
You get into a very different mode, so particularly after a day like today, so it was very,
it was very exciting to talk about some of that and I think that within, I'm going to say
a couple of months, we might be able to release something that you could just download
and install and run on your Windows Media Center Edition, it's pretty cool stuff.
Let's see, there was a reason I was saying that, oh, I know.
So along with all of this development in the United Kingdom as we continue to move forward
with our partner British telecom, I said this before, it looks like we're going to be doing
something in Germany and it was pretty funny.
There was a meeting that took place last Friday at Seabit and that's in Hanover in Germany.
Germany and since we were kind of stretched between multiple places, we had all the
sales stuff we're doing in New York, Ron and Head Sales Weasel, Chris Jacob went over to
Hanover, they did the meeting and I think I did mention this on the show actually because
a comic strip blogger sent me a note and he said, hey, it's just a hop skip and a jump
from me to head and over to Hanover and interview Ron Bloom and we were like, yeah, cool.
Well, you could definitely interview Ron.
I don't think it worked out because of timing, it was all messed up.
There was actually no hotel left in Hanover, so Ron was like taking the train back
and forth and Berlin, whatever.
So that didn't work out as too bad because, you know, one of these days, we will eventually
actually get to meet the infamous comic strip blogger.
I'm so looking forward to it.
So the reason why I'm taping the show tonight is because we have an agency presentation
tomorrow because all of a sudden it's heating up now in the UK and we have an awesome opportunity
to present to McCann Erickson.
We've already been doing a lot of work with them.
They are the agency for a lot of the Johnson & Johnson brands in the state, so being
you know, explained as one of theirs, obviously.
So being doing some work with them and so the UK side should be pretty interesting.
And then tomorrow afternoon, it's really it's full days here.
Tomorrow afternoon we have, I think a whole bunch of producers slash podcasters who are
on the network on btpodshow.com, on the bt side, the UK side, even, I think our buddy
from Germany is coming in and does the tips from the top floor, somehow he's signed
through the UK division, you must like those pounds, I don't know, and so it's going
to be cool.
We're going to have a pretty big meeting and we're going to talk about some campaigns that
are coming up and the stuff that we learned about how to promote shows and how to promote
cross network and that's going to be exciting, but so there you go, that's the reason why
I'm up at, you know, past midnight, way past my beauty sleep bedtime, bringing you the
show.
Then we got some cool stuff to listen to and to talk about.
Let me just see, this is something I, I caught through a blog post that Andrew Grummit
had made on his weblog.
Now, I'll put a link to Andrew's blog and also a link to this particular piece.
I believe it's, of course, I forgot the page that I got it on, now I should have put
it in the show notes.
I think it was at Stanford University and so it's my partner, co-founder and CEO of
Pacho Ron Blue, in a question and answer session with one of our members of the board
of directors Ray Lane who was also a partner at Clienter Perkins.
So what's nice about this, and it's about an hour, so I listened to half of it on the
way and half it on the way back, it's a moderated session and it's really about the
relationship between an investor and a company or someone who took investment, how we
came together, what decision making process went through both parties to take investment,
to make investment, what the ongoing relationship is like and it's really great because
the setting was so calm and relaxed and both Ron and Ray are really, you know, I was
listening to it in smiling because I'm like, yeah, this is exactly it, this is really right.
So if you want to know more about the people, kind of the silent partners, if you will,
of Pacho and how they're thinking and what they believe in, you definitely should listen
to this and it's kind of funny because I want to play a little bit of it because you hear what
was the question, I think, oh, it's background, how did you get from wherever you started to
hear? And I'm actually going to play the piece where Ray Lane talks about his background and
how he went from a kid in Pittsburgh to one of the arguably most powerful men in the venture
capital business and then Ron will also give his background and then Ray does something really
interesting and I'm not quite sure what his point was, but I know he listens to the show.
So let's try and figure out what he was trying to do in this piece. I'll give you the piece of
the moderator first. It's good listening and if you're not interested, fast forward.
You both have had really interesting and exciting careers and instead of my introducing you and
sort of telling a story that probably isn't so accurate, I'd love each of you to tell a little
bit of background of how you went it up on this stage here. How long do you have? As long as you
want. Yeah, I'm going to go first. So I've spent my entire career in technology.
Born and raised in the East Coast grew up in Pittsburgh, educated in Pittsburgh and West Virginia
went to West Virginia University in Carnegie Mellon. I still have an association with Carnegie
Mellon today, I'm on their board of trustees. So I'm a router for Carnegie Mellon.
By the way, Ray. Ray, dude. We've got to do something about the bio, man. I mean, that's kind of
bland sounding. West Virginia, man. That's like there's a lot going on in West Virginia.
You know, we've got to sex it up a little bit. No. And stand for partnerships. If we can
generate them. Yeah, yes, I played James Bond for a couple of seasons. But focused early on computer
science technology, IBM, EDS, spent 12 years with Booz Allen as a senior partner. Hey, you got to
spend spend years boozing with Allen. That's good. Now you're sexin it up. That's good.
They're running the information technology practice and then I spent eight years as president of
Oracle. And I left Oracle in 2000 and joined the Cliner Perkins and have been for the last six
and a half years investing in startup companies in information technology software primarily
services and in clean tech. So it's an interesting new area for the venture industry
and in Cliner Perkins is in the last several years really focused on that say 40% of our resources
and now focused on clean tech. Making investments in solar companies and electricity generation
and storage in biofuels. And then I'm on a board of a coal gasification company that produces
natural gas to the pipeline by gasifying coal and a single step. So yeah, it's really interesting.
When when we met Ray, I'll just interject here for a second. He was like, yeah, you know, an
Oprah and Robin Williams and Bono's investment and Rob Reiner, not Rob Reiner. Yeah, Rob Reiner,
you know, it's like all these celebrity names, you know, and I was like coal gasification, Ray.
That's the shortest I can do it for that amount of time. Great. So Ron,
about 180 degrees opposite of Ray, I was raised in Atlanta and tended Georgia State University,
the study philosophy, but my early career was as a musician, written and produced over 300 songs
that have been published, played on over 2000 albums and began to get interested in technology.
After building a couple of recordings, studios, my last one, I built with Chuck Norris as a partner
Los Angeles and building that studio. I came upon this technology called Fast Fourier Analysis,
which is now called Sampling through the uninitiated and Fast Fourier Analysis.
Isn't Fast Fourier Analysis a show at a pod tech.net?
And realize that we could use the internet to exchange files as we were trying to develop this software
and I discovered what software was as a musician and that I needed it as to help me with my tools.
I sold my studio. I heard about this thing called the internet and decided to create a concept called
CybroKass and the idea of a CybroKass came from a thought that I had that somehow the internet television
and radio could work together to create information and entertainment rather than one displaced the other.
This was in 1994. I needed a project in order to demonstrate how a CybroKass might work so I
had worked on some Grammy projects as an artist. I convinced the guy who fell around the
Grammys at that time, my green to go ahead and give me the license to create a CybroKass for the Grammys.
Asked around if anyone else knew what the internet was and you'd be surprised in 1994.
How many people said no? I found the guy who had just left MTV as name was Adam Curry, VJ.
No, no, no, hold on a second. I want you to hear what listen to what happens next.
Now, Ray is going to do something that I just don't understand what he's trying to prove.
But have a listen. Yeah, and a VJ and a guitar player put together a company to CybroKass the Grammys in
94. Just for fun. Yes, for fun. How many of you have heard of Adam Curry?
I was hoping to be none of you. Yeah, see, see a whole bunch of hands went up. That's what happened,
Ray. And then, and then what?
Even he's getting too old for this population. Oh, okay. I get it. It's he's trying to show
that all these young people don't know me. And then I'm over the hill. Is that it, Ray?
Round again. We get reused like that bio energy.
This might be just an interesting question. All right anyway. So you should take I have no idea what Ray was doing.
I think he was just trying to mess with me. So the next board meeting, he like pull out this tape and go,
or this recording, go, ah, ah, you think you're all that shit. You're nothing.
So as venture capitalist man, they'll do that to you time and time. Again, got to watch your back.
So definitely check out the show. No, it's really interesting. It goes on and on. That's about an hour.
But yeah, you might want to try it out on the weekend or something.
Okay. Let me see. Did all that? Did all that? Ah, of course I have to mention today sponsors.
Unwind is the new show that Angie B is put together. It truly is a show to unwind by. It's brought
to you by Tylenol PM, which soon will have an endorsement from the lady Patricia on this product.
I hope if she wakes up from it. And of course by Folger's Coffee, you want to try out the gourmet
blends. I had a like a flash of doneness on my way into the city today. I was like, you know,
this is really stupid. I love Senseo. You know, but the Folger's thing is what's happening right now.
So I said, I got to get me one of those kits. So I couldn't, you know, using a Senseo machine,
has nothing to do with their coffee. So I can't wait. I mean, check out this, this like mega
mega combo of God going on here. So we're going to get the Senseo machine. Well, I have the
machine. I'm going to get the kit to make my own pouches, my own pads, pods whenever the
hell they're called. And I'm going to put Folger's gourmet blend in there. And then I'm going to
top it off with some splenda. I love it. How we're grouping advertisers. That's really nice.
It's working. You just watch they're going to be they're going to be auditioning before too soon.
Now talking about money or following the money. I was actually I was listening to the
most recent tweet. I think episode 91. I wish I would have been on that show. It was a lot of
really good guests. And they were talking about Google and YouTube. And you know, you know, a show
was really good when when you start yelling back at the show, you know, you're listening to it and
like, what are you talking about? You know, I was like, oh, I can't hear me. You know, this was
recorded on Friday. But you know, that something is really resonating. I really wish I had been
a part of that. Actually, a comment came in regarding the same topic. Let's just get this started
with this. Adam, it's Andrew Terry. Listen up from the Midlands in the UK. Just listening to the show
that you did on the 19th. Kind of the number when you're talking about the Viacom versus Gucci
lawsuit. And that you're kind of making the point that Viacom have a right to sue
YouTube because it's copyrighted material that people are posting. I don't profess to be an expert
and I did have a thought that you have several pod-safe music artists, code in and say that
when they hear when when their music is played on the daily source code, they see a jump
in in sales that can be directly attributed to being played on the SC now. I'm just wondering
if that translates across to YouTube. So some of you posts a clip from a Viacom show. Do they
see an increase in viewing figures or does it drive more viewers to go watch the whole program?
I don't know, but just like I think the Viacom might be killing the goose that lays the gold
necks a little bit, but there you go. Not the show. It's still a folder. Bye.
All right. Thank you very much. You know, from the Midlands, no less.
Yeah. You know, we've got to distill this down a little bit because there's a couple of pieces
of the puzzle that you have to really understand to really know what's going on. And the number one
part is the money. It's all about, it's fuck copyrights. I truly believe that, you know, of course
there are lots of really ancient, tried, and tested laws that go along with mainstream media. So
you know, these, of course, do not necessarily apply to the internet. So that's kind of where the
the whole conundrum is of how things work or how things should work or shouldn't work. But when it
comes to money, you know, these guys are all about monetizing. So whether it's ABC or CBS or Viacom,
the parent company or GE or MTV networks, they're all about monetizing what they do. And, you know,
they understand promotion very, very well. But there's a lot of things that happen when you
don't control the flow of money. Oh, there it is. Excuse me. So when you don't control the flow of
money, it's very, very frightening. How you're going to, you know, how you're going to manage
what is going on. And obviously there's, there's part of a copyright conversation where look,
if some, if you want to actually do anything against copyright infringement in the future,
you, you have to pretty much show the history that you've always been right on top of it.
You haven't just let this go. So that, that's part one. I mean, the real issue here is that they
couldn't come to terms about the money, because the way Google operates is, you know, they
have seen these deals before. They pay money upfront and they say, okay, we're going to do
X amount of ad revenue for you. And, and here, the terms of our deal. Now, the advertising business
of YouTube is so uncertain. It is so unpredictable that I think they really are afraid to put a
real number out there, which is, which would be meaningful enough, because obviously the way
juice is set up, you know, they cut a deal with Viacom, no problem. You know, of course,
there's control there. There's, you know, access to who sees what and how. And that's all with,
it is done with digital rights management. And, you know, YouTube just really doesn't have that.
And also, you know, juice is being programmed. It's not going to be a happy go lucky thing,
upload anything you want. It's, it's going to be a controlled environment. You can see there the
Viacom is very happy to jump on board. You know, I'm really sorry if you're listening to this
on serious stars 102, because we're just about to get to the good stuff. So, of course, you've got
a whole line up this evening for you. But if you go to dailysourcecode.com, you can download the rest.
So, um, so clearly Google couldn't make an offer that Viacom, you know, found acceptable
and just, you may be the realm or other deals that they've done understood. Here's the thing that I
believe is starting to get a little bit dangerous. Um, and it really dawned on me listening to
the episode 91 of Twitter. Let's stop telling them how fucking awesome it is online. Okay,
everyone's talking about the promotional value and how, you know, ever since these clips have been
up on YouTube that these shows, the daily show and late night with David Letterman that viewership has
gone up, stop telling them that. Stop using that as an argument. If we ever want any of our shows,
to get through all the clutter, look at iTunes for Christ's sake. It's not easy, you know, to get
into rotation on iTunes. It's very hard, you know, to, to be one of the gems of independently
produced media that, you know, audience are out there trying to pick out from, from anything that's,
you know, that's displayed on the homepage. It's all NPR and mainstream stuff. So, stop telling them
how to do it. Please, stop telling them how good it really is. What are you trying to convince them
to do? You know, I, I say, go around them. Please, and, you know, that's exactly what we're doing
with bum rush the charts. And I, I, I, I really, really like this initiative. I have nothing to do with
it personally other than I'm on board. I'm on it and I totally want this to work on the 22nd.
So, that's tomorrow, the Thursday, March 22nd. We would like as many audience members as we can
put together and I have no idea how many shows are actually participating in this at this point.
But I did see an article on, um, where is it? The article was in Billboard magazine,
checked this out, written by Anthony Bruno, a grassroots group, a grassroots group of podcasting
official nodos. Oh, yes, official nodos. You hear that Chris Penn, financial aid podcast,
you're an official nodo? Are hoping to catapult an indie artist to the top of the iTunes
digital track chart this week. In initiative called bum rush the charts with the hyperlink
there. Very nice. The group is running promotional videos on YouTube and other sites as well as
in various podcasts of participating broadcasters. Interesting choice of words there to encourage
music fans to buy the song, mine again by the band Black Lab on March 22nd, home on a second.
Did they just say, YouTube? Oh, here it is. Oh, excellent. If you go to bum rush the chart
start calm. Oh, this is awesome. It's a YouTube video of Natalie Delcante. Oh, let me see what she says.
Oh, she's got one of those low cut dresses, not the like the two top. I want to encourage you to
please bum rush the charts. Yes, Natalie. I'll bum rush anything for you. Now, bum rush is about
the power of organic music discovery. We need big record labels to tell us what's good music
talking about the internet connection ourselves. Let's show big music what the little people
can do and take a song to number one on iTunes. On March 22nd, download mine again
a new song from Black Lab and every commission. This is pretty awesome. Made will be donated
to college scholarships around the country. You know, this I'm glad that she participated in this.
Let me see if she winks at the end bum rush. Come on. Give me a call to action, Natalie.
Set a calendar reminder, tie a string on a string around my finger finger, set your cell phone to
go off whatever. Just don't forget because we're bum rushing the chart.
A nice smile. Okay. I should put that in my show notes as well. That's pretty cool.
So I think I'm going to post the the link today because you know, a lot of people don't get this
until a day later. So you know, since we're on such a time shift is exactly how we started the show off.
I'm going to start plugging it now. So the point is think about what's going to happen. Think
about the message we send. Well, all this turmoil is going on and all we're doing, you know,
and you remember, you know, my speech, my saliliqui, about doers and and talkers. So a lot of
people talking about via com and YouTube and big big media and big record companies. Now we can
do something and you don't have to be a podcast or please, it's it's it's really about the audience.
You guys listening to this. Let's show them. I mean, you'd listen to some of the pod safe songs.
You know, I'm sure you listen to a couple of podcasts if you're listening to my, you've got to.
And I'm sure I don't think many people only listen to my show. I hope not.
So it's really up to you. It would be so nice if we can make this happen. The ink is out there.
If we make it work, the ink is going to come flowing in. We're going to have a lot of people who can
take credit for it, which is really, really nice. This is not a pod show initiative.
Yeah, there's some pod show, aficionados, but it's not a pod show initiative.
This is not like some kind of fucking pyramid scheme. The money is going to scholarships.
Black lab chosen because they were dropped by a major label. We'd like to, you know, for them,
yes, it's a big FU, which is very cool. And I know that this is going to be very exciting.
Already I've been contacted by two record labels. One of the large labels as, you know,
a small division of one of the four large labels. And by a large independent label,
both already saying this is what I found interesting. Hey, we really like this idea that you've got
going on there. You know, can we do a bum rush to charts with the one of our artists? Well,
isn't that interesting? So the answer, of course, is no because it doesn't work that way.
But if you jump into the middle, you join the pod safe music network. You start promoting
your shit like everybody else. You know, you start doing interviews. You start working it.
You know, you become involved. It's going to happen by itself. We're only showing the power.
The power is going to be within anyone who wants to harness it and wants to utilize it
and wants to join in with what we're doing. It really, really make the new revolution happen.
Let's see what Mark, Mark sent something new in about this. This is Mark Yoshimoto,
Namcoff, author of the podcast novel Shadow Falls Badlands.
Bum rush the charts on March 22nd is almost upon us. And I've heard some people grumbling about
what iTunes and I hate DRM, so I'm not going to do it. That's funny. That's exactly the way
podcast pickle sounds to me as well. And podcast alley for that matter. Well, I think these folks
are missing the point. Digital rights management is another issue entirely that has nothing to do
with Bum rush, duh. I mean, it's basically like saying, I won't give blood because I hate needles.
As to the question of why iTunes? Well, I'll tell you why. Because for the last two years,
iTunes has been one of the top 10 music retailers in the US, beating out other top tenors
like tower records, borders, and Sam Goodie. And when a conservative minded company like Walmart
is the number one music retailer in the country, you can see why corporate media chooses to push
water down bullshit like Nickelback, Clay, Aiken, and Justin Timberlake. Think about it.
Entertainment is being dumbed down to pander to the lowest common denominator. And this is exactly
why we need to bummer us the charts on March 22nd to at least begin to show that independent music
and entertainment is a choice that people are making. You know, what's that old saying? Stand
up and be counted? Well, bummer us is just that. It's a role call for all of us taking part in
creating and consuming new media that understand that the power of any social movement is the ability
to make people at least consider that there are alternatives out there other than what society tells
you. And if you're willing, just sit on your couch and settle because it's easier. Well,
then traditional media will provide you with the problem you're looking for. But if you,
like me and millions of others who consume new media every day, want to make a statement that says,
I'm making my own choices for what entertainment I want. Then you'll go check out bummer us the
charts.com and see what we're doing on Thursday, March 22nd. Traditional media's networks are
groups held together by corporate and financial agendas. New media's social networks are groups
held together by people who enjoy creating relationships and communities and by taking two minutes
of your time and 99 cents to bummer us the charts with us on March 22nd. You're saying,
you want to be part of a community that values independent media. For more information, go to
bummer us the charts.com. All right, Mark. So while Mark was in his, uh,
in his little speech there, I was looking at bummer us the charts.com. I was looking for the link for
the affiliate link. But I guess the page actually changes on March 22nd. So I'm just going to put
the bad job. Because because all we have to do is put the put the I'm in bummer us the charts.com,
logo in our show notes. And then you'll click on that on the 22nd you'll be able to go and buy it.
And I guess it'll stay up from that moment on. So I really don't expect any results until
probably the 23rd, maybe the 24th. I don't know. It could be surprising. And of course, we have
no idea how the charts work on Apple side, uh, someone could totally be gaming it. It could be that
someone writes it down. I don't know. And for the same reason, we could have some friends over
Apple keep their eye on it and, uh, and give it a nudge. But either way, if we could actually
pull this off, think about how exciting that's going to be. That is going to change the rules dramatically.
I promise you, because it's all about the money. How many times have artists called in and said,
dude, you played the song on the show, other podcasts, there's played the song, uh, all of a
sudden, we're we're selling stuff. The right tunes were selling full CDs through CD Baby,
attendance at gigs is up. Merch sales goes up. It works. It just works. And this is how we work together.
You know, podshow takes no money. I take no money. I'm not interested in shaving pennies off of
an artist's sales. I'm just not interested. That's not my business. I want to help you because
you're giving me content in in four to five minutes chunks every single time. I love you for it.
Okay, a black lab. Mine again is the song you want to buy. And there's so much of good black
lab stuff on the PMN. I picked this one up again. See the sun.
I can't feel you. I can't feel you. I can't feel you. I can't feel you. I can't feel you.
I can't be on your mind. You're my side. I feel fine.
Are you my lovely show? Are you the answer to my question? Have I wasted my time now?
Cause if I feel this feeling, but you crawl out of your foot
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm crying the night when you shine
Will you be in my life?
Cause I can't see the sun, I can't feel it
Crying more, I can't see the sun, I can't see the sun
Will I don't run in your blood my side?
I feel fine
I feel fine, I can't see the sun, I can't see the sun
Will I don't run in your blood my side?
I feel fine
Crying more, I can't see the sun, I can't see the sun
Will I don't run in your blood my side?
I can't see the sun, I can't see the sun
I can't see the sun, I can't feel it Crying more
Will I don't run in your blood my side?
I feel fine
Crying more, I can't see the sun, I can't see the sun
I feel fine, I can't see the sun
I'm looking for that darn link
The Stanford thing
I got it through Google Reader
And it had a whole set of different links from Andrew's blog
Okay, so at least another half hour of getting all that crap done
And then off to Betty by
Tomorrow I'll be back remember
Get ready to bum rest the charts, click on the link, go to the page
bum rest the charts.com
We're going to make this happen
I know we can
DailySourceco.com for all the links
Adam at podshow.com
See you tomorrow
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear