At the tone, the DSC will be 572.
Tone.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sorry.
B.
Dude, you suck.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Tone.
From the UK send me an I am and I'll make a day. I'm 22 and my name is Darrell nice to meet you
They're all my name is Carol. What do you like Carol? I like to go to shows. I collect comic books and vintage clothes
What do you like? I like to skate that play rock guitar
But I'm not that great. I like to go in dates and stay up late. I live in San Francisco and hang out on the hate
Do you like the golden date? I did when I was eight maybe I can come and visit
Maybe you should wait so you're in really 47. I've kids no one the way through her pounds and I hate my life
Are you serious? Yes, well, I've got a secret to I'm not 20. I'm really 32
I only have one leg and I like to sniff blue. You like to be Carol. You like to be too
I want people can surprise you from behind the screen listen to this version
Can you see what me?
I am CC.
I like your profile.
I checked out your pics and I like your style.
Sounds good, Susie.
All be your friend.
We can read each other again and again.
Come on in my case and post on the page.
Join my groups and guess my age.
You must be 18, how could you not?
You can't be in high school.
You're just too hard.
Let me send you pics for your personal collection.
I hope they inspire you and give you a smile.
Susie's a simple pixel.
The borderline's a cop side up.
It's door she was only 16.
It's my boy.
I haven't made any good friends.
I'm running like she's such a spitting.
I'm walking hard.
I'm going to sustain.
I'm going to get out of here.
If you don't believe us, here's a fun of story.
About when that marks and is unlike a finale.
Time to monitor truth is hidden from your eyes.
Fuck's didn't know that you was in for a surprise.
I've been dead for a while, but let's cut to the chase.
I don't know what you look like and I want to see your face.
I want to see my teeth.
I know who I am in someone.
You're not a woman in this whole time you lie.
You got me there?
I'm not really a female, but I'm a guy who protects me.
Go for me man.
So this is why it's bad to meet women online.
Living like behind the screen is a total waste of time.
Check.
Fuck.
I'm in a physician.
I'm in a girl.
I'm sure.
Yeah.
on this my space page and I listened to the song a couple of days ago and I was like yeah
I'll play that went to the same page today and they've taken it down but it is available on iTunes
and that's where you heard this version from I don't know kind of the wrong song to choose
so that I got a bit of a headache left low it's a daily source code 572 coming to you
from Gilford in Surrey in the United Kingdom my name is Adam this is the daily source code
coming to you from the curry manner the the attic as it were oh let me see where shall I
wish I start today whether or not so nice I knew it's not going to be nice today in tomorrow
and that may pick up on Saturday I really hope so I really want to pick up my aircraft
here's something that's interesting Google notebook changed overnight I'm not quite sure if I like it
it's certainly a better aesthetic if you never tried this out you should it's kind of like an online
outline or only it doesn't quite function the same way it's changed a few things which I don't
like for instance when I add a new note it appears at the top instead of the bottom
and you can't just drag and drop that easily in the small notebook view but it's cool
and it's definitely expanding there's a lot more to it than there was I was going through the
news before I started I'm a little bit late today it's was at the left or two in the afternoon you
okay time I was watching the news what you know this thing with these 15 British Seaman is it
one one C woman and 14 C men who have been who have been held I guess captive by Iran this is weird
I don't like it at all you know and quite rightly I think Tony Blair has been making noise about this
saying hey you know hey screw this and now it's so childish and now Iran is saying we want
an apology you have to say uncle all right shove a new cup your ass motherfucker this whole thing
about territorial waters though it's a it's a very very complicated thing and it's not like
you know I don't think these guys want some covert operation I think this is just a political
move for some reason but it's a good one and it's working I think Iran definitely has our
attention who knows what's going on while we're all focused on this news media please let's see what's
going on in my own backyard a couple people sent me sent me this message this is a pretty big news although
still a bit confusing but Yahoo apparently will be offering unlimited email storage I have been using
the new Yahoo mail system a little bit kind of as an interim step where I was well I'm still in the
process of fixing fixing my Gmail and it has some of the same features you know I love the
short the keyboard shortcuts that's pretty cool but I'm pretty loyal I think at this point and
pretty locked into to Gmail but the unlimited storage is pretty interesting and will that be for
anyone is that for free users or only if you have the premium service which I have because if you
want to access your email through pop three or eye map or any of the protocols that have been around
for a thousand years and just work then you have to become a premium subscriber so I do pay extra
money for that and I wonder if that's going to be unlimited for everybody and of course
when you start to think about that you start to think about email as once again it's it could be a
very interesting distribution mechanism it is a store and forward mechanism it is a it's not quite
published subscribe but I think you know there's enough in there that we can make it publish subscribe
it certainly is something that really works efficiently for newbies people who are just figuring
this stuff out I know that if Patricia received the daily source code in her email every single day
no what am I saying she'd fucking ignore it
don't you dare even he's don't you dare possibly so much better on the DXC if you bring back lady
Smith at it again I email that to one to her Jeff you know I did that so and this is
subject line I said show tomorrow question mark and then I just attached this file I know she
was how to open the attachments so hopefully that'll work and we'll have a proper food bar Friday
which of course is good because next week I'll be in San Francisco portions of it in Los Angeles
it's going to be another one of those crazy weeks then I come back for about half a week and then we're
going on vacation yes and I think I'm going to pretty much unplug yeah it's uh I don't do that very
often and uh I think I really needed I just need to unplug I always have email with me and stuff
and follow along and check in but I really don't want to be doing any production of anything and
we can do best of charlie's or we could just wait we could just do nothing you're subscribed to
the feed right you know it'll show up when it's when it's time for it to show up
hey guess what I fixed my uh my ADSL router problems you're not going to believe this and thanks by the
way to people like Philist May who offered uh even offered an ADSL router for me to go pick it up
and and try and he'd keep pre-configured for me a bazil um from uh bubble boy's from Belgium right yeah
bazil bazil from from Belgium he's trying to help me pronounce his name better uh he also said a
whole bunch of technical information you're not going to believe what I found out and why I was
having all these intermittent problems remember yesterday I said that the Apple airports I had no
problem seeing them connecting to the network uh the ADSL part of this uh beautiful net it actually
is quite nice it's a very aesthetic looking uh modem router in one I'll get the model number for
I tell you what it is um I was seeing it on some computers and I had and I'd reset it to you know
to factory defaults just to make sure I wasn't messing anything up so it popped up as net gear
but I couldn't connect to it with any of the computers it by the way was sitting right next to the
Apple airport so you know there's no reason why I shouldn't be able to uh connect to it of
course that is one of these end routers which is backward compatible all the way down to the
802.11B standard so I had my question marks about that backwards compatibility until uh last
night Patricia who has a television in the kitchen and this is something we've had since the curry
cottage I have one of those uh transmitters that uh sits uh it's connected to our satellite box and
transmits whatever's being watched in the on the main television in the in the television room in the
media room how's that sound uh in the media media media suite a transmit it to the kitchen so she can
follow along and even if you change the channel you can walk back and forth and you don't really
have to miss anything she said oh my television sucks so what do you mean well look at it and I could
see the without even hearing the sound I could say I could see the repetitive um well first of all
lots of snowy picture uh and I could see this repetitive black bar in the middle uh kind of popping
on and off and scrolling up and down at regular intervals well I knew where that was coming from that's
obviously some kind of wifi device trying to connect or or scanning frequencies and and it went
oh wait a minute yes my brain went off I said oh I'm not gonna believe this so I disconnect this
transmitter boom I could see the the access point I've got to 1.5 megabits per second
can you believe that all this time the problem was not routing um and I'm sure that the the
ADSO mode on my head wasn't the best one and I know that these Apple airports can clog up a while
particularly if I'm I'm streaming porn on Windows media then after all you have to reboot them you know what I mean right guys
uh so all this time it was RF interference which makes so much sense so of course now
that I have the network uh fixed uh yeah and 1.5 megabits per second that's fine that's fast enough for me
we've only three people in the house we're not all sucking on the pipe at the same time
so that's gonna work just perfectly now I have to figure out a new solution for the television of course
the ultimate solution is to run a cable but you know it's really you know unless I pull up floor
boards or or something like that it's gonna suck it's gonna look shitty so here's the thought I had
and I wouldn't mind you weighing in on it and let me know what your thoughts are I was actually thinking
of putting a sling box onto the main set and then uh particularly with you know with this new fast
with this new uh very funky spanky brand new router we should just be able to stream that
to Patricia's eye Mac in the kitchen or any other computer in the house for that matter
so that would be the the newfangled way and of course I could also then see it outside the home
which is also nice that's what the sling box is for or I could look for a different digital
transmitter pair or uh yeah I think that's about it those are about my options
um to let me know Adam at paucho.com tradition I'm off and running in the 100th time
Boston America dedication if this friggin thing was a hundred miles more there would be stuff
that doesn't make me some brave hero that just makes me persistent as hell history fellow runners
this is Poelston Street and this is the sound of crying Steve runner host of
the depudations the podcast for runners at stevener.com will podcast as he runs the 111th Boston
marathon on Patriots Day April 16th 2007 subscribe and listen in April as we present four special
episodes dedicated to the Boston marathon complete with Steve's running of the 26th
point two miles from hot content Massachusetts to downtown Boston it's the 111th running
of the Boston marathon on for depudations the podcast for runners at stevener.com right on last year
a steven with a a pod show t-shirt on are you running with a pod show t-shirt on this year
Steve because it was really cool people were like cheering them on you could hear uh because of
course he was recording everything and you could keep people saying go pod show go it was a
hard small contribution towards the sponsorship it paid off very well and of course Steve has all
this cool technology we can actually track his progress uh because of some uh whether something
a little micro transmitter or something that's uh that's inside his shoes so we'll be looking
out for you Steve and rooting for you of course. I'm a perfect programmer here with this in the
year C571 when you played me comment and said that you uh wanted to schedule a Skype call with
comics to blogger the nylon and myself I would be definitely up for this I have a Skype ID it's
HDIWN uh many times also apologies for the length of last comment and we're going to have been
this long. It's easy. It's easy prolific programmer easy does it with the words you'll get them all
I'm the really trying to teach him thank you for sending that on MP3 yeah that was a little more
manageable than the 29 megabytes you sent the other day so great so we've got prolific programmer
is in oh and he now is nylon and comic strip blogger and then we're completely set for the tower of
Babelcast let's have a word with the nylon spread the news with the smile on where the
hollow right we're in your polite let's listen world around you the nylon hey Adam Mr New Yorker
the nylon hey dude they give me performance anxiety with a jingle I'm not gonna be able to get it up
now come on I can't have this sort of high pressure on me um couple of things um she might
talk about part testing the audience there was a little bit of a little disappointed because you
see one day I had a dream I had dream that part testing will be about the audience enlarging the
audience audience focused audience relevancy I had a dream that the part testing community would be
different from the mainstream it would it would be more tolerant that they would accept diverse
views in fact they would embrace a divergent view ensure I had a dream that the podcast in
world is going to be more inclusive oh I can't take it inclusive dude 80% of this show is the
audience what do you think's happening right now I'm embracing you come here come here nylon in my
arms let me embrace you when you're alternative views I want to include you I had a dream that
part testing itself was about controversy it was about freedom it was about autonomy it was about
independence it was about not letting the man dictate the way you're thinking the way you do things
I will come a little bit this morning and listen to the show and yeah that dream kind of crumbled
what are you talking about all the things you just mentioned right there controversy we don't
do controversy on this show we do controversy it was got inclusion every single time you send
something in if I put it on dude but also because it's interesting and for my own personal
benefit it's entertaining it is about audience participation it is about sticking it to the
man I think you need to keep go back go back to bed take some Tylenol PM and call me in the morning
sorry hopeful that dream may come true that we may be an inclusive and tolerant and caring
audience embracing those who have a view that's different finally not a banker not an IT guy not a
frequent visitor to London actually a resident of London but raised in bread in New York South Bronx
Jackson Mississippi taught you so and I know you're a scruncher you don't have to say it don't worry
about it but there's something going on with you nylon because not only and I'm sure you heard there's
another jingle the one I just played which is of course a Jeff Smith original and of course the
one that slowed it for you whoa he's an island outspoken expatriate he's in London buddy's from New York
whoa he's an island controversial my long he's in London buddy's from New York
hey mate says Phil just wanted to add my weight to the growing discussion on nylon I'm sick of his
corrections and correctness what a pompous bastard he should move on from his views and take a
wider look at everything you and your show is the essence of positiveness and looking forward
even CSB has a sense of humor when he runs I say scrap the nylon and his self inflated views
Phil I think that's a very sound advice but I can't I can't do it because we've got all these cool
jingles to play let's have a word with the nylon spread the news with the smile on where the
rollo right window for light let's listen well to the nylon yeah I don't have you been following
this story I'm gonna open it up right now BBC it's a one blogger let me see what is her name
Sierra right her last name is Sierra uh wait what's her first name oh man I suck okay
I don't know if you've seen this kind what is her first name I can't even find her first name
okay Sierra Miss Sierra as I read through the I'm I'm trying to talk and read at the same time which is
basically impossible for men she received a number of death threats on her blog and so this is whole
thing back and forth and they were they were definitely not nice you know like pictures of a news and
you know and talk of slicing her throat and I'm not gonna get into the whole thing but
turns out that someone who had accident you know someone's uh profile or identity or email was
hacks so someone else was clearly using that a fantastic story someone was apparently using
this other person's identity to post these uh well of course if you're threatening to kill someone
I'd say these illegal comments and so this is resulted in and I will put a link on the
in the show notes a daily source code dot com so you can read this story this is a result in
a call for a blogging code of conduct and let me see there was some excellent quotes here from
Miss Sierra uh here we go these people are interested in rage and they think that if you aren't
in rage then you are part of the problem it seems that they hate my optimism they think I am
poisoning people's minds with my positive outlook I guess she's a marketing consultant or something
she looks kind of hot in a milky sort of way which is nice so and then there's the you know
there's a lot of people weighing in saying oh this only happens with women a Kathy Sierra that's
her name I'm sorry Kathy Sierra um you know that women are more susceptible to this and I'm saying
bullshit I'm saying bullshit to the whole thing to the code of conduct bullshit to your uh every
single one of you is whiny you know your full of shit this is Andy Warhol's prediction come true
this is your 15 minutes of fame in this what's happened this what this is what happens
I've been getting death threats for half my life I've had people actually stick a fucking knife up
to my throat my Patricia would say because I'm not a very likable guy but it doesn't matter this is
what it is you know you put yourself out there you grow an audience this is exactly what's going
to happen it comes in all forms and it is it is it is hate it is rage but it says people projecting
it's so easy to do it get over yourself you know stop stop blogging that's the best for you stop
because this will never stop a code of conduct is not going to help it's human nature this is what
we're learning about the internet this is where this is human nature this is what we do is a human
race I've known it for 20 years we're sick but maybe on the other hand this is really beautiful
because people can say these things and and get them out there and and unload whatever tension they have
I got to think about that one but get over yourself you're fucking
blogging code of conduct oh yeah people it's the same thing as paper post that I've never talked
about that on the show because it's that everyone is fucking selling something you know whether you're
being paid by another company to to to to blog about something to post something you know or say
something favorable about a product look at your own weblog you're probably not saying that you're
a dick you're probably you know trumping up yourself I should try that tonight a little bit
of trumping up myself sorry honey I was trumping up myself in the shower
so it's like please and that does kind of come back to nylon my lungs comment you know this
stuff is happening the mayhem and the anarchy that you're looking for is happening and and I know
for sure that it's going to take a lot more time for it to get a lot more worse before it gets any
better and that's with all media we're in the middle of one huge one huge confusion look at look
it I mean I'm from I remember we didn't have cell phones I'm sorry it sounds so lame but so much
is happening such a short amount of time and we're just learning how these hammers and screwdrivers
and machetes work and one of those machetes is a beautiful wheelbarrow called serious satellite
radio and I'm about to close the window on that puppy listeners stay with us more of the pod show
on serious continues for those of you brave enough to hang around or actually going directly
to the source for the show hi Adam this is Billy and this is Jordan and Henry and we just want to say
thanks so much for mentioning this on the DSC the other day we really yeah and thanks again for telling
Adam about our show and you said you check out our show 10 minute bullets and that would be
pretty great and Adam by the way anytime man that you want to be on our show that will be awesome you've
got a standing invitation man thank you all right and our show is pretty cool it's a daily show
time to song and it keeps you up to date with the daily news and three of us take turns hosting
pretty much and yeah we rotate hosting duties which we totally stole that idea of BG blast obviously
and we also have 10 correspondence from around the world fellow team pilot gasters and they appear
on the show pretty regularly we talk about everything from Britney Spears to RR and latest technology news
and Adam say if you want to get a show it's at ten minute blip dot pod show dot com or just ten minute blip
dot com and you got a standing invitation or the hundredth episode all right thank you for the
very important sounding background music that it does add I have to agree jersey Todd sent me a gmail
subject of the email you'll get a kick out of this well you know Todd doesn't have to send me anything
with any subject and I'll still open it but he uh he points me to the site called it's pizzizz dot com
and uh pizzizz is what is it uh a personal life coaching system energy and stress health and fitness
hypnosis nlp system and what it is is well actually you know what let's listen to the yeah
I think it's the CEO or the founder have a thing of him on the website he'll explain exactly what
it is I'm fascinated by this stuff as you know with our infamous senseo berpa system we've proven
that advertising uh even just um well that wasn't really advertising I wasn't getting paid for it
but the things can be linked can be anchored in your mind so that when you see something
or you'll think of whatever it's anchored to I know that many people today still when they hear a
burp think either daily source code or senseo hello I'm Edward Lying see a very relevant
Edward your audio sucks dude I hope you guys can hear it it's it's a little flash thingy on
their website let's just let me just see if if this is bearable
but I'm possessed because this was created to help people reach their full potential both at work
and at leisure and they're currently two suffer matches the first energizer is designed to help
you to relax, destress and re-energize the second module sleep to help you to switch off at the
end of a busy day and get the most beneficial and restful sleep possible unlike other relaxation
tapes and CDs because this software allows you to choose the length of this time anything between
10 and 60 minutes okay now I realize that in the middle of this I downloaded this wonderful demo
they had they've made available and uh I can't find it oh crap hold on a second I want to see if
this stuff actually works okay I've got it here check this out
now that you've taken this time to rest and recharge it's a good idea to ensure that you'll not be
and that you can be as comfortable as possible both physically and mentally find a position for
your body where you can relax completely so that it's easy for you to let go of the events of the
day so far for a little while that you'll get as much benefit as possible from this time out
you can continue relaxing comfortably while I offer some preliminary ideas and suggestions
for a little more great 12-chus coffee at any time you can make my voice fade into the background
gently relaxing your attention to what has was comfortable and split down pleasant and solid
split down better sugar all you need to do is let you body in your mind become and
relax to try not be an effortless and efficient man and when you're never in time it's
complete I'm going to wait until we join your day and relax to refresh and I'm going to
wow now simply relax okay I got to turn this down because I'm too relaxed
is this love you know check this out pauses.com and download their free I think it's like a
like a 15-minute free energizer track listen to this stuff just really jammed the buds in really
really derives if you haven't already take a moment to stretch your body you're neck
arms hands back legs and feet and allow yourself to look sure it in that feeling
you
don't know what it's coming to but I see the world do different I just let
there seems like we're coming through so many other super visual age going crazy people
amazed me act so hasty rest I'm in it then they call you lazy whilst the game went gone
and same well chasing money till it brings us pain and it's so plain to see the we need to
snap back to reality on it's so plain to see the we need to snap back snap back to reality
snap back in my living room looking at the TV telling me I want to wear around dreaming
I've another day when I get away from the walls that keep me there why do I care up so
I want to wear up the reasons that I sit and stare at to the scene man on the screen I
long to live inside the TV dreamer it's so plain to see the we need to snap back to reality
on it's so plain to see the we need to snap back snap back to reality
don't see who represents me not the TV not my MP not the MC not the MTV talking
so big but what's empty will it talk about cash ego plenty ego's in trick and then ego's in
tree make me feel sick but can't prevent me from a fancy mine dreamer but no reality
where I'm a member of a world society and I'll be keeping my individuality I know
I don't need religion or freedom I don't need a culture or freedom I just keep on
planting my seed a positive idea because I believe that I as long as I can see
on it's so plain to see the we need to snap back to reality
on it's so plain to see the we need you
on the we need you
on it's too plain to see the we need you
her
she said
you
who are about a
agree
Oh, man. I was looking at an app so I wanted to play a song that sounds just like it.
Uh-huh. All right. I'll have to play the song again.
I'm not going to tell you what it was, but if you guess it, send me an email at
them at podshow.com. DailySourceCo.com for the show notes. I'll be back tomorrow
with the Lady Patricia for a Fubar Friday. Meet you right here.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.