Dromatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise cancelling headphones
and work, home or travel, shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones, Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good.
You're a gotta-see at him, putting on a show when you're feeling like shit, that's great stuff.
You don't man, Adam Curry, bring on the DSC-696.
It's Monday morning and I'm back in work again, thank you for telling me to work until I'm dead.
I've got a boss man and he's spent being the man.
I should have died and I wish I was in bed, it's Monday morning and I'm back in work again.
Get the boss man and he's in work until I'm dead.
I've got a boss man and he's spent being the man.
Don't you ever know that he's in jail.
But don't you ever know that he's in jail.
Something I've heard before I am in my way.
Loading his friends when I'm home and got his fame.
I've been so bad shot.
But don't you ever know that he's in jail.
Oh yeah.
A soundtrack to my life for sure.
At least to track to it.
Airborne.
I'm so sick.
You don't ever love about punk rock.
And of course this comes from the podseg music network.
Just about the moment you're thinking.
And this song is actually a bunch of noise.
Then it's over.
It's always short.
Two minutes to 12 seconds.
Love it.
Hey everybody.
Episode number 696.
It's a palindrome.
Still in San Francisco.
Looks pretty much like when to be here the rest of the week.
But it's okay.
Except for the weather, which today was raining, which was really shitty.
I had an okay night.
I went to bed after the after the show last night.
I slept through most of the night.
I slept through a couple of phone calls, which is pretty extraordinary for me.
I have the phone literally next to my bed.
And I have that because, you know, if it's anything with the girls, I want them to be able to call me.
It wasn't them, of course, who called me as other people who thought I was back in the UK.
You know, text messages go off.
So I didn't hear any of them.
I was really out for the counts.
Still, you know, much better.
I had my first real food.
I had some oatmeal at the office this morning.
And much better.
Much much better.
I still a little bit shaky and going real easy on what I'm eating.
But what a day, huh?
I would say pretty much this report that came out from the EIN.
I believe it is.
We said that well, guess why do Ron has no nuclear weapons program?
Hasn't had it for, you know, everyone's saying four years.
But it's almost five years now.
We hit 2008.
And exactly as expected, the spin is a word dangerous.
It can be dangerous.
That will be dangerous.
It's like, come on, please, we're not going to let it happen, right?
We are not going to let it happen again.
So there's no weapons of mass destruction.
It's not there.
Obviously, you're going to, you know, keep an eye on what everyone's doing for different reasons.
But maybe the proper response, Mr. President, represented of the people,
would have been, hey, you know, I'm really happy.
That's pretty damn cool.
All right, dudes.
We had to go and run.
You know, we should chill and have a beer at the ranch.
You know, it looks like we're in compliance.
We're, we understand each other.
So I don't have a lot of energy today.
I just don't physically have it.
In fact, what time is it now?
It's 10, 10, 10, 10, 10.
Everybody, 10 pass the hour here in the Curry Condu.
That would mean it's much, it's tomorrow.
We know, Australia.
It's tomorrow everywhere, basically.
But luckily, a lot of comments came in,
particularly in response to yesterday's show 6, 9 or 5.
And the first one is about the clip from Eisenhower that I played.
And I didn't realize this before I heard this comment come in.
Hey, Adam, it's Paul, the tech guy from Kirkland, Washington.
What we're talking about was at 6.95.
You know, you had interesting thing.
You had eye con there.
Eisenhower.
And it's amazing.
Wait, hold on.
What's amazing to me is you said you had an eye con there.
And the first thing that shot into my mind was like a desktop eye con.
And it took me, I'm sure there are other people out there.
It took me a second to figure out he was talking about a person.
Eisenhower as the eye con.
I just wanted to mess with your brain because I knew it was happening with it.
It's amazing.
You think it's amazing how intelligent he sounds and how together he sounds
and how why he sounds and his speech is president compared to what we have today.
I mean, you listen to today where you used to listen to this guy that seems to really have some forethought
into the world is interesting.
Anyway, just a little thing.
I like I too.
I guess anyway.
Oh, and I love you.
Adam Curry.
All right.
Yeah, you know, and absolutely right.
And you go back.
If you hadn't heard, if you didn't hear, yes, there's episode.
Go back and listen to it.
He did have so he sounded like a leader.
You know, and he was making some sense there.
It wasn't just a part of the show, part of the big show.
For those of you who are really active on the show and go to dailysourceco.com
and check out the comments.
There's always, you know, there's always at least three or four comments for every episode.
I never say there's really a whole bunch of them.
But this one guy I think is Bill Gilton or I think is his name.
In fact, we'll find out for sure in a second.
He's always posting something in the comments.
And in fact, he's, I think the only person I ever said,
Yo, you know, Bill, he's up on all the embeddable videos and stuff.
It's not entirely on topic.
And but he's, he's a savant in his own right.
I think he may go a little bit too far to the extreme on some of the,
some of the conspiracy.
I don't want to say conspiracy theories.
And some of the theories, just theories, that he's following.
But Bill called in and I'm happy he called in for once because, you know,
it gives me a little chance and gives all of us little chance to,
to listen to the guy and find out a little bit more about him.
And it's a, he actually hit the cut off on the, on the comment call in.
But I think we should all take a listen because he is,
with it out, a part of the Charlie family.
And certainly the comments about.
Hey, and I'm, it's Bill, you're holding her from Austin, Texas.
I've been enjoying your podcast even though I haven't called in for quite a while.
And I've been amazed overall looking back at the year of,
of, 2007.
The amount of grounds you've covered on the DSE.
It's been pretty amazing.
And I never would have expected you would have started the,
I know agenda podcast that John, to, to Borough.
And that's been quite entertaining.
Overall there's just been a lot of material to review and enjoy
through podcasting.
And I would just want to appreciate that.
I'm not sure I can, want to say a lot of you,
but I understand that it's,
Well, that technically violates the rules of commenting,
but I'll let you slide.
The change as you announced on your,
the DSE today to maybe get away from the old ad,
but that let's see.
I agree with you completely about the political analysis,
how it's all just a big show.
And especially when it comes to this idea
that how could be is going to be,
you know,
I've been coming horse,
and you know,
it's, you might as well have a big person
and somebody to call the horse race as it goes.
You know, and let me just repeat that.
I really believe that how could be is being played.
He's being played by the media that they're going to toss him up like,
like an orca whale does with a sea line.
You know,
you know,
they bat him around for a while.
That's what I think.
I think it's a total set up.
I could be wrong and, you know,
power to the guy.
He actually says a lot of things that Ron Paul says.
I don't agree with everything he says.
And I, you know,
I've chosen my guy for this, for this round,
for this time around.
And of course,
the Chuck Norris thing was funny.
That was, that was very cool.
But I have a feeling he's being played,
and he's going to,
they're going to tear him to shreds.
As much as it means.
But underneath of course,
all our lives are all are affected,
and we do need to figure out
some way to get control of this whole mess.
And if you think you're feeling old,
I'll be turning 50 here in a few months.
So you can imagine that your discussion of Abby Hoffman,
and that was more of an early 70s kind of teenager,
but definitely I had the idea that we were trying to whip
a bunch of these problems way back went,
and boy is that turned out to be a joke.
Some ways, I think,
the situations a lot worse and more dire than you do.
I definitely listened to Alex Jones,
although it's good to listen to him.
I don't think he's really someone he can
can lead us anywhere,
so I think he turns a lot of people off.
So I have mixed ideas when you start mentioning
some of the things that are associated with
the more crazy conspiracy stuff.
But as you may know,
I post there at 911truth.podshow.com.
I post some things that other people think
or some of the wackiest conspiracy that could be imagined.
So I guess to each zone,
it was kind of funny to listen to Carmen Tyler's podcast
and find out that she knew how to be evidently.
She had some interaction with him over the years,
and is knows in pretty well
from one way or another.
She didn't say she supported him.
She just said it was funny to
know a presidential candidate like that personally,
which is entertaining.
Anyway, so I'm rambling on.
Thanks for providing the pod show
and all the personalities and
regardless of whether we whip some of these
fundamental governmental problems.
And that's where it ends, unfortunately.
Because I know he's going to say he loves me at the end of that
comment.
Thanks Bill.
I'll go to the next time if you don't mind.
Actually, while Bill was talking,
I ran quick to the bedroom here in the condo.
To grab the weekend edition of the financial
times, which is printed,
well, it's probably printed locally,
but it's,
uh,
a lot of the editorial comes from the UK.
Here it is.
I found it.
Thank goodness.
They also have, obviously,
they have journalists in the states.
This is a piece written by
Christia Freeland.
And,
it's a really interesting piece.
Of course, I'm not going to read the whole thing to you.
But it's, it really caught my eye when I read it.
It starts off by saying,
by stereotype,
America is a pretty optimistic place.
In my personal experience,
I've found that to be true.
Even in New York,
I don't have a lot of light here,
so I'm kind of,
I'm reading by the light of the laptop.
Even in New York,
which pride itself on being tougher than the
sunny heart loons.
Half a dozen people urge me to have a nice day
by the time I get to my desk each morning.
Yet this land of Disney and a motocons seems
rather downbeat at the moment,
particularly about its own role in the world.
The post-cold war expectation of an era
of the easy and benign American dominance
now looks hopelessly romantic.
And she goes on to talk about,
really all of the,
all of the problems that the states
is going through,
you know,
how the rest of the world
certainly can view us.
And she's viewing it through the eyes
of basically a European.
But what I really liked
is the way she wraps it up.
Let me see if I can get to the right spot
here, hold on.
Crap, I wish I had more light.
And you're sitting there going,
like, get on with it already, curry.
Here we go.
So of course, a lot about the sub-prime crisis.
And winds up us saying openness.
So, you know, what are the,
I want to find the right spot to jump into this.
It's too long.
Openness is valuable in and of itself.
Once we are safe and fed,
liberty isn't enduring human need.
But even if that sounds to you like the abstraction
of a latte drinking liberal,
I think you will agree that openness
to money, to ideas, to people
is one of the most important drivers
of which economies will flourish
in which ones will founder in the coming century.
By all means, watch how the supreme saga unfolds.
But if you want to know if America will remain great,
look to whether investors from Abu Dhabi remain welcome.
College kids continue to found new Facebooks
and immigrants for all the pre-election
fewer continue to make their homes here.
And I thought, you know,
and you have to, if you can get it,
I'll see if I can put a link to this article.
If it's available online,
you really have to read the whole thing because
it does give a view of America
in a way that I agree with.
And that there is something that remains to be very special here
in the United States.
Just as I'm sure,
and I wish I could get some Iranians on this show,
we have no idea what Iranians are really like.
Please.
If you know an Iranian,
if you know someone living in Iran,
please get me in touch with them.
Let's talk.
I hear that, you know,
90% of that country is like under 30 years old.
I know they have internet.
I can speak a little bit of French,
maybe some of them speak some English.
We can work it out.
We need to get a long people.
And I need to switch gears for a second.
Happy holidays, Adam.
Yeah, I'm happy holidays and Merry Christmas
from the Daddycast, from the Love House to your house.
Ah, lovely.
Yeah, let's talk about that for a second.
You know what?
To kick it off as we're talking about the holidays.
Yeah, come on.
I'm sweating.
You're breaking out.
I beat up a satellite repair man
coming after you.
satellite repair man.
What's he gonna do?
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions too.
There's nothing in the universe
so he can't do for you.
satellite repair man.
Woo, woo, woo.
Man, I am so glad you dropped the closing
expletive requirement for voice comments on the DSC.
That was just something I was not really comfortable
with saying to my boss.
I've gotten myself on enough trouble without
ever telling the boss.
Damn, I almost said it.
Yeah, at least not to my face, Peter.
I get you.
But hey, I'm here to pimp my own show digital
I've got some the latest episode features yours truly
reading the famous night before Christmas
from my earliest memories
reading that poem on Christmas Eve
was a tradition in my house
and I am now extending it to everyone's house
as my happy Christmas wish to all.
I love you, Adam Curry.
No, really.
Yeah, I love you too, Peter.
For sure.
Adam, it's a monster even in San Francisco Bay area.
Hey, Steve.
That's really sucks.
I don't get it.
The kind of stuff has the tendency to travel.
Yeah.
Okay, so I mean this in no sense with no sense whatsoever
to Mr. Steve Webb.
Oh, that's always the setup.
I mean no offense.
Here it comes.
I'm really getting sick of people
accusing somebody or other
out there of trying to get
word rid of the word Christmas
and replace it with happy holidays.
That very Christmas goes away
and we're all saying happy holidays.
Now, dude, appreciate it.
It's not happening.
It's in your head.
It's a made up conspiracy.
Nobody's freaking doing that.
I see no offense, but you know, it's in your head.
I've got a song.
One of my favorite Christmas songs.
Andy Williams singing happy holidays
from the freaking early 60s.
It's not before.
It's not happening.
Nobody's nobody.
There's no conspiracy against Christmas.
You're listening to Bill Riley or one of those other Irish idiots.
There is so conspiracy.
So Boston cuisine.
Stop it.
Fuck you Adam Curry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait a minute.
That's not okay.
So I'm Steve again.
Obviously, I didn't get all the way through the podcast.
He ended my comment the wrong way.
I do love you.
Adam Curry.
Yeah.
I want to make babies with you.
Okay.
All right. That's enough.
Yeah, man.
You know, I think what
Steve looked from the life-spring family of podcasts.
What Steve Webb is probably hearing is that advertising
has done away with Christmas,
advertising has made it into happy holidays.
And this is just because advertising wants
the biggest bank for your book.
It's a lot cheaper to say,
let me see if I can get the the the
Christians, the Jews all in one shot.
By the way, happy Hanukkah.
Don't we like the first candle tonight?
Where are those phone calls?
Excuse me, I'm for clement.
I got to play the Hanukkah song.
There's a couple of them on the podcast.
Music, now we're tomorrow.
Remind me.
That's what it is.
Andy Rooney, I saw him.
I'm like sick bed.
I was watching 60 minutes.
I saw Andy Rooney.
And he had exactly the segment.
He showed all of the catalogs that were jammed through
his mailbox for Christmas for the holiday season.
And not a single one said Merry Christmas or happy Hanukkah.
They all or happy quans.
Whatever.
So much out there.
They all say happy holidays and it's just because it's cheaper that way.
You know, you want to don't want to reach just one segment.
You want to reach the you want your dollar to go further.
It's that easy.
So I think that's what's really happening.
I have to agree.
And I'm enjoying all the Christmas movies.
I love all the, you know, how I saw the one with Jacqueline Smith.
Or she's flying a sessna over like the Arctic or
Alaska or something.
God.
I had a crush on her.
I still do really.
She was always kind of a milk.
And she's awesome.
Jacqueline Smith.
And then what happened to her?
Didn't she do the Kmart ads for a while?
Or Kmart?
I can't remember.
Anyway.
Here's what we'll do.
Let's do something completely different from normal.
Instead of playing, and again, I'm just going to run through more comments
because there's so many good ones that came in.
Let's just keep it in the Christmas vibe with a little, a little Christmas
Diddy will do DSC style.
Ready?
Let's bang your head.
The monster balance for the podcast music network.
This is ducking.
And then watch out.
You better not cry.
Better not come till you.
Why?
Santa Claus is coming.
To town.
She's making a list.
And shaking the twice.
Gonna find that last night.
And nice.
Santa Claus is coming.
To town.
He sees you when you're sleeping.
He knows when you're awake.
He knows if you think that or not.
So be good for good.
You say you know.
Better watch out.
You better not cry.
Better not come up till you.
Why?
Santa Claus is coming.
To town.
I almost makes it sound like no fun.
Let's go.
the press about Santa comment.
He's like...
Oh yeah, duck in.
Hey, speaking of Santa Claus coming to town.
Hello, Adam Curry. This is Oscar from the Netherlands.
So, I guess I don't know what kind of feel you're taking,
but I think it's red, very red, and...
Well, it kind of made you sick.
So, what is that coming here?
Too much red.
Anyway, I wish you a good health, and just when they need to go to San Francisco,
I hope the weather stays good, because the press deck is really fucked up on Thursday and Friday.
I need to go through the birthday area well, for some kind of meeting.
So, I don't know, man.
What are you doing?
I just wish you a good health, and you're really sounded really down,
and I hope everything goes very well with you.
Well, that's it. Oh, and...
Yeah.
I love you, Adam Curry.
Thank you.
By the way, if you've called in and you said it once, you don't have to say it every single time.
Unless you really want to, obviously.
Here's something interesting.
This was a very interesting call. I had to think about it a couple of times before I finally...
I think before I finally figured it out, and it's... well, let's listen to an older.
Hi, Alan.
This is Eric from Iowa, and I just had the call in, because I had the weirdest thing happen.
I just heard that I didn't have anybody else, but my husband must have some sort of weird virus on his computer
that he was just on internet and just playing around, and any max voice topped up and started talking.
It's the weirdest thing it was like one of our shows was playing,
but there was no windows open or anything.
You never even heard who Amy Mac was, and it's just something you're sure that I even knew who Amy Mac was.
So, I don't know if you have anybody else in this problem, or if there's a virus coming around where some pod shows
like start popping up and playing a people's computer.
I decided it was weird.
I'm glad you're back.
Alright, first of all, love the voice, send me naked pictures.
Your husband was not... I mean, what did you say?
He was just surfing around the computer.
He was looking for porn, first of all, home I was.
Listen, what was my husband doing?
Yeah, yeah.
My husband must have some sort of weird virus on his computer that he was on internet.
Yeah, just on the internet.
Was the webcam on?
No, look.
Clearly, he was surfing for porn.
Actually, I thought about this and like, well, this is kind of weird.
I don't want to troubleshoot everyone's computer problems,
but to think you have a virus that makes Amy Mac play on your computer,
I see as a feature.
So I'm like, this is great.
What is going on?
And then I remember, we've been doing a whole bunch of experiments with promoting the network.
Folks, there's a Google group.
If you're a pod show producer, you should join that.
There's a Google group.
Marcus couch maintains it right now, and we talk shit amongst ourselves.
Really talk shit, which is fun.
And so I've mentioned it there.
And we've been trying different ways of promoting.
And I recall, and I, you know, first of all, I hate pop-ups, pop-unders, windows,
and crap shit like that, that just I hate it.
So we would never do that.
But on the peer-to-peer networks, you now have advertising opportunities.
And I know that we've done some test runs, advertising on peer-to-peer networks.
And the way that works, apparently, and as someone set me a screenshot of it the other week,
is that it pops up a browser window with an ad.
And in this case, that probably would have been a flash video of Amy Mack show.
Now, it couldn't have been on any other type of advertising network,
because they don't allow you to have sound on by default.
So I think it was probably from a peer-to-peer network.
And it's kind of, it's kind of interesting the way these things work.
And obviously, it's not working.
It's quite annoying because, you know, if you can't see where it's coming from, then something's not right.
So let's try and figure this one out.
Call back.
Let me know.
And, you know, your husband clearly was surfing on a, he was on peer-to-peer.
Looking for porn.
So don't feel bad when you send me the naked picture.
And let's see if we can work this one out.
Because that's highly annoying.
That's not advertising.
That's annoying.
But, of course, it may be to get your husband to check out Amy Mack.
So, yeah, who knows, right?
Hey, Adam.
It's Jeff Sass here calling you after a nice early morning running along the beach.
And beautiful South Florida opening through the beach.
Nice.
Well, the 800 and the 10th.
I bought it in 800, which I love.
Thanks to your recommendation.
I'm using it as my mobile phone in Europe with Skype.
Since I don't have a GSM phone.
I'm a sprint customer, otherwise.
But mine is in mint conditions.
Beautifully cared for in a nice leather case.
And I'm trying to figure out what to do with it when I upgrade to the N810 as soon as you put your special offer available.
So maybe I show.
For some of you guys can organize some sort of a.
Exchange or swap or maybe.
For those listeners, you don't want to spring the full price for it.
A 10.
But want to get a great and a hundred at a good deal.
Maybe you guys can help facilitate that.
And anyway, let's be forward to the deal.
Hopefully in time for Christmas.
Talk to you soon.
Yeah.
And by the way, I've gotten a lot of reports for people saying that they put the new OS 2008 on their N800.
And that they love it.
You know, it's optimized.
I think that's the same processor.
A lot of the bits in these two machines are the same.
Of course, the the slide out keyboard is the main main difference in this.
Some dimensional aspects that there's a lot of differences.
But the new OS definitely is a huge improvement over the previous one.
A lot of the things work much better out of the box like the media player finally makes sense.
Of course, the the browser, the Mozilla Gmail Google Docs.
You just can't beat it.
I'm doing Gmail on this thing all the time.
Now with a shortcut keys.
I mean, there's no command.
No mouse.
So I know touch that can beat that.
Nothing beats the keyboard in just some cases, which is why, you know,
the same JK commands NP commands and O and V are having used for decades in computering.
Because it's just easier.
But we could set up an exchange.
I mean, you could post it on daily source code dot com or curry dot com.
I mean, anyway, like that.
I'm sure that would be a good way.
And, you know, looking at the prices these days on Amazon that go in for like a hundred bucks.
So you might just want to hold on to it turn it into a web server or something.
It's a little low.
You can get a web server package.
So you could have a wireless web server wherever you go.
I mean, there's all kinds of fun things.
You could do with it.
You know, you could shit.
You know, I just thought, you know, all this talk about the hundred dollar laptop.
One laptop or child thing.
There you go.
Giving the $100 and $800.
That's a laptop.
It would beat every other project.
Send it to send it to the third world countries.
That's actually not a bad idea.
No case to think about that.
What a great PR idea that is.
We have the the $100 laptop.
There you go.
You know, people hand crank on that sucker.
They sell.
Don't the for these cell phones.
You can get solar chargers.
Yeah.
I think I just came up with a real idea.
All right.
I got a couple of way.
31 minutes.
Okay.
I can bore you guys some more.
Actually, I'm not going to bore you because it's always exciting when you hear this.
Jingo.
Come extra.
Hello.
Speaking of military industrial complex of USA.
The GPS system has been conceived and created by US military to be able
to precisely bump somebody.
And when US Army conducts military operations like, for example, bumping some country,
then GPS system is being authenticated by US Army.
And location fix will civilians like yourself is impossible.
Yeah.
Okay.
A little translation.
So yes, be.
So this is about the global positioning system.
And indeed, since it is owned and controlled by the United States,
it can be jammed.
There's all kinds of shit that can be done to it.
You know, it took years to just get the accuracy back by discrampling some bits.
I am, of course, paraphrasing what actually went on.
A lot of people depend on it.
But it's kind of, it's kind of frightening to think that for, for certain reasons, it could just get turned off.
You know, God forbid, we have to go back to finding VORs and NDBs to shoot our approaches.
I mean, Jesus, how will I fly if I don't have my GPS?
How will I find my way home in my car?
Hmm.
So I think, me thinks that it is good idea that you appear in your own.
It's just agreed to finance.
And after all, complete Galileo, Galileo positioning system, which is more precise than GPS.
And right from the scratch created from, from peaceful purposes.
Galileo will be built after all with bases in Germany and Italy.
For the control centers.
By the way, are you coming to Barcelona to mobile work congress in February next year, Adam?
You?
Where's my love you?
Yeah.
I don't know, maybe.
Maybe I'll come.
Ah, excuse me, I'm cramping.
Um, yes, so, um, comics are blogger.
I'd love to know if there are any extra bits that are throwing into the Galileo system.
So, and, and by the way, it's, it's a, it's a beautiful gesture.
I totally agree.
It's like we're putting a shining star, a beam of light up into the sky.
Uh, for anyone to use to develop and create fantastic applications with the knowledge that you're shooting kind of break one day.
Is there extra stuff that they're putting in there that goes above and beyond the current global positioning system?
I'd love to know.
I'm sure you have an idea.
Hey, Canada.
Canada bringing, uh, bringing in some comments now.
It's nice to have people in Canada listening.
All right.
I have a feeling there's, uh, there's a lot of, uh, consumption of independent media in Canada.
Just seems like the Canadians are that way, you know what I mean?
Hey, Adam, it's Kevin Colling from Ottawa.
Canada's national capital.
There you go.
Uh, long time listener, first time caller.
Thank you.
Uh, love the show.
And, like, most hate the nylon.
However, what's with the whole Ron Paul reach around overall the deal?
The reach around.
A few months.
It can be great that you've been on the drone.
But I don't have to say this delicately, but have you actually read his platform?
Other than the whole constitutional thing, which is kind of a simple minded approach.
But actually, no, he's not simple minded. He certainly has strong convictions and interesting fellow.
But the answers to all the world's hills do not fall into the US Constitution.
Uh-huh.
That's correct.
That is absolutely correct.
It is also not meant as the answer to all of the world's hills.
It is meant as the blueprint for the way.
America's supposed to function.
So it's not saying that it changes all the world's hills.
But I think a lot of it could affect the world in a very positive way.
If you're looking to hire, sir, if you're looking to vote for somebody or back somebody who also.
Hey, that was a great fruity.
If you're looking to hire, yeah, that's exactly what we do hire the guy.
Okay?
We are looking to hire the president.
It is a job interview.
I love that.
That's funny.
If you're looking to hire, let me hear that again.
If you're looking to hire, sir, if you're looking to vote for somebody or back somebody who also doesn't have a chance of voting or a winning.
You certainly go for a Dennis Cassinant.
She seems to be much more in line with your values and interests.
And he's got a hug.
You've got a hot wife.
Yes.
With a tongue piercing, no less.
Yeah, I agree.
I have to say, I have to say that Cassinant definitely and he saw a UFO.
So I have to say that, and I'm not making fun of him.
I think right on to this guy.
You know, this is a lot of other stuff I don't like about him.
But yeah, right on, right on.
But yeah, just right on for him.
More in line with your values and your interests.
And he's even got a hot wife that you can ask for.
Make it pictures of.
However, I don't think Ron Paul is a crackpot.
I just think he's a pro.
And more importantly, his platform is kind of out of whack.
I mean, the guy wants to abolish the UN.
You know, yeah.
Okay, I'll let you go through all these.
Pulling out of the UN would be horrendous for while the fairs.
He wants to eliminate federal government agencies,
which is probably not a great idea to eliminate them completely.
Yes, they can be inefficient, but my God, that's crazy.
I mean, that's not really, you know, really
Robudding anything just by saying that's crazy.
Okay.
And I think you're drawing conclusions out of the platform.
I think, you know, you're,
I don't think you're really analyzing his platform,
which is the Constitution.
First property rights on environment,
which means he won't do anything to help
environment to protect protection from a national standpoint,
which is horrible from an environmental standpoint.
You know, I think I think that you are making that up.
That you're saying that he won't do that.
I don't think anywhere he said,
I won't do this.
And also he's positioned himself.
I think he's really fairly positioned himself as a transition.
A transition from where we are to where we should be.
It's going to take a lot longer than the possible eight years that he could do it.
So I think that's what he's saying.
And consistently I've heard him say,
no, you can't just cut everyone off from everything
and change everything overnight.
It just, nothing works like that.
You can't snap your fingers and have all troops from 130 countries
around the world home.
You know, this transition, that takes years.
Years and years to do that to set it up right.
And it's going to take a while.
It's going to take a decade for us to change course.
And we're going to get any kind of real cotton.
And that's important.
There's no quick fixed all this, my friend.
There is no quick fix.
There's no shortcuts.
It's not like, you know, you saw it with the Democrats in Congress.
Well, boy, that really changed everything, didn't it?
Not about that.
So I don't know.
All I can say is you should really take a look at his actual issues.
Like how he stands on the issues because they're kind of scary.
If that's the approach he wants to take.
Other guys on the Democratic side.
I know you're not on a Democrat or Republican have much different ideas.
That are certainly much more in line with progressive thinking.
I think the progressive thinking has nothing to do with the government.
The government has a very specific role and the progressive thinking comes from the citizens.
And we need to have the room to be progressive thinkers and to live our life as a community in a progressive way.
Okay, that's not the government's role to be progressive for us.
You know, I guess to end it.
Oh, one last thing.
DS6A, one mad at how I'm not going to take anymore.
Absolutely loved that episode.
It was one of my favorite interests for a while.
So to end it, folder, sit and tinkles and fuck you, Adam Curry.
No, no, I'm sorry.
I mean, I love you, Adam Curry.
I mean, I love you.
Not in a gay way though.
Anyone more can you ask for Adam, first man, and Curry.
The best food in the planet.
Have a great day.
Look forward to listening to more.
Take care.
Oh, man.
If you ever listened to Costa's world, we'll find it on pod joke.
Go to costosworld.com, Tony Price.
He does his great show in Los Angeles.
And Andy did this one.
I've talked about it with him about it.
It's a couple of times it's really funny.
It's just thing that black guys will do to each other.
And I say, hey, man, I love you.
No homo.
It's essentially just the white guy version of it.
Not in a gay way.
It's okay.
It's all okay if it's in a gay way too.
Don't worry about it.
I'm cool.
Hello, Adam.
I'm time to listen.
First time, caller.
My name's Andy.
I live in Portland, Oregon.
I was listening to you by this in all your shows.
But 65, you asked about
So you asked for us to think about how to affect change.
And I just wanted to respond to your earlier comment in that show.
Where you say, you don't think of matters.
Who's the president.
And I think that that attitude has gotten my generation.
I'm just a couple years younger than you.
But I think my generation of people has taken that to heart.
We realize that for a long time.
Ever since Reagan, essentially, that doesn't matter.
Both parties are the same.
It's not a two party system.
It's a one party system.
And it's self defeating attitudes.
And I think I don't think you really think that.
But because you are still, you know, supporting Ron Paul.
And I have a problem with Ron Paul's.
You know, strict constitutionalism.
And, you know, strict property rights interpretation of the constitution.
Because, you know, this is the second call about the property rights.
So let me know exactly what you mean by that.
Go in a little detail.
Because I do want to understand it.
Because property really is at the basis and the foundation of the constitution.
By the way, you don't own the land that your house is on.
Just so you know, actually in Texas, you mind.
I think that's the only state left in the union where you actually can loan.
Can earn the actual land that your house is sitting on.
Which is why you pay property taxes.
And you don't own your car.
Funny enough.
This is, this is really true.
The government owns your car.
Okay.
That's why they can tax you on it.
It's kind of like interest for you using it.
You know, look into it.
It's really true.
You don't own your car even if you think you do.
Even if you have a certificate of title.
That's not an actual ownership document.
We could do a whole another show on that.
But I'd like to know what this thing is about property.
Please let me know.
The matter for this one.
I mean, is if you can get elected a third party of a person who's not a member.
Or strictly other Republican or Democratic party.
But what we need in this country.
I think is a labor party of party.
You know, the thing with independence or anything outside of these two parties.
Of course, it would be great to have a third party or a fourth party.
But running as an independent, you have to be a billionaire to get on TV.
You know, you have to spend so much money to get into the debates, to get into the forum,
to get into the public forum.
It's almost impossible.
The system is truly fucked.
I have the people.
And so far, the Republicans have been that.
And the laborers have been behind the Republicans and their support of the war.
Something has to change in the attitude.
The other thing I want to say is your dollar is your vote.
Vote with your money.
So, as you've been saying, follow the money.
Well, yeah, send your money.
Decide who is invested in the war and don't buy their products.
I don't buy anything from GE if I can help it.
I don't, you know, I have a few thousand dollars invested in all green investments.
You have to be careful where you spend your money.
And that is how the difference was made in my opinion.
And I vote with my dollar.
I also voted the polls.
I try to vote for third party candidates, green candidates, libertarians and whatnot.
But anyway, I just wanted to get that out to you.
It's no longer a two party system.
I need to say another party, a labor party in this country.
And I vote with my dollar.
And it sounds like you do too.
And anyway, your dollar is your vote.
Share your own.
Yeah, I'd like that a lot.
No, I'd love to.
Thank you.
Hey, you know, that's a good idea.
So, since Burger King and Pizza Hut, both are involved in Iraq because I've seen it with my own two eyes.
I'm not going to eat a Burger King or Pizza Hut anymore.
I don't think you should either.
And let's compile a list.
Absolutely.
That's a great way.
Vote with your dollar.
Wall Street talks about the mighty force of the American consumers.
It's a very important number, the consumer purchasing power.
The, you know, that is like five different ways they track that.
Boy, that's really important, you know.
So, what if you had the Black Friday or Cyber Monday, but it excluded a number of companies?
Yeah, we do have that power.
That's a great idea.
Vote with your dollar.
Wow.
Great.
We vote with our dollar by spending on the candidates we, we like.
And we vote with our dollar by not spending on the companies that are basically,
that's the election is against them.
There you go.
It's really all of the candidates running against the machine.
You could call it the military industrial complex.
Whatever.
It's not just that, of course, but that's a big part of it.
And that's a very good idea.
And of course, what, what companies are attached to GE?
NBC?
So, we'll stop watching that.
Can we really do it?
Do you think you can really pull your head away from the, the box with the light?
Or just a little while?
Turn that thing off.
Really?
Turn the television off.
You're being hypnotized.
Okay?
Three years ago.
I wish I could do it right now.
I can't do it on command.
But three years ago.
I hypnotized tens of thousands of people by burping and associating
the words and say oh.
And today it still works.
What do you know?
Do you have any idea what television has been doing to your ass?
Speaking of that, if you want to domain name, the cheapest way is to go to godaddy.com
and use one of my checkout codes.
You can find a link in the show notes to find out what the RDSC1,
2 and 3 different great deals.
Wait, don't stop.
I got to hypnotize you next about Sony headphones.
They're awesome.
Go to Sony.com slash headphones.
And then there's the San Diego Hard Rock Cafe that is opening up.
And your band could be performing live on stage with black.
Black piece, black eyed piece with the hell is it?
Black piece.
I did a shitty job at hypnotizing you today.
I'm sorry.
And of course, be on the lookout for the Nokia N800 10 link.
It should be in well in time for you to order it for Christmas.
I, from what I understand, we're just waiting on the codes.
Can't wait.
I really can't wait.
Hi, everybody.
Let's wrap it up with one more.
It's actually took me a little longer than I thought.
But boy, there was a good bunch of comments in there.
And it really helped because I just,
I just don't have the energy to talk too much.
Mr. Curri, you self-guide Germany.
Do you think that Gary Alexander could get a slightly overweight 31-year-old
Always in the car sitting, that Donald's beating skills guy
in shape to do a round of fighting with one of his fighters.
If so, also interested in following this with a camera
and making a soap out of it could be kind of funny.
I am looking for a trainer.
Gary Alexander, if you can help me, let me know.
I like to fight around for soup.
Just be for Germany.
I don't care.
Let's leave it to you.
Alright, Gary Alexander.
I know he listens to the show,
or the ultimate podcast.
I wouldn't want to follow you around,
but I bet you Gary could make a pretty fun show out of it.
See, some Dutch sales guy in Germany getting his ass kicked.
Yeah, I'll be down with that.
Alright, everybody.
I appreciate you listening.
Hope it didn't bore you too much.
Hope you enjoyed the comments.
As always, Adam at podshow.com.
DailySourceco.com.
And if I keep my shit together, literally,
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Imagine headphones without wires.
Now, their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset.
A rechargeable listening experience
with 11 hours of music playback.
You and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com-headphones.
Sony wireless headphones.
Your music are unplugged.