Yo, what's Tony Costa telling you to check out this Christmas podcast.com.
It's the official podcast for the new Sony film, this Christmas,
starring Chris Brown for Genie King, Columbus Short, and an all-star cast.
The site includes a special holiday podcast from yours truly,
exclusive interviews from the stars in the film,
and a special red carpet coverage from the premiere.
You can exchange gifts, but you can't exchange family.
This Christmas is truly the next holiday classy.
See it in theaters on November 21st, and check us out at thisChristmaspodcast.com.
Welcome back to Business Insight, where tonight we have special guest Adam Curry,
the pod father and co-founder of Pod Chef.
Now, Adam, before you get off to the DSC 686,
we want to know about the special programs you have for employee retention.
Now, how have you traditionally handled employee retention?
I've worked pretty hard for the past couple of decades, so most of that I take care of myself.
Then you say take care of yourself, what exactly do you mean?
What kind of programs or offers do you make to the employee?
Karen T. Blowjob time. I'm telling you.
Do you mean let's just leave that one alone for right now.
Here is the DSC 686.
Here is the DSC 786.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
turn in the next generation rainy content in my ears.
I like to think I'm shining, to the future.
There are interesting things across his chest, prepared to lay him down to his race.
He said, I see my race is running, when I thought it had just begun.
But no, no, no, I think it's plain to see.
There's been a day in the mercury.
I hear a whisper, the voice of doom.
I hear the repair is in the room.
Night now, one time, come to the side.
Hey, hey, you know what I mean?
I think it's time to fire the night.
From a very young day, she hears a call, something back up and beyond the walls.
She stays the course on quiet streams.
But when she dreams her shy girl dreams.
She's alone on the high seas out on the day.
Begging her, please, I have no confidence, I have no choice.
What do I do with my wild heart?
Young down, slant by, one of the stars are starting to cry.
Hey, hey, you know what I mean?
I think it's time to fire the night.
From a very young day, she hears a call, something back up and beyond the walls.
Hey, hey, you know what I mean?
I think it's time to fire the night.
We march and start, we walk the line travelling through this life unkind,
Wrapped in chains to be bound
Until they put us in the cold cold ground
The leash just hands across its chest
Repair to lay him to his wrist
He said I see the time has come
My wild heart beats with the thunder of a drum
Nothing at all, it's right now
Our nature just starting to run
Hey, hey, hey, you know why
I think it's time to fire it all
Time for me come to so
It's time to strain it all
Hey, hey, you know why
It's time to try it all
Oh yeah, now that's what I'm talking about when you want to kick off the food bar just right
Some food no vocals
Have he asked us all
And you got my tip
Stone, that coyote is
Fire it up from the pot safe music network
On daddy's George code episode number six eighty six the Palomgrom at the show
Are you doing I'm back at the curry manner
I'm the affluent subversory known as gilford on the west side of Gtown
Yes
Good to be back arrived last night from Finland
Man
What an interesting place to be and what a great
It was just a great set of meetings we had up there with with the folks from Nokia
Nokia, I should say all right. I got so much to learn never been to Finland
Big country not a lot of people
I
Did one spectacular thing that I've been wanting to do for
Let me see I think this was it must have been 30 years ago
And I can't remember the circumstances although what's with my parents and I remember it was
It had to do with flying somewhere maybe it wasn't with maybe it was 20 it was long time ago
I remembered I had once had reindeer
And I had it again and I got to tell you
Man, that is that is just so nice and when it's served to you and this great restaurant we went to
They tell you exactly
What town the reindeer was from and what farm the reindeer was from and like that sounds kind of weird. Yeah, but you know, there's if we don't
Where they call it call or
Harvest the reindeer the entire country would be filled with reindeer so I guess it's in necessity
Oh, man
Give me all the power I need for a football Friday
Hey, Adam is just sitting in the hands of USA again following up. I just left you a message
But it sucked in a lot of words
Yeah, because my other things I forgot to say fuck you so fuck you. Okay. Thank you
And I had recently told you that I wasn't going to listen anymore. I had a dial out because of the political content
Uh-huh
The TSA stuff and what happened while I I'm still not digging that I couldn't stay away
Find myself looking for the DSC and if I could drive or something then I I will
Probably continue to fast forward through some parts and your main line in my friend. You can't help yourself
And I think to be all right with that so this I was calling about boil
The comment that you made that you had claimed that oil would hit $100 a bell
I do remember you saying that but it was late late summer early fall
2006 so you were a little bit ahead of the time
It wouldn't have hit that mark by the end of 2006, but obviously you're right now and
Fuck you all right, all right, so it was I
Telling you the older I get the more I witnessed this problem you've been doing this stuff for like three three years now
No wait, it's we're coming up on three and a half years we've been doing shows
Oh my goodness. Yeah, yeah, well just for you my friend. I've got something about the clear program
I'm very good morning
This is Michael calling from San Francisco
I actually kind of live all over the west coast
I've been listening to the FC for a couple years and I just had to comment about the clear program
I actually got several offers by email from Freakland's Liner and Freakland hotel programs offering me a
Complementary membership to have the TSA inspect my ass
I slide three four days a week
I absolutely see the IDC of the TSA action every day every week and the whole thing is absolutely just a joke
I another time I told him I will tell you about an interesting gift stop
I'll experience I had with the eight on the three power craze
TSA and all right at the LA expert
Anyway folder and
Fuck you. No, thank you
Yeah, I got an email from Ola
Ola who Christian Valle who sends me a little tidbits now and this from the New York Times
There was a test that was done by undercover
Lucy
It's here inquiry airport security not tied enough
You'd like this
So some tests were done let me just find out who did this over the past year investigators have been testing airport security checkpoints for vulnerabilities and have found some disturbing ones
Check this out
As a mock terrorist sell
Investigators found instructions for building devices that could quote
Call severe damage to an airplane and threaten the safety of passengers. They found this on the web
bought the parts online for less than $150
Tested the devices in government labs and then succeeded in smuggling all the parts needed to make
Right through the checkpoints
Yeah, of course
I know and everywhere I go people are talking about this of course I've been traveling a lot
So it is a topic of conversation
It was like yeah, of course and again
I just want to point out we're doing this in the UK okay, and not just in the UK
We're doing it in
Finland had the same the same restriction slash qualifications nor to get on the airplane and
You know
Where did we do it at the terrorist attacks take place in the UK again? Was it the airport or was it that?
That's right it was tubes and buses funny. I don't see any any
Any type of security there well if you thought the TSA was nuts
Trying to try to scare us a terrorizing us literally about you know
Why don't we just all fly naked wouldn't that be better it wouldn't just be better
It was no bags no clothing you know you don't have to take a shoes off. It was really easy
Maybe we'll actually get together you know and it'll be fun because we'll all be
Naked we'll all be you know all be hanging out there literally and
And we'll all kind of be in the same boat together and maybe it actually will be a very humanizing experience
Maybe maybe maybe then again maybe fucking not you could always of course just go to the land of the mouse and get the same treatment
Hey Adam that's Howard Greestine and hello very source code listeners
Why are you talking today on the November 12th?
I don't know the the number of the source condition about the new
system that allows you to glide through the airport by just showing your biometric spending over letting the government
Take a quick peek and
You know getting you through in the fast lane
You know
One thing you should be aware of I believe that system was created by Stephen Grill who's I believe someone of a libertarian
So you know, it's probably more to it than
What you see. I don't think it's just a home and security monitor anything. Yeah, of course the
Oh, stop stop of course atomic energy wasn't necessarily a nuclear energy wasn't necessarily
Discovered to create bombs
You know
You understand what I'm saying right gunpowder was wasn't gunpowder invented for fireworks first or was it dynamite?
I don't know the bring your attention
This is not the only place that you're getting fingerprinted and checked out
I just took the family to do the world and guess what you have to give them a fingerprint in order to get into the park
It's at least your card to use you don't you know give your past to somebody else if you haven't used all the days
Of course, you know when you enter the park you don't say which finger you need to give them
So
That's
Just out there yeah, and yeah, I really wasn't thrilled about it. So fuck you Disney
Yes, I'm guys. Yeah, right on man. Thank you. Okay, so
Well, that puts the land of the mouse high in my boycott list and we're planning on going to Disneyland and
Europe to Paris. I wonder if you have to use your your finger there to identify yourself
Wait a minute. Let me just identify myself to you right now with this finger. There you go
It's a four bar Friday. What means we need a mash-up
To get us into the weekend
I'm just a little
You
Yeah
I'm going to get you out of the shop
Who are you being alone?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh but oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh my oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh I oh yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ohå¾ oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh aye oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Podcast ready is not open source, but it's definitely a cross-platform iTunes replacement that is opening up some gates.
Not only does it work on iPod, Zoom, Iriver, and just about any other MP3 player, but it's shipping on 35 million Kobe and Sandisk devices.
Now, every copy of the software comes pre-subscribed to 10 sample shows, and I just wanted to let you know that we added your show no agenda to that subscription list.
So, start watching your download stats, see what percentage starts to show up is coming from podcast Reddy's My Potter.
The floodgates are about to smash open.
Love the new show, folder, and let me tell you that my pill is so beyond red that it's white hot, maybe.
We'll have to swap conspiracies one of these days. One word, eugenics.
Oh, and in an odd to battle star galactica, frac you Adam.
You genics, huh? I'll have to Wikipedia that.
Yeah, as I was listening to that, I'm like, oh, yeah, no agenda. I got to do that tonight with John C. DeVorac, and I have a business dinner, which starts at typical British time.
830 this evening. I'm going to be so hungry by the time we go on get to eat crap, so I don't have to figure out how to do that.
Maybe we'll have to do a Saturday recording. I don't know if we can do that with the DeVorac. I'll check, man. That sounds pretty cool.
It's tough, though, with these types of things, you know, where you have to make decisions about what you're going to put into a top level.
Discovery directory, and I really do like the podcast ready idea. I've always thought that was good to put stuff on to memory cards.
I wonder, are people now discovering this, and I will take a look at the, I will take a look at the stats and see, and we're doing okay, actually.
We're doing about, I don't know, about 150,000, yeah, like 150,000 now. I think that, that have gotten the show.
So it's, it's getting there. It's getting there. Basically, it's not, you know, it's no agenda, it's no jingles, no talent, no music, and we don't really care if those ratings are not.
It's just to, to mid-laged cranky white guys talking about some shit, but it's hard.
In fact, here's something that was interesting, this comment came in today, which of course we've known about for a while, but people are just discovering this as well.
Hey, Adam Curry, this is Julio from New York here. I just want to let you know, I'm not sure if you're aware of this, but a table has some pot show related content on it's a table cast.
And I was just wondering if you're going to be adding any time soon, the, you know, that cop show you have texture, banging with butt lyr and some other of your online video content to have on your, in that work,
especially since this writer's track is going on, and TV shows are probably going to go on hiatus, we get to have some stuff to watch on my, on my table.
Anyway, a calculator and yeah, you know, are you kidding me? I'd love to have port city PD on the table cast.
Now, unfortunately, the table, of course, is the boss of their stuff. So they determine what is appropriate for what they deem to be appropriate for their audience.
In fact, we even have to put ratings on all of the shows. And we have to, you know, it's a pretty big process because original files have to be encoded in the special and peg two format, then they have to go to some special server.
So there's a lot of work involved in this. And of course, we wanted to, well, I'd like to have all of our, all of our video shows and some audio shows in fact show up on the, on the TV cast.
But it's just a start of the relationship, you know, we originally proposed five channels and now we have one. And so we're working on it. But yeah, we'll text or make it on. I hope so.
I don't see where that would be. Well, sometimes native, they'll content can be kind of arrated.
But port city PD was declined, which is a bomber, especially because you pointed out so well, you know, with the writer's strike over.
Maybe their tumult change a little bit because, honestly, compared to a lot of things you can get on television and cable, I think port city PD is rather tame.
Let me see. Oh, yeah, it was one of the things I was going to say about to know a gen that just skipping back for a second.
I was Stefanos sent me a Hulu beta login, which I appreciate very much. John Devorkin, I've been talking about this Hulu thing, which is NBC's online video offering.
Yeah, all these reviews that were running around that were saying was a cool and awesome. Well, I don't really understand what they're talking about.
It's a site and it has a nice interface to view their TV shows. And that's it.
If you like the shows, yeah, then I guess it's cool, but please, you know, it's not like there's anything groundbreaking going on here except for the fact that they're ripping writers off.
And not paying them for that.
He forever changed the face of popular music, one man, one voice, a lifetime of stories, somewhere between the famous sorrow and the real king of rock and roll.
People tell me I'm a natural, but I'm not those who are what that means. I work hard on my music, but that doesn't mean I understand it.
I love it like I love a painting or a beautiful woman, but I don't usually get to talk about it too much.
And I guess you could say the same about my life.
But the very first time you are peek behind the curtain at the real Elvis Presley.
Some people would have to believe that the night I was born, there was a strange lad in the sky, or three wise men came from the east.
It wasn't like that. There was a lot of blood and pain.
I went a little bit of guard out.
The Lost Elvis Diaries, coming in 2008 to headphones near you, only on Pod Show.
Yeah.
Speaking of coming to headphones near you, I think we got a pretty cool sponsorship on the way.
For Sony headphones, which would be hearing about across the network.
Trying to log into my stats right now to see if Pod cast ready is actually putting a dent in some of the numbers on no agenda.
Slow, slow. You know what we do when things are slow? We do when things are slow on a Friday.
We try to pick things up with young Palette.
Pod crawling casting with Adam Curry.
Hey Adam, who are you ready to be stumped?
Because he used a new test with young Palette.
Hey Adam, this is hit test number 96, and boy, do I have some great music for you?
So here we go with intro number one.
Uh-huh.
Don't push it. Don't force it.
Just relax and let it go.
Number two.
Yon, my brain is fried.
Uh-huh.
Crap, I don't know what that is.
Number three.
Okay, no, that is.
Uh-huh.
Cray.
It's a bright next door, man.
Uh-huh.
Michael Cray.
Something cray.
Right next door.
And time's up, and this is answer number one.
I'm sweating.
Yeah, I got this or five times.
Uh-huh.
From 1980, Leon Heward.
Leon Heward.
He's 14.
Patience isn't up as I've heard you.
Remember that word, huh?
When I'm in the mood for the...
One, two, three, four, four.
Don't force it.
Just relax and let it go.
It's no fun.
Leon Heward is answer number one.
What the hell is this?
This is answer number two.
I'll bet you don't give it up.
From in 1993.
It's the first time that you're saying that.
All that.
This is give it up in the headlines.
And this is Anton No. 3, the Robert Craven and right next door.
I can hear the couple fighting right next door, and I rang we were, something we didn't want.
She was right next door and I'm so just wrong, we're swayed up, in the silence I can't hear her breaking heart.
Anton No. 3, the Robert Craven from 1987, and that concludes here test number 96.
So I don't know how did you do?
I would like to. I would like to do this.
So thank you for playing, and next week I'll be back for hit test number 97.
So until then, take care and bye-bye.
And of course, Jan has links to all of the songs.
I tunes links that is all of the songs played in the hit test at hittest.podshow.com.
Hey, just looking to see if there's any jump in the numbers here.
And that's about the same.
About the same as it's been.
All right, we'll keep our eye on it. If we just got at it, it could be very interesting.
See what happens there. Jan, thank you so much, man. Good.
I really got like one and three quarter stars this time on a three because I didn't have all the names right,
nor all the titles right, but I'm trying.
It is football Friday.
Daily source code episode number 686.
Checking in from the Garden State, my friends.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Your honor, please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give a nod.
To the hardest work in the lawyer, he's jersey tied and bad yet.
He's jersey tied and bad yet.
You're on it.
What do you say?
You might even get wet in this case.
You're jersey.
Yo, how's it going?
I'm a jersey tied.
The official musicologist of the Chacha.
Hey, my main man, my brother from another mother, jersey Joe,
sent me an email this week indicating that he was going in for some surgery.
And we're all really really thinking about him this week.
And before he went in for surgery, he's an email about a guy named Jake Leer
that just got added to the positive music network.
And Jake is absolutely fantastic.
And jersey Joe found another one that just absolutely rocks.
Jake is out in New York, New York.
He has got the soul of Bob Dylan.
Make someone with the soul of Steve Ray Vaughan.
This is an incredible, incredible blue song.
I think you're really going to enjoy.
And I know that somewhere out there jersey Joe is listening to it.
And really enjoying it too.
Hey, check this out.
There's a Jake Leer on your food bar Friday.
There's some good stuff trying to blow.
Break now, shake down.
Don't you come down me.
Break down, shake down.
Don't you come down on me.
Bow around, see.
Six feet in the U.S.
My baby doesn't have me.
And you're way to shake it.
You know about me.
They know good place to stay.
Break down, shake down.
Don't you come down on me.
Bow around, see.
Six feet in the U.S.
Break down, shake down.
Don't you come down on me.
Drop around, see.
Break down, shake down.
Don't you come down on me.
Breaking down, shake down.
Break down, shake down.
Don't you come down on me.
All in right I think six we ain't mutison
Been a man standing we're the girl in his hand
Sometimes the same thing so hard on the same
All in right I think six we ain't mutison
Oh yeah the music college is called to write once again
You kinda gotta be into this stuff but if you do a man you love it
Jake Leer leave this town from the pot safe music network and a special warm shout out to Jersey Joe's going through a rough time right now
Say hi make sure that he knows that we're all thinking about him here on the cha cha
Last night I came home and my wife showed me with gifts man. I was so nice. She gave me a
She went out shopping for me. She got me some new slippers which is really nice because I've been wearing the
The boots and I've been getting kind of worn and actually they're black boots. So they rub off on the carpeting
It's maybe one of the reasons there she got me an awesome new coat which I'm going to try out when I go to the city later
Just afternoon for you know the meetings and the business dinner and she also bought me a nice and new lighter
Which has kind of it's a
Here, can you hear it? Can you hear it? Oh, here comes. Oh shit fuck
Oh crap
Oh, I'm a douche bag
I just burned a hole
I can't believe I did that
I have one of those wind screens in front of the microphone and this is one of those like Bunsen burner blow torch lighters
But a classy looking one and I just burned a hole in my wind screen
Okay, love the presence
Well, I'm sorry. I still have got you again. I'm on a roll today, man. A lot of IDs in my and my brains. Hey question again for you
Can I buy virtual merchandise?
She spoke about the three ways you make money yesterday
Maybe if you start selling merchandise and I do some de-shoots get you know
Bross
Pot show gross that would even give you an excuse
To do a model shoot using gives out a bunch in and then you just you can hold our tips and you can tell Patricia that you're
Art directing
There we kind of fun with it. So hey, maybe and start selling pot show merchandise if you need somebody to sell it in Germany
I'm your man
Bye bye
I'm used to there
No, I just want I thought you were gonna wait
No, I'm so I was showing my my gifts that you gave me and I burned a hole
I'm an idiot
Thanks on I love my gifts
I won't burn down the house when I'm promised
Hey, you man you turn it into a savant calling in with all these awesome ideas by the way
I don't think though I don't have to make anything up lady Patricia be into that too
She thinks that'd be pretty funny selling a pot show bras
No, I don't see that as a big line of business
What I do see as a big line of business and something that we've been working on for a little while is
Enabling any show on the network to create their own merchandise and an incredibly good price
Like let's just say real cheap cheaper that you can get it anywhere else even at
You know what are these places cafe press et cetera and
And
And setting up real simply so you could sell your own merchandise that is something that we've been looking at but it's it's really
And it's interesting a lot of people called in when I and I just kind of offhand of they said well, you know, here's the three ways to make money is we've got
Cindicating our our platform and our company so that's like our British telecom deal and then we have
Advertising which I'll just loosely call advertisement because it's not just
All spots and banners and stuff and overlays, you know, it's a host endorsements
Which is something codely new and then there's the seller tame and part which I really believe in
Just look at the success of go daddy and lots of people been calling in about this remark I made
Hey, yeah, I'm the state of marketing
Southeast Texas
Last time I was on your show
We're not calling stuff out one of the first I thought touches in September and Houston
Now that it's packed, I think it's the most wonderful. I thought I'd ever seen in the whole universe
Although I just saw the
Nokia I guess it's eight or N-810
Yep, and now access to own the home operating system has created an overlay for that device
So that you can run run the palm or F on it, which means you can run theory a bunch of
Palm apps on there. Nokia really
Yeah, and so I held one yesterday. I held one in Finland. I found old one in Finland
Don't tell me that that's very cool if that's true that it can run palm OS apps. That's awesome. Hey, this new device
It's freaking cool. I didn't get one
Uber sales Weasel Chris Jacob took the one that was given to us
But I do I did as I said I found it. Oh, man, this thing is it's liquidy split. It's thin. It's got a real keyboard
It's faster than the N-800, at least it appears a lot faster
The flash videos played much more smoothly very very impressed with this thing
And of course has GPS built in including maps. So yeah, man
When I get one I'll be telling y'all about it and I'm sure. Well, I think it was just released either today or Monday
So it is a it's a pretty wicked eye pot. I'd have to say
That's kind of cool. If you get one
Tell us all about it. So we can figure out what the heck the deal is there because
Sounds pretty unique
And just listen to one of the episodes and you're talking extensively about how
You guys make your income and you're talking about go daddy
And I've been using go daddy pretty much
Now I'm going to use this for all my domains. I've got about a hundred domains
All in there right now give or take a
Redshirt with them and their interface is really great. So I like it
And would like to see some discounts on some of their nails
And so that would be awesome or some bulk for an old discount
Just register them as I think of them
I'm going to put up a few for auction. See what happened anyway
See you around. Thanks. Bye
Yeah, so a couple things there. First of all, I believe you can
If you use well at my own codes, if you use DSC1 as your promo code
And you can find these links in the show notes on any data source code program
You get 10% off of anything you do including renewals. Let me know if that's not true
Of course, go daddy promo code DSC2 gets you $5 off any order of $30
Or more and if you want to domain name for $695
Use a code DSC3
So I think I can
I hope I'm not speaking out of turn here because we had the lawyers in the room yesterday
Up in Nokia and you know and the deal is pretty much set
Although not set in stone so don't go blabbing about it everywhere
But the whole point of the one of the points of the trip
Was I really am excited about this Nokia and 810 web tablet
It it for me truly is it's the missing link between
My laptop which as you know is a Mac these days
And my and my cell phone it kind of sits right in the middle
And it's perfect for all of the just you know whip it out and need a real key
Just whip it out baby. I need a real keyboard
I need some real functionality. It's a great device
And what we've done is we've gone out and we've cut a deal
Again, it's not completely signed sealed delivered
But I expected all to go as planned and the deal is that any anyone who wants to
Want a network as a part of our seller payment initiative
We'll be able to sell these devices to their audience at a discount
I'm talking discount cheaper than you I mean it should be cheaper than you can get it anywhere
Of course anyone can you know decide not to make any profit and sell it however they want
But it'll be cheaper than you can find it anywhere that I found online
So it'll be a great deal to anyone who's listening to a show on the on the pod showing network
And of course I'll be pimpin it out here and you'll be able to buy it using one of my codes
I'm really looking forward to it part of our seller payment initiative
Hey Adam it's Alex Ross here and we're down to beach California
We're listening to episode 64 I think and you were talking about seller payment
When you advertise and pedal stuff you really believe in
That well it works. I've been listening those go daddy ads for a time immemorial
And finally purchase one and got something to say
Block it with your new quick blogs. So I'm blogging it and I'm going to throw it out there on the show
And hopefully some people will take a look at it. It's a lot of fun
Just quirky and kind of a thoughts rattling around my brain
But it is blog dot loss and roll dot com blog dot loss and roll dot com and it's good
All right, thanks again for all the work you do
No, I like to say fuck you
Oh, I
Yeah, I'm thank you very much if you use my code or someone else's code appreciate it and this let me tell you
When it comes to consumer goods and services
This is where I think if we were ever looking for a business model for podcasting this is it
I think and no, I fact I know for a fact that
People could make a lot of money in seller payment even with relatively small audiences
It's just been proven over and over again. So I'll look for more offers that your favorite pod show host or producer
We'll be bringing to you on a program very soon. Now, of course, lots of people get sick and tired
I'm talking about this like this. Yeah, what's going on? This is Zach and Las Vegas
And I was recently listening to the DSC 684 where you're explaining how pod show makes money
And well, here, let me play a little clip to tell you that seller payment
I eat the idea of me promoting products or services in my show.
However, I feel fit and then essentially, well, I don't get paid
But anyone else on the pod show network who participates does get paid
My money goes straight back into the pot. So that's another way pod show makes money
Okay, so that's another way pod show makes money
But don't you get paid by pod show?
So essentially, you're making money off this seller payment
I seriously hope you think of a better word for that because that's just fucking gay
So, you know, don't be modest, don't lie. We know that you have like butt loads of money
You know, and that you make money off a pod show and some of that money comes from selling ads on the daily source code
And you want to know something speaking of ads, what the fuck is this Christmas movie that you're pimping before and after the show
It's just 30 seconds of my life that I'll never get back
It's 30 seconds that you could be using you fucking lazy bastard to put more content into the daily source code
Maybe a little bit more effort, you know, not like, oh, I'm so busy with meetings and I'm so tired and blah blah blah
That I can't do this show every day bullshit dude, you sleep right?
You don't have to wake up at 7 o'clock in the morning in an office
And then wow, there's 50 people in here that I have to present for you know, you got to drive somewhere
You got to walk somewhere, take a little portable recorder and just hey, I'm walking down the street to this meeting
I just wanted to say hi to everybody. I'm really looking forward to it blah blah blah
Put it up daily source code every day. There it is fantastic. No effort. You're lazy at him
And it's getting even lazier you're putting ads in the show
That's more time that you could be talking you can play a comment from somebody maybe not talk about something political
Oh my god, what a concept wow, you know, okay, so there's a lot of other things that are really pissing me off about the DSC
You want to know something. I'm going to do something about it
And I'm sure I'm not alone on this and I'm sure a lot of people are going to be very happy
I'm doing this. I registered fuck you Adam Curry dot com
And I'm going to create the fuck you Adam Curry podcast and everything that I hate about every daily source code that you produce for a week
I'm going to complain about it every week whatever show you post
I'm writing notes for
And if you don't put a show up that week fantastic
I'm going to be on your ass like white on rice
So the fuck you Adam Curry podcast coming soon to fuck you Adam Curry dot com go there right now
There's a number on there. You can call in leave a message
As I'm back and I start reminiscing about my existence and how I have lifted
When I learn what your people even still something to happen then you get my teeth away
I'll take for example the time that I was married
Yes, I think I was across a threshold she was carried we would do an okay
Just about a minute in the shit now
I want to give you get it shit on me
Oh boy how it happens far and then scattered in the dirt
So I was nauseous all day
It's a real losing little way
But always I learned to forgive
Swallow my pockets off that fabric just forever
Open my heart and took her back in
Bitchie went for somebody else again
So with the punch line I got to be a punch line
With the punch line I got to be a punch line
Hold in my breath and I'm waiting to say
So many ways to drown I know
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
When a drop sits covered on the wait and say
I know that things will come around
Life likes to have this fun with me
Marc Clark As sharks
Erik Whinsenstein
Height Hollywood Dr Répont
Hey man, that was interesting in comment
Hahahaha
No, I don't have to get up at seven
Nah, no, I don't have 50 people in an office waiting
No, it's 100
You're talking about Dude
Oh yeah, sorry, I forgot about that
Really big paycheck, I'm getting, please
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, anyway, the website actually exists.
That was pretty interesting.
Thank you, AdamCurry.com.
Hey, you know what?
As long as you bought that with one of my codes, it's okay.
All right, I'm gonna wrap it down and get you ready
for the weekend with some live love spirals.
Hey, Adam, it's Andy B.
So hey, I just wanna check in with you
to let you know that I just released the Love Spirals
debut performance in Second Life on Pod Show Island
on October 27th.
I released it as a special episode
of the channel The Love Spirals podcast today.
Ta-da!
So you can now hear that nearly one hour acoustic performance
in its entirety.
And I also selected one track from the live set
to put up on the PodSafe Music Network.
So I went with our second single, this truth,
this kind of an upbeat number,
and I think the recording turned out really fine.
So I just thought you might wanna share it
with your DSC listeners.
I hope you dig it.
And here it is, this truth acoustic by Love Spirals.
We've been together a decade.
We're always gone by and we're playing covered now.
When I think back on our years together
The only thing I wonder is why
We didn't begin our lives, my son
From the first time it
Wherever moment we've shared its precious
And there's nothing better said I would really know
She will never take away from that
And that's nothing cheaper said I would really know
She will never take away this truth
Which you belong to me and I belong to you
This year it will be a decade
We've stood together hand in hand
Then each other ever there
Just in the younger understand
Oh, we have never been this dream
I don't think we ever were
But doesn't seem to be how need that
I'll give love care for them
She will never take away from that
And that's nothing cheaper said I would really know
She will never take away this truth
Which you belong to me and I belong to you
Yeah, you belong to me and I belong to you
And I belong to you
Yeah, you belong to me
And by the way, fuck you Adam Curry
Angie, you just made my weekend
Okay, I hope the weather stays like it is today
Because it's going to be beautiful flying
I'm going to take my wife flying
We're going to go somewhere nice and just hang out
And I'll talk to you guys on Monday
Well, interesting week
It'll be thanks giving week in the US
So it'll be kind of low on the workloads
I'll be able to get a couple of shows and they're getting done and have some fun
Have a great week on everybody
I'm Adam Curry
You can find me at dailysourcecode.com
Curry.com
Live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom
Another pot show pot cast
Stick it in your ear
Yo, what's up, is your man Tony Costa from Causes World
Telling you to go check out the Sony Pictures release
This Christmas is Star's Chris Brown
Mokai fight for Regina King
Lauren London, Columbus short and an all-star cast
You can exchange gifts
Which you can't exchange family
Check it out November 21st at a theater near you