Are you tired of that yet?
Me too.
This is Matt DiTilo of Matt's Today in History, and on this day in 2007, I helped
pod show suck a little less by putting together a shorter blur of asking you, a podcast
producer and listener, to visit suckless.podshow.com, and sign up to participate in some
pod show surveys that will make a difference.
Once the last time a media company asks for your opinion, never?
Well then, let's make some history together.
Visit suckless.podshow.com, and get involved.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, welcome to the best show on the internet.
It's the DSE6203.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Adam Curry was just a guy with big hair who sold his first company and thought he'd
just kick back and take it easy, but he never counted on this.
Adam and Patricia, the king and queen of the matter, or just the lady and the
tramp, only on the daily source code.
And with this angel from above, there's nothing that they both can't do.
I'll make you wildest dreams come true.
So grab your ear buds and gentlemen, and let the fabulous show begin.
It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia.
Adam and the lady Patricia.
You sure are a birding man, Adam.
If I was poor, I bet I was looking for you.
And just the best of the attention.
Oh, but there's a broad that you need to believe.
Yes, there's the broad attention.
When you've had it with me, I know that you're true.
And you're swallowing in the communication.
You're true.
You're not in the room of the nation, see.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, just you okay?
Just the way the way the way the way the way the way you dressed, right, right, right, right...
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
I am your generation
saying
SHARE
I've been told to a problem, and come in the other world
And don't miss me, don't miss me, just you, don't miss me
Don't miss me, just you, don't miss me, don't miss me
I have no sense, no matter how long I'll tell
Oh, nothing I'll tell, oh, nothing I'll tell
Oh, nothing I'll tell, nothing I'll tell
Oh, nothing I'll tell, I'll tell, oh, no, nothing I'll tell
Oh, nothing I'll tell, oh, nothing I'll tell
Oh, nothing left me, no, no
Oh, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon
Now let's take it back
Oh, c'mon, c'mon
now let's take it back
Now let's take it back
Well well well well
Will'll take it back
They never stop.
No, they don't. It just keeps on going.
I think it's a real life band probably.
At the end, they just run away from you.
But isn't that an awesome song?
It is a great song.
I love those guys.
Yeah, a little bit too much at the end.
What do you mean too much?
It runs away suddenly.
It just runs away.
It runs away from you.
What is it?
It's 60, 70s, stones,
a donko-gumala game melting pot.
The band sound can be described as high energy rock and roll,
drawing heavily from mod, soul, garage,
and British invasion influences.
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Daily source code episode,
623 coming to you from the curry manner.
And as promised,
the lady Patricia on the microphone.
Hi, everybody.
Hi, Adam.
Hey, baby. Good to have you on the show.
Oh, nice.
Nice to hear somebody so happy.
Yeah, well, I am very happy.
It's been, uh, how long has it been?
A month, maybe even longer than since the last time you appeared on this program.
Right.
And it's so good to see you because I was basically on, uh, on tour.
On tour, yes.
A three-wing, a three-wing.
A three-wing.
It was much more wanked than that during the three weeks that I was on the road.
It was a three-week world tour.
Did you miss me?
Yeah, I went.
You wank?
Ah, righty.
How many times?
Shut up.
But so, so...
I really missed you.
I know.
It was so long this time.
It failed very long.
Well, it was a long time because, uh, normally, um,
normally it's a week, but, uh,
um, on longer trips it's 10 or 11 days.
And this time it was, it was like 10 days for me to get back from,
New York, San Francisco, Los Angeles, and Washington.
And then I was home for, like, a day and a half,
and then went straight to Con.
And you did a couple of shows?
Did a couple of...
Yeah, you always called it you show.
Yeah, well, I came home and I had to do a show.
Yeah, that was very difficult, uh, Friday night, right?
Yeah, because I came home Thursday, Thursday,
and I had no energy left.
I was, I was, like, passing out everywhere.
But also, the things that you do when you're on the road,
you know, it's showing somebody or something.
Oh, you mean the showing.
Good show, you're doing on the road.
Well, okay.
Well, that was, um, it wasn't really a show.
I was on a panel.
I know that.
Do you know the woman that I had dinner with?
Yeah.
When did the Lord?
Yes.
Oh.
I thought I told you.
You know, I told you it's the chief sales officer of Yahoo,
really powerful, uh, force in the advertising business.
Yeah.
And I told you that I had, you know, like an argument with her on the panel.
Did I tell you that?
No.
Well, I had, you know, like a good argument, though.
Yeah.
And then, uh, and, and that's what she said, oh, you have to come to dinner.
I was like, okay.
And then we'll couple other people there.
Um, and I said, look, this argument that we had could have only ended in, in one way.
I said, I, and I'll still do the same thing.
Uh, I, I want to offer you a job.
You have to come.
Come and work at Pod Show.
And she's laughing.
She was, you know, she's, oh, that's right.
You know, flattering.
And today, I read that she actually left Yahoo.
And she's now gone to work from Martha Stewart.
No.
Yes.
She's still different.
Exactly.
Oh, my God.
I was like, man, if you had the excuse.
She was because of the argument?
No, no, no, no, nothing to do with it.
She was probably, I mean, that was probably also.
I don't know.
You went all the bad thing.
I was about to, it was just, you know, about advertising.
It was fun.
It was just bantering back and forth.
Yeah.
Keeping the audience awake.
Uh, but she, uh, she, uh, she left.
She left.
Yeah.
So she knew probably when I was, when I was kind of half jokingly, but, of course,
very seriously offering a job.
She probably had already accepted the job with Martha Stewart.
Oh, okay.
And I'm thinking, if you had the choose between working with Adam Curry and Ron Bloom or Martha Stewart,
I think you, you guys are so cool.
It seems like a very obvious choice to me.
Yeah.
Anywho.
Because you don't want to smell like ham, would you always say?
I'm telling me, yeah, when we had our office in the same building as Martha Stewart,
I remember that.
Whenever Martha Stewart was in the elevator, it smelled like ham.
And yeah, I said, if you didn't let me say, but she smells like ham.
She does.
I think Ken would say that even better.
Really?
She's not like ham.
Oh.
It's strange, isn't it?
So what did you do while I was gone?
Well, actually, I'm exercising my voice a little bit.
Because I noticed that if you don't sing that much, that distracts in your vocal cords.
Get on stretch.
Yeah, get on stretch a little bit.
Steph.
Why are you planning on using your vocal cords?
Anything, lady Patricia?
Everybody's always asking, when is Patricia going to sing?
Yeah.
And so I thought, you know, after the dancing and feeling feeling a lot of energy in my body,
why not try to sing a little bit?
So after I did, you know, what we spoke about the last time in the last show,
we did together.
What was that?
We talked about dancing with the stars.
And I did the star sisters, remember?
Yeah.
Well, that was a great success.
Everybody liked it.
And it was like a party.
Everybody was standing up, the audience.
And it was like we never left.
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
It was like a warm blanket of love.
It was like just rolled over you.
Yes.
Yeah.
One of my colleagues, Yelik Arbetti always says,
It's like a warm blanket.
You can't live without it.
Yes.
I don't feel like that you know that.
But the moment you did it.
You liked it.
What I always liked, I noticed that I missed the tension.
No, no, no.
It's not all about the tension.
No, no.
It's the fun that you have from it.
And the moving around and the energy that you put in it.
And I think also, let me think.
Don't hurt yourself.
Being creative.
That I can understand.
You know, being creative because of the TV gig that we did.
You've got like all kinds of offers coming up.
Yeah, we've got offers.
So I'm thinking about doing a couple of gigs.
Why don't you once you just move back to Holland.
Oh, my god.
My god.
You have really.
I mean, it's like, no, life used to.
I'm about it.
Life used to evolve around me.
You have to.
Now we have to.
Now we have to think about your agenda.
But you are always the person is that you have to sing.
You don't forget.
Yes, sure.
But not in Holland.
He was happy.
Well, that's where there's, you know, where I'm famous.
So that's easier for me than somewhere else and starting all over.
Although we have a couple of things going on here in the.
Oh, you say.
Yeah, we're not for bid.
We're not for bid.
You actually catch a fire.
Oh, man.
We're not going to tell our.
How are we ever going to coordinate our careers here?
I mean, you know.
We've got some invitations for maybe.
We, um, some shows in here in, um, um,
English television.
We'll see.
Yeah, we'll see.
So, um, we had a, a really nice weekend.
We played together a lot.
Yeah.
Didn't we?
It's up for Saturday.
Yeah.
I was waiting here for you to come back.
Oh, that night was a wonderful night because we went out for dinner.
Well, first of all, our daughter decided to have a sleepover at some
friend's house.
Yeah.
So that's always good news.
Because then we have the house all to ourselves.
And I have to say she is hurting this month.
You know, the last couple of.
Yeah.
That you have to elaborate on that because I have not to discuss this in the show.
Oh, is enough.
No, no, no working.
I didn't.
Well, you, you, you started it.
So what I mean, you so now you have to, you have to finish it.
Well, all the parents know that if your teenage daughter,
uh, is in love was in love who are, you know, has,
or whatever they think love is.
They think love is.
Um, and, uh, they have some problems with that with the relationship.
Oh, the first one.
They don't want to listen to you.
Whatever you say, it's like almost it's not going into the brain.
Yeah.
Well, did you accept anything your parents told you when you were 17
years old?
No.
Absolutely.
You left the house.
You were so non-acceptive of what they had to say.
Yeah.
But I keep telling her the whole story.
What happened.
And, and I, I took so much differently to her than my parents did.
And she knows.
She tells me everything.
I couldn't tell my parents.
She certainly does tell you everything.
Yeah.
I mean, she always hates me because I'll tell you.
And then you tell me.
And then I do say, I'm not alone.
Oh, what?
How come I can't know everything.
I want to know all of this.
Actually, I don't want to know everything.
Yeah.
Don't want to know.
No.
There's more that you haven't told me.
No, no, no, no.
I mean, you always very flabbergasted.
Completely fabricized.
Yeah.
But so, um, uh,
So anyway, so she, so she needed to be with her friends and eat ice cream with, uh, you know,
you know, on the couch, watch and tell her vision.
Yeah.
Curl up and, and, uh, disgusty.
I think it's all going to be a, it'll be okay with our love birds or, or not.
I don't know.
Who knows.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm hard broken.
Yeah.
I'm hard broken too from it.
We knew that.
Well, you said to see your daughter like that because she's so much, you know,
but it's, she's so young and she thinks that this is the end of the world.
I keep telling her. I said, you know, it's like, you know, how coincidental is it,
that of all the guys in the world, all the places we've lived, that the one guy that is the,
the man for the rest of her life is in Guilford.
Yeah.
You know, it's possible there may be some,
maybe there's some other stuff out there you don't want to look at.
You don't know.
You never know.
You never can tell.
That's what I keep telling her.
That's what I keep saying.
You're only starting.
You have to test drive a lot of cars.
You know, like that.
How many test drives did you do?
My dear.
Can you count them?
Not mine.
I think not many.
If you, if you.
I saw an study.
The teenagers these days, they count like 30, 40.
Oh, I already had 30.
Oh, God.
I read in a study somewhere that the average number of pre,
marital sexual relations that women have had in.
Gosh, I think it was, I think it was the United States.
Mm.
Was four.
Which seems really low to me.
Wow.
Yeah.
Seems really low.
Now for me, I think it was,
and maybe that were a couple of that.
Stop counting on your toes.
I don't know anymore because it's not,
I was so not impressed.
So probably,
maybe eight.
Really?
Be 10.
Not much than that.
That's it.
And I wish I did more, you know.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, dear.
But as long as I can watch,
you can have as many more as you want.
I was so proud of them.
See, I was busy with music and other things.
And when you are, you know, when I was at my age,
I was about 16 when I did my first recording.
And from that moment on,
actually,
famous in my country,
which was different than now,
of course.
But when you were famous,
then there were only maybe a couple of people
that were really, really famous in these.
And you couldn't go anywhere.
Yeah.
You weren't TV and if you weren't TV,
everybody's seen it.
And that was actually.
So you were like, you're kind of like Michael Jackson.
Yeah, a little bit.
Well, not, you can't.
Michael Jackson, of course,
these.
He's never, I mean,
a sexual like Michael Jackson.
He's, you know,
famous all over the world.
He cannot.
I'm from Holland.
Yeah.
He's the jury will disregard.
So, you know,
I couldn't go out.
Couldn't have fun with teenagers.
So I actually skipped that a little bit.
That's why I always stayed a teenager.
I think in my head.
So how do we get from Christina to you again?
I don't know.
Once again, it's about me.
How many did I have?
Right.
That was the question.
So I said,
I didn't have the time for it.
So that's why I wasn't that much.
I think I had more than 10.
Well, thank God for that.
That's very important.
Yes, it is.
I wouldn't like to have a geek that didn't do it that much.
You know what I mean?
But I was good out of the gate.
Wasn't I?
Very good.
So we had a play date.
Yeah.
So we, that's.
Right.
We had a lovely dinner.
I have to say it was,
we usually sit in the restaurant much shorter than that.
We really, we stayed for like more than an hour,
which for us is a long time.
Well, the thing is when we sit in the restaurant,
we actually have something to say to each other.
We always talk.
I have to constantly say,
you're not alone.
And next to the aga,
to tone it down a little bit.
You're really fucking loud.
Talking.
And your phone's gone.
Baby, baby, baby.
Really?
That's my daughter.
You are like a one big noise box.
Oh, you know.
I can't take you anywhere.
Very loud and happy.
But anyway, so we had a little bit.
And she's, and we're sitting there.
And after the art derves,
you know, the,
the waitress said,
I was Chinese.
Is that you finish?
No, she's no Chinese.
She's a Vietnamese.
Vietnamese.
Are you finished?
And you said,
yes.
What?
You kept selling her everything.
No, you can have it.
She actually looked off.
I looked a little bit for you.
And she actually went,
oh, thank you.
Like, fuck you.
I just took.
I just took that girl up your ass.
She just didn't want that.
Did you?
No.
It's for you.
And you have it then.
But then you asked,
you asked for tea.
And they gave you Chinese tea,
which were convinced is actually
dish washing water.
Yeah.
And I did that.
If they put you,
you know,
they give a big part of
Chinese,
or Vietnamese,
or whatever of Thai tea.
It has no color.
Yes.
It's brownish.
It really leaves in it somewhere.
And I think.
Which could be like chives from someone's
between someone's tea.
And we always think that somebody in the kitchen
is, you know,
looking at us and see.
They think.
They're drinking the dish water again.
They think they drink,
you know,
oriental tea.
It's just water.
It doesn't taste like anything.
It doesn't.
Oh, God.
So we had a play day.
Yeah.
Anyway, so we came home.
And Patricia,
you know,
who has become this like surfing
mevan,
found this website called
SingShot.com.
This is awesome.
And you'd have remembered the name.
How did you remember the name?
The song.
SingShot.com.
She was like,
What was the name of that site?
I said,
Well, singShot.com.
And you said.
And you said,
Oh, I remember that.
I just think about calm show.
I'm glad you're laughing about your own.
You see.
Yes.
CalmShot.com.
You're right.
But this is awesome.
They have.
Don't tell everybody.
It's great sight.
Now it's a great sight.
Yeah, it is a great sight.
It's kind of like a karaoke.
Yeah.
It sounds a bit better than the other karaoke.
Well, yeah.
So all the tracks are actually really good.
And then you can hook up your microphone or even your webcam.
And then you can sing along.
Yeah.
And you can compete.
It's like an American Idol social network.
It's fun.
Yeah.
It's an awesome, awesome.
Awesome.
And we had a lot of fun.
Didn't we?
In fact.
You have to.
You want to.
Do you want to sing with one of them right now?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll give you another example.
Hold on.
Then I have to give you a little bit of, uh,
I have to give you some, uh, some.
Let's take one of,
some that we did last night.
Hold on.
I need to hook up your echo.
Give me some.
Okay.
Check.
I mean, no more.
You didn't do.
Now you say you're lonely.
You cried the whole night alone.
Where you can't cry when you're with her.
Cry when you're with her.
I cried when you're with her.
Now you say you're sorry.
Oh, for me so, I'm true.
Where you can cry when you're with her.
Cry when you're with her.
I cried when you're with her.
You're drooling and you drooling.
Out of my head, while you never shed a tear
Remember, I remember, all that you said
Tell me love was to begin, told me you were with me and now
You say you love me, well, just for you to come on in
Promise me you're with me, I'm glad you're with me
I cried the river over you, and I cried the river over you
Nice stretching of the vocal cords, baby
It's almost an ocean
An ocean
I love the way those lyrics go across the screen
That's an awesome sight
I think your vocal cords work fine
No, no, no, I'm still a little bit too low here in there, I can tell
You know, the vocal cords don't listen to me right away
But it's getting there, it's coming back
So what's happening next week?
And I did the last week, I think about ignore whatever I said
Whatever you say, I'm used to do that on TV in the talk shows
Do you interview any questions?
Any questions that I don't like, I just asked you what you're doing next week
No, I was telling that I just wanted to say that last week we did about
I think 38 interviews Ivana and I for a local radio station in Holland
Really? How many?
I think 38.
Also you have nothing left to say, is that what you're saying?
No, what I mean is that my brains are a little bit mushy
A little bit Dutch
Oh, I see
That's another byproduct that keep warning you about that
You're English is deteriorating
I know, especially when I speak so much Dutch
Yeah, yeah
So because I heard that a lot of people say that if I speak English, I speak a lot of
No, I speak a lot
Lazyer and a lot of slower
That's because my brain are not catching up
Yeah, because they saw me on the internet talk my own language
And that goes a lot faster, I have to say
So we have a new Prime Minister coming in, I wanted to ask you your opinion
Not that you necessarily follow all of the ins and outs of British politics
But you can see the two guys, we have Tony Blair going out
And Gordon Brown coming in, your thoughts, lady Patricia
Well, of course, I don't know what they expect from their new leadership
Leadership, I think leadership is a good leadership
But what I can say as a human being listening to this guy
To Gordon Brown
I also always have to think about it
So Gordon Brown
The strongest
Let me see if I can find that
Gordon Brown
Someone should do that, that's an awesome school
But if I listen to his voice, which is very important
I agree
I think he has sort of a fatherly sound in his voice
Which is very, very good
He sounds very trustful
Kind of comforting
Yeah, comforting, that's it, yeah
So that's good, that's good thing
You did some good things, I think as Chancellor that he basically stopped the UK
Well, they could have had the referendum, but he made sure that the UK didn't go
To the Euro
Yeah
And stayed with the non-stirling
Which I think is really, I think that's very smart
Look at the economy here, it's unbelievable
Unbelievable
Yeah
So it's probably, maybe a good politician
I don't understand it, what's you keep
One second
Stranglers
Yeah
Want to be funny if I could find it
And somebody has to do this, Gordon Brown
Give up what's the rest of the lyrics
What can we moving from 11 Downing to 10
Gordon Brown
It's not going very fast
Napster still says search
And he has a nice face
You see, I look at these things
Sometimes you get somebody's saying, oh, I don't like his face
And I'm like his voice, it just doesn't work
Well, Blair didn't have such a great voice
I thought he was sexy
Blair
Here it is
You have Blair with sexy?
Yes, I thought so
Was or still is
Still is
I'm going to do the live live with me
I don't know
We should write some lyrics
And then get the karaoke version
Yeah
Here comes
Gordon Brown
Text you like that
He lays me down
You're going from 11 Downing to 10
Never a friend
Every time
Just like that
That was a great song, wasn't it?
I love that song
Yeah
That totally totally springs for someone
Do that, you're so right
There's never a friend
That Gordon Brown
That's funny
Yeah
So the names here are so fantastic
You didn't you say
I heard somebody doing the
The weather and she says
This is Fennelafar
Fennelafar
Yeah, that's on radio too
With Steve right in the afternoon
Fennelafar
Should we hear Fennelafar
So Miss Fudge
This is Fennelafar
She has a wonderful voice
She does
She has a great voice
You know, she's going to be really really beat-looking
She has the perfect voice for radio
Good
Yeah, vanilla Fudge
I'm so hot
I'm vanilla Fudge
You can judge my Fudge
No, no, no
It is time for you to touch the Fudge
Fudge
Exactly
You want your another song?
What do you want to do?
Some music?
Yeah, I have a new Howard Jones
Which you're probably proud of
Yeah, he puts all that stuff out pod save
How would Jones?
I would not
Yeah
Over the last one
Don't give me that face
Be arch
Don't say that
You're not
Make fun of the pod save
Music Revolution
You
You make fun of our songs running away
I know
The pod save music revolution is also there for you
When you're ready to embrace it
When you're ready to embrace
Pod save
Then you will be welcome into our world
With open arms
I know, I'm still in the old world
Oh
All right
Like our friend Howard has done
He's opened his arms to the revolution
How sounds a bit like the weather girl's kind of doesn't it?
It's called Revolution of the Heart
Howard Jones
Fuck, I crashed
It's a beautiful world
Feel me, isn't it?
About the future
Time to end the world
Against humanity
Time to build the peace
We're all in the sunshine
We took a little revolution
And evolution of the world
It's called Revolution of the Heart
Open arms
I know, I'm still in the old world
Just pass your words
So much you can hear
I'm running by
I'm reaching out for you
Let's change in my life
And everyone should go home
There's a feature on
The beats that everyone fills the universe
Without exception
From a speck of dust
To forget, see, let's write that down to you
The hearts of you and me
We took it matter revolution
It's called Revolution of the Heart
Open arms I know, I'm still in the old world
Just pass your words
So much you can hear
I'm running by
I'm reaching out for you
Let's change in my life
And everyone should go home
I like it
That's awesome
It sounds just like the weather girls
No
I see your mallets
Okay, excuse me
Who's the man of the time tables
Yeah
I'm feeling a fuck
Back the foot
Yeah, that's awesome
Hi
Hi, you're a weather girl
Yeah, the weather girl
We've got a lot of great things
I bet you can go from the weather girls into Howard Jones
Okay, the mixed the other way was fantastic
Who?
We're having fun again
Dude, I'm sorry that was like an awesome mix
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm sorry
You can do gigs now
Everybody has joined
DJAC
Into the sea
Yeah, raise the roof
Y'all
Yeah, excuse me
Raise the roof
Y'all
It's like I think the wrong week, please smoke
Raise the roof
Y'all
That felt good
Yeah
We have fun when we play with music tonight
Yes, we do
It's very childish, but it's like
Yeah
That's true
So you said to me, what are you going to do?
My plans are for next week
You're going to fly me over to Holland
Fly me to Holland
Yes
And get your hair cut
The favors country
And while you're there too
I know
Get rid of that mullet
Your favors country
Where people clap on the one in the three
They're so rhythmic
We've got the funk
It's in the man, Diana
Who will Greg has got the funk
And we're going to do a couple of TV shows
I probably the last one before the holiday
I wish you came on this show every day
It's so much more fun when you're here
Do you think so?
I love it
My English is not good enough
Yeah, but it would improve overnight
I mean look
Yeah, that's true
If they offered us a morning television show
Would you say yes?
Okay
I can't even read the
You can't
What?
The teleprompter
Oh God
You don't have to read the teleprompter
You just have to read what they do
They're reading the
I'll do all the reading part
I'll do all the serious part
You do the vanilla-fudge part
We did a show that everybody did
Like
We did a show that everybody didn't like
I didn't count
That wasn't that wasn't a
An award show
And so I think we did a very good job
I think the people, all ten people who saw it
Like it
It was crazy
That was a very expensive production
There's no one's no one
A beautiful show
With lots of great things
Was it like a football game on or something?
I don't know
You got to fuck them
So, of course we got to fuck them
We got to really fuck them
Put us
The story of our life
But we had to present it
And of course you're the professional
And I did everything just from hard
So let me ask you a question
Are you still like in your
Now that you're putting your toe back in the
In the frigid waters of show business
Are you liking it?
Well in a different way
Because you don't give a shit
In a different way
I think I enjoyed more
Because I see you differently
You know
And it's not that I don't think
Let me see
Now I just, yeah I just enjoyed
Because everything that I do now
Is just
You know
Unbelievable
That I still can do it
And especially my age
Let's be honest about it
And that I still can do it
Especially after I've been sick
And thought that I, I was almost dying
So there's nothing that's irritating me
Well I see I don't let it
You don't let it irritate you
I got to check up on you
And make sure that you don't get irritated
I don't
Nothing irritate you
It's just that
I left my head off
I think it's funny
And I'm, I'm still standing
Yeah, yeah, yeah
All right, so what do you do?
So you have three shows
I think these one in Blankhamburg and Bergen in Bill
That's Belgium
That's a big show
With a whole bunch of different artists
Who are here
Okay, that's cool
And that'll be on what, for what television station
That's for the VRT
VRT, isn't it?
VRT
Yeah, the Vlamsa
Glad you're televised
Televised
Yeah
And then I have one for the truss
Truss
And I have one for the nuss
What's the truss?
Well, you know what
T-R-O-S
No, I know, but what is the show?
Uh, it's like...
Do you hear the birds?
Yeah
You're singing for you
Yeah, I know
Why do birds?
Suddenly a piece
See that everything is wrong
Every time
Everything is a song
You wanna be
Every mood that you are in
Just like me
They want to be long to be
They long to be
Close to you
On the day that
You were born
The angels came together
And the scientists
You created dreams come true
I'm true
Oh man
Some dreams
Yeah, everything is a song
Everything is a song
Like monomona
And also your memories
Isn't it funny how your memories
Always sing another song
Go together with
I said
Well, no, no, this is what we call the soundtrack to your life
Exactly
And we're creating a new one right here
And if you hear a song
You think about
You see all the
The movie actually
Yeah
You see the movie
It's a soundtrack to your life
Thank you
Oh
That's philosophical
Well, so
Yeah, I'm gonna do a couple of TV
All right, so what kind of show
You didn't tell me yet
What kind of show is that
For tea
The last one
And the T.R.O.S.
Is a whole bunch of
Idiots
It is like me
Still think
You know, you can really some records
What is it?
They'll tell me what's the show
It's a pop show
It's a show
What's the name of the show?
I don't know, actually
Hey, dude, I let you on the show
To promote your shit
And you
No, no, no, no, no
It's just
Well, who else is on it then?
Everybody who has anything
Out at the moment
Oh, so
Okay, is it like a one-off show
So it's a
You don't know
It's probably a lot of people in there
All right, what's the other one?
Then the other one is about
Me feel the router
A famous admiral
In the Dutch Navy
In this 1670
Something like that
Yeah, yeah
And that's the me feel
That out a day
Mm-hmm
And you're going to have a lot of
Ships and boats
And parades
Okay, so that's where your
Marines fit in, right?
And there
It's mine
What's so funny?
Oh, because you
You hated
No, I like the whole Marine thing
Just, okay
What do you mean?
I hate it
As it's fun, but they think it really suits
With the real Marines
All right, a bunch of gay guys running around
And white suits
Yeah, we've got the densest with us
Yeah, that's fun
Yeah, yeah
So it's going to be great
And what's so you're performing on a ship?
On a
Fliftex ship
An aircraft carrier
Yeah, really
Yeah, yeah
Do the Dutch even have an aircraft carrier
I guess so
Yeah, of course
Why not?
I don't know, I've never heard of it
I've never heard of Dutch having a carrier
Oh, no, I'll be performing on a ship
In a zodiac
In a rubber boat
Maybe they just push us away on the ocean
Oh, my gosh
Okay, so that sounds like you'll be there the whole week
It might be a lot of fun
That means I'm here with the heartbroken teenage
Yeah, we do
That's like really
I don't know what to do with it
No, I do
I'm going to
I can solve her, I try to make her feel better
But you know whatever you say
Doesn't matter
It doesn't matter
As long as you're there for them
I am
You're there
I'm here taking care of the whole fucking house
And you can get some of her car
You bought it in this car
Yeah, I hope so
The weather has to get better
I'd like to get
Well, that'll be this week
And you're not going to tell next week
So hopefully I can have a visit
So she's going to be happy with that
That's going to be very easy
Yeah, but she can't drive it
She can look at it
Yeah
Yeah, and that's my pink mini
I'm going to drive around
Yeah, but I'm going to give her some lessons
You're in the mountain
Oh my god
You might want to find some other place
Than here in the mountains
This is not a good idea
Why not
The hell is that all about
I'm a great driver
No, no, you just want to find a spot where there's no traffic
Yeah, I know then
At the end of the end of Gulfert
I know where that is
Going to go
This doesn't
I mean, why don't we just let it go to professional lessons
Yeah, this is not a good idea
Of course, she's going to have professional lessons
Of course
Somehow even though I know that I couldn't pass up the opportunity
For getting this beautiful car
It's a bad idea to have
Why did you say yes anyway
Because I'm a sucker
Yeah, no, it's like you'll never find it
It's perfect
You'll never find a crime
Did you tell the listeners?
Oh, yes many times
It's pink, of course
Yeah, no, it's as cute as button
You know, it's like
You just will not find a car like that
But to have it before she has her license
And have it sitting in the car
We have this kind of cruel
We have to sort of take two pictures
Put them together
Yeah
That is Christina
When she was four years old in her
Oh, and her pink carpet
Her pink carpet
And then pink
Isn't it fantastic?
Dude, you live in such a
Fucking 1950s white-picked fence world
Don't you?
Well
What the
Yeah
Yeah, that's it
Well, play one more song
Get out of here
This one's good on Monday, but two days are fine
We thought you'd do a big boom
But two months are on show
Oh
Pretty much so
Taken to you women
Damn the day
I really want to buy a gun
Every night to change
And to me
Do you really just like I do
You just will smile
She says it's because you're right
With you
Two days
Five bardzo
One day
Seven
Two days
Five foot
One day
Five clapping
Sparing Waves
Two days
Six and Two
And then in a
So many
Seven
Two
I hate the way it's said, and I don't know why
I never did stop but never knew about you, I don't mind
Never really thought to knew people, but I thought you might like to know
Never really thought to knew people, but to my sorrow, shall I?
Two days, fine and with me, say
Say it over into things, fine and with me, say
Say it over into things, fine and with me
Five, six, five with me.
Fire it, choose this fine.
This summer, when you buy Coke, you get music.
You can win an iPod or Freaksongs on iTunes.
So you just like a real show.
I got commercials and everything.
Cool.
Alright, baby, hey, almost 48, four, yeah, almost 49 minutes.
So I'm wishing you can end this.
I think I've got a pullback now, because the people have had enough of you for that.
Oh, I think so, yeah, overdue.
All right.
Send the woman away.
Well, you know how much I enjoy it when you come on the show.
Well, thank you, Han.
That's very sweet of you.
So please come back anytime.
Really?
Even this week, if you're thinking, I'll look at the poor boy struggling to put the show together.
Maybe she goes stairs and hit her with a little dude.
Well, I didn't put a smile on your face, huh?
Yes.
Last night as well.
Let's see.
Put a smile on my knob.
I'm not a puke.
Yeah, really?
Yeah.
Okay.
So what are you going to do?
You out?
You going to do something today?
Uh, yeah.
Get some groceries.
Okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
I think I'm going to make some Italian food.
Oh, yeah.
It's very hot.
It's what I want to.
Maybe a nice spaghetti with my beautiful.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I really need you.
I need that.
What's your secret ingredient?
I'm going to tell you.
You put, uh, you do put everything sugar in the sauce.
And everything.
And it's a scoop of sugar.
Lots of garlic and lots of fresh basil.
And a little bit of oregano and a bit of tears and a bit of that.
A little bit of love.
Lots of love.
Okay.
No, I don't think you're so much for being on the show.
I thank you for having me.
And I know my listeners thank you too.
And they're your listeners too.
I hope so.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Oh, and if you want to download the stars.
Is this please do?
Oh, you have a hive's account.
Which is in people there.
Yeah.
Well, the Dutch, of course.
No, no, no.
This thing is version.
Oh, yes.
It's completely in my space.
Okay.
But they can download it.
Star-sisters.
Hives.nl.
Hives is H.y.v.s.
Hives.
I put a link in the show.
A new CD single is star sisters, proud to present a 2007.
And we know that's part safe.
I mean, it's still being played.
Yeah.
So, you know, we need it.
We need it.
And you need, you need some pod play.
Yeah, I do.
Oh.
Yeah.
You artists of the day.
I know.
I'm such a lucky woman.
What was that?
The pod show radio?
Yeah.
I think it was pod show radio.
You are.
And I thank everybody for that.
Of course.
Your peeps.
Shout out.
Shout out to your peeps.
All right.
Data source code.com.
Adam and pod show.com.
Thank you very much.
I love you.
Another pod show pod guest.
Stick it in your ear.