Another pod show pod guest.
Stink!
We interrupt the show for a special announcement from Pod Show HQ.
Attention podcasters, viewers and listeners, Pod Show needs you to help us suck the lads.
Help us suck the lads, help us suck the lads, Pod Show needs you to help us suck the lads.
Hi, it's Jade, I like Matt Pod.
Pod Show needs your help, so we are creating a special place.
The pod show suck less zone at suckless.potshow.com.
The best of pod show.com!
That's right, and once you are there, you can join our super panel.
Give us your feedback, earn points, and get valuable stuff.
It's fun, it's easy, and most of all, you can help us suck less.
Now, back to the show!
The Jewish tradition holds that there are 613 meets vote, or commandments, that people should live by.
Strictly following all 613 is a lofty goal, managing to do it is at best difficult from your humans.
But 613 episodes of the daily source code has simple task for the pod father and his disciples and savons.
Welcome to the DSC 1610 link.
You want some soup, you'll look hungry, and put on a sweater, will you?
You're making me cold.
Have I told you about the pain in my ear?
Aye!
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Turned me in!
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking turns me in.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Fantastic! It's Adam Curry!
At the toe, Pacific Standard Time will be for 20.
Exactly.
Fly up, give me some rope, and I might just chill.
But I'm the type that like to like the other joint.
Like Cypher Seal.
I still do these bellookees when I fall from me.
I got some bucks on it, but today I know from it.
Go get the S13 IDES.
Nevertheless, I'm Ella Fresco.
They do it's like a cigarette.
So, plastic from the table, like pain from dumb gums.
Be in my chest, like hey come.
It's on around my lips around the bone.
And when it comes to getting another stocky.
Bulls all here, like you know me.
Know me, I know me.
To begin with, let's go get me hands to beat.
Fly by that my friend hip-width.
I'll let you pull out the fact, Chris.
Beat you five down the beer, warm the real before was history.
Cause we'll be having a vacuum, looms.
And if you let me, then before you, well, let down.
Da-da-da-da.
Oh, see you.
See you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I
love you, my love, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you,
I've got sex to the face whenever I can't don't be no crush. I'm so teed up to the
joy be burning my head next time I roll it in a half a tap on slow so the asses won't
be burning that my hand rock. Who's he still here but they know they got the pitch and then
I roll it short that's longer than your extension because I'll be dammit you get high
yours me for free. He'll know you better bring your old strip cheap. For some
don't babysit that man to pass the drawings. I think because you know you got asthma
crack the movie open homey and you're so late cause I know where my system is
getting lonely. I got to take the whizz test to my CEO. I know I'm the
author. I'm the smoke major weed throw and every time we request that full rolling up a
fatty but they'll take a race straight. I got me. I got my boy. I got my boy. I got my boy.
I do it. I got my boy. It's heavy stuff and I got my boy. I got my boy. I got my boy.
One of the left go out on the side. One more time to give the fair.
You just imagine flying over the clouds displaying softly in your headphones.
Which we want to order be like to fly while listening to Pink Floyd.
Must try.
Then it's source code episode number 613 coming to you from the Curie Manor. Wow, it's been quite a
couple of days.
Hey, make this right man. Stop at the light. Make my yes the night bank.
Got me hold off the night train. You fade out. So let's head through the heat.
Take the shoulder that I know so we can throw big hatches. I wish I could
take the eight but I know what it's still over there to go. Let's get it.
Just for a second.
Comes to us from art from mashupton.com. It's the voice dude for 20 and art was actually kind
of apprehensive about sending a two of me's like, dude, I don't want you to fall off the
wagon, I know.
Yeah, not only the smoking, but
the smoke.
Of course, you'll find a link to that in the show note to daily source code.com.
Yeah, you know, speaking of speaking of the smoking, it's been going quite well, actually.
Although, wow, yesterday when I was alone here at home was Patricia was doing another
show in the Netherlands. Actually, I flew her over on Saturday and I flew back the same day,
which, of course, guess the the blood pumping, it was a beautiful day.
Christine was out in the town and I was just like walking around the house like, wow,
I'd really like to smoke right now. Luckily, I didn't.
I just had to send you my congrats on quitting smoking and offer up a word of warning.
I was a very heavy smoker. If I was conscious, I was smoking. The only time I didn't smoke was
when I was scuba diving and only then because I never figured out how to do it.
On May 11th, 1990, I stopped just like you called Turkey. It's not an easy thing to pull off,
so I appreciate what you're experiencing. But on DSC 612, I heard you mentioned that one of the ways
you distract yourself is to have something to eat and that is my warning to you. On May 11th, 1990,
the day I quit, I weighed 160 pounds. You met me in New York. You do the math.
I am no longer 11 16. Now I met you in New York as well and you could use a little meat on your
bone. Yeah. I know in 60. But I, on the ways you compensate. But aside from that, it's of course
wonderful that you've quit. Stay strong at him. It's a while before you forget the feeling.
Yeah. Patricia tells me after 16, 17 years she still has the feeling. What a great prospect
to look forward to. Let me see. Okay, so let me just fill in to Patricia's doing the show.
And today, of course, being Monday, I got up right in early. There was a lot of fog this
morning, but I went over first to Antwerp to go see the wind commander because the aircraft
has to go to the radio shop and get the radio fixed. And then from there to Amsterdam,
to pick up Patricia and then from Amsterdam back. And it was, well, it was pretty crappy weather.
I went over the top of the clouds across the channel, which was really nice because then, of course,
you're above the weather. And it's just nice and sunshine, just nice and calm air. That was wonderful.
Came in at Flight Level 50 over Ostenda, which is the Belgian coast. And there was just
huge cloud buildup, CBs, building up high into the sky above my altitude. So I said,
let me just corkscrew down for a second here. You know, like Flight Level 50, which is
over 5,000 feet down to 1,500 feet in just a matter of not really quick, but still really,
really misty. And bad weather on the way back, the channel was okay, but it got progressively worse
and we got into rain. It was just nasty. But I'm really happy with where I am with the flying
right now. I've got my everything is really under control. I feel at one with the aircraft. And it's
the same thing you have, you know, when you drive in a car or bike even, when you know, hey,
I have complete control of this thing. And whatever comes from outside of it, I am one with this
machine. And so whatever weather is going to hit me, whatever the conditions are, it's an extension of me.
And so, you know, immediately, the wind commander, you know, being the businessman that he is
recognized as this and says, hey, you know, we should think about a Seneca twin. And like,
okay, and there was one of the airfield, and we got back to Ferrox and Patricia saw it. She's like,
yeah, I do kind of like that club seating in the back, you know? It looks nice.
We're going to see you here, by the way, before I left this morning. Oh baby,
I'm going to buy it. Oh, you are so good. It's nothing to do with you, by the way.
A little baby.
What is that?
Very good. Sometimes you want them to suck more. Sometimes you don't.
Suckless.potsho.com. Just don't tell you, girlfriend.
Bronco.
Rockacity, Talia, you're killing me, man.
It's a very funny one.
Oh, yeah, a lot of talk over the weekend in the blogosphere about the Suckless survey. Actually,
not about the survey so much. And the Suckless zone more about the the first spot we ran, the
long one.
Yeah, learned. Learn from this.
Must do better. Right now we have about I think eight of them in rotation. And this is really
good exercise because we're coming to understand a number of things. We already had a special
being set aside for family friendly shows. There's also people who are interested in explicit
non-explicit because, you know, and you really comes down to taste and it's personal taste. I guess
there's no clear cut rules as to, you know, when is something offensive, when is something
not family friendly? And please don't send me all kinds of examples because everyone has their
own version of examples. You know, where is that fine line? So learning a lot about what people want.
Mainly from podcasts, as I must say, haven't heard a lot from, actually, I have heard something
from a listener, hold on. Hey, Adam. This is part seven H.G. I just got finished listening to
episode 612. It was great. I also went and took the survey and put my new board to sleep.
It was a pretty standard marketing survey and I didn't take too long, but I think some of the,
especially the first questions were confusing me a little bit, but I did have a screaming kid at the time.
Anyway, uh, will you the best and love the daily source code? And hopefully, uh, get a
here lady Patricia on your show here in the new feature. So anyway, take care and have a good week.
Bye bye. All right, man. Thank you so much. Now, unfortunately, no lady Patricia for the next two
weeks. I know. I know it's almost enough reason to unsubscribe, but I'll be leaving tomorrow morning
630 a.m. leaving the house to go to New York, being New York for the rest of the week,
San Francisco the week after that, and then I come home, and then we'll have sex.
Oh, yeah, we'll do a show. Oh, in the meantime, though, she came back and she had a whole bunch of
tracks that her record label, the one that, uh, that's so kindly released the, uh, the medley
2007 remix of the Star Sisters, they're going to, uh, to release it to the pot to have music network. I'm
sorry, um, they're going to release a number of other tracks, pot safe. So let's see what happens.
And it's some really good stuff. She has an amazing back catalog. I've all, I've been waiting for
this moment, you know, finally people are waking up, and it's low and behold, it's my wife's
record label. Of course, it's a very small label, and really one guy calls all the shots, and, uh, and,
you know, I don't even think that he gives a shit if his company makes any money. He's just
been doing it for so long. He, it's in his blood. He can't stop it. Um, you know, so he takes care of
all the rights for everything, which is amazing. Uh, so that will be in the near future. Hey, uh, for those
of you who've been listening since, uh, probably since before we were counting, uh, before we were
now, now we were counting, I guess, uh, one of the, one of my favorite bands, uh, which, I think
they wasn't before the pod save music network, but, uh, that I played a lot in the early daily
source code, uh, days, uh, is a Dutchman called Mo Jones. Uh, when I did radio show there for about a
year, um, they were on my show, they performed live. These guys are great. They do everything on
pro tools in their attic. It's just, you know, three guys, uh, I think two of them are brothers.
Hmm, can't quite remember. It doesn't matter. Uh, Mo Jones M-O-O-Postrophe J-O-N-E-S, and they've
released a new record. Um, it's not on the pod save music network yet. I'm, uh, I'm going through
all the, uh, every pod cast who's trying to get a band on the pod save music network goes through
this and you explain it and, you know, you do a couple emails back and forth and, uh, eventually
when, you know, when someone plays it, then everyone involved is so happy that the reward is
just immense. So they did send me a track to play on the show. I want you to check these guys out.
Hey you. Oh, Jones. On the Charlie D.S.D. 613.
I would want to set you free in the name of you. Hey you. Wake up.
Sometimes you look back and forth. Hey you. Come out. Sometimes it's good to be someone.
Hey you. You could try to keep it for you. And that's the same way to you.
I'm lucky I thought I'd fly the show on my own night night. I promise I'll forget. Tell me
not to be afraid. Tell me, shall we come out for you? Get me. Hey you. Wake up. Sometimes you look back and forth.
Hey you. Come out. Sometimes it's good to be someone.
Hey you. Wake up. Sometimes you look back and forth. Hey you. Come out. Sometimes it's good to be someone.
Hey you. Hey you. Hey you. Hey you. Hey you. Hey you. Hey you. Wake up. Wake up.
Hey you. Wake up. Sometimes it's good to be someone.
Oh my gosh. Rojoans from their new album Mid-Legged angry young man. That's hey you.
Unfortunately, we used to be proud of this stuff. Unfortunately exclusive on the daily source code.
I used to be a big deal. Exclusive only here. Now I'm like bummed out. I want everyone to be able to play this.
So, still working on that. You can check them out at mojones.nl. Mike Oscar. Juliet Oscar November echo cierra dot no.
November Lima. Hey James, who was kind of very close to savon status and maybe he truly
is a savon because he comes up with the most brilliant ideas without even knowing it.
Adam James, I felt compelled to ring this afternoon. I'm just driving home from work and
it's about half an hour journey from where I was at home. I thought I've got no podcasts
on the iPods this morning or last night. Bit more recent at the same tracks on the
night, but all the same. So I'll pop the radio on. Yep. As soon as we start at all on the
radio, I don't know. It wouldn't be surprising here. I thought I'd be able to load a
estate anyway. But the podcast is goodbye. So it's almost perfect James because I was very
interested in hearing what site was on the radio at the time. And that would have
been cool. So could you do that next time and just like scan through the dial, don't
take a long time doing it. I'm just talking like, you know, just let me hear if there's a song
playing or the topic of conversation move on to the next station. That's kind of cool, man. If
you're going to need ideas, there's a couple numbers you can use to call in. Use the plus
for extra savings. If you can't tell Adam from Patricia when it comes to French
retro music, listen to Radio Ola La, the French retro podcast. Radio Ola La, the
France retro podcast. I like very much. James, what of James sent me here? Oh yeah, this was
interesting. An ancient plant. Oh my ear, it's just sorry about that. I may become new source
of biofuel. I'd never heard of this. The Camelina. It's a plant that flourished almost three
and a half thousand years ago in Europe. If planted on a large scale on marginal farmland
from Eastern Washington to North Dakota, could provide a significant source of clean energy.
So apparently this is really potent stuff. And it produces more seeds,
can produce more oil from its seeds for lower price. It doesn't require I presume they mean
than any other type of bio crop. It doesn't require the excessive use of fertilizers, pesticides,
and herbicides. Not as kind of cool. I guess we've been looking for something like that.
Oh, man, it's so much happening. Between that and trading carbon deficits, it's a lot of things
to think of, including where to live. Adam, atomic rod atoms here, your listeners have been
suggesting locations for pocho germany. This morning, I came across a rotor's article about
a town that really needs your help. If you want a location on the other side of the tracks,
you need to put German pocho office in Buxberg, Oxford City is located in the former East
Germany. His population is strong from 3,000 people down to 1,500 so there should be a lot of cheap
vacant space available. Never fear those. The town's economy is looking up.
That in fall is investing 800 million euros in an upgrade to the massive brown coal plant located
there. After this complete, the town will be producing 17 million tons in CO2 every year.
Watch as New Market has a government that agreed to phase out as nuclear power plants.
According to the rotors article, that in fall's new addition is simply part of the electrical
generating capacity that we needed to replace a zero-mission nuclear plant. You will need to
consider boxwork instead of meaningful women. You can have a city where the trees are coated with
the yellowish ash and the town covered with an offloader and cool. If you have a great visit to
Germany but go soon, the flying might get a little less enjoyable once the country starts sucking
more coal out of the ground and blowing more waste into the air.
Hi, doesn't sugarcoat. It does it there. Atomic rods, savant of the Charlie. I wonder
remind you that I have a video podcast which has started crank up just a little bit. It's called
perversion for profit and it's more like a place where I test my video things.
And Cas Blaster Mike has created a new program. It's been in beta for a while now. It's called
Vid Blaster. I'm more information go to vidblaster.com, Victor India Delta, Vid Blaster.
And so I think he's getting pretty close to releasing a public beta. And this thing,
once again, it's a complete different approach to the typical production tool just as
where Cas Blaster really has become a little online on-air studio right on your box in your
own box. Vid Blaster, I can't do it not explain it. But essentially, it lets you create a video podcast
in a very similar manner as Cas Blaster. You can load up videos and you can plug in as many,
I think as many USB cameras as you want to, which is awesome because you can actually switch
between cameras. It's really cool. Doesn't have an external mixer yet, which you know is something
I want. But you'll have to try it out when it comes out. It's hard to explain, but it really produces
a great, it enables you to produce a great video podcast, which looks really professional
because it's just all fit together and it just kind of works, typical mic fashion.
So go to pfppopa, fox trot, popa, pfp.podshow.com. You can check out what I've been doing.
Basically, if I just shoot any video anywhere, now I have a way to throw it up onto the delivery network
because it will automatically upload to podshow, just like Cas Blaster. So all you have to do is
fill in your, was it your email address that you used when you signed up and your password and then
you can hit record from there, you can load up clips, play those, whatever when you're done,
you just, you save it to your drive and you say, upload it to podshow and it goes off to your account.
And if you have multiple shows, there's a selector there, drop down box and you can select
which show it should be uploaded to. It's awesome. It really is vidblaster.com is where you
can check out the information. I don't think you can get into the close bait anymore. In fact,
I know you can't, but the public bait it should be coming very soon.
Hey, Adam, it's Kevin Crossman. You know, I haven't been a, you know, a complete fan of the
all music football Fridays because I just love your regular shows during the week and, you know,
sometimes the musical selection isn't the greatest, but let me tell you the one from last Friday,
today, man, you know, if you can have that kind of music every week, let me have a full bar Friday,
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday too, just an outstanding selection in music. Just, just really great.
And by the way, congratulations for pulling the OCR out of your ass. I wonder what else is up there.
Anyway, you're listening to what you interested. We have at fratpackpotcast.com, a series of
audio interviews from the stars of the new hit comedy movie knocked up, so you might want to check
up and let's see, I'm a full, but you know what, I'm not a folder,
got to be in it, I'm not going to fall into the pure pressure and, you know what,
I'm at the pressure and I'm proud of it, you know, I'm a good man to worry about. It's all good.
If you like Friday's football show, you'll love this. I also recommend it by jersey top.
Let's keep fighting!
Definitely, this summer is 2017, just.
2018, where should I live?
I want you to see how I get down so now we take this
And I can see my muscles to the sound she wants from me
No penalty, you know how to bounce, I'm gonna take that chance, bitch
I'm going back love to her, yeah
One of the things we need to get you out of the fun of things
One of the things and nothing break it all
It's kind of piss, it's like I'm finding things I never saw
But no, I got it, just my arms, the song's so close
It's feel good, feel good
It's that old soul, it's not your bones, it's real, it's real, I feel good
Now you want more, you need to get that chance, these songs is powerful
These beats, these songs is powerful
You doing the feel, you're like that, don't you but
I show you how I'm a coach, you do, stay true
Watch out for the photos too, because that's what count on you, you better move
Not as much cheddar but still a better groove, we gotta warm that he hold harder, not ready
Way black, ready to vote, cause I know you got slow, I won't
Now let's skip money, money, keep a lock down, plan to take from me
They all want to find the things, yeah, yeah
Find the things we need to get you out of the fun of things
Things and what they break it always, and look business
Find the things I know, the songs, yeah, yeah
I got it, just my arms, the song's so close
Find the things we need to get you out of the fun of things
Find the things and what they break it always, and look business
Find the things I know, the song's so close
Find the things we need to get you out of the fun of things
Find the things they break it always, and look business
Find the things we need to get you out of the fun
And there's a link and it says do you naughty naughty boy?
Yeah, I've had very bad experiences with just playing stuff on the show before listening to it
What do you say
Should we do it? Yeah, I know what to help us do it. Oh, man. Let me open up the second channel here
Adam. Why do you always have to be so darn naughty?
I want to really appreciate they played motherless child. That's a close-out song on the DSC on Friday
I didn't appreciate you saying that the picture I sent you was naked when it said really was not
It's show business. I'm putting out a little show, Angie
Just a set the record straight. I want to head and upload it the vintage
lingerie pin up
So airlessness can all set us by their curiosity and check it out
How are you being like calls about it, Angie?
Why not you just play along with the game?
It should be calm. I made a blog about it and I also put my those child up on the podcast if music network
Yeah, so all the podcasts are listening can feel free to play it on their shows as well
So I don't know why you had to exaggerate you naughty naughty naughty boy
It wasn't it wasn't exaggerating. It was a daydreaming. You know that
All right, so
I don't think maybe a show tomorrow night from New York
I don't know because the minute I hit town it straight off to meetings. This is
It's time once again once a quarter we're off to New York
It's the big sales meetings. A lot of interest for our sports channel which will be announcing very soon
So it'll be there. We'll be there all week everybody
So I'm not quite sure when the show will be out tomorrow, but it would be it would be nice if I could get one out tomorrow evening
Until then, daily source code calm is where you can find the show notes and see a relevant links to everything discussed on today's program
Adam at poncho.com is my email address. I'll talk to you tomorrow. I hope from New York. Bye, everybody
Another poncho podcast stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery poncho and linelight