Need new beats for your headphones?
Check out e-music.
Over 2 million jacks, log on and get to 25.
Headbanging.
Pro-brain that Seeker's crack and slow dance and hip-fried and beat the slamming.
Trouble tweaking.
Cheers.
That's 25 free and be free.
Get it at e-music.potshow.com.
Delta Sierra Charlie, 665.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can govern
what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media
corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Podshow, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the daily source code with
Adam Curry.
Yeah, it's a red pill, everybody.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah
It takes him all the time, you might've had him once, but I got him all the time
You might've had him once, but I got him all the time
But I got him all the time, but I got him all the time
And all the time, but I got him all the time
I got him all the time, but I got him all the time
So I got him all the time, and all the time
And all the time, and all the time, and all the time
And all the time, so I got him all the time
To everywhere that I was at there
Which has something good about the industry
He's been getting a breeds.
That's me, alternately
Not yet, not yet.
Well, it was at six o'clock. So it is the sun has gone down over the yard arm. I've got a nice little
little glass of vino here to share the medium music footballer Friday with you because as you
mind of red on curried.com. I pre-announced that today's show. I got to talk some red pill
blue pill stuff. I had an interesting red pill experience and red pill moment myself this past
week while I was in staying over in the city. So we'll we'll get to that. Speaking of onion
mobile phone, by the way, lots of people now picking up the iPod touch. And I have a theory
about the iPod touch that I'd like to share with you after we listen to some of the feedback.
Hey Adam, our green seeding hand today is September 19th, if you play this comment immediately
is my birthday. And from my birthday, I got me one of those iPod touches. You know, I have to tell you
about it. This is the music player that you need. It's like all the sex of the iPod
and none of the commitments. So you don't have to get one of those AT&T accounts, but you
know, fun and Wi-Fi everywhere. And I can not do it with a fiery browsing and do my
little pink thing and check out the web page is. And it's a great music player. And the videos
look awesome. I mean, it's significant more screen mail estate than a video iPod.
So, you know, how are we? Let me in.
Let me in. I actually have a show that everybody is port city PD and widescreen. And it's
just rocks, man. It's a great job on the show, but it's a great thing to just show off.
It is called a widescreen. I agree. I agree. Well, first of all, Howard congratulations
dude, happy birthday. So, you know, and look at this iPod touch. And I was the first one to
say, you know, I would be perfectly happy with this with the iPhone without the phone capability.
And so you'd think that the iPod touch is really the iPhone without the phone, but it's
not. I'm a little suspicious of this device quite honestly, because it doesn't feel like
a complete Apple package the way you'd expect and to put something together. So many
little things were dropped. So many things that you'd expect to be in there, you know,
just from reading the reviews. And I have not purchased one purposely, because actually I've
kind of fallen back in love with the N800 because it can do so much. It's almost
overkill. And it's kind of industrial feeling and clunky. But, you know, the idea that you have
a calendar on your iPod touch, but you can't enter in the calendar. Oh, that's just ludicrous.
You know, no camera, the email app is out yet you have Wi-Fi. I mean, it's like, why
why is it so crippled? And I have a theory about this, I do.
I'm going to add on this mark in Los Angeles. Hey, I just wanted to give you a little
feedback on stick to explore the iTunes and the iPod touch. I was fortunate to pick one
up, I think it was Thursday. And Neil is to say, it is awesome, although missing podcasting
is really a big mistake, I think. And I'm wondering if there's some legality to it.
The reason why I say that is that the iPod touch has such a cool way of buying songs
on the iTunes music store. I mean, it is already bought. I've bought it. I heard
it buying anything. It was just so easy. It was like, wow, cool, new CD. Cool.
I want it. And that's on the go pushing that button. And, you know, pushing it. And
buy is just amazing. Well, of course, they made that really good and really easy.
They want you to feel good about buying.
A little device. And the reason why I'm leaving this comment is, I'm wondering what
you think on the legality of it. I wonder if there's something about
podcasting, not being on in the cloud, you might say, on a small device that has
some legal issues. And that's scholar. And if I need it, but there's just something
that makes me think, you know, there might be some issues there about the content
and who owns it, how it's delivered and that stuff.
Your thoughts if you have some that you can share. And always appreciate your
shows. And whatever you get them out, that's why with us.
Thank you.
Yeah. All right. Like not getting them out for the past two days.
Well, I don't think there's anything with legality there. I think this is Apple's business model
is clear, you know, and they need people to be buying these devices to buy stuff.
They've got the end-end experience. It made it even nicer with purchasing.
And there's really nothing to purchase with the podcast, you know, at least not
as far as I know from the Apple iTunes store.
Yeah. So it's all those little things that are left out.
You know, of course, you would expect you be able to access podcasts wirelessly.
Wouldn't it be nice? Wouldn't it be nice? Well, got to get back to the music.
Here's what I think. Remember when all those rumors came out that the screen sucked
and it was, you know, there's a lot of reports, even though you're quite happy with
the video quality, a lot of reports that the, and I've seen side by side comparisons
that the quality of the, the screen brightness and just the quality in general is better
on the iPhone versus the iPod Touch.
Remember when those reports came out that the screen wasn't going to be all that great
and the battery life was really short. Well, now I'm seeing reports that the battery life
of the iPod Touch is leaves a little bit to be desired there.
It's a little left to be desired.
Do you think it's possible that they made a first run of iPhones?
And they really just sucked.
And, you know, like the screen was okay, but not fantastic and it was going to be huge
scrutiny and criticism and the battery was okay, but not fantastic.
And do you think it's possible that they took that first run of iPhones and said, you know,
why would we just to repackage these in a, in a, in a smaller case, which, by the way,
does not include a camera? Maybe the original one wasn't supposed to include a camera.
It just feels to me like this iPod Touch is a mashup of stuff that was, you know,
kind of put together last moment, not really in the Apple type thought of way.
You know what I mean? It just feels like that.
And maybe that's why I don't want it because I'm willing to deal with all the crap that you
have to go through with using lots of Apple devices.
You know, there's just stuff that seems so logical that don't put in.
But now it seems like it's just not even logic to the stuff they did put in there.
So I don't know. I'm glad you guys are happy with it.
I think I'm going to stick with the, with the 800 mainly because, well, actually two devices.
Now, of course, battery life.
It's all about the battery life from me. I'm sorry.
It's just, it's just where it's out.
If I could buy an extra battery for the iPhone, it would be a different story.
But man, I mean, I do these 12 hour days.
And I just can't have a phone that crap's out after six, you know, six,
seven, eight hours or whatever.
I'm heavy user of Wi-Fi and Bluetooth and all this stuff.
So, I don't know, but I have a sneaking suspicion that some, by the way,
I'm a home all alone.
The girls are off jet setting to some award shows.
Some glamorous award show.
And you can hear the dog barking in the background.
Probably saying, hey, nice you're doing a show.
But where's my damn food, boy?
Hey, Adam, zero from North Carolina here.
Seems like references to things on your show are starting to pop up
everywhere around the external last couple days.
I was split in by the other night with my wife, went by the Emmys on TV
and Jersey Boys sang, trippy to the sopranos.
Over here at our realtors conference in the mountains of North Carolina.
John C. before that, given a keynote speech, you're everywhere, man.
I just want to let you know you're going to open them a wall.
It's a thing that wouldn't know the live note.
You're a show.
And look, what is here anymore often?
All right.
And I don't know where you live in North Carolina.
But poor city PD is produced in Guess what?
Poor city.
Wilmington, North Carolina.
Yes, we're everywhere.
And it is a football Friday bringing you the medium music addition.
Fire apes are back.
They've got a brand new one that just put up on the podcast music network.
You know I love the fire apes.
So here's their latest for a day.
And I should try to let you know in wonder why.
And I do feel for you.
But I can't reach you for my view.
But I love you for a day.
Well I love you for a day.
That I want I want forget.
Can't let go, no not yet.
Sit too, wait.
She's rocking, babe.
Who's the saying?
Who's the plan?
And I love you for a day.
What I love about now too, for a day
She knew I so much you did,
And I know I'm still living,
I can't remember what it meant
She took my hand, my soul was bent,
And but I loved you for a day
And I'm saving it all for you
Yeah, I'm saving it all for you
And I love you for a day
And I'm saving it all for a day
She always wondered what I thought
I never knew because I was lost
She said I don't know why she ran
Yes, I do, I understand
And I love you for a day
And I'm saving it all for me
Yeah, I'm saving it all
Fire apes, straight from the pots,
I'm using that work to your ear buds
For a day here on the chat chat
And red pill moment coming up,
As I said, but of course,
What is it, food bar Friday without?
Oh, I'm casting with an inquiry
Not a fucking item,
I'm trying to be stumps,
Because he used the entire so young
I need some help
Yeah, this is, it does number 88
And this is in drone, number one
As I'd preface, I'm a little tired, young
I think I'm already over one here
Number two
And this week's final one, number three
Okay, I know that one
Let's see if it appears to everybody once in a world of war
She's, what's the second one?
Ah, it's on the tip of my tongue
Don't you hate it when I happen?
And times happened to each other, the answers
This is from 1988
Oh,
I would not have known this one
I was tough, young
Good to hear this jam again, though
Johnny Campan, just got paid as answer number one
And this is answer number two
Oh, it's, uh, different, different, different, different, different
Laura Branagus, love a boy
Oh, boy, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I don't know, I thought you could
But a place with mine, I won't do so, but I won't be your lover
Love a boy, love a, love a, love a
Millioschines answer number two
And only one left, and that's this one, I've got one
Pretty easy
Song from 1985
And answer number three in this week's hit test
Cheers for fears, and everybody wants to rule the world from 1985
Alrighty, well, thank you for playing again Adam, I hope you had them all
No, I think if you had the last one at least
Last week, I'll be back for hit test number 89
And of course, as always, the answers to this hit test
And also the links to iTunes, so you can buy these tracks
Can be found at hittest.pasho.com
And that's also the place to dig the show
Alrighty, thank you for listening
Until next week, until then, take care, and bye-bye
And after every single hit test, there's so much, such a wall of a sound that comes through the headphones
It feels like I just had sex, although not very satisfying sex this week
Damn, that was hard, y'all, and I don't mean it that way, I'm just saying it was difficult
Crap, and I knew, I knew, I knew Billy Oceans' lover boy
And then I confused it with Laura Branding and ah, suck, suck, suck, suck
Oh, yes
Alright, let me see what do we have here
We have some feedback on mainstream media deception, always good for Friday
This is Mimi and I'm catching up on my summer daily source codes
And I just listened to your episode number 637
In 19th and 10th you were behind
Fireed up in this episode that you talked about the deception of television
The fabrication of facts and reality
We just finished our summer podcast Big Brother Lova on the US's Big Brother 8
And boy, I'll tell you there sure was a division in the audience
I think it was pretty evident this season that the fix was in and that CBS
Went to great lengths to try to deceive the audience
So I was happy to hear your episode because I'm exhausted from this number
Yeah, listen Mimi, Mimi, Mimi, Mimi
It is not all of a sudden that the fix is in
The fix has been in from day one on that show, please
You know, you really need to take this NTV experiment
And just knowing how television production works
Do you notice by the way these people who are in this house for like 90 days
Their hair is always neatly trimmed and gets cut
I mean, how do you think that happens?
Is that like magic?
Or do you think that producers come in
That's when they roam around the house and they set stuff up
And they tell people things and they get them excited and angry and emotional
Believe me, it's all a part of it
So you don't even have to ask me to think about it
Of course it's fixed and I have to say the difference between the US version of Big Brother
And the UK version is like night and day
It's completely different completely different set up format
Right down to people having their own bedrooms
Or at least their multiple bedrooms instead of one big bedroom
Where everybody has to sleep as is the case here
The UK big brother house, so yeah all that reality stuff
All of it is all set up, it's all faked
Not all of it, but people go back and retake stuff
It's the way the medium works
So you might as well stop thinking that any of that is real
Or correct, it's just not
But it's entertaining, no doubt about it
Let's see what we're talking about it
Lots of responses to my posting on korea.com about my recent TSA experience
Some good, some not so good
Hey Adam, it's Marathon Jesse in New Hampshire USA calling
You know, you come across pretty arrogant on this airline security stuff
I know it's inconvenient for all of us but you'll remember
They blew up a couple buildings here and if it means that we have to carry our
Let's say in 3-ounce bottles, by the way, that's been made very clear
That it's 3-ounce bottles and so be it
You know, take your pills while it's not going to have to move on
Some wine and bottles
All right, so a couple interesting things about this comment
First of all, notice that he says something very interesting about the buildings
Pretty arrogant on this airline business
I know it's inconvenient for all of us but you'll remember
They blew up a couple buildings
Yeah, they sure did blow up a couple buildings
Uh, because I got to tell you, I'm very skeptical about
Aircraft because, you know, the official story is not that
Buildings were blown up or imploded for that manner
Uh, but that airplanes brought it down
So interesting that you're already thinking in a different way
I think there is a little bit of red pill in you trying to slip through
Even though you're clearly sucking on the teeth of the blue pill mothership
And what's the this is three ounces shit?
Of course it clearly states three ounces
How many milliliters is that?
Because my bottles are all labeled in milliliters
That's probably why they took away all my stuff
And the buildings that were blown up, as you say, that didn't happen
Because of dangerous liquids being mixed together
And how much do you need?
Can you do it with three milliliters?
Can you create enough bad stuff?
Or is that the cutoff point?
It's bull crap, it really is
It's just complete horseshit
I can do more damage with my lighter
Which I'm not allowed to take along with me
I could bring a blow torch
In fact, I'll buy one of those blow torch lighters
And I'll prove to you that I can get that through security
You just can't sell it to me
You can't sell to me
That that is not dangerous and can be carried aboard
I gotta understand if both were forbidden
But it's not the case
Because I have to say
After this latest piece of information that I have processed
Which I'll tell you about in a second
I'm seeing that all of these things are little pieces on a really big chessboard
I'm not a conspiracy theory type guy
I really even though everything in my human body wants me to be
I'm just not
I just think logical about stuff
Until I saw that there's a much, much, much bigger
Game at play here
Okay, Adam Duke in Portland, Oregon
Your airline ramp rat up here in the beautiful north west
Hey, listen to you rant about your friend and mine
The TSA on 17th show
I gotta agree with you
It is the biggest government moon doggle in history
Of course, I can't tell you why they do the things they do
Because the TSA has their own version of no damn announcements that were found by
But to help ease your travel through the state
The standards are pretty simple and they should be fairly uniform
No more than three ounces of anything with gel or pasty
They get pretty particular about the three ounce limit
No more and no less if it's 3.2 you're host
And just keep everything here in a one quart plastic bag
No bigger than one quart
You can have multiple one quart bags
But it can't be bigger than a quart
So anyway, they're those tips in mind
And hopefully they will keep you sailing smoothly through those screen
Checkpoints in the states here
Bye-bye and tailwinds my friend
Yeah, I'll tailwinds my buddy
Yeah, so you can have multiple bags
Oh, go away
You can have multiple bags
One quart bags
How many milliliters is the quart
So tough
I need a fucking scientific calculator
Okay, so you didn't get a show for me when they are Thursday
When's that was in the city really early?
I had a long day and I stayed overnight
To get an early start for an 8 a.m meeting on the Thursday
Which was great by the way
With the good buddy of mine, Erica works at the BBC
It's a Dutch kid
I used to work at Microsoft and now he works at the BBC
And it's actually responsible for the eye player
And so people who are outside demonstrating
Saying that this thing is horrible is not cross-platform
And it's the beast
The beast from Microsoft
Owns BBC's ass and all this stuff
That was against him
And I was chuckling about it
Kind of like oh man, you got yourself into some crap
Now I can't tell you everything we discussed
But I think your prayers will be answered in that regard
So they are doing some new stuff
But anyway, that's not the point
Wednesday nights I stayed at the hotel
I got an email from podcast junky
Real name Alex
And he sent me a link
To
Something called the zeitgeist movie
And you can find that at zeitgeist movie.com
And this will be one of the few links in today's show notes
Because it is of utmost importance
That you take a look at this movie
It's almost two hours long
And it's documentary style
And it's really, it's a beautiful work of art
Because as far as I can tell
This has been composed of many different videos
That I've seen surrounding many different topics
Which also includes 9-11
And the towers and implosion
They're not implosion, they're controlled demolition
But it's really not about that
It's about something that I like very much
Following the money
Not just as it relates to 9-11
Not just as it relates to the United States of America
Although that is a big focus of this movie
But just in general
How, and this is probably one of the best lines in the movie
Which of course is a well known quote
Absolute power corrupts absolutely
And I think the red pill that started to slowly transcend
It's way down my throat
It was one of realizing that there are just a bunch of rich people
And I mean not rich like you and I can even imagine
I'm rich but not even like I can imagine how rich
And these people don't really even conspire together
So it's not a conspiracy
It is just the way the world has always worked
Think about your history
Who has always controlled the masses
It's always been the people with all the money
And I mean all the money
So I hate it when I get interrupted by
Let me just just kill Skype for a second
Sickened tired of people skyping me while I'm getting into it here
So the movie, which you can find at
ZiteGuysedMovie.com
Zulu echo india tango
Golf echo india
Sierra tangoMovie.com
ZiteGuysMovie.com
It's really a mashup of a whole bunch of stuff that's already been out there
But it is so nicely done
I should have been sleeping
Because I was dead tired
I watched this thing until I won 30 in the morning
And then of course I could barely sleep
Because I'm just saying myself
Oh of course it makes so much sense
It really, oh it's starting to dawn on me
I get it
I understand
So let me see if I can add a little bit of spin myself onto this
So this movie actually starts off
Talking about religion
And how all religions or many religions are very very similar
Particularly when it comes to the story of Jesus
And the Mach of Conception
And the 12 Disciples and all of this
And they relate that to some common themes
In particular astrology
But I believe that they put that in there to show that
That really the masses have always been controlled
By people who have some kind of controlling mechanism
And really before money
Religion was a great way to control the masses
And I don't want to debate about religion
Because if you want to believe in anything you want to believe in
That is fine with me
And I don't give a shit as long as you're happy with it
And I don't believe religion is that effective anymore
At least not in the Western world
It's not that effective in motivating people to do things
We're clearly seeing
Islam being misused
To control people to do things
And their thoughts
For better or for worse
It's controlling factor there
And then it quickly moves on to the money game
And all of these facts and pieces of knowledge
That I've read about
And even beautiful pieces of video
It's really chock-full of mainstream media video
So of course this could never make it into
With theatrical release or television release
Because you could never clear all the individual pieces of this movie
That's why I guess this is just
Whoever did this deserves a fucking medal as far as I'm concerned
I do want to play a couple pieces from it
Because the audio will suffice
And they also do a lot with text
And it's basically voice over video, some animation
And lots of quotes
Sometimes it just appears on the screen
So I'll actually read those
So for today's football
I just want to give you a little
A little taste of one of the really big games
Again
Absolute power corrupts absolutely
If you have the money you can control all the strings
If you control the flow of money
Who controls money?
Where does money come from?
What are the origins of money?
These are the questions that are in many ways answered
And of course I've done no fact checking on this
But a lot of it sounds pretty much right to what I recall
Now that my brains are starting to fire up a little bit
The first thing really is how the
And this is really going to go back to where
I think the start of where we're at today
As historically
People with money have just always been able to control
And wanted to control
And I have to say that
People with who are rich
I'm not talking about the people in question
They're really really really really big
Fucking filthy rich people
And why would you even call it filthy
But still
Rich people are a lot of times
I just ask holes
And those two seem to go hand in hand
I've noticed that
And maybe I'm an asshole in many regards
It's quite possible
I think money does change some things
But it's not like money
Like you get some money in your hand
And your brain turns to something else
One thing is people always want to get your money
But when you're in the money making business
And tons of it for yourself
People can get pretty ruthless and forget things
You can have someone killed today for 1500 bucks
Maybe even less
People are willing to do a lot for money
I think we all agree on that
So let's just look at how money started in the United States
And it's very current all of this
Particularly with the federal reserve
Just lowering the interest rate
Now we take it for granted
Yeah the Fed lower the interest rate
Great, who the fuck is the Fed?
Well the Fed is part of the central banking system
And the central banking system has members
And these members are banks
And bankers
And they control the money
Let's just listen to a piece of this fine documentary
This is actually from part 3 title
Don't mind the men behind the curtain
I think you'll enjoy this in audio
So it says here there's something behind the world
As governed by a very different personages
From what is imagined by those who are not behind the scenes
The real truth of the matter is that a financial element
In the large centers has owned the government
Since the days of Andrew Jackson says
Franklin Delano Roosevelt
The American Revolutionary War began
As the American colonies sought to detach from England
And its oppressive monarchy
Though many reasons are cited for the revolution
One in particular sticks out as the prime cause
That came George III of England
Outlawed the interest-free
Independent currency
The colonies were producing and using themselves
In turn, forcing me
Okay, so I just wanted to pay attention to what's being said there
That King George Outlawed the interest-free money
That was being used in the new world at the time
And he wanted to use money from England
Which was not interest-free
Which means you have to pay for it
Them to borrow money
From the central bank of England at interest
Immediately putting the colonies into debt
And as Benjamin Franklin later wrote
The refusal of King George III to allow the colonies to operate
An honest money system which freed the ordinary man
From the clutches of the money manipulators
Was probably the prime cause of the revolution
In 1783 America won its independence from England
However, its battle against the central bank concept
And the corrupt greed-filled man associated with it had just begun
So what is a central bank?
Here you go pay attention
A central bank is an institution that produces the currency of an entire nation
Based on a historical precedent
Two specific powers are inherent in central banking practice
The control of interest rates
And the control of the money supply or inflation
The central bank does not simply supply a government's economy with money
It loans it to them and interest
Then through the use of increasing and decreasing the supply of money
The central bank regulates the value of the currency being issued
It is critical to understand that the entire structure of this system
Can only produce one thing in the long run debt debt
Okay, so you understand how that works
And this is a simplified version without a doubt
But the money comes from the central bank, from the federal reserve
And it's loaned to the country
So it has to be paid back
So when do you think we need a lot of money?
When do we need billions and billions of dollars
That creates a nice percentage of interest
Well, turns out when you go to war, it's pretty damn costly
So someone, this is my follow the money
Someone benefits from that debt that is incurred
And that has to be paid back
Central banking system, there you go
For every single dollar produced by the central bank is loaned at interest
That means every single dollar produced is actually the dollar plus a certain percent of debt
Based on that dollar
And since the central bank has the monopoly of the production of the currency for the entire country
And they loan each dollar out with immediate debt attached to it
Where does the money to pay for the debt come from?
It can only come from the central bank again
Which means the central bank has to perpetually increase its money supply
To temporarily cover the outstanding debt created
Which in turn, since that new money is loaned out at interest as well
Creates even more debt
The end result of this system without fail is slavery
For it is impossible for the government and thus the public
To ever come out of the self-generating debt
So they go pretty deep into the slavery thing
Which in a way, if you don't believe in income taxes
That's one thing
But if you pay income tax, they calculate it and say
Well, you're probably working four months out of every year for your income taxes
You're working for the man
And that makes sense about 30 percent
So that would be four months out of the 12
Am I saying that right?
Yeah, I think I am
Working for the man
I'm going to shuttle ahead here for a second
Into about one hour and 40 minutes in this thing
Where I want to pull another quote
I mean, they go really far in this
They trace the federal reserve system back to a gentleman named Prescott Bush
Yeah
Guess what?
Turns out he's George W's granddaddy
Pretty interesting stuff
And where he got his money from is a whole story altogether
So they do something and this is interesting because, you know, just like we're joking about red pill blue pill
Which of course came from the matrix
There's been lots, lots and lots of great pieces of art in media and particularly film
That have produced warning signs about about what's going on
And this is something I harp on all the time is that, you know, today's media
You know, we're still talking with all due respect
Madeline McCain, yes, terrible story, what a tragedy
But it's not, it's not the most important news in the frickin' world, okay?
It's just not, there's much bigger things going on
Why are we obsessed with it?
Well, we've been trained in condition to be obsessed with it
We are completely fucking hypnotized by television
So of course, they go into a beautiful piece of
Brainwashed AmeriFox
Your home is it's not working
He's so shit
Here's a beautiful piece from the film Network, which is one of my favorite movies
Let me see if it'll actually work here
When Howard Beal gives just a fantastic rant about how we are enslaved to our televisions
Which is really important to consider my friends
Because that's what mainstream media is doing to us right now
It is keeping us away from the real issues
It is keeping us from thinking for ourselves
Alcohol and every kind of entertainment
To keep the human mind entertained
So that you don't get in the way of important people
By doing too much thinking
You have better wake up and understand that there are people who are guiding your life
And you don't even know it
We're in a lot of trouble
Because you people
And 62 million other Americans are listening to me right now
Because less than 3% of you people rebook
Because less than 15% of you re-newspapers
Because the only truth you know
Is what you get over this too
Right now
There is a whole
An entire generation that never knew anything that didn't come out of this too
This too is the gospel
The ultimate revelation
This too can make or break presidents
Poets
Prime ministers
This too is the most awesome
God damn boss
And the whole God as well
And well, he's not even older than as the wrong people
And when the largest company in the world
Controls the most awesome God damn
Propaganda boss
And the whole God as well
Who knows what
Shit
Well, we've been on the true thousand network
So you're listening to me
Listen to me
Television is not the truth
Television is a god damn amusement park
Television is a circus a carnival
A traveling troupe of acrobat story
Tell us dance and sing as jugglers
Side show freaks lie, damners and football players
We're in the border killing business
But you people sit there day after day night after night
All ages colour screams
We're all you know
You're forgetting to believe the illusions we're spinning here
You're forgetting to think that the tube is reality
And that your own lives are unreal
You do whatever the tube tells you
Do dress like the tube you eat like the tube
You raise your children like the tube
You even think like the tube
This is mass madness
You maniacs
In God's name
You people are the real thing
Where are the illusions
Oh man
I love that piece
That is a perfect monologue from network
Was it like 1972 or 1972 or 1973
Howard Biel
Who of course
He's really close to home
And gets killed in the movie
And when you think about it
Lots of people who open their mouths about stuff
Like this run into some
Pretty nasty trouble
And there have been some courageous people
Particularly some courageous journalists who are trying to uncover what is really happening
And really following the money
This is something I was not aware of
Apparently
There is something now called the North American Union
And this is also very topical
As the Canadian dollar
I think as of today is actually worth a little bit more than the US dollar
First time in my life time that I can recall that
So this
I'm not quite sure what you call it
Maybe the video actually gives us
I'll play it in a second
We'll tell us what you call it
But it's some kind of agreement or something
That unifies Canada with North America and Mexico
Essentially
Making it borderless
And making room for a single monetary unit
Known as the Amaro
And this is apparently really happening
This is just driving me insane
I didn't know about the Amaro
Which of course sounds a lot like the Euro
Which makes a lot of sense
You know the European Union
Pulling everything together
Central banks
Now what if we pull all the currencies of the US
And Canada and Mexico together
That could be pretty interesting
I think there's a blue dobs I believe
Is reported on the last thing
Behind the curtain wand is a conscious
Informed public capable of critical thinking
Which is why a continually fraudulent zeitgeist
Is output via religion
The mass media and the educational system
They seek to keep you and distracted
Naive bubble
And they are doing a damn good job of it
In 2005 an arrangement between Canada
Mexico and the United States was made
This arrangement unannounced to the public
Unregulated by Congress
Merges the United States, Mexico and Canada
Into one entity
Erasing all borders
It's called the North American Union
And you might want to ask yourself why you've never heard of this
In fact there is only one mainstream reporter
Who's actually heard of
And has had the courage to cover this issue
The Bush administration's open borders policy
And it's a decision to ignore the enforcement
Of this country's immigration laws
Is part of a broader agenda
President Bush signed a formal agreement
That will end the United States as we know it
And he took the step without approval
From either of the US Congress
Or the people of the United States
It's a deal that few have even heard of
It's being done again by very few people
At the very top on behalf of the investment class
But the working class of people
A political officials across our country
From communities, from cities and so forth
They don't know anything about this
This isn't some trade agreement
It is a total removal of sovereignty from these countries
Which will also result in a completely new currency
Called the Amaro
A part from that
I think one thing people who are dollar based need to focus on is the Amaro
That's the one thing that nobody's talking about
But I think it's going to have a big impact on everybody's life
And Canada, the US and Mexico
The Amaro is a proposal currency for the North American community
Which is being developed right now
The US and Mexico to make a borderless community
Much like the EU
And the dollar, Canadian dollar, US dollar
And the Mexican pays to replace the Amaro
By default of this agreement
The American Constitution will eventually be obsolete
Okay
So there's some real reporting in there
But not a lot of it
But it really does seem to be happening
So in short
The concept and what they're trying to say
In this movie and this documentary
I guess we would call it
Is that people with who have all the money
And there's just not a lot of them
There are families, particularly
Usually
So the Rockefellers
The Morgan's
The Rothschild's
Maybe some royal families
Wouldn't surprise me if they'd been
Lodden family was one of them
Who fight over turf
And control markets with money
Through the central banking system
And to make more money
Well, it's good to start a war
Because war
Makes you tons of fucking money
If you're in the money business
Or if you're in the
Or machinery production business
Dick Cheney
So
I'm really, I gotta tell you
I'm really starting to see a big picture here
Now again, not a conspiracy
I have a hard time believing
That all these rich families
Are continuously conspiring to take over the world
Yeah, that's where it's headed
But I think they don't need to conspire
I think they can just look at the open up the financial times
And look at the
The currencies, how they're trading
And look at what the cost of war is
And then look at the balance sheets of the companies
That they control
They own
And all the while, of course
Feeding us bubble gum
For our brains through mainstream media
Which is not necessarily conspiracy
It can be done by helping people out
Helping people who produce bubble gum
Entertainment
Like a rooper in Murdoch
Helping
Become an American citizen
And have lots of ownership
And deregulate stuff
So it's not really controlling
That's more like
Yeah, motivating
You know, just kind of massaging the marketplace
And it clearly doesn't always work
They don't have control over me
You don't have control over you
In no way shape or form
Well, indirectly
The IRS of course is pretty powerful
They control a lot of people through the IRS
That's basically how they fuck you at the end of the day
But that's just money
You know
It's not entire economies
Which they're able to
To manipulate
So you start a war
How do you start a war
Well, you've got to have some kind of
Cataclysmic event
So we've had several
We've had Pearl Harbor
We've had 9-11
I think they probably tried
With the first World Trade Center bombing
And then, you know
Once you have some event like that
Then of course a war cabinet
Goes into place
And your freedoms are taken away
And stuff is shut down
And the power builds
This is exactly what Hitler did
With the Reichstag
Which is well documented
He orchestrated
The Nazis started that themselves
They burned down the governmental building
And that was all that Hitler needed
That in some money
And, you know, you need money to start a war
And to follow through with it
And you need a good enemy
That you can personify
These things
It's real
I'm, oh my gosh
If you cut me right now
I'd bleed red pill
Let me shuttle forward a little bit
This is here
Do you want to hear a really, really rich mother fucker
Talking about money
Oh, you've got to listen to this
Actually, I want to read one or two quotes here
Maybe I should play this whole bit
So what we're going to go into
Is a guy who was talking about
A conversation he had
With one of the Rockefellers
And the conversation is pre 9-11
About a year before 9-11
And there's some other things that are coming up right now
In this piece
And if there's something on the screen
I'll just read it off to you
There's a currency for the North American community
Which is being developed right now
Between Canada, the US, and Mexico
To make a borderless community
Much like the EU
And the dollar, Canadian dollar, US dollar
And the Mexican pays so replaced by the Amaro
By default of this agreement
The American Constitution will eventually be obsolete
You would think that a situation like this
Would be on the cover of every major newspaper
Yeah, that is until you realize
The people who are behind this movement
Are the same people behind the mainstream media
And you are not told what you're not supposed to know
Okay, I'm going to know what the American Union
Is the same concept as the European Union
The African Union and the soon-to-be Asian Union
And the same people are behind all of them
And when the time is right
The North American Union, the European Union
The African Union and the Asian Union
Will be merged together
Forming the final stages of a plan
These men have been working on for over 60 years
A one-world government
We shall have world government
Whether or not we like it
The only question is whether world government will be achieved
By conquest or by consent
Paul Wallberg, Council on Foreign Relations
Architect of the Federal Reserve System
Banker
We are grateful to the Washington Post
The New York Times, Time Magazine
And other great publications
whose directors have attended our meetings
And respected their promises of discretion
For almost 40 years
It would have been impossible for us to develop our plan
For the world if we had been subjected to the light
Of publicity during those years
But the world is more sophisticated
And prepared to march toward a world government
The supernatural sovereignty of an intellectual elite
And the world bankers is surely preferable
To the national auto-determination
Practice in past centuries
David Rockefeller
Council on Foreign Relations
Banker
One bank, one army, one center of power
And if we have learned anything from history
It is that power corrupts
And absolute power corrupts absolutely
This is Aaron Russo, a filmmaker and former politician
To his left is Nicholas Rockefeller
Of the infamous Rockefeller banking and business dynasty
After maintaining a close friendship with Nicholas Rockefeller
Aaron eventually ended the relationship
Appalled by what he had learned about the Rockefellers and their ambitions
I got a cool one day from the Terry woman I knew
And she said, would you like to meet one of the Rockefellers?
What did you say?
I'd love to
And we became friends
And we began to divulge a lot of things to me
So he said to me, one night he said that there's going to be an event there
And how does that event?
You're going to see we're going to go into Afghanistan
So we run pipelines from the Caspian Sea
We're going to go into Iraq
To take the oil and establish a base in the Middle East
And we're going to go into Venezuela
And then trying to get me into Venezuela
And the first two, they've accomplished Venezuela
They didn't accomplish
And you can see guys going into caves looking for
Looking for people that they're never going to find
You know, he's laughing about the fact that you have this war
On terror, there's no real enemy
He's talking about how
By having this war on terror
You can never win it because the sea is so sea eternal war
And so you can always keep taking people's liberties away
And I said, how do you convince people that this war is real?
This is for the media.
The media is convincing, right?
It's real, I mean, you know, it's just that you keep talking about things
You keep saying it over and over and over again
And eventually people believe it
You know, you created the Star Reserve in 1913 through lies
You create 9-11, which is another lie
Do 9-11, you then you're fighting a war on terror
And that was when you go into Iraq, which was another lie
And then I was going to do I ran
You know, and so one thing leading to it, I'm leading to another
I would say, why are you doing this for?
What's the point of this thing?
Yeah, well, the money in the world, yeah, but what?
Yeah, all the power?
I said, you know, you're hurting people, is it's not a good thing
And you would say, what do you care about the people for?
Take care of yourself and take care of your family
And then I said, so what's the ultimate war?
What are the ultimate goals here?
To the ultimate goal, the ultimate goal is to get everybody in this world
Chipped with the two with the RFID chip
And have all money beyond those chips
And everything on those chips
And if anybody wants to protest what we do
Or violate what we want, we just turn off the chip
That was okay, my good job, okay
So I don't know if you could hear all of that
They actually put some of the words on the screen
Where it may be a little difficult to hear
So the ultimate goal, the ultimate goal is to put all the money
On an RFID chip
That's one of these chips that people are now implanting into themselves
Some doing it to get into nightclubs
That happened in Barcelona, Spain, year or two ago
Some brave families are doing it
Just, you know, was it to be able to find each other
As a GPS, like a locator thing
But here is, you know, of course it's second hand
But I got just got to believe it's true
Here's the grand strategy
Everybody has all their money on a chip
Which is embedded in your arm
And if you act up, if you're not marching with the program
We just turn off your money
It's what the IRS does today
But that's what they'll do
To just turn off your fucking money
And that's the end goal
That's what it's all about
So it's really just a couple families
A couple guys
I don't even think they're really conspiring together
Sometimes they do, you know, to create an event like 9-11
3,000 people is no fucking big deal to them
None, whatsoever
And just look through history
Anyone who's ever stood up to these types of forces
And these types of power
Have been killed
It's that simple
Politicians happens all the time
Just get off
It's not that hard
It's cheap, that's easy, expendable
When if you think in today's world
That doesn't happen?
You got another thing coming
You think Pete that there are?
That can't be some people who actually think that way?
Absolutely
Now, here is the under estimation
Now, you know what?
I'm going to save that as the final thought of the week
I want to take a second here
Let's just relax
Too much red pill flowing through the veins
Stephanie Sesskin's on
When we first started
You were so sincere
My night and armor
Had nothing to fear
You never did things that you did not feel
I should've known to enough for real
You said the right words
We did all the right things
I love make others move like one night
When we may love it, may my body hold
But now I see that you don't have a soul
You've been jerking my trade
Oh, all in my strings
Oh, playin' me like someone
I own land
You've been jerking my trade
Oh, playin' your game
Oh, playin' my boy now
Oh, I'm safe, dream
The good news baby
Is I've seen the light
And here I know
I'm going to be alright
In some day
When you two listen bold
You'll wonder why
You can't have it all
You've been jerking my trade
Oh, all in my strings
Oh, playin' me like someone
Oh, playin' your game
Oh, playin' my boy now
Oh, playin' my trade
I could've agreed to a good night's revenge
Could be my sailor but it'd be my sailor but it'd be my sailor
It'd get depressed to wallow in hate
But guess what?
Your love wasn't all that great
You've been jerking my trade
Oh, all in my strings
Oh, playin' me like someone
Oh, playin' me like somebody
Oh, playin' your game
Oh, playin' boy now
Oh, go playin' me like someone
Oh, I'm safe, dream
You've been jerking my trade
Oh, all in my strings
Oh, playin' me like someone
No, playin' me like someone
we can.
Now we're moving all day.
Stepping by the way in the history...
Let's go to the James history.
Yeah you give it all.
Stephanie Saskin.
You'll find her on the Podsive Music Network links in the show notes a daily source code.com, of course.
So what if we learn today from this, what I think is just accidentally produced a piece of video
that war is good. And by the way, according to this philosophy, the war in Iraq is going beautifully.
Have you ever heard of the concept divide and conquer? You know, take like two people who
kind of hate each other anyway, like Sunnis and Shea's and then divide them and then feed them weapons
and crap and intelligence on both ends so they kill each other so you don't have to do it.
Ever heard of that one? That's a pretty old trick.
Dog does not agree with anything I'm saying. War is good. We need more war. We need an endless war.
We had a war on drugs, which of course is probably a scam as well.
Well, it's probably a whole bunch of people feeding new drugs to keep you stupid.
So this is not about small conspiracies and in the grand scheme of things,
9-11, very small conspiracy. Big thing to pull off, masterfully done, pull the wool over all of
our eyes. I have my own thoughts about that, but it's not what I want to focus on. We have to figure
out a way to shut up. We have to figure out a way to use this wonderful new medium that we're creating
to get people to take the red pill. You've just got to be aware of it. We have to stop.
Now there's two ways we can do it. You can do it by voting the right people into office
and protecting them. They will need protection because the people who are smart and mother
fuckers get killed. We'll have to protect them. And of course, thank God for the shot up.
I'm in the middle of something important here. Thank God for the American Constitution because
right there it says we have the right to bear arms, which means we can form a militia and go
fuck those motherfuckers up. I believe the right way to do it is through the system that was
set up and that seems to be still kind of working, but we are under utilizing it.
We have people in the European Union, ministers, not elected officials who are determining the
fate of what's happening in Europe. It is completely ridiculous. It's Friday.
All right. So what has gone awry really with this plan? This global idea of just keeping
us dumb and milking us for all we've got and taking us up to the point of being enslaved by
having our money embedded in chips and our bodies, which can turn on and off at the flick of a
switch just to control us. Well, we've got the internet to my friend. We've got the series of
tubes. We've got communication. We're talking to each other. We've got video. We've got audio. We've got
a voice. We've got ideas. We've got minds. We can mash it all together and that is exactly what's
happening. So we need to figure out a way to get this word out. We need memes to spread. Red pill is a
good one. It's a good analogy. Of course, not everyone saw the matrix. We have to keep people awake
and we have to get the right people into positions of power, governmental power, that are clearly
spelled out. You know, then we have to protect them. And America, we're lucky, as I said, we got guns.
We can protect people with those. We're just going to have to. I feel it just may go that far.
So I don't want to put a bummer on you. We can't drive anything. I think it's actually quite
invigorating. I'm looking forward to figuring out how to, how to gather. We can pass the word on.
Get people to wake up. Get them to understand what is taking place. And how even Brittany
spears is a part of that. It's the bubble gum that we're chewing on. So we don't pay attention
to things that are really important. Madeline, Madeline McCain, same thing. I got to tell you,
it does not belong at the top of the news. It is not the most important thing going on in the world.
So I wish I had a snappy slogan. Maybe we'll come up with one. I cannot wait to hear back from
you guys. I know I've worked on a few people up. And even the people who are going to be angry and
say that it's not true. And I'm off my rocker. It's okay. I understand. It's just a blue pill moment.
So watch this movie. ZiteGuysMovie.com. Link to it in the show notes at Daily Source Code.
And we'll be sure to talk about this next week. Adam at potchow.com. DailySourcecode.com. Have
yourselves a great weekend. Red pill.
Another potchow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
This podcast is brought to you by Potchow and GoDaddy. The show will give you a special code
to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com. Got something to say? Walk it with your frequent log
from GoDaddy.