Hey, this summer, when you buy coke for me, you'll get free tunes, that's right.
I got a bunch of cassettes of guys from the neighborhood, they make some tunes, you get
a free one, you buy your coke for me, yeah, me go, what's the matter?
You don't like my tunes?
Maybe you want your tunes from Adam Curry on the Daily Source code.
Okay, well, say hello to my little friend.
That this year, try six to six.
Hey, you don't put that dial in the DSC, so 46 is coming up.
Six million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I was reading in the shop, but back in Drake, you walked in and a new plot.
Was it your destiny?
The words I grabbed left from my head, the letter said nothing to me.
I've been trolling, I've been so transparent on the pitch, I couldn't see.
I asked if you liked Oscar Wilde, I'm drawing on comedy.
But what were you like as a child?
And did you feel the green?
But what's your main job?
And what's your main job?
So we may not have our giggles.
We've got Andy Stone.
When the pot saved music network in the coffee shop, when kicking off a
food bar Friday, more or less maximum music because, well, let's face it.
I crapped out on you yesterday, so all the stuff I had lined up for
today.
We're going to do today.
It is Daily Source Code 626 Apologies on Wednesday's show.
I said it was episode 626.
It's been one of those weeks.
It's been just absolutely crazy.
Yesterday I went into the city again.
I met with the head of daytime programming for ITV.
We had some stuff we had to talk about, so very excited about that.
But really by the time I got back, which was five in the afternoon, this whole week I've
been calling our partners and producers.
Actually, I've been having so much fun doing it.
We were thinking of calling the top 20.
I'm like, fuck it.
Let's just keep going.
Let's keep going all the way down the line.
Let's call everybody.
This is a lot of fun.
I've really been learning a lot.
Great to have some feedback.
The network feels a little bit more like a network now.
So that's what I'll be doing today as well.
For the next couple of weeks, it's groovy.
Learning a lot.
And producing some cool shit mode, which we're talking about later today on the football
Friday.
But first, something we haven't done all week.
It's time to be the other microphone.
There's my girl, Amy Mac.
Amy.
Hello.
Hey, Adam.
Hey, Amy Mac.
It's time to get that ass in gear.
Yes, I'm ready.
What do we do?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Just tell me.
Okay.
Today you're going to need a chair.
Get your chair and get all situated.
Do I sit on the chair?
Great.
Okay.
Sit on the edge of the chair and put your hands next to your hips.
Your fingertips should be pointed away from the chair.
Your feet should be at a comfortable spot in front of you with knees bent.
Yes.
Now lift your booty and squeeze.
And come down.
Up.
Squeeze.
Yes.
Don't forget to breathe.
Can I go down?
Thank you.
Oh my goodness.
Last time.
Oops.
Up.
Squeeze.
Hold it.
Oh, man.
And down.
Fabulous.
That's it.
You're doing so well.
It's smoking.
It really makes a difference.
Doesn't it?
It sure does.
It's so proud of you.
Okay.
On with food bar.
And until next time.
Yes.
How are you, Amy?
I got to tell you.
You know, and since I haven't been smoking, the dreams are coming now at night.
That's always just, it always happens.
I start dreaming a hell of a lot more.
And yes.
You are in every single one of them.
Games.
What's that?
Come on.
Hi, Adam.
It's Matt from Games Weasel.
On this week's show, I've got five copies of our victory for the Xbox 360 to give away.
So if you're into your first person, shooters and you're like your World War Two game.
This one's for you.
And if you want to stand a chance to win, just go to gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
Don't know the show.
Have a listen.
Answer the question.
And you can be a winner.
Alright, Matt.
Thank you.
Amigo.
Oh, let's get into a matchup for the footballer Friday.
What do you say, huh?
You're going to like this one.
Dr. Art sends it in once again straight to the heart.
Oh, yeah.
I've got some towns in town that I can't find what I've got to do
I've got so desperate that I sent a rocket to them
No, you're serious, I'm upset, they saw you sang in the blue
I wasn't meant for nowhere, man, they look like you
I've got to keep such an eye, this feeling's much too strong
My heart is ringing, I'm singing this song for you
So close to take so long So I've got to sing a song to let you know how I feel
What's the deal, baby?
I've got to wait for you I hope you make me feel
My heart is ringing so I'm tinging in this cycle
Give me authority
For you, you never have to let me feel
My heart is ringing so I'm tinging in this cycle
Hey, I hope you do it
Make me feel
I love it.
Lula Placino.
Orny has a damn thing.
Of course, mash it up.
Danny Warhol is a moose tea.
On D.S.C. 626.
While that was running, I was trying to load up
young Pulets hit test for this week.
And I think I've knackered the cast blaster.
It's not like in what I'm trying to do here.
There's an error in file or format and not supported.
Okay.
Oh boy.
I'm just hoping this thing keeps rolling on.
Hey, you had a mix of Raymond and your buddy from the Netherlands.
Ray?
Oh, actually, no way.
An end of the unaffordable booze.
This is Raymond.
We were talking about him just earlier this week.
When GD called in about people listening to bite-sized bonus
at Glastonbury in the tents.
This is Raymond, who was listening to a daily source code
in his car while I was recording another one in my car.
And we were both in traffic.
I started my new job here two weeks ago.
And so far, so good.
Got a new cell phone.
The Nokia E65 device, by the way.
I downloaded the podcasting application.
We're subscribed to the D.S.C.
Obviously, in order to be able to catch up.
I listened to it on the bus on the along the way to work.
And there was mention being counted.
We had almost three years ago on the Dutch A4.
It brought back all those good memories.
So thanks for that, Mike.
We keep in touch.
That's a say in Norway.
Hard of it up.
This is what they say in Norway.
Meanwhile, I'm trying to get shit organized here.
I guess I'll just have to play the hit test from the separate player.
That's hope that's over.
That's hope the cast blasts are hangs in there because well,
that is kind of par for a football Friday.
No, isn't it?
Good morning, Adam.
See you soon, Farod.
It is Thursday morning.
Nice morning here at Farod.
I'm ringing in really strong slate for my
combat fit, the prolific program.
I believe what he said was.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is indeed prolific programmer.
Call then he said something about Tony Blair and Gordon Brown,
which I just, I couldn't understand.
Let's see if I can find, see if I find this comment again.
May not be easy to find.
I get so much stuff in.
Let's see.
Hmm.
Was it, uh, P.P.
Ah, crap.
Anyway, it was, I thought it was like the two cheeses of the same
something.
That's what I, that's what I understood in design.
The Gordon Brown and, um,
Tony Blair are two cheeks all same back side.
In other words, they are like they are.
Like they are.
Hmm.
Possibly many others as well.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Wait a minute.
Telecopter Day at Farodx yesterday.
There's lots going on, at least half a dozen,
Augusta 109s of different marks.
Hmm.
There was a wonderful Bell 47,
registered D-Math and completely tricked out
as in Korean war, liver, even with the letters on the sides.
And somebody had one of those kind of whoops moments when they
would ground running a do-fap for engineering reasons.
And we were walking by and the, um, the floats will
deploy onto it.
We need to do that.
In fact, it's an engineering.
Uh, unfortunately we didn't do much fine because we can't
get our equipment to work properly.
Yeah.
Uh, that's an official aviation term, I'll have you know.
Uh, that doesn't work.
Yeah, that's a very embarrassing moment when you accidentally deploy the floats on a helicopter
Particularly when it's on the ground and not near water
And that can be pretty spectacular if if the engine if the rotors are running that could be a pretty spectacular event
But oh, man, yeah, that's that's a very embarrassing thing. Thank you. Thank you so much for
For both the update the pharaohs update. I think I'm flying Monday
I'm gonna take the lady Patricia over to Rotterdam
She's gonna be there for a week of shows and show business stuff and basically leaving Christina and I
All alone
Yeah, of course that means I can geek out a lot more at night
And also for the two cheeks of the same backside. Thank you
We're in the middle of a bomb scare today in London pickadilly circus large portions of it have been roped off
Apparently some form of device was found maybe in automobile
They were taking a car away. I just saw on the news. It's it's 11 30 a.m. So
By the time you get the show it
Everything may be all over
But the brand new prime minister immediately came out and said well, you know these are these are trying times
We're under constant threat. Thanks and we have to be vigilant and damn those brids are there you guys are a vigilant bunch
There's just just not a lot that's gonna slow you down and there's and what I like about
We've talked about this before with the seven seven seven bombings
There's not a lot of sensationalism
When you look at the news. Yes, everyone's following and there's coverage and then we're trying to get information
But it's just not a sensationalist and
It's not being taken to extrude the discussion is not yet taken being taken to extremes mainly because we just don't know what's going on
But it's certainly never a boring moment. What should we do? We can do yarn
Actually, yeah, I'll do a yarn. Let me get the sponsorship of the hit test out of the way first
This summer when you buy coke you get music
You can win an iPod or free songs on iTunes
So I think the way this works is you use a code that's in the cap of
Either the bottle top the cap. I don't know if it's on cans or not and you can win free tunes from
For my tunes. I think you can win a free iPod
What I'd like to know is have you actually tried this
Please
Give me a call. Let me know if you've had any success
I'm not a I'm not a soft drink drinker myself
And if we have coke then
You know we might have a bottle. I'll I'll look and I'll see if I have a code and then you look and let me know
Let me know if you've gone to the process and and if you want anything
All right
Foo bar Friday. It's maximum music
There's only one thing that everyone really is always looking for it is the hit
Hey Adam hi doing. I'm doing great man. How are you this is the hit test the one and only way to
Test your hit knowledge and it's episode number 76 and again three short intro and three answer
So here we go. This is number one rocket
Yarn yarn yarn. What do you take me for?
Some classical music a disco truckie and number two
Yeah
Leyla Leyla maybe and the final one for this week
That's Wangchung. I know how record I think so the last was Wangchung
I don't know if it was Leyla or some other earthcraft and project and that's it did you get them no is number one
All right we got 1984
Friends my revolution
I would die for you as number one in the hit test
Friends says answer number one
And this is from 1985
I'm simply red money's too tight to mention
We'll count for that
Oh
Simply red and money's to tight to mention is answer number two
And it's is answer number three from 1984 as well when Chang
That's all right
Answer number three Wangchung
And dance all days and that's it for hit test numbers 76
Next week I'll be back for a hit test number 77 but in the meantime you can find the answers to this hit test
And of course the iTunes links at hit test dot bot show dot com
Well Adam I hope you had them all there were not too difficult
Until next time hopefully next week
So until then take care and bye bye
Guys got the biggest balls in the business young pull out everybody with today's hit test
We're up to number 76 two stars for me today. I can't believe I got simply red wrong and it's so amazing to me
And the UK people think very differently about makehocnall then and they all call them ugly all the time
It has you know there's a whole thing with with red-haired people with redheads here they're ginger and they're like
Contagious and they're really outcast of society
It's crazy how that works here
Where I think Mikhocnall gets a lot of fucking respect in the rest of the world. He's done some great songs
He's done some and he's had some hot hot girlfriends too
Major props for that make okay, of course if we have a hit test
To the hardest working audience jersey time
Yeah
How's it going Adam and Jersey Todd the official musicologist of the chacha
So dude, I was thinking this week one instrument haven't we hit on a football Friday yet
We've hit our cowbell we've hit our rock and region metal guitars and the one instrument the one instrument
Then I'm thinking that we haven't hit is the banjo
I think we need to hit the banjo this week because I've got a great great song the band is Ryan Schupe and the rubber band at a Utah
They've got a great great song up on the pot safe music network. He got to check this out. It's banjo boy by Ryan Schupe and his band check this out
That's like a hip hop banjo
You'll need this
When the banjo play the banjo play the banjo play the banjo
You see
I
Have a little jet kind of limousine
Whenever I put my plans for screaming hey, I'm your boy
We love you
Please don't think I'll ever expand you
And you'll see me on the TV talk show with day
Come have a jail and oh the only problem is I'll play the banjo
I'll play the banjo play the banjo play the banjo play the banjo
I'll need a banjo
Todd once again you do not disappoint as official music colleges of the chacha
Ryan Schupe and the rubber band I'm the banjo boy
Direct from the pod save music network. You can find that in the show notes at daily source code dot cam nice
Nice nice nice and pretty excited later today
I'll be working on the new channels interface
That is still in the development sandbox
But yesterday I got an email from Devon Devon and Andrew and I are working on this couple other people and I'm not exactly sure who's who's all involved
I'll find out
It takes a lot of people to get this stuff on the live servers
But it's really
It just hit me like a like a fucking title wave yesterday when I saw the work that Devon had done now
I know exactly how we're going to make this thing fly and it's going to be a very interesting experience to mess around with
So you Charlie listeners
You will be the first one to be able to play with it because we want to push it public into the at a secret URL
That I'll give you and you'll be able to to mess around with it and and feedback so we can actually have kind of like an iterative process
It's going to be I think it's going to be very cool
I did want to
Mention something you know I've been complaining for the past couple days about cast blaster not working
You know it would report
No errors it would say look the show has been uploaded but it wouldn't appear anywhere on daily source code dot com and not just basically
It wasn't getting up to the server. We've seen this problem before
So we have an email list. We have a couple of them
One is the critical list and so what you know that's usually what I post my I would could I I
Think a cast blaster not working as a critical bug
So I I post a message and you know there's lots of people a jump on this this people are up 247 to monitor shit
And it's just it's it's great because I get fucking awesome customer service go figure
So they're trying to figure this out and it takes like two days and I'm uploading through the new flash interface
Exactly as advertised so I'm really happy with it, but still it's a copy and paste project from cast blaster into the web page and say
You know and it should work it should work perfectly
So we finally decided to do it because I did say a my defense
I said look I can't rule out that there's something wrong with my set of locally
Andrew Grummet had seen the problem occur once he thought
But our QA team could not reproduce the problem so we decided to try it out and what better way to try it out than
By doing a Skype call
Brin and Andrew and and of course, you know, and actually I thought of it about two minutes into the test
I said well this is stupid
I should actually be recording this because I could let you hear how how we troubleshoot this stuff
So here's me
Andrew Grummet and and Brin so fuck Brin I know you last name
Brin is from ops and and we're troubleshooting
Okay, so tell me exactly what you want to do
Okay, um, so there's I think right now there's
Just basically have you do an upload again, but you know, maybe not your main feed so that you don't have to put other stuff in there
And we can just watch it and see so Andrew just said something really important here
He said upload something but maybe not to your main feed
Well, just look at people you can see something something in the logs indicate where the problem might be
Okay, so you want me to do this now you want me to upload this now from cast blaster
Yeah, yeah, so um
Yeah, okay, hold on hold on
Brin are you ready? Oh, yeah
Okay, I've got logs up. I'm watching just the access logs. Okay, watch show it first. We have to make a file worth uploading. So
I sure so
You sure are a pretty man at him. If I was woman, I'd have something for you
I should have recorded that bit wait. I'll repeat what I just said
I said oh shit. I just found the problem
And I have put the entire engineering staff of podgeo all of two wheels are in motion to satisfy my every demand
For a frivolous pursuit
Operations as well. I just noticed that in cast blaster the show that selected is not the
intended show that is the daily source code
Okay, just so should we go to the other show and see if it's there
Yeah
It's under a show called Adams family so I wonder
Let me see if you go to my profile and you can go to my shows
Where is it? Adam's family ID 1939
Yep going there
And yeah, you're probably gonna see three days
Yeah, yeah, today once from today
We
I am such a douche bag
You know I bet I bet you I did the same thing
Hey man did something reset maybe what does that happen?
There you go. I look like a pretty big fool. I have to say
It's one in from Marcus couch
My hands are
Send the powder from Los Angeles
You might recognize
What is a much never-be
If I take it out of you
And if you say to me to my own
It's bound by me how it would be
And I've missed out my friend
For living without you
And I've said yeah, yeah, yeah. Stay away
Don't let them on, dude
I keep gonna be home
I miss you, if you wake up with the sun light
And I'll endure and stay the rest of the world
The happiness is what you need for me
Go, it's the love we're in
Guess the reality will be the day we arrive
And I'll endure and stay the rest of the world
The happiness is what you need for me
Go, it's the love we're in
I'll endure and stay the rest of the world
The happiness is what you need for me
Go, it's the love we're in
And I'll endure and stay the rest of the world
The happiness is what you need for me
Go, it's the love we're in
I'll endure and stay the rest of the world
The happiness is what you need for me
Go, it's the love we're in
And I'll endure and stay the rest of the world
How the! What is and what you'd never be
Thank you Marcus College for sending that track along to me
Completely legal of course to play it on the show
But it's a full bar Friday, what can I tell you?
Marcus, another guy who I'm looking forward to talking to
I think we're scheduled to speak either next week or the week after that
I'm so happy
Oh shit, hold on a second
It's really raining now
I gotta close the window
Otherwise everything's gonna get wet
Hold on
So we meet my printer, we'll get wet
There we go
Yeah
Does somebody say something about
These conversations I'm having with the network
Because that's essentially what it is
And it feels a little bit to be honest with you
It feels like a
Almost like I'm calling the sales staff
I know that sounds weird
And I don't want that to come across wrong
But when you think about it
Whether we're converting customers for Go Daddy
Or whether we are trying to get
Customers for ourselves
Essentially we want our audience to work with us
To help us understand how to do better at what we're doing
And we're creating a company and building an industry at the same time
A true media industry, a parallel industry if you will
That's a sales job
Because it's almost like it's one thing to say
Hey, do you want a domain name anyway
So you can get it from me a little bit cheaper
That's easy, easy, easy sell
But then it's like, hey, I want you to take a survey
It's like, you know, could I just poke this knife in your eye
You know, it takes a real sales job
You have to convince people
And of course I want to convince my audience as well
And the reason why is because after we get through this initial survey
There's going to be a new one every month
Which you can opt in or out to participate in
That's up to you
But you'll be testing new advertising
How a placement of advertising
We'll be talking about music and shows
Just tons and tons of information
And the size of the panel that we're building
Minimum 7000, we're looking for 10,000 people
Which I think we'll get quite easily
We're already well on our way
That is unheard of
That's larger than any any size audience that is pulled for presidential elections
Even, I mean, it's huge
Absolutely huge
And it's a pity because, you know, lots of people say, hey
All right, I took the survey, but how come you guys couldn't be
You know, it was so old fashioned
It was so traditional and you know what?
Yes, of course I hate that
The reason why it's very traditional
Certainly this first one is me
You'll feel if you ever done a survey
You can say, this is kind of like every other survey
I've done with little different questions
But you have to do that if you want to have results
That the advertising industry is going to accept
That has to be in a certain format
And it has to adhere to certain standards
That they wanted to adhere to
And in fact, we actually
The initial survey, I looked up a copy
Just what the powder was playing
Because I had sent it to Mark Nemkov
And I said, dude, let's make this survey fun
You know, so that, you know, we can have people laugh
And be entertained while they're taking the survey
Now we weren't allowed to do it
Because everyone feared that
Because it's, you know, we basically put a
Funny answer after each question
And the fear was, is that the results would be discredited
Because a lot of people may be put, you know, maybe
Distracted by that
I'll just give you a couple of
So it's like, are you the number one, are you currently
Subscribe to any podcast within the magnificent
Potion network
A, yes, B, no, C, not sure D
What in blazes is a Potion network
And then question two, why the hell not?
A, I don't know, B, I don't know how
B, I'm not sure D, I've suffered several blows to the head
How do you typically watch or listen to podcasts?
A, on my computer, B, on an iPod
C, on an MP3 player, D on a mobile phone
Or E, through the alien implant put inside my colon
During my abduction
You know, we had some fun with this
And I should put this up
It's like, how much do you agree with the following statements
About pod show?
A, my interest grows as I watch or listen to more pod shows
See, I get bored of this crap
And usually turn it off before it's over D
I look forward to the next episode of this show
E, I look forward to the next episode of the show
When I forget my medication
F, this is the kind of pod show I watch
Listen to all the time, G, I like cookies
H, I feel that pod shows are informative
I spend a lot of time my basement alone
Because the world is plotting against me
I mean, we had some fun
And when you read through this, you chuckle
Throughout the whole thing, but we weren't allowed to do it
So that's how we came up with the whole suckless idea
What we learned and I think
Well, obviously made some mistakes
What we learned is that it's far more effective
To have each independent producer or host or pod cast
Or whatever you want to call them
To communicate with their audience
In the way that they're comfortable
So even, you know, naming a promotion like this
Makes it very difficult for everyone to adapt that to their audience
So we're now doing something
I think is quite revolutionary
We are going to fully support with all of our resources
Each individual producers, many campaign
Whatever they need, however they want it done
We're going to support it
If they want to call it something else
But we've all committed to try and convert
5% of our audience
Which would put us way over the 10,000 mark
But we can commit to converting 5%
To actually take the survey
Please don't just go to survey.podshow.com
Go to dailysourcecode.com
And click on the link that I've put there
Because I want to track my performance
And see how well I do
And asking all of you to do this
Incredibly unfriendly thing
But it will get better
This is what I'm committing to you
Because you're going to be
Seeing things happening in pod casting
First before they're actually exposed to a larger audience
So just like
I'm looking forward to lots of people working with us on channels
I'd like lots of people working with us on this
So that we can really create something
Something real intangible
That's going to stick around for a long time
A real industry
Now I spoke to soccer girl yesterday
Very hard for me to talk to her
After the back and forth banter we had
I was kind of like
I don't know what to say
I love you
And she has her own ideas
Around a mini campaign to convert her audience
And to motivate her audience
To help us
Sockless
By taking the survey
Hello
This is soccer girl
Today I'm going to talk to you about a topic that's near and dear to my heart
Sucking
Sometimes sucking works for us
Like when we eat a lollipop
But other times
It works against us
Like when we want to save that lollipop
Well now it's possible to have our sucking and eat it too
Visit suckless.podshow.com
Exactly the way I thought it should go
Yesterday poor city PD launched
The season finale episode 7
And in July we're going to be kicking off season 2
And there's some startling revelations at the end here
Someone does get killed who you kind of wish wouldn't get killed
So it's very dramatic
And I really am so proud of this show
It is done on such a ridiculously small budget
I'm just ridiculously small
But we're very proud
In conjunction with 11 Bravo Productions to bring you poor city PD
It's a cop show
A cop show with no limits
Because there's no limits
So some of it's pretty violent
But it's violent in a different way than you see on television
I think some of it's a lot more real
Some of it were not quite pulling off yet
But the story lines are there
And there's a mistake and there's
And the whole thing is just I don't know
It's kind of sexy
Hi Adam it's Kevin
Lawyer listener from Cambridge also from first person show
Listen to you
So watch the pod show
Cop drama
Last night
And just wanted to call in and comment on it
A couple of thoughts
I was really weird watching the show
Thinking this is an a TV show
With the limitations of what can happen
Of what the sensors you know
A lot
So I really was thinking about anything
Can happen there
You know same with it
Not being a movie and not wondering
No idea what rating it is
I thought that anything happened yet
And the thought of the cool show
Overall
The acting was good
The writing was interesting
You know, sent me an interest in
One of them maybe want to come back and check out more
So it's pretty very nice to do action
From sort of thriller drama
On to a small budget
Because you can actually see
The fight things
Look at the content
And it's where somebody's got blood on them
Yeah, you know
Some of the you're right
So what happens is you do recognize
Some settings and scenes
As like hey, wait a minute
Didn't I see it was not the warehouse
From three episodes ago
But there's this charm to it, man
This charm to it
And the blood thing yeah
That's like the biggest item on the budget
All these actors are in it for free
I mean, or basically for cost
Let's put it that way
And people love to have a listing in the IMDB database
Because there is a true production
And they're all professionals
Because they work on lots of stuff in North Carolina
You remember I went there with the
With Richard Brewer hay
And we hung out with those guys for a while
I mean, so this is part of the results of that
Is the continuation in season two of
Or poor city PD
But each time someone gets shot
You use one of these blood squibs
Fifteen bucks
You know, that shit starts to add up
When you've got a dramatic gun battle
I mean, it's amazing how
How spoiled we are
And high standards we have as consumers
Because I noticed that somebody would get hit
And then they would have blood on them
Which you don't really think about
But I'm sure it's one of the budgets
It's budget problems
So maybe the radio, maybe the radio
Maybe the radio, maybe the audio
It's just that so much simpler
That can be easier to do
On a shooting
Or maybe we don't expect quite so much
But at the video
Or visual entertainment
The primary means of entertainment these days
We really do expect a lot
I don't know, maybe
It's too much to take on
Trying to do an action
Drama like that
But I'm interested to see
Whether you guys come up with anything else
Looking at the format
I'm sure there's other format
They would lend themselves even better
To a small budget
Yeah
So he was good work
I'm away in the work now
So I hope to hear you on the GFP thing
Thanks
Right
So you're saying something interesting there
You're saying that there may be other formats
More suitable to a lower budget
Yes, that's true
But I do like trying it
I think the budget per episode
I don't know
It's like a couple grand
It's really not a lot of money
But I think it can be done
And I think that
We're looking at a much smaller screen format
Typically
The way this is consumed
Although always keeping a bigger screen in mind
I think the writing and the production
And the special effects
They're already damn good
And I think that they can work around any problems
But you're right
If you look at CSI and Miami
Or CSI, any of the CSIs
That could be a million bucks in episode
Minimum, maybe it's more
So yeah
It takes a lot of people to make something
Really slick the way we're used to it
Sometimes we get a bit jaded
We don't think about how many people it takes to make a great
A great production
I'm just saying
So that's Port City PD
Link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Hey Adam, it's Chef Mark in New York City
I was really bummed that you didn't play my comment last week
I sent in some information to the listener
Who was looking for cheap and fun things to do
In New York City
Well, maybe I don't remember
It was boring Mark
And it hit me
I got to play my theme song
That's what it did
She walks on the street
From Chelsea to Times Square
A personal chef
Without his cook
Where he tells his stories
With his main team name Steven
We've our remarkable Steven
We've our remarkable
Well it just so happens that I just posted
Remarkable Pout Podcast number 96
Which of course you can find on pod show
And that was my coverage of the Taste of Times Square event
That happens on restaurant row every year
And there I spoke to a number of restaurant tours there
And there's some good cheap inexpensive fun places to eat
One of them is House of Brews
It's right on restaurant row
And it's a beer hall that has over 86 beers
And so he should check that out
It's on 46th street
Also for cheap eats
There's Pam real Thai food
And that is right on 49th street
Between 9th and 10th Avenue
You can find it at Pam real Thai.com
And this lady is from Bangkok
I interviewed her for an upcoming podcast
They only accept cash
And is the most authentic Thai food in all of New York City
It's surely
If you like Brazilian food
There's rice and beans
Which is on 49th and 9th
It's a little hole in the wall place
But man it is the best
Brazilian food you will find in town
Now for diversions
Of course Brian you can check out the museum of sex
That's at 5th Avenue at 27th Street
It's only 14 bucks admission
Pretty cool huh?
14 bucks for all you can learn about the history of sex
So Brian
Before your trip
Check out my remarkably mark podcast
I have a number of sound scene tours
Around New York City
All my favorite neighborhoods
And I talk a lot about the history and all the cool
Fun spots there
And you can find that of course at
Remarkablymark.podshow.com
That's it
Catch you later Adam
Add episodes going into the travel channel
Remarkablymarkable
Chef Mark everybody
Thank you so much my friend
I've come to love you ever since you cooked for me
Understandable yeah
Yeah
Adam
Any from Berlin California checking in
A couple days ago
And I made a couple weeks to you
Are so
You played Howard Jones
Revolution in the heart
Right
I think it's what I just did
I downloaded our iTunes
To tell all those music labels out there
That you know podcasting really works
Especially when it comes to trying to push music
I just pay for this
Legally
And now I
It's mine
So
Talk you later
Hi man
And despite the fact that you're a scruncher
Yeah
You know we should stop and think about that once in a while
There's something amazing
Has taken place over the past couple years
There are now real vehicles
With thousands of people listening
That can be used
You know for marketing
Gee
Who would have thunk it?
So if you if you've got a band
If you have some tracks
And you want to expose them to the world
You know there's a lot of things you can do
Put getting up in my space page
It's probably the top of everybody's list
But throw some tracks up on the pod safe music network
Because this enables podcasters
And independent producers around the globe
To use your music
In their shows
To promote your music essentially
Because they'll play it they'll talk about
They won't play it if they think it sucks
You know and there's all kinds of specialty stuff going on
It's really beautiful to see this happen
And we just don't stop and I think
Look around us
Often enough to see how well we've done
You know look at all these connections we've made
I have friends that you have been friends of mine for two years
I've never met but I'm not just a friend
You know I'm a fan
Join me and GB and pod safe musician
And podcaster Matthew Ebel
For an informal Skype chat
On the chill cast with Angie B
If you knew what I did on a day-to-day basis
It's not a glamorous job
I know tell me about it honey
Driving for nine hours in New York traffic
It's not a glamorous job
Especially for when I did the show in drag and Pittsburgh
Oh yeah that would be a problem
Yeah
People wearing next to nothing all over the island
I mean like you know that
There's girls in bikinis and
And you just happen to be the key guy
I can't
Yeah
Well I'm the guy to pee on
Why will let them?
Oh come on
We all know that you're gorgeous
Sally went
Check out the special one hour
Chill cast chat over at angiB.com
So you know you hear a promo like that
I'm thinking that's awesome
Matthew Ebel's getting exposure to angiB's audience
Thousands of people listening to the chill cast
It's gonna do some form
It'll bring people to gigs
It'll move tracks
It'll do something amazing
We're doing it people
We've pulled it together
We're making it happen
Wouting around the man
Matthew Ebel on the show
Sally went down
Sally went to savage
Sweet southern bummer
Every Sunday she filled her piece
But you got, come with me, I'm not too happy now
What's the girl like her gonna do?
Saturday never made it to the road, never saw the night never even heard the drink coming
Saturday only walked on the track, man, where the rails took a never thought to look back
It's Saturday not the sea was doing right, but you went home, hurt it, but you never saw the light
Never heard the drink coming, let it hit her in the back, Sally went down, Sally went down
Sally didn't want to get involved with the scene before her
Keep it down, walk it on the track, maybe they were just ignore her
But she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down
She didn't listen to the man before her
Sally
No, no, no, no
Sally came down
He said you had to leave your stomach, that would be a drink coming
It's a dream coming when a theater in the night
Saturday, we're in town
Sally, we're in town
Matthew, you evil, we're in the front of the show
Sally, we're in town, you'll find him with the pot safe music network
What day is it today?
It's Friday
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday, and a spinal fund for the week
Okay, so maybe not so philosophical as I usually get on a football Friday
So we bring you the final thought of the week
But what I just said
Kind of stuck with me throughout the song
I was listening to Matthew, it's like
You know, we just don't stop
and count our blessings off enough
Look at what we've achieved in a very short amount of time
We've created an entire industry
And you know, fuck community
It's an industry going on here
There's something that we can all participate in
Whether you're in it to make money or not
We've really done a lot, we've made a lot of great connections
The connections being devices to content and
Content to people and people to people and
Music to programming, it's quite astounding really
So what I'd like you to do is just
One year next time you are listening to a podcast or watching something
Cruise and around maybe you're messing around with your channels
I'll be messing around with channels
Just think about how cool it really is and that a few years ago none of this existed
You know, we just we just take that shit for granted
Way too quickly look at cell phones
Fifteen years ago no one had one in fact if you had one you were kind of considered an arrogant ass
And now look at it
Remember those science fiction movies where one day we'd be walking around with little devices a
Touch story here and we'd be talking to each other
Uh, I think that happened
Is Bluetooth earpieces? It's exactly what's going on. Oops, sorry
Pilot error
So you know, that's that's really groundbreaking stuff
And there's a lot happening in what we're doing
Independent audio independent video podcasting
Created people getting their message out whatever it is
So it's probably going to be a long fourth of July weekend for most in the states
Of course I'll be here on Monday and on Tuesday
We'll do it's about fourth of July especially if you got any great Americana songs
You'd like me to play on the fourth of July episode of the Charlie police and those on to me
And of course out of it pot show dot com is the email address where you could send me all your other crap daily sourceco.com
For the show notes links to everything played today on the show and I'm looking forward to a great weekend
Hope you are too
Friday and I'm spinal thought of the week. Hey, I love you. I mean it
Another pot show podcast stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Subdupt daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pot show and limelight