Greetings, Adam. This is Dr. Lancaster. We have something extra special for you for the
DSC-610. My group has been studying unique birds in West Virginia and we've found
the current enjoyable. On the endangered species list for years, it's an amazing bird, a bright
yellow battery, we've found one of the tree sitting in front of us. Perhaps you can hear
listen most of the other birds at the unit call. It's amazing bird.
What? Hey, did it get it? Was that a little yellow bird over there? Did it get it? What is that
quail? That was a cutlass well. A cutlass well, but it's a, it's a, well, it has a taste.
Now it's a bird on the endangered species list. I don't know about no danger, it's dead.
You can't understand, it's very rare. That's right, I just, I just cook it a little long.
I just don't, can I borrow your gun for one moment, please? Well, sure what you would see
an element when you wouldn't get, hey, hey, wait a minute, why are you putting that thing at me?
Oh, I don't know, buddy, I don't know. You see, sometimes Adam, you have to text,
matters into your own hands when you're dealing with someone who doesn't quite understand what
you're doing. Now while I'm on a roll, if there are any radio executives around here,
with $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio content
in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I know that I still do what happens I won't do. I'm flying into the future, I just have it all by,
and I get high. So I can say stop at least into my mind, but I think I never really thought to
new people, but I thought you might like to know. We never really thought to new people, but to my
sorrows show up, preach about so, track it to you, woman, damn the day I only won't buy a gun.
And the dream that the change in me, do your feet just like I do,
me, then you turn as well, she says, it's because you're right with you, oh, oh, oh,
Tuesday's five with me, say, say it over again Tuesday's five with me, say it over again Tuesday's five with me,
say it over again, say it over again, say it over again, say it over again, say it over again, smile
I never didn't stop but never left you out of my mind
Never really thought to knew people but I thought you might like to know
Never really thought to knew people but to my sorrow shall I
Two days find it with me say
Say it over and two days find it with me say
Be it me before, and let your wife stop
Say it over and you've turned wr
Say it over and two days found it with me say
Say it over and two days find it with me say
All right, with you, I love you.
Two days, five with me, say.
Say it over again, two days, five with me, say.
Say it over again, two days, five with me.
You know, how can you resist when you find a fire eight song
that has two days in it.
You find it on a Tuesday, Tuesday is fine,
and it's just perfect for episode six hundred and ten of the
daily source code coming to you from the curry manner,
west side of Guilford.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It is Tuesday, obviously.
And I'm late, because today was almost like a job day.
Patricia and I both had to be in London.
She was working on something that I'm not allowed to tell you about.
You know, maybe next week she'll tell you come on the show
and tell you yourself.
And I saw I tagged along for that,
and so I had, you know, just general stuff.
I had to do this morning.
I'll have you know that I finished the admin.
I had simplified my life so well,
and no matter how little comes into this house through the mailbox.
Actually, I'm amazed at how much it is.
And you gotta open this stuff, because it's like,
it's like the email obsession, you know,
you're gonna miss stuff.
And boy, did I?
Let's see.
They were about to turn off the gas about the same company.
So the British gas was about to turn off the electricity.
The council was going to have me arrested for being behind
uncounseled tax.
Yeah, you know, it was only only three things.
I kind of messed up.
But at least I got there right under the wire under the on the nick of time.
In the nick of time.
Yeah, I had a quick lunch with the super agent Keith.
He's gonna be working on some stuff for us here in the UK.
Basically getting some, yeah, getting some ink and some press on on the network
and shows.
And he's a crazy guy.
He's come up with some interesting strategies, which,
oh, man, once I'm back, I'll be able to tell you more about
because yes, I'm gonna go to San Francisco.
No, I'm sorry to New York next week following on to San Francisco
and I'll be out there for a week and then come back.
So I know, and it's just the way things are going.
And there's so many cool things happening at the same time.
Just like being thrown around like a sack of potatoes around the world.
But I've been home for a while.
So I'll be pumped up for it.
I got some interesting, well, not just feedback,
but interesting slew thing.
You know, whenever there's something I wonder about on the show,
someone will usually find out.
Hello, my name is Michael.
I'm from Bristol.
There are songs to listen to.
Yes, he's 6-0-9.
Almost towards the end of it now.
There are songs from the film.
Hello, we in Halloween.
I think it will season up the witch.
Three more days to Halloween.
Hello, we in Halloween.
Warden.
Zero, Sam Rock, if I cover some kind of masks on the head.
And the year I did, was it was a chip or something into the bucket of things.
We'll have from stone heads, rock, it was stone, and I know yeah.
And it was triggered on there.
It was like a doomsday film, when that...
No, come on, let's insert this film.
I've never listened to the other two Halloween film.
No, but I like that idea of using Mass Media,
or using some form of distribution to trigger people's minds.
You know, I mean, that shit.
That's it. I love it.
Do you think it was going to ask you?
What if that actually is happening with Trinity?
You done the free Trinity thing.
That seems to have gone quite an over the year.
There was a lot of logistics involved,
but we don't see that much about that for months.
If you still got Trinity,
I was Trinity being solved.
Is it on Great List?
That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it.
Two, three.
Thanks.
Yeah, man.
Well, I'm going back to San Francisco
so finally I can get something done.
How hollow does that promise sound to you?
Ha ha ha ha.
Just don't love me.
You know, put on the mask and you won't go.
Kill me.
There are lots of people writing in from Germany
in an anticipation of Pod Show coming to Germany.
Alexander, by the way.
Alexander Almoff. He emails me a lot.
I'm not quite sure what his deal is.
He's on the inside with like military.
He's like someone under deep.
He's like deep throat in.
He knows everything about what's going on with the government.
And he's interesting.
I think he might be a savant actually.
Adam, not all German speaking, which that well.
Okay, this is a reference to me saying I thought that the Germans
that I met and spoken was very well.
After World War II, Germans divided two parts east and west.
Yeah, okay, I get that.
All right, so of course the east didn't have as much
access. I understand that.
And interesting.
Interestingly, he says, recording.
Regarding Pod Show in Germany.
I'm already speaking like a recording.
Pod Show in Germany.
You should definitely go to Berlin.
And not a lot of people are recommending Berlin.
I think that,
Cologne has the, has the upper hand right now.
Great city Berlin.
Great public transport.
Great airports in the city and close to the city.
Also air Berlin flies to almost all the major cities in Germany.
If you have to go to other cities.
Sony Center would be the best location.
Hmm.
Okay.
I know I have to go look at all these,
where all these spots are on the map.
We have a, a frapper map or something with all the good.
Well, actually, that would be, there must be a German frapper map.
Isn't that so we can see where with the highest concentration
is of producers.
Might be something.
And Johannes says Cologne would be the perfect location
for the German ponchoage queue.
Very big and all kinds of media.
And it's a very, very nice city, which is often described as
Italy's northern most city.
I like the sound of that.
Yeah, that's nice.
Comic strip.
How the Adam.
Here is CSB from comics to blog.com.
So you mentioned serious radio on your latest podcast.
But, oh, that was in reference to no cameras and saying
that serious sucks less than an accident.
Yeah, okay.
I have a feeling that you never really managed to deal with this
tactic.
In my view, you were not mean to think with other serious presenters
enough.
You know, there's something to that CSB.
Not that it has any influence on us not continuing with our deal.
But I have to agree that there was a very difficult to kind of integrate with
the other channels and then with the other shows because not all of them were
actually from New York and, you know, we were definitely West Coast based.
So I also, I'll agree, but I have to say, I was promised that they would arrange
for a spot on Stern as well as on Jay Thomas's show.
Because I did listen to your advice to CSB, but I guess either they didn't ask or
we just got turned down and they were afraid to tell us.
And we should have given interviews and evangelized podcasting by the way.
Well, of course.
Jay Thomas, my path, and how I'd stand.
And also, your show on series was playing too much of potential horrors instead of the best
of hope on the sphere.
I need to do it.
Go get your own satellite deal.
Then if it would mean playing case and the blow job podcast.
Adam, I kind of ask you, please talk to serious folks to bring.
You know, I think we asked them one time if we could run their show on series and they declined.
So, what can I tell you?
I like the name though, the way you describe it.
Thought showing podcasting back to serious.
Please, we'd make one on top.
Go back to serious.
You know.
On May 29th, unwind with Angie B.
We'll present an artist spotlight on love spirals and love spirals down here.
A lot of it has to do with time.
That was where I was in the 90s with the low spirals downhorns.
And low spirals is where I am at now.
And with Angie, a whole different person.
Band founder and my musical partner, Ryan Lomb, joined me in the studio to discuss the band's
16-year history during one of the most revolutionary periods in music history.
And I just amazed, like, wow, you could get all the songs on your computer.
You could, like, move the tracks around, it blew my mind.
I already knew what I wanted to do.
I wanted to, like, produce an studio.
I just didn't have access to that technology.
Now, anyway, goodbye and Apple and have Garage Band built in.
Plus, the world debut of a brand new track from upcoming third album.
Check it out and unwind.podshow.com.
And, uh, unwindies.
Wow, vintage bars brought to you by Tyler and all PM.
Probably presented by.
Yeah, I can't believe that this past me by.
Yeah, I'm so, sometimes, this is so much going on.
I cannot believe that I've missed two new tracks by the Louis Vuitties.
You know, they've probably sent me email.
And I probably have just, it's gone past the queue and I've not seen it.
And you know that, for me, these girls really were the,
well, they were it.
They were part of the spark that led to the pod save music network and the pod save music license.
Actually, I should tell you that story because I don't know when the last time
is that I did talk about it, but before anything was called pod casting,
I've, they had somehow stumbled across one of their MP3s on their,
on one of their sites somewhere and it was the song famous.
And I really liked it and I sent them an email.
I said, could I please play this on, on my show?
Calling it a show at the time.
And they said, yeah, no problem.
And, uh, and I did and other people who were doing these,
what we now know as pod cast heard it and they would also send off an email to the,
to the, to the, to the biddies and you know, I'd given the email address or whatever,
and then they get permission to play it.
Um, and after a while the biddies got in touch with me and said,
you know, we're actually like selling more product because of whatever you guys are doing apparently.
And, and then, you know, it was so, so clear, you know, we need to make it simple for,
um, the artists to give out the license, the, you know, a particular use of their music,
without all this emailing back and forth and then put in the, hey, I'm reporting it.
Um, that I actually played it and please, I do hope you report when you use music from the pod same music network.
And, um, so that, you know, that really sparked it all and then, uh, well,
long story, uh, fast forward.
We've got, uh, you know, I mean, how many artists do we have on this thing?
I think we have probably about 60,000 tracks from, I don't know if it's 18 or 19,
maybe over 20,000 artists now, I should check as you get those stats.
Doesn't matter. It's all good stuff. It's all good.
Now, um, they have a new album coming out or it's, I haven't seen it yet.
So I guess it's on the way. It's called Love You Mean It.
And, you know, and that, you can see a picture of one of those candy hearts.
And this is one of my favorite expressions. So right there, they've stolen my heart once again.
Love You Mean It. You know, that's kind of like a thing that we did in, you know, the 80's post breakfast club.
Um, and then there's two, uh, oh, a second.
Um, it's a two new tracks, uh, last night in Shelburne.
And then this one, and I swear to God, they wrote this about me or for me.
It's just, it's me. I know it. I'm absolutely sure.
And even, uh, they don't even have to tell me it's true.
Because I know that they wrote this song about me and I love them for it.
Odd Bird. Here's a list of his bitties.
Love You Mean It.
You're one of the weirdest people I've met.
Strangest duck in the pond.
Oddest Bird in the nest.
How did I get?
I got it.
You wear your grandfather's pants.
With ties that are much too bold.
Yet you walk with a bounce in your step.
Oh, oblivious.
Though you may be quirky,
It's strangely working on me.
You make the rest of them wonder.
But you just make me smile.
Like so many other men.
You tell a good dirty junk.
You get drunk now when again.
It's not too bad going at you.
It's no good.
Though you may be quirky.
It's strangely working on me.
You make the rest of the wonder.
No, you may be worried, just keep on doing that thing.
That makes the rest of them wonder, but you just make me smile.
I can't talk to you on the phone.
You speak a language all your own, but sometimes I speak it to the time I go.
The lascivious bitties, odd bird, and that is so I just love them.
I just love it.
It's a fantastic.
You'll find it on the Potship Music Network.
You'll find it at Potship.com slash music.
You can search for it.
Of course, go to datingsourcecode.com, click on the link.
It'll take you right to their page.
And girls, I want you to know that I have had at least one sexual dream about every single one of you.
And sometimes two of you were in the same dream.
Adam, maybe a good idea.
Next time, you do a sound sightseeing tour.
Sound seeing tour on the plane to upload or show an AAC format, including pictures.
Don't picture.
Next time, space music, I'll make you the AAC field.
Okay.
But the reason I pull out the emails, because his P.S.
This is from a SNNTC space music.
I quit smoking too after I heard you quit.
That is cool.
Thank you.
How many other people try to give it up or just give it a go?
When you heard me talking about, I bet there was more out there.
And it's a bitch.
Damn, it's a bitch.
Let me tell you, let me just tell you that it's what's so messed up about it.
I love mixing my, you know, my weed with tobacco.
And you can perfectly self-medicate yourself throughout the day.
You can't do that now, because if you smoke that stuff pure, I'll be standing on my head all day long.
I've worked to do.
I got stuff to do.
I just can't be lethargic, so I can't smoke anything during the entire day.
And until, and this is what really pissing me off, you know, had a long day in the city now.
It's almost 10 o'clock.
And I'm like ready for something.
But I am definitely over the whole feeling of the nicotine and tobacco.
I really, really miss sticking something in my mouth.
I really do.
Yeah.
They'll get any ideas.
Have you heard of this e-sigarette thing?
It's from Asia.
I think it's from, is it Japan?
And it's somehow, it's, it's like a wooden fake cigarette with a little, like, a little LED at the tip.
And, well, let me look this up.
I saw this the other day.
Where did I held it?
I see that.
This will drive you nuts.
I've heard a lot of people about this.
E- would it be that simple?
E-sigarette.com.
I think I saw one on, maybe on eBay.
Let me see if e-sigarette.com works on a crap.
I'll just try.
Now, there it is.
Yeah.
E-sigarettes.
You notice that in Firefox now, if you use the Google search window in Firefox,
then it starts to give you suggestions as you type a dropdown list.
That's pretty cool.
Okay, E-sigarettes.
From the far east.
This will be well worth your while by the time I get to this page.
Believe me.
Because I just want to get it right.
Because it's quite an ingenious little device here.
Man, these pages are loading slow tonight.
I bet your Christine is downloading some shit.
Or Patricia for that manner.
All right.
We'll see if this loads anyway.
So it actually gives you, like, a fine mist.
It has a power supply.
I think it has, like, one of those faggy tips.
You know, there's, like, a French movie director tips.
Filters that you connect to the cigarette.
And so when you inhale, it actually exhales like a fine mist of nicotine.
I have no idea if nicotine is good or bad for you.
But I think that's the stuff that makes you feel good.
So the combination is kind of there.
You know, you're sucking on something because that's really what this is all about.
And then you get some of the, some of the nicotine.
I'll look into it.
I'll get back to you once this fricking page loads.
Hello, Adam.
It's Mike here from Bristol England.
Also known as Go Lemon Out of the Lills.
I've just touched up on me.
If you can get the C.S. and a car here.
Look at one last week when you're in the other plane.
Do you hear, do you hear in the background?
He's got the love, the moonlight sonata that I played.
If you have sophisticated that sounds.
Two over 200 years old that song.
And you just hear the guy with that talking with that in the background.
Already he sounds like James Bond.
Yeah.
Oh, well, I take that back.
Another one of the minutes and other plane, which is on today.
You said he's D.F.A.C.
Hey question.
I have to be forward about what they didn't want to.
Oh.
Port city P.D.
P.D.
The actual day when this show comes out, you know, people who have been following this show so far, they're subscribed, they're getting it automatically.
And they'll know.
So, you know, and it's like nowhere, is there a podcast to, I don't know if it's many podcasts or if any at all,
that say, okay, this show is always available on this day of the week at this time.
You know, it's always going to fluctuate. We don't have to hit the top of the hour news break.
So, that means we can be very flexible at working with the extremely inflexible mainstream media.
And when we think we can get a great article or an interview or something that, and of course, we're positioning the final two episodes of the first series.
And that will be, well, I shouldn't really announce it, but obviously we'll be timing that with, you know, some great news about a second series coming, perhaps I'm just saying.
What's really great? So, when we, and, you know, we're pretty close now.
In order to maximize our investment, we're trying to time the release of the episode to some news that we can generate around it.
And it's really cool that we can work that way because it's completely the opposite of the way traditional media has to do it.
But, you know, so in that case, yeah, it's taken us a little bit longer, but it's also, it production took a little bit longer as well.
And I think, and this is something that we are planning for the second series, should we complete that deal on, should we be announcing that?
It used to do companion episodes, just like, like Scottsigler does, like Mark Yoshimaru Namcoff does, you know, and to have that interwoven with the episodes.
And we've learned so much, I tell you, we've learned so much.
All right, I got to cut this a little bit short, so let me see. I can do, uh, and I have two more comments. I'll save those for tomorrow.
I will have a regular day regular show and back here at the man or not going anywhere.
And, uh, so there's two more fun things to talk about.
Please visit the suck less zone to help pod show suck less. It's important.
I really would urge you if you're a listener of this show.
Or any other, uh, any podcast, really, because this data that we are, um, trying to aggregate is going to be used to make.
Our programming better, our network better, uh, all the podcasts that are participating in it, which are thousands.
Um, are also, you know, they're getting the same data. They'll be able to understand what else they can do with their audience.
And if we're really good, then, uh, we'll be able to make more money, which helps a lot of people trying to make a business out of this.
God, that sounded so fucking commercial. I just, just love myself now.
And this is Nigel's thing, man.
I like these, uh, these remixers, the young punks.
Stuff is getting better.
Norman Kirkdanks.
Okay.
For the next dance, move to the dance floor, take your part to buy the hands, and repeat these moves after me.
Yeah, God, look it and load that and aim for the hearts, spin it and flip it, rewind to the start.
You've got to use it or lose it or give it away. You've got to plug it and play it.
Yeah, you've got too much it, ascratch it, ascratch it, ascratch it, ascratch it, ascratch it, ascratch it, ascratch it.
Ascratch it, asbin it all, yeah, cuts my em Lash it, and arrows it.
And I'll touch it the song, yeah, got to speak, and destroyed, and take it to town.
Tell me what that you're saying, Jabot that.
Rhaise it, adjacent, all over the town, play it and crush it, rrate into the ground.
Are you gonna repaint a B'nean and pump up the sound? You've got to pull it.
I'm looking yeah, отнош…
It's full and I'm push it. I'm jumping on our str But I'm sure you can't subscribe to our circuit.
Slide in our notes, and switch it, remove it.
It's worth it, remove it, and we have it to vote
Tell me what do you have to take, how about that?
It's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth it, it's worth
it, it, I'll take it to town, tell me what are you're taking about that.
Race it, NSA said all over the town, fly it, and question,
intuitive the round you go through repair and burn it, I'll pump up the sounds, you got some wood, I'll plug it, yeah,
Seriously, Pull it and push it on don't bump on this already, you're gonna cap the work it,
bajo it, it's sliding our nose, it's rotating remove it and we live it to varios, to tell me what
where you take how about that?
You gotta do whatever you want, boy
You gotta do whatever you please
We gotta do whatever I tell you
You gotta do whatever I say
Yep.
Yeah.
Yes.
I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running
I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I run, I'm running, I'm running, yeah, I'm running, yeah, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running, I'm running,
I love that mix.
The battery power device is used exactly like a typical harmful cigarette, but rather than delivering
tar and toxins to the lungs along with nicotine, the poisons are stripped away and the
doses of nicotine are still provided.
Interestingly, the company claimed it's product is simply the best way to kick the habit,
but if these things can actually do what they claim, honestly it seems like a mark that
we get into and gadget editorial.
$200 a piece, $28 a piece, and I'm looking to picture here, and so it's like a cigarette
and it's in one of those filters which is kind of lame, but that's where the battery
powers, that's these leds, these LED, like a red tip, and it's like some kind of gas,
which I guess is the nicotine gas, and that's kind of what you want, you just want, you
want that something to hit the back of your throat.
I can do what I can live through this stoppage.
If you all are with me, you know what I'm saying, I can probably question if you're good.
Alright, everybody, dailysourceco.com, Adam at poncho.com tomorrow, we'll see if we could
get Patricia up here tomorrow.
That would be a good change about my sphere, and it'll be, what, day eight, nine, I've
lost count, smoke free, fucking love in it, another poncho podcast, stick it in your
sphere.