Oh yeah, Adam, I noticed that you're getting into the D.A.C. 4-5-7.
Double 5-7.
Too shale, chap, mayce me think back to the time when Miss Moneypenny, or yes, would be actress
who plead Miss Moneypenny.
She and I got together had a little trist and I showed her what the double owes really
are.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios, and record labels still think they can
govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media
corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code with
Adam Curry.
I've never sleep anymore, and I can't be with you anymore, and I can see in the darkness
since you left me in the dark, I replicines from our direction, along the screens
I've never been the same again, not since I had the operation, the searches were down
behind, but the left me with a plane, yeah, but they left me with a plane, so I watch movies
in the darkness, in my garage speak, and above it all is sub-titled, there are so tiny
dreams, but I don't speak Chinese, so I'll just never understand why you don't have
me anymore, and why your boyfriend wants to kill me, and why watching this film,
and for the night, so I can't be a living, so I can't have a place to see, or not depending,
I'll always plan at the multiplex, and what is plan at the movies, I need to try and eat a
strange book, freak accident, Chinese phrase book, taken off daily source code episode 557,
hey everybody, how are you doing coming to you from the affluent suburb, sorry, I'm sorry,
it's the curry manner on the west side of G-town, how are you doing? It's been one of those days
already for me, yesterday I had that whole BT thing I did in the morning, today at 930 I knew
I had an appointment with my dental hygienist and dropped Christina off at school and then continued
on to the dentist, but the road was diverted, broken up, so I arrived like 20 minutes late,
and they said, no, you know, I have another customer 10, I called you that I was late, why didn't
you say come back later, and she said, well it turns out we can take you to a clock, so
kind of got to hurry to show along today to make that appointment, and then of course I came back
to the manner, I walk in, I open the door, and the minute I hit the, the, the mat inside where you
where you wipe your feet, which is right inside the door, I know exactly what has happened,
how the little Yorkie took a dump, and I walk right in and step right in it, and man, it was one of
those, like those, you know, dark crap doesn't always have to smell, but when you step in it,
right, and then my finger started bleeding again, the one that I cut open on the, on the
nav kit, for the N800, I got lots of fun stuff to talk about when it comes to the N800 today,
but first the seems to be all kinds of trouble in mainstream radio land and and also with the
streaming media, I don't know if you've been following all these stories, I see Scott Penton sent
me story about first the payoff over all the fines that were paid over Payola accusations.
The company's accused were clear channel communications, CBS radio, enter-com communications,
and Citadel broadcasting, combined the paid a total of $12.5 million in fees for taking money in
exchange for playing certain records, or songs that actually says, a practice poppin on his
payola, which of course, you know, in a free open world, I guess, isn't a problem, but when you're
using very limited resources that are licensed by the government, you can't play favorites like that.
And let me see some interesting things in this story, not so much about, you know, well,
first of all, what did the guy from Clear Channel say? He is pretty funny here. It is Andrew,
W. Levin, Clear Channel's executive vice president and chief legal officer said,
well, no violations were found. We are pleased to announce that Clear Channel has agreed to
settle this long-standing payola investigation with the FCC. We believe it is time to close the door
on this ongoing inquiry and move forward. No violations were found, then I don't understand why
you paid the fine. The way this works, by the way, is through independent record promoters.
It's not like some record executive comes into the studio and slips the guy some bills,
and he starts playing the song as much more sophisticated than that. Independent record promoters,
and I know several of them, and a really nice guy's, but they are totally sitting at the
asshole of the industry of mainstream RIA and broadcasting. That's where the real money flows.
And I think I've mentioned before how it works, but they will essentially pay an independent
record promoter money. And it could be millions and millions, and it's often based on number of
plays, number of spins that a song gets on radio stations, that independent record promoter
basically represents. He doesn't really represent them in that case, and he doesn't really represent
the record company, but he can do things like say, hey, you know, I'm promoting Kaiser Chiefs.
I'm just pulling something out of my ass, doesn't matter who. I'm promoting the Kaiser Chiefs.
I'll tell you what. I'm going to give you 100 tickets to their concert when they come through town,
and I'm going to give you a promotional budget of $40,000. He's a real figures, by the way.
I'll give you $40,000 and 100 tickets, and now you're not allowed to spend that on anything,
but promotional activities. There's a little catch, which of course is, you know,
one of the monies in, right? And it gets paid to the station. It's not paid to disjockeys or to
program directors. Of course, there's all kinds of, you know, business-related dinners and lunches,
but that's normal in any business, I guess. And so, and of course, it's not written down,
but that is an exchange for an X number of plays. And those plays are determined by rotation.
So if something gets put into medium rotation or hot rotation, you know how many times it's
going to get played, because that's all automated. So that's essentially what this is about.
But here's something that I found very, very interesting. Where is it?
It was a very, it was about independent labels.
Let me see, here we go. So this is Eliot Spitzer, who brought this wrath upon
his radio companies. Mr. Spitzer's inquiry disclosed how such payment payments have become widespread
as label executives pressed to obtain exposure for stars. In some cases, label executives offered
pay off directly. Oh, okay, I stand corrected. In others, they hired middlemen known as independent
record promoters to funnel gifts or other enticements to radio station personnel. It's much more
sophisticated than that. I'd love to see the original court documents. I don't know if you can
get them anywhere. I'm sure under the Freedom Information Act somewhere. Here's, here's this
extra deal. So this settlement with the FCC, this article states, it's from the New York Times.
Comes at a time as a separate arrangement in which broadcasters agreed to devote more time to
playing artists who are not signed to contracts with the four big record companies. I caught my eye
because that basically could mean everybody. I think. But it appears that this deal, I'm reading again
negotiated by the American Association of Independent Music provides that the radio companies will
broadcast the equivalent of 8,400, so 8,400, half-hour segments of music from such artists.
I guess who are members of the American Association of Independent Music.
The segments can run anytime from 6 a.m. to midnight any day of the week,
according to the people briefed on the deal. Wow, this is very interesting.
And how do you get into into one of those 8,400, half-hour segments?
And that seems pretty exclusionary by itself. Could we set up a pod safe music
a pod safe music association, PMA, and negotiate such a deal? Why did they agree to that?
That's very interesting. I'm sure this is the independent record label, so I'm sure that
they're struggling to get anything they can, but it seems not like we have the really
the four big ones, then we have thousands of smaller ones who are basically a fifth big one.
8,400, half-hour segments. I wonder if that's from all radio stations?
And is that over what time is that? Is that over one hour, one day, 24-hour period? So is it
8,000 stations all have to do one half-hour segment? Does anyone have any more information on that?
That's pretty interesting. A lot of things changing there.
And the other thing was, I don't have an article to point to,
a docksurls actually, a dock.weblogs.com, I think.
He posted about the new rates for streaming, so you can stream licensed music legally if you want to.
And apparently the sound exchange has now posted new rates, which pretty much put the small guys out of
business. And I say, you know, start streaming pod safe music. This is crazy. I've got to tell
you, I'm afraid again to play anything from my first gen iPod when I look at all this and like,
now these guys are pretty fucking serious. They're really, really, really grassy. We had anything
they can, and it's a bit frightening, I have to say. And by the way, that $12.5 million, I'm just going
back to the FCC Payola case. Where does that money go? Does that go to artists who got
jipped, who didn't get played because stuff that was for pay for play was put into rotation?
Where does the $12.5 million go? Does it just go to the city? Does it go to Elliott Spitzer?
Inquiring minds need to know. Fantastic news. Nokia. I am such a fan of this
N800 tablet. I really am. It's not a cell phone. It's the web tablet that I've been using.
I'm just waiting about because I love it so much. I was doing email. I don't have to walk around
a laptop. No, can't. Everybody say it. Nokia. Nokia could turn on thousands of podcasters,
but I really like the open source nature. I'm SSHM from my laptop. And then I have the NC running.
Next to it, you should see this development environment. That's what the N800 is fantastic for.
It's available now. Love it. By the way, this is not paid endorsement. No money has
exchange hands with Nokia. All right. Sunder from podcast studio, Donna Nell. I thought the
vocals were a little low and that makes their sunder. I liked it though. Yesterday I tried it out.
I tried Void for the first time at the entire day to see how it would work and this gizmo project
is awesome. Now, of course, the reason why it's awesome is because I'm using it on a device that
is portable throughout my entire home. I can walk wherever I want, continue the conversation.
I mean, that's talking about the Nokia N800 web tablet. And I plugged in the headphones that come
with it. It comes with headphones with a microphone built in. So I love doing phone calls in stereo,
or at least with two earphones in. So nice. Because then you're really in the conversation.
It's much easier to concentrate. And so there's a mic built in. Everyone said that they could
hear me find. It was a very minimal delay. It seemed like an ongoing conversation.
The only thing I couldn't get to work at all yet. And I've looked around and I've googled it
and it seems that not everyone's having the same problem where they have had the problem and it went away
is a DTMF tones. So when I'm calling into a conference line and I want to, you know, I need to
control the computer on the other end with the touch tone keypad. It has a keypad. This gizmo
project software. And I hit it, but it, you know, it doesn't respond on the other end. So maybe it's
just a one-off that I didn't work. I like it. I really do. And people are calling me on it. Now
there's still some, some crap going on with it. You know, and I hate this every single time
this, you know, you work with new technologies and particularly when it comes to stuff that we're
so used to. Color ID is way, way, way important. And it just doesn't seem to work very well through
many of these voice applications. It shows up as asterix caller at sippphone proxy01.cippphone.co
whatever it is. It's not handy. Give me the, please, show me the number. So I know who's calling me.
I got a lot of comments about about voice over IP. As I, as I had expected and
this asterix thing, I've been reading about that for a long, long time for years it seems.
It looks like it's like a very robust platform now for a building open source based PBX's or phone
switches. Hi Adam, TJ for a user. I was just listening to the DSC on my every other day
commute back from Brussels. And you were talking about two things. One, getting a folks'
discussion, maybe for your offices. Plus, just want to say, have a look at a asterisk,
which is definitely a great open source PBX, which is not already your average open source project
that this cable is only in complete call centers. Yeah, he goes on for another minute in 24.
I'll save you. But yeah, I checked out the the Asterix project. That's awesome.
I'm going to see if I can, if I can get Brian to look at this, Brian is the operations
of pod show before he goes and buy some really expensive voice systems. So typical the way that goes.
But I think it'll work. Particularly for these phone conferences, it's fantastic. I call the
whole day yesterday. I think they used like 17 cents. I was on the, I was on for hours.
Yeah, so totally digging it. By the way, I have two accounts on the Gizmo project and the one
that's searchable. I don't have the password for it. I'm not quite sure how that happened. Maybe
someone else registered it. But it's not me. I'm not listed in the white pages. I don't want this
number to be known. If you don't mind. That comic strip blogger posted a comment about the
N800 yesterday in the comment section on the show site daily source code.com. As I'm looking
for a name, you know, we have Trinity, the lovely, the lovely beauty that is my baby poo colored
1984 Mercedes station wagon running on biodiesel that is going across the country as we get the
N800 system ready to feed back information. So of course, this box is about to open reports.
White open. So a select few developers can come in, violator file system. And of course,
if it's a sheet, and Trinity has a name, she has a name as well. I thought Angelina would be nice
because those are highly desired ports. Comic strip blogger yesterday with another suggestion.
He says, yes, Angelina Jolie is sexy because she's a mixture of two races, native
American and European, but you would be more proper to call the N800 Tariah. That's Tango
Alpha Romeo Juliet Alpha Tariah. It is a popular Finnish name and also first name of current
Finnish female president. Fins would love you for this. Tariah. And it's probably like
Fuck you in Finnish, and only comics would block it. Comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip,
comic strip, the daily source code with crap. That wasn't it. Oh shit. How did I do that wrong?
Oh man, it was so perfectly perfectly set up. All I wear is a comic strip blogger sent in this whole
thing. All right, I found it. Here we go. Where come? To help the city of Charlie,
557, a podcast of Adam Kerry who is a young boy compared to me an old prick who can't get it up.
Neither with Viagra nor with Levitra, but wrong cop off for just coffee with splendor.
Let me stay worthy. It's back. Oh boy. Yeah. I have no idea what he's talking about.
But thank you. Now I don't have to mention Splendent Folgers. You did it for me. Here's
a thing I played before the kind of misfire. The daily source code with Adam Kerry. It's my art
being able to choose the music that I want to play for you is virtually Nirvana. It's musical for my
work. I love the cowbell on it. Oh, it's sweaty. I really want to lift that leg and squeeze the
butt. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Good. It's geeky goodness. I mean, just start this thing up on a
command line and then lock that puppy down. You know, that's about all this need. It's low.
You're supposed to be my trophy wife and I can just see it now. And it's all for you. It's my job
to entertain you. If that means going to jail, so be it. I love Brian. No, just started working
at Pod Show at the beginning of the month. Welcome, Brian. He does that at the Frank Truth podcast.
It was a cool man. We're doing a whole mess of them for and we're going to do them in video.
I think for our, like, top 80 shows or something. It's a tremendous task. I have no idea.
We're going to pull it off. But this was kind of a test to see if this is, this is, you know,
kind of the direction we want to go. I love it. I love the way that sounds. I don't know, Jim.
Jim. You've seen fused. I've just got an invite this morning and I've just installed it.
Me, this is this is each of this. This is definitely the future of television.
Oh, I haven't gotten the invite to the minute, but if you don't already have one, give us a
certain, if I do get one, I'll certainly send you a link about you. This is fantastic. Hey,
so hearing James's enthusiasm, I have received a couple of invites to juice. That's the Skype
guys or it's a company, the Skype guys invested in. I don't think they're running the company.
And actually it's a Dutch name, which you would pronounce Yost. But okay, everyone's saying
juice fine, which makes it sound so much more like juice, the aggregator. But anyway,
so I think they're, their beta must have opened up a little bit wider because now I'm receiving
invites left and right. And I got to say, fire this thing up. It's like, wow, you're blown away
by the quality. They really, really did that right. And I'm looking at it. I'm like, I had the same
reaction James had. It's like, yeah, this is television. This is fucking awesome. And that, of
course, is the great thing at the same time, it's kind of the bad thing. Because it feels very
much like television and navigation. You know, it's like a cable system, so you have channels.
And actually more like programs, I would say. So you have, you know, the discovery network
has a channel and they have one show in there. I presume they're going to have more shows
per individual channel. It's going to be a lot of mainstream content in there. So I think for
for saying it's a, it's a different way of watching television. Absolutely.
Is it YouTube now? Is it, by the way, I would not mind having a, a pod show channel in there.
Definitely see if we can get that we can weasel our way and wouldn't be much different from
producing for serious satellite radio, I guess. Because, you know, it's, I'm not, I'm not sure if they
have like a subscription type service. The one thing I do know is, and I'm not quite sure how they,
how they add up the numbers. I know actually, yeah, they have it right here. When you use this
per hour, you will be downloading the equivalent of 350 megabytes and uploading the equivalent
of 150 megabytes of data. So that's half a gigabyte per hour of, of watching. Now, of course,
you're probably going to watch it for an hour, half an hour. It seems like that's going to be a
problem. If, if that amount of, if forget about, you know, people who are on set payment plans and
and stuff like that who could run into some significant issues. I got juiced by juiced
when that suck if someone didn't know that they had a cap on their bandwidth and they're playing
with this thing and then, you know, they get some astronomical bill. I guarantee you that's going to
happen. You know, someone is going to get fucked by that. But that can happen with anything. That
can happen if you leave a bit torrent open or lime wire or anything. You could get severely screwed
on you. I used to have that all the time in Belgium. Oh, it's suck. Because you couldn't even get
unmeted bandwidth there. But this half a gig thing, I think is going to be tough on just networks
in general. And I wonder, I think that it's highly possible. Now, these guys are kind of smart because
they're taking a, they're taking a stance and they're saying we're really going to go after,
you know, big television shows and mainstream content. And yes, we'll have some, what they call
user generated stuff. Crap, serious people. Stay tuned. More coming up. Yeah. So they say that they'll
have a channel for user generated content. So I pretty much seems like it's going, they're following
the iTunes model. And their business model from what I've understood is based on advertising. I haven't
seen any ads pop up yet. So I don't know if they've enabled that yet or how they integrate
them. They seem to have a lot of cool overlay technology. So when you're, you know, watching a show,
I presume something could slide in over the top. It wouldn't necessarily have to interrupt.
You know, that could be interesting to see what they come up with there. But this, this bandwidth
thing, I think it could spark off the first example. We'll see of a net neutrality debate in the
real world, because, you know, think about it for a second. That type of traffic. It's just a lot.
I'd ask any network engineer. If a lot of people are using this, I don't care how distributed
it is sucking down 350 megabytes. And well, it basically transferring half a gig per hour.
If that happens a lot in your network, it's going to start to suck. And maybe some of their
topology is set up. So, you know, it does work better within networks. But, I mean, my DSL, here's
pissed poor as is. Imagine if, you know, because, of course, I'm sharing it somewhere.
It's some head ever ratio. I forget what it is. So, of course, I'm sharing that somewhere else.
It's some head-end connection thing. Some switch point. And, you know, so, if a couple people
are watching juice through all these different, you know, local network points, it could, I think
it could bring down the network. I'd love to hear from engineers who know about this stuff.
I know a little bit about it. That's why I'm concerned. But, I couldn't really tell you if that
is a big deal of prepared for it. But, it seems like a lot. It seems certainly like a hell of a lot
more bandwidth than your YouTube usage, if you know what I mean. I mean, that's, of course,
that's why they get this beautiful quality. So, I think the, the telcos, the telephone providers,
basically, who are running a lot of this, well, even the cable guys, a lot of the same problem.
The cable guys know how to distribute video very efficiently. And this has, I just don't think
a very efficient way of distributing video. At least not with current capacity. So, I think that
they're going to say, hey, you know, juice guys, fuck you. We're switching you off the network.
And they're probably more likely to do that because the television networks and production
companies who are contributing. Now, again, I'd love to contribute to it too, because I think
the experience is fantastic. You know, they're licensing their content to juice. You know,
I think that they are, in effect, in direct competition with a lot of the services that the telco
providers, you know, think of IPTV, you know, the British telecom wants to provide their own television
on their network. In their own distributed way and their, in their way, you know, it's their
network. They know what the hell they're doing. I'm sure Virgin Media wants to do the same. They're
in fact, they're already letting you download stuff. So, you know, but that's through their system.
You know, we're going to have two systems with huge downloads running across the same network that
it only one party is paying for. I'm telling you, it's a train wreck. It's something very bad
is going to happen. Hey, Adam. This is the nylon from Wimbledon. So, let me say, I appreciate your kind
of editorial correction when you're sure about my call. Thank you. This is subject though.
Is I want to get your reaction to a e-mocker report that predicted that advertisers will spend
about 400 million on the podcast by 2011. And they say that compares to about, I think,
it was 40 million or 80 million last year. And that's compared to a 20 billion that they predicted
will be spent on online, advertised in 2007. So, basically, they're saying 400 million by 2011
on a 20 billion spend today's online, which sounds somewhat minuscule. So, one of the
goodger reaction, because this is your business, and you have been to capital behind you,
they've made assumptions. I just want to see if this jives at your view of where the podcast
business is going. And you're happy with that 400 million or what do you think of the assumptions
that may have made that a wrong estimation? Thanks. Well, very good question.
Good question. Okay. I know you're a scruncher. You don't have to tell me.
Yeah, I think it's way off. I think it's a very low number. I'm not sure. I'm not very familiar
with e-marketer. But I think that they're only look, they're not looking at brand advertising. I
believe that they're looking at the Google Adsense interactive budgets and how those are growing
and how those are being implemented and all of the metrics associated with it. I don't believe
that's where podcasting is going to make a difference. It's very hard to do contextual based
automatic insertions into podcasts. It's just hard. There's a lot of manual labor involved.
And while you're doing that, then you might as well really deliver the goods that brand advertiser
wants. So this is a big company's Pepsi Coke, KFC, McDonald's, Johnson & Johnson, Proctor &
Gamble, and Heiser Bush. Hey, look at what Anne Heiser Bush is doing. Anne Heiser Bush started their own
station. They know. Anne Heiser Bush beer marketers in general or any package goods. These people
are very, very smart. They know how to reach their audience. And actually, Anne Heiser Bush has
been having a very hard time with their products. They know how to reach the audience. But the
audience is, you know, things have changed. These, you know, what do you call, Alco Pops?
You know, the mixed drinks that come in in beer bottle sizes. You know, that's what's really
ruling their bris, but their business. I know they used to be a client. I know some folks over there.
I think the general consensus is, you know, if you're drinking a beer, you don't get laid.
That's kind of so they need to turn that message around. And that's very, very hard to do. And so,
you know, they're saying, hey, you know, screw this. We're going to create our own culture, our own
content. And they've got Anheiser Bush TV. It's very, and they got the same very skilled people on this.
And they're spending millions of dollars huge investment. So I believe that a better strategy for
a company like that would be to find existing content that has the culture you want and work with them.
I mean, you know, in a sponsorship arrangement, because only those people who have that audience,
like you, you're my audience. You may, I know that there's some people who listen to me just to hate
me, and that people just listen for all kinds of reasons. But, you know, I know you and you know me.
And so, if I'm going to start advertising a product, you know why. And we have a way of discussing that.
Anheiser Bush can't come in and just jump in and start talking the way we do as the daily source code
family. All 12,000 of you.
You know, so I think it would be much smarter for brand advertisers to go look for these,
these groups of communities who have a clear, not a leader, but someone at the head is an audience.
You know, it's that everyone, all these companies are looking for customer engagement.
Yeah, that's what we call an audience, okay. Audiences feed back to the performance, whether it's
in the theater, whether it's in the movie theater, whether it's on the radio is a little tougher,
but, you know, phone calls, it's the same thing. That's big feedback. You know, that's what an
audience is. That's what brand advertisers are interested in. People who are listening to shows
because they really want to listen to them. And not because they just happen to, you know,
catch a, catch a great snappy song and then we'll hear the ad right after it, you know.
So I think, uh, e-marketer is it? E-marketer? Yeah. I think they're low. I think they're very
low because a lot of this money is going to come from other budgets that e-marketer does not track.
That don't think they track radio and television advertising spend, particularly radio.
And mind you, radio people have been so restricted. Radio media buyers and creative people who are in
creative audio advertising, which says a lot of very fucking smart people really creative and they get 15
seconds, you know, do your job. And there's so many more things that can be done.
They've been sitting around watching the interactive people, you know, just their budgets grow
and all kinds of euphoria. And, you know, they still have, you know, the radio buyers still have
kind of the same budgets and the same dreary kind of existence. You know, it's nothing much has
changed. That things only get more limited. And, you know, that's tougher to, to get what you want.
And the buy what you want and get the information you want is these companies have consolidated.
And, uh, they're, um, you know, they're also looking at diversifying their spend. So I think it's
going to be much much higher than that. Certainly by that timeline, I can see it. It's just,
it's going to be much more. I think that most advertisers now probably are dipping their toe
in the water at around 100 grand for a month campaign. Um, you know, so if they start to go full
time, the numbers start to go up pretty quickly. And I think that there's, you know, I've said this
before. It's going to turn around advertisers will literally have to audition to get on certain shows.
And it's not like, you know, like American Idol type of audition. But, you know, uh, we already
see this today. We have plenty of sponsors who, um, we think will fit with a show in the show.
So, man, I don't think I can sell that to my audience. I don't think they'll be interested or
I'm not interested or, you know, I don't know a way to make it work. I'm okay. Don't do it. Next one.
I got a couple more comments before I get out of here.
Hey, Adam, this is Don calling from the West Coast account. And, uh, just picking up on a comment,
you may in the DSC553 about trading water. And, uh, we're probably already trading water. We'll
in fact, we are already trading water. You know, United States has been buying water or access to
water rights from British Columbia since, well, probably in the 50s, but certainly in my generation,
certainly in the 60s, uh, United States sponsored huge hydroelectric projects here in, uh, British
Columbia to allow the control and flow of the Columbia river, which flows down into the United
States. And, uh, they have, uh, basically sponsored, uh, some of these projects, uh, for the return
rights of having, uh, Canada not cut off large volumes of water going down into the states for two
reasons. One, the generation of hydroelectric power, which is, uh, is an extremely abundant resource
here in British Columbia, which gets sold at that very, very, very low rates down into the United
States. And, obviously, the continued flow of the Columbia river down into the United States,
so that farmers down south of the border can actually get access to the water for the purposes
of growing. So, uh, water trading, uh, on a global or an international scale,
it's been going on between the United States and Canada for many, many years. And, I'm not sure
if you're aware of that, just like, yeah, uh, this stems from, uh, I can't remember exactly what
the comment was that I may, but I read after that, and before this, before I saw it, I heard this
comment. I read that, um, uh, what was it? It was about email, um, that, you know, the, the, the, the
idea of paying for email, even it was one cent, which, of course, would kind of stop spammers,
but also would raise the bar a little bit on the quality of, uh, of email. You might think a
couple minutes, but, you know, if you're sending it in 100 emails a day, it's a bucket day,
but for a spammer, it's, say, it's much tougher. Um, you know, everyone's like,
up in arms saying, that's impossible. And no one will pay for something that used to be free.
Water is a very good example. It used to be free everywhere. And we buy it in bottles a lot more
than you'd think. And, uh, and there is a lot of, and, and the comment, the next wars are going to
be about water. That's for sure. Brent from Podio Radio sent me an email, uh, perfect subject line,
subject lines really do catch your attention. You look very pretty today, Adam was a subject line.
Of course, I opened that up. Uh, Bo Hall loves you. Some kick ass music for the DSC. Of course,
on the PMN, the song is Hell and Ecstasy. The artist is Bo Hall. You'll love this guy. I've played
them before, I think, living in love or something like that. Yeah, I do take this. It's like country rock.
Bo Hall on the DSC. Hell, ecstasy.
I can't even ever tell me you'll really leave me. I mean, it's not so bad.
Oh, you're serious, you're a girl who cried wolf. I don't believe you'll tell me why you
made the way you come back. But anyways, I'm done with this. See, I don't really want to hate you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
or we'll wait until we got you from me and have to see.
Paul Hall, hell.
And next to see you find that on the Podsave Music Network links in the show notes
of dailysourcecode.com.
Thanks to PD Love for another fantastic opening to the show.
I'll be back tomorrow.
It's going to be a weird week traveling to New York on Friday, then to North Carolina.
The reason why I'm in North Carolina on Saturday nights of Sunday is we're filming a new
episode of Port City PD and I play a role.
I have a cameo in the next Port City PD, so I can't wait for that.
They needed my clothing sizes, so I guess there will be costumes involved.
I'll be back tomorrow with a very sparkling clean teeth.
Talk to you then, bye-bye.
Another Port Show Podcast, stick it in your ear.