It's time you've got in the game.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get a domain name, free-click, blog, and complete email.
Get in the game at GoDaddy.com.
Delta, here it is, episode five, five, nine, or maybe source code with Adam Curry.
It's my art.
Being able to choose the music that I want to play for you is virtually your bomb.
It's musical for my work plan.
I love the cowbell on it.
Oh, that was so cheap.
It's sweaty.
You really want to lift that leg and squeeze the butt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good.
Now it's geeky goodness.
I mean, just start this thing up on a command line and then lock that puppy down.
No, that's about all that's needed to load.
You're supposed to be my trophy wife and I can just see it now.
I got this.
And it's all for you.
It's my job to entertain you.
In fact, I mean, it's going to jail.
So be it.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Turned me to see this.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not sticking greens, man.
I like to think I'm flying.
Just join me.
I'm testing his out of curry.
She's right, and all this black and white at killing time
She's a tree, I like her dress, and I like it on her own
But there's no way to believe him, but she says
Because her eyes are misled
I don't know her, like I thought I'd get
A long time ago, she used to look wrong
That whatever it was all
Sweet December, not in the inside
I don't know where they went, or if it meant
But everyone's gonna dance with the feeling inside
She's a tree, I like her dress, and I like it on her own
But there's no way to believe him, but she says
Because her eyes are misled
I don't love her, maybe I'm a friend
But if I don't treat you right, all through night
As long as you stay quiet, at killing time
I don't know what the weather's like where you are, but
This fits so perfectly with the weather surrounding the curry
Manor, the vinyl strangers and patriotic girl
Kicking off Delta Sierra Charlie 5-5-9er
It's a nice song, it's a happy song
From Georgia, and I guess they're touring around the Deep South
Getting ready to follow up, of course
They're music is available on the Podsave Music Network
Links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Hey everybody, how you doing? It's Thursday
Got the end of the week, it's creeping up on us
So two football Friday, which we'll be celebrating today
From tomorrow, I'm sorry, from the manner
Because I think I told you, yes, I've delayed my departure
On Friday, so that we can party down together
You know?
Yes, it was so busy, of course, I had that delay
Because of the lady Patricia's massive loss of blood
Through her nasal passages
It was up until like 12 o'clock, 12 o'clock, 12 o'clock,
12 o'clock, 12 o'clock, 30 o'clock, still on the phone
Using the VoIP, of course, the Gizmo project
Man, I'm really liking this thing
I'm really not liking my ISP though
The DSL that I'm getting into the cottage is just shit
You know, I'll get a single, a single connection
We'll probably do about
Hmm, from one server, so let's say I'm bringing in music
From the positive music network as an example
So I'm downloading the tracks for the show
It's, I don't know, about 35 kilobytes
About 350 kilobits per second, give or take
And that's slow, you know, I'm supposed to have four megs
Yeah, right
Maybe I should try one of those speed sites
That actually test the speed of my link
Anyway, so I can open up two of those streams
And both of them will come in at about
Three, four hundred kilobits per second
About half a meg, a little less than half a meg
So if I can do both of them the same time
That's telling me that somewhere there's some kind of
Throttling going on, it's not a very nice experience
But then again, we don't have that nice dedicated line anymore
It's just a old fashioned consumer setup
So as I said, it's beautiful today
The lady's out, lady Patricia's outside
Of course, why should she sit in the studio and do a show?
Why?
I mean, why?
Gracie with her, you know, you should send her email
You really should
Patricia at curie.com, tell her she had needs to come on the show
It's just like I can't coordinate it with her
And she has other things to do
You know, she doesn't listen, you know, there's a whole part of my life
The ones that we share together that she knows
I think about is a little bit of the concerning I have to say
Especially when you know what I'm doing with Amy Max
Hey, baby, it's Thursday, it's time
Get that ass and shake, and I should firm, take me up
Amy
Happy Thursday, Adam
Hey, baby, how you doing?
And hello to Patricia, she's there with you
She's outside, I just sitting in the sun
Go ahead and switch your mic, we're doing an old school move today
Okay, hold on
I got to move it up, it's moved actually
Reminds me of basketball practice
Okay, get ready
I know, take a moment to picture me trying to play basketball
Boy, boy, boy, boy
Anyway, you always talk about your fencing background
So I thought today we'd put it to the task
Okay, I'm ready, what do we do?
You're going to start standing tall with arms above your head
Okay, arms above your head
Now you're going to squat down to the floor and place your hands on the floor
Okay, now
Now you're going to shoot those legs out to a push-up position
And then we're going to go back to the squat
And jump up and lift your arms toward the ceiling
Excellent, seven more
Squeeze that butt through the whole thing
Breathe
I love it when you tell me to breathe
Extend those legs out all the way
I just hit my head on the ceiling
Is that all the higher you can jump?
I can't jump higher, I go to the fucking roof
Are you breathing?
Yes
Great job
Ow
Okay
And by the way, thanks for the ass compliment
I really do appreciate it
We are working on a plan for ass-ercise video
Although I'm not sure when we can get it out
After all, Chris and I are just a two-man team
You will be the first to know when it's done
Until then, you're going to have to get your move of the week video from FitLife
Have a great weekend
Did your wife just ask us to double-team her?
I didn't understand exactly what she was saying
Does she need help?
It does get the blood pumping
I couldn't jump so high because the attic only has
I mean, I can't jump high in any house
Actually
No, correction
At the curry castle, I could jump as high as I want
Of course, we could also ride the segway
And doors in the curry castle
I gotta fire that thing up again
It's just sitting in the garage
With empty battery and flat tires
The tires are just deflated
So they're not actually punctured
I should get that rolling again
That thing was so much fun
There you go
Let me see
Quick chat about the name for the N800
It seems like we have a real conversation
That's going here
Tariya, I think, is still the best name so far
Tariya is a finished name
So, you know, being a finished product, et cetera
And Tariya also being the first name of the president of Finland
Makes sense, right?
Well, let me see
Rick Denhan
Says Adam, with all the ports open
Remember, this is what we're doing
We're opening up this N800 Linux-based device
So the developers coming can come in
Violate the ports
And a violator file system
Through or wide open ports, I guess, as the way I should say it
Excuse me
Why don't you try out some nice folders
You know, the folders, they got these new gourmet blends
And for XR points, combine it with some Splenda
Flavor brand
Stuff
Rick Denhan, Adam, with all the ports open
Developers having full access being able to do whatever they want
You won't have any idea what's going on in there
And I will you
So why not call it Pandora
You'll never know what's coming out of Pandora's box
Someone else sent in a suggestion
That since Trinity is also a name from the Matrix
That we call the N800 Neo
It makes a lot of sense
That's way too cyber geeky for me
And Tom Scooting, official biographer of all things curry
Said maybe it's not a good idea to name a Sharon Stone
He sent this picture, I got to post this link at the show notes
The Sharon Stone, oh my god
No, if that's what Sharon Stone looks like these days
I don't think we want that analogy carrying over
To be kind of a bit freaky
And we're doing all this, of course, for the free Trinity ride
As my 1984 Baby Poo colored Mercedes station wagon
Running on biodiesel
Tracks across America
And we want to have some technology to track her
And for her to send stuff back
In the form of GPS positions
Periodic picture
Maybe some video, but certainly just some data
So we can follow the track as she goes from the west coast to the east coast
And far, far beyond
Okay, we focus your ears
Ready for Roger Smalls
Remember he talks in a very high voice
And it's an English accent, so it'll take a few minutes to adjust here we go
Hello, I said Russian here
He mentioned everyone he tries Trinity across the world
He's going to have a problem when they can't get her
And after that finish
Why then you buy a second biodiesel car
Skiff paperless back
After that finish driving that stretch of the journey
And I also think he's supposed to have a second beer
Cool for spare parts when Trinity breaks down
And that's now Roger
Oh yeah, oh yeah, you have a little faith Roger
Yeah, you don't hear from the guy for months
And now he's calling two days after and after another
Oh Roger, have some faith
Trinity's going to make it
Cars driving just fine
She's lovely
I remember I got to remember to check the tires
And make sure there's enough profile on him
I think the tires are okay
Everything else has literally been replaced on this thing
Now normally I play the Trinity jingle
The Jeff Smith free Trinity theme song
I found something in the Podsake music network today
Let me just find out where these guys are from
The home on the sec
I couldn't I can't believe no one else sent this to me yet
Because it makes so much sense to play this
It's from an outfit called 2012 AM
I think
201 to AM
So I'm just going to say 2012 AM
Let's see
Let me just read the bio here
2012 AM is the hottest new esoteric experimental
Alternative break beat band
I've come out of the San Diego
The San Diego
This lineup of all star groove masters
Which features DJ Quinique
Mark Houton
Emily Richards and Jason Brock is a booty shake
And sound generator and leaves audiences
Transdanced out
Well how can you not
When you read that
You're like hey I got to play this
Particularly
When the title
Is about all American hero
Willie Nelson
Check out biodiesel Willie
This might make it a lie to think into the tunnel
Some of the places where we go
There are people who come to the concert
So then you can spend your love
And my sister right there
One pair of set bio decent
This might make it a lie to think into the tunnel
Just a game
If you see a city
Back up to the world
My burning pain
I'm living my closest and far
It's a gift
Every time we change it
Yeah
One pair of set bio decent
One pair of sets bio decent
One pair of set bio auction
resources and terribly unfair to those arrested and their families.
It's time we stopped arresting adults who smoke marijuana responsibly.
For more information, visit normal's website at www.normal.org or call toll-free 888-67
normal and tell them will they sent you?
No!
Tell them will they sent you?
Hi, I was kind of an interesting experiment with 2012 AM.
I think I have to be in the club to fully appreciate biodiesel-Willie.
Hi, hi, yeah.
Okay, hold on.
You're someone's weird with my windows laptop.
When I right click on something on the desktop it takes like 10 minutes for a contextual
menu to come up and I can't close windows and shit.
It's still running though, which is kind of the cool thing.
Talk about bum rush the charts yesterday.
This is where we want to show.
I think ourselves mainly, but it would be nice to hold up a fist to mainstream, the music
industry and the broadcasting industry go really hand-in-hand when it comes to
mainstream and making hits as is proven by the recent pay-o-la scandal between the
four of the largest radio companies in the United States taking money directly or indirectly
through independent record promoters in exchange for airplay, which of course, it's such
a backwards, isn't it a weird world where in the mainstream world where the system is all
set up and oiled and it's been working fine for, I don't know, 40, 30, 40 years
and you know, no one's been making too many ways.
We've had a couple of pay-o-la scandals in the past, but these things just keep coming
back in waves, because that's the way it works, you know, it's just, there's no way to
regulate that, you know, interpersonal contact and high things are added to playlists.
But anyway, so here you have the record companies, the RIA associated record companies paying
radio stations to play songs in their limited resources, which of course belong to
you and I as well, the airwaves, you know, yes, they're licensed out to individual companies,
but you know, there are airwaves too, it's just like the skies, you know, not everyone
can fly over the United States, not everyone can land at any airport, all that shit is licensed,
because it's also ours.
Now other people are making those decisions for us, of course, in government, and obviously
we get the government we deserve as those any nation.
But it's so crazy that when it comes to playing, you know, those songs, the catalog, whatever
it is, maybe it's only 100,000 songs that they're really actively concerned about on a daily
basis.
You can't play those in a podcast.
In fact, it works exactly the, oh, here comes that contextual menu, gee, thanks.
In fact, it works exactly the opposite.
You have to pay for the privilege to play the songs.
So it's kind of skewed, isn't it?
Whereas probably the people who would want to play licensed music are probably big fans.
That, of course, this is all because of the ludicrous thought that these downloads of podcast,
that that would negate legal sales of songs.
No more than radio does, I guess.
I've never been a CD buyer.
I've always been a radio listener.
So I don't know, I guess you'll never get me anyway as a buyer.
But anyway, so the idea is to show that there is quite a lot of power in our open society
of podcasting independent audio in the broadest sense of the word, not just people who
play songs, but also those who create them.
And of course, we have the Podsate Music Network set up, which works quite well.
It's a beautiful ecosystem where podcasts are to complete this music, free of charge,
audiences can enjoy it, free of charge, and the artists get exposure, and they also find
that out when a song has been played.
It's kind of closes up, you know, it makes sense.
We've got people making charts off of this information, like the Podsate Music was a
PMC top 10, the Podsate Music Countdown, well, all kinds of stuff like that.
So March 22nd, the ideas were going to bum rush the iTunes charts, which, of course,
these download charts these days now make a difference in overall perception of the success
of music.
And we truly believe that there is enough audience.
There are enough podcasters and associated audience who will click on a link spend 99 cents
on March 22nd to buy one single track to get that track moved up into the top of the
iTunes download and for pay download chart.
So the song that's chosen is Black Lab, mine again, and the way it's going to work.
If you go to bum rush, the charts dot blog spot, actually you can go to bum rush the charts
dot com, the way it will work is if you participate.
And as a listener, you can also participate.
Obviously, the whole idea is to get the network effect kicking in so that, you know, if you
don't have to have a podcast to put this affiliate link up on your page, the affiliate
link, by the way, is proceeds to go directly to education and the band has also put up
half of their take for the ghost stores education as well.
You know, we actually, we have a promo.
How professional is that?
We're almost like the big boys aren't we?
On March 22nd, you can make history, yes, you.
On March 22nd, you and your fellow podcast listeners will be working together to bum rush
the charts.
What's that?
On March 22nd, we're all going to buy a song from the iTunes music store from a
pot-safe musician, mine again by Black Lab, to put a pot-safe musician at the top of the iTunes
charts.
But there's more than just that.
We'll all be buying through an affiliate program to raise money for college scholarships,
and the band has agreed to donate 50% of their earnings to the scholarship fund to help
needy families make college affordable.
Make history, show the world that you are in charge of media, not corporate radio and record
labels.
bum rush the charts on March 22nd, learn more about how to bum rush at www.bum rushthecharts.com
Chris Pan from the financial uh, financial aid podcast.
Great promo, Chris.
Now, people are coming up with all kinds of ideas to make this play even better.
I really like this because of course, you know, we're going to do everything we can
to bribe the audience, listen to the difference there.
Record companies bribe radio stations to spam the audience and podcasters bribe the audience
to spam the mainstream record companies on their own chart.
Maybe we just don't have enough to do during the day.
But there's more that you can actually win something now.
And this is something that is going to be set up through the daily source code that just
came in today.
I kind of like the idea.
Anything that'll get us more traction on bum rush the charts.
I'm a fan.
I'll check out this concept.
We say podcasting doesn't matter who are they that the record industry, that the radio
industry, maybe they're right, maybe we don't matter.
But maybe we do on March 22nd 2007, we all have a assignment, sure.
We have things to do, sure we have places to go, but there's one thing that we all
have to do.
Go over to iTunes and buy the track from Black Lab and toddler's might again.
The cost is 99 cents, but this one day, don't go buy the Frappuccino, it's been 99 cents
and it could be a price.
And yes, I'm going to put my money where my mouth is.
For the receipt you receive from iTunes to Adam at curry.com and then the subject line
to it, I made a difference.
One entry per person please, you know, March 30th 2007, Adam will draw off from these names.
And the winner will receive a iTunes gift certificate worth $100 courtesy of PotShowReadyow.com.
So don't forget, in March 22nd, it's your turn to make a difference.
So you can win 100 bucks and it immediately incentivizes me to get my, I got the Google
apps premiere edition for curry.com.
So I'm slowly implementing everything I don't want to mess up anyone's email, who is also
on curry.com.
So that'll be working by then.
Won't it now?
Yes.
I'm sure we'll.
My older geeky go talk in there.
I'm going to make it happen.
Folks, listening to serious satellite stars, 102, we've got a great line of 40 this evening.
Coming up after the break, I think it's a number one with a bullet with Mark Hirsch
Motor Nemkov.
In fact, I know it is.
Oh, let me see, yesterday kind of made a joke out of a good old Paul there as I was talking
about voiceover IP systems and he called in and he's a consultant and just implemented
a voice system.
I was amazed at how crappy the quality of his call was and well, he called back, of course.
Adam, it's Paul again from Kirk and Washington.
You mentioned, I moved voiceover IP comment and I wanted to make a correction for you.
I was actually talking to you on my singular Sony Ericsson cell phone in traffic with
my job owned DSP processor headsets and I guess the DSP when it's recording on voice
now like you have doesn't, doesn't, doesn't, doesn't, it has some degradation apparently.
Anyway, my point was, this is a packet eight might be a voice solution that you should
look at that, but I used words a lot better than the recording and we're going to remember
not to use my DSP headset when I'm leaving voice now because apparently the volume levels
quite low.
So anyway, that was a point of my voice now and thanks for doing what you do and folder.
Yeah, all right, man.
Okay.
Sounded much better.
You know, whenever someone, I mean, all this digital recording stuff, everything is
a digital recording.
So of course, a cell phone call these days is a digital call.
It comes in and I wonder when it comes into the voice mail bank, I guess there's no audio,
there is no actual analog signal passed off.
So then it gets transcoded into the voice mail system, which uses the GSM protocol, which
is very, very low, low bandwidth, I then have to, or low bandwidth, low bit rate, I then
have to convert that to AIFF and then from AIFF to MP3 and before you know it, well,
I'd have to say this thing sound like total shit.
Regardless, please give us a call.
Here's the UK number for you.
For those of you in the United States, or if you're using any version of a tip protocol-based
voice system, this will be a free call for you.
Now, then again, it may not be a free call, but virtually a free call for you.
Hi, Adam Jack from GetJackPodcast.com, you know, you've made a mistake on today, it's Wednesday,
March 7th, but the podcast says that it's March 8th, which would be tomorrow, a date
I'm intimately aware of, because not only is it the day that Jersey Todd scheduled his
next child to be born, and isn't it odd that one can schedule these things?
They have busy lives, best do it on Thursday and have the weekend.
Anyway, it's also my birthday tomorrow, March 8th, so I think what you should do is send
Jersey Todd a Nokia N800 Internet tablet, so you can do videos of the new child and send
him up to Pod Show and for all to see, and go ahead and send me one to you, because it's
my birthday.
Okay.
GetJackPodcast.com.
You know, and I think Jersey Todd would, I had a quick email exchange with Jersey Todd.
The day indeed, in fact, he sent me a note about an hour ago, and he said that the
sea section was about to commence in 20 minutes, so by now we probably have a Jersey
Toddlet wandering around, but you'd be, I think you'd both be very disappointed if you
wanted to use the N800, the N800's built-in camera to take pictures of anything other
than, you know, like, for a web, you know, like a web conference thing or just a reference
photo.
That's the, I have to say, that's kind of a bummer, it's like a VGA quality camera, it's
not even, I don't even think it's a megapixel, it's really a shame because, you know, the
sound is great on the N800, it does some awesome things because it's a full powered
computer, basically, running a full operating system, but the, but the camera is crap,
so you'd probably do better with the, with a different camera, but, you know, just listening
to that kind of, you know, makes me think, like, you guys think, I'm actually I'm looking
for a song here, it reminded me of a song, let me see, the hell, I think my bandwidth
is host again, crap, oh, I hate it when this happens, let me see, let me try the artist.
Uh, I'm not going to tell you what it is as I'm typing it in because I would give it away.
Well, this may not work, hold on, stop, man, Windows media player sometimes is such an
incredible piece of shit, it, it will freeze up, you know, particularly if you're logged
into Napster, it's like it's waiting for data from Napster and it just sits there and
it freaks out and, and it won't move and then you hit the stop button on the search and
fuck it, it's not going to work, okay, maybe I'll look at my first gen iPods, see if I can find
it.
You remember these guys played them quite a bit about a year ago, they're back with a
brand new song, they are from Sweden, so, you know, they're going to look out for
those Swedes, remember New Leaf, Mr. New one is titled Other Side.
You can't do those, no student fire, but your food, I do let you go, don't kill me inside
I need so bad, they tattoos and I aren't as bad, you don't see enough so fast and you fall away
to be bad, you got bad to me for sure, but I'm going to buy it, let's make up for this
gen iPods, see if I can find it, let's make up for this gen iPods, see if I can find it, let's make up for this
gen iPods, see if I can find it, let's make up for this gen iPods, see if I can find it, let's make up for this gen
iPods, see if I can find it, let's make up for this gen iPods, see if I can find it, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up
for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for this gen iPods, let's make up for
I'm the other side
The cry on me is too high
To keep me on the side
With a broken glass I let it to live
Now it's all too late
You got back to me for sure
But I don't want it
Let's make up for this good night on the other side
Life is yours
It has only begun
You got back to me for sure
But I don't want it
I'm the other side
Well, it's definitely something very different from their previous track
I love so much which was a magic carpet
Yeah, that's the guy from Sweden, New Leaf
The other side on DSC559
And it, thank you
Alright, I've got one
What's playing on
Adam's first gen I bought
Let's take a look
It was a song that I was reminded by this song
By people think that I'm the guy that hands out
The Nokia devices in the Pottersphere
Some would also call me The Candy Man perhaps
Candy Man perhaps
Candy Man
Alright, everybody
Get around the Candy Man here
What kind of candy you want?
The sweet chocolate
Chocolate's more the candy
Come drops, anything you want
You come to the right man
Because I'm the Candy Man
One, two, three
Who can take a sunrise
We put it with you
Cover it with chocolate and a miracle
To the Candy Man
Candy Man
Who the Candy Man can
Candy Man can
Because he mixes it with love
And makes the world taste good
It's the wildest one
Who can take a rainbow
Come on man
Does it put you in a happy mood when you hear that
It's probably also going from one of my favorite movies of all time
Willy Wonka's chocolate factory
It's Sammy Davis Jr. in the Candy Man
What's playing on
Who's first
Can I find
A Jeff, you kill me man
Alright everybody, that's it for the Daily Stories Code for today
Tomorrow we'll be celebrating Fubar Friday in style
And hopefully we'll have some news from Jersey Todd
I'm the New Jersey toddler walking around
Which should have been born by today
And I believe Brian from audio attitudes is going to
Slide into the place of a visual musicologist of the Cha Cha
Adam at potcho.com
And DailySourceCode.com
Was where you can find out everything about this show
I will talk to you guys tomorrow
Take care
What's playing on
Adam's first Jedi Bond
Another potcho potcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily by the
Sharpest minds in content delivery
Potcho and Lionlight