Hey, it's Tony Costa telling you to check out this christmaspodcast.com.
It's the official podcast for the new Sony film.
This Christmas starring Chris Brown for Gina King, Columbus Short,
and an all-star cast.
The site includes a special holiday podcast from yours truly,
exclusive interviews from the stars in the film,
and a special red carpet coverage from the premiere.
You can exchange gifts, but you can't exchange family.
This Christmas is truly the next holiday classic.
See it in theaters on November 21st,
and please check us out at this christmaspodcast.com.
I like to think I'm flying into this christmaspodcast.com, it's Adam Curry.
In my mind, I'll rehearse these lines a thousand times.
I guess that I've made that way, I hope you understand.
I'll try to make a scene of reason why we just can't go on like this,
watching two of us all apart.
Now the rain is falling, and she's falling apart.
She's the last forever,
she's the last forever,
she's the last forever, she's the last forever.
She's the last forever, she's the last forever.
She's the last forever, she's the last forever,
she's the last forever, she's the last forever.
I can look her in the eyes,
can't hide, she looks like she's lost a lot,
by her demons looking alone,
as I'm looking at her way.
It's a show on one, a love today.
She's the last forever, she's the last forever,
she's the last forever,
she's the last forever, she's the last forever,
I'm really not sure how I, on Mr. Span's record came out, but a year ago, from the UK, PG Devon and 3D.
Tears don't last forever.
If I'm looking at their page here on the Pod State Music Network, influences, yeah,
no kidding, the Beatles, Green Day, Led Zeppelin, Otis Redding, Sam Cook.
Fanta, one of these guys is still around, no new tracks in November 29th of 2006, great
music to kick off at Tuesday on your daily source code, episode number 690.
Well, actually, turns out I somehow skipped two episodes.
Someone pointed this out to me, yes, the only one person emailed me about it.
I posted show number 689 yesterday and indeed, looking back on Friday, it was show 686.
So 8687 and 689 are MIA, which means I think I'm just going to continue the count from
690 and then somewhere we'll do two secret episodes.
I don't want to mess up people who have a perfect collection, then you have stuff coming
out in the wrong order.
So, sorry about that.
Ha, must smoke less crack.
Hey, another a dreary day here in the UK, it's gray outside, it's wet and, of course, I'm
going to go into the city, battle the traffic, battle the new expanded congestion zone,
which has screwed everything up and let all kinds of people from Chelsea into the city
for almost zero cost.
Ah, so it goes.
Yeah, we've done some cool shit.
You know, we launched a new show on Monday here in the UK, it's called Spirit Messenger
with Gordon Smith.
Gordon Smith is a guy who's been getting a lot of attention here in the UK in the past
couple weeks, and maybe even months, he's a psychic, or as we call him a spirit messenger.
He's a medium quite well known, used to be known as the psychic barber in the UK.
I think he's trying to change that image.
I stumbled across him through super agent Keith Bishop several months ago, and we
kept talking about, you know, we really got to do a show and then finally we just sat down
and we just did a show and his great spirit messenger dot podshow dot com.
This guy is pretty unbelievable and he does it in in under 10 minutes, at least that's
what's that's the show that we're making with him.
I don't see why you have to have a spirit show that's longer than 10 minutes.
Get to the point, help these people.
He's actually, he doesn't do a private reading and readings anymore, or even public readings
for that matter.
He's written several books and he's now in the field of grief counseling.
So the entire point of the show is there are people who have lost their loved ones and
they missed them dearly and he helps get in touch with them and counsels them as a medium
he passes on the messages from the spirit world.
It's funny because we've got a couple of people at the office who just don't believe
in this.
They're working on the show and they're at, you know, really trying to say, you know,
this is just not real and even the biggest critics are now like, well, shit looks
pretty damn real.
Sounds pretty good.
Ah, let's see, trolling the voicemail line.
You know, I haven't played the voicemail lines in quite a such a time.
Actually, it turned out that there were more people calling in on the UK voicemail number
today than the US number.
So I'm going to give you a shot at both for a second.
Here's one for the Yankee Doodles.
Oh, what the hell was that?
Let's try that again.
Now, of course, here's the first message that came through.
All right, I'll write a random fuck you.
Adam Curry.
Stop talking about that.
I'm not.
All right.
And I'm going to buy it.
I just bought the N95 and now I have to buy this, you like, to thank you, have a nice day
and fuck you.
I don't buy it yet, man.
I haven't received it.
I haven't been able to do a full test yet, so I don't know if it's really going to rock
that hard.
Actually, I do.
I know it's going to be awesome.
I've been waiting for this one.
This is the device I've been waiting for.
Finally, I think all the pieces are coming together.
I've come together and it's a great intermediary between my cell phone and my computer.
Yeah, I got a page at curry.com.
Then keep your eye on a daily source code.com for a great deal on the N810.
But first, let's wait until I get my device.
And because if it sucks, if I don't like it, I'm not going to be
hawking it to you.
Trust me, no matter what anyone else does.
But I have a feeling I'm going to like it very much.
I've been spending even more time with my N800 recently.
Last night, I think the, I wonder how long the battery, how many
rechargees you can get on one of these batteries.
They use a standard cell phone battery so that it really lasts a long time
depending on what you're doing.
But I don't know if I just don't know how long the last.
I wonder how long have I had the N800 a year or so?
I should just look that up.
Yeah, I think it's been almost a year.
And let me see, it's still holding in charge.
I'll check today.
I'm going to load it full up today.
And then hopefully tomorrow, if I can eat a show out tomorrow,
let you know how many hours it lasted.
But it does do a pretty good job, which is one of the big, big advantages of this over
any other portable device.
That was really the bummer with the iPhone.
It's combined with the web surfing I do, which I do a lot of, you know,
just checking me email and looking at other things, Google reader.
I use a lot, I use the phone a lot.
And a seven hour day is just not enough.
I mean, maybe enough for people in Cupertino, but it's not enough for me.
Ah, let's check in with our European Congress.
Come on, come on, strip.
Come on, strip.
Fancy a carry in a carry.
Mr. Adam carry.
Hiya, here is CSB, your EU correspondent.
So England gets closer to Europe.
Last week on Wednesday, Europe start trains from England to France.
And to Belgium are leaving, not from the shameful water load station.
You know, French is where I'm meeting at Waterloo.
But from Renewed, Saint-Pavent-Cath station.
Yeah, what's up with that?
Wait a minute, I thought it came in the Waterloo station, or at least on the Euro rail side,
the Euro Star side of the Waterloo station, which is quite nice compared to Waterloo
station itself, which is my station.
I thought they were going in there.
Now, travel to England, from England to Europe, short ends by 20 minutes.
And after 2012, it will be even possible to go from England to Germany, from which
original Anglo-Saxons came from anyway.
So happy on the road to you, Adam.
You.
Ha ha.
Happy Emery to you, to my friend.
Although the pound has lost a little bit against the Euro on the dollar recently, which
is in a way kind of nice.
I still have lots of Euro, so that works for me.
Forget getting dollars.
That's just the sad state of affairs.
Yeah, this high-speed train stuff is pretty cool.
And I think it's a lot more convenient than the airports these day.
Well, of course, you know, with the Delta Shira, with my own craft, it's the easiest of
all.
But yeah, it seems like, in fact, the girls were talking to me about going to Disneyland
Paris just before the Christmas holiday, which I think is a great idea.
I do, I am a sucker for Disneyland, I have to say, and you particularly when everything's
just right.
So that's what they do with Disney.
Everything's just kind of right.
It's the way you expect it to be.
And it's only like two hours or something like that by train, and so it's going to go
to Germany as well.
This is cool.
This is very cool.
Right now, I would say flying out of Heathrow or Gattwick is just not worth it.
You know, it's, yeah, I mean, sure, if you have to go to Finland, then you can't get
there by train easily, just yet.
Of course, the French and the Germans are striking.
So the German real workers of striking, I don't know if that affects the Euro star.
And the French, if it's Tuesday, of course, they're striking.
They always strike on Tuesday.
So they can get the maximum benefit of having the rest of the week off or almost as good
as the rest of the week off.
Speaking of strikes, New Story came out yesterday that the CBS news writers are now
having now approved a strike, which they would do to support the writers' guild of America
strike, which is going on there.
It's still going on in what it's third week now in California.
Let me see, I got the, it's a market watch story.
Let me see what I've got here.
Yeah.
So here it comes.
CBS news writers voted to Spurn, CBS has contract offer in November of last year since
then the network has refused to put forth any new proposals.
It looks like they're going to go on strike.
And then, of course, there's the non-scripted drama, a better known as reality writers.
They aren't in the guild.
There is no guild for that.
So expect to see a lot more reality shows in the coming few weeks, because I don't believe
they're going to work this out.
In fact, I think it's very difficult to work out this writer's strike because, well, quite
honestly, it's very complicated to make money online with video.
No one's really making any, we're making money.
It's costing a lot still to do it, but look at YouTube, I don't even see any ads.
Let alone a few.
Just look at many other sites out there.
The no one is really making a lot of money.
And of course, if there's not a lot of money to be made, then there's no profit to be
divvyed out.
And of course, that's not what the writers are going for.
The writers are going for a piece of the gross proceeds, which is just, it's Hollywood.
It's the movie business.
You're never going to be able to figure that out.
I feel really bad for him.
I don't know.
I still like Jack Myers.
If you haven't ever seen Jack Myers column, he's a media analyst.
Jack Myers.com.
And his suggestion was that the advertiser should create a pool of money that should
be divvy out to the writers.
So any money that is spent on interactive advertising, instead of getting it from the
recipient of that money, which is the studios and the producers, he's suggesting, why not
do it at the source and just have, whatever the budgets are, whatever budgets any of these
agencies, who, of course, collect 15% agency commission over any media buy they do.
So it would technically come out of their pocket and not out of the advertisers, that
1% should go to this pool and that should be divvyed up amongst the writers.
But of course, there's a lot of other unions that will pop up, who also work on these and
probably don't get residuals either.
So tough.
I think that's called a conundrum.
I got this awesome email from, who do I get that from?
This is, man, this is almost something I want to hear this.
Of course, Alexander, he sent me a link and I'm going to post this in the show notes
of dailysourcecode.com of private contractors that have US government contracts in Iraq
and Afghanistan between 2004 and 2006.
This is essentially where our tax dollars are going to fight to terror in those regions.
And what's interesting is, and, you know, this, he has links to public integrity.org.
And at the top of the list, there's 20 billion, actually $20.4 billion going to unidentified
foreign entities.
So that's just $20 billion that is not identifiable as to what, what our money was spent
on.
Number two is KBR with $16 billion in two years time.
Of course, KBR formerly known as Kellogg Brown and Ruit, a fine halibut in subsidiary.
Then it's Dine Corp International through Veritas Capital with $1 billion, boy, it's a big
drop.
Washington Group International Inc.
Another billion.
And then IAP Worldwide Services Inc, a division of service service, I guess, service capital
management.
This is, let me just see if there's any recognizable names, Blackwater USA, 485 million
Lockheed Martin, that mall makes sense, that's all.
What I'm not seeing, oh, Tyco International, Boeing Corp, Zapata Engineering, these are all
pretty new well-known companies.
I'm looking for, because when I was in Bosra in 2004, was that 2003 at the Air Base,
which, of course, has been, has been a lot of crap going on in Bosra in the past year.
It was a Burger King and was it a Burger King in a Pizza Hut or Macdonald?
No, I think it was a Burger King in a Pizza Hut.
So I'm wondering if they show up here, wouldn't that be funny?
This is only the top 100 with the number 100 company being ODB construction company,
receiving 8 million, oh, only a poultry, 8 million, oh, there's a fine Dutch company
there.
SHV Holdings and V, let's find out what they do.
Well, second, I'm going to go to this public integrity.org website, let's see, Defense Logistics
Agency, Contract SP0600411D, full and open competition after exclusion of sources.
They provide converters of the electrical non-rotating kind for $17 million, nice, nice job.
If you can get it, let's get into the spirit, shall we, since our government is giving
away all of our money, why don't we think about giving away some money in the form of
presence and think of the horror they see as in?
Bull hay, everyone, this is Ed Roberts from the Looking Out the Window Music podcast.
It's that time of the year, time to ring in the Christmas season, time to ring in another
season of Pods' Safe Christmas.
Every day between Thanksgiving and Christmas will roll out three or four great Pods' Safe Christmas
tracks to get you into the Christmas season.
Visit PodsafeChristmas.com and look forward to having you join me here in this Christmas
May be full God, you should know that you are alone, because you're there and you're
shining, but like a bigger, but there's another storm, so don't worry, pick up, say that
we'll find you wherever you are, say that we'll find you tonight.
If you're listening for, bring dear and say bells as it's in golden tap on the ground,
you're awake, piled in blankets with your cousin, sapphgram on, send you home, don't
be present for you, because you're there and you're shining, but like a bigger, right
is another storm, so don't worry, pick up, say that we'll find you wherever you are, say
that we'll find you tonight.
Visit PodsafeChristmas.com to bring dear and say bells as it's in golden tap on the ground,
you'll never be lost if you truly believe in your heart, when you're there and you're
shining, right like a bigger, right is another storm, so don't worry, pick up, say that
we'll find you wherever you are, say that we'll find you tonight, yep, it is time to
be here again, my friends, when we all gather around the fire, hope to find your sweetheart
of the mistletoe, it's Christmas, and we're wishing you a podsafe for you.
Mindy Smith, Santa will find you, I guess.
This is a crazy story that came across my spectrum this morning, there's now a drug that
lengthens eyelashes, this of course is what Revlon and others have been claiming for years
to be able to do with the pure mascara, which of course is horseshorshit and they even got
in trouble for using stick-on lashes, false eyelashes and the commercials, which of course
is something the lady Patricia has been calling out for years and years, but now there's
this glaucoma drug called Lumagon, Lumagon, I guess, and turns out that if you apply
this to your eyelashes, it actually makes your eyelashes grow longer.
So BIMA TOPROST is the active ingredient in Lumagon and others like it is a commonly
found in glaucoma drugs, it looks like mascara tube has a brush or tip for applying the product
along the base of the lashes and typically sells for $14260 in spas and doctors' offices.
So of course this is going to be a big news story because it's irrelevant, so be on the
lookout for it and it'll be top of the news everyone's going to be talking about it.
Even though we're spending billions on commercial companies fighting a non-existent
and well not a non-existent, an invisible enemy, a poorly defined enemy, namely terror.
Which is everywhere, it's on the roller coasters.
I'm not in college today, that's all I can say.
Hey Adam, you're Germany.
Hey you?
Hope all as well.
Yes.
It's been here to be 689 chilling out, nice couple herbal tea, if you know what I mean, and really enjoying
it.
I read this awesome book over the weekend.
You probably know when it's called Mr. Nice.
No, yeah.
It's written by Howard Knox and this guy's something else man.
I think he was one of the biggest smugglers of Mario Wana while back a couple years ago.
And he wrote this book in which he describes exactly how he smuggled and what he did to boost
the government and to get everything across the borders.
Great book.
I really enjoyed reading it.
I think he's also definitely a red pill guy.
I go a little bit, but it seems that he's pretty open to doing some to do an interview.
So you might even get him on the other day in the source.
That would be really nice.
See you, bye.
Yeah, interesting suggestion.
And I'm always looking for someone interesting to talk to on the Charlie.
I read the book, Mr. Nice, about Howard Marx, which was actually should have been my first clue
that my, one of my old business partners in Holland who later fled the country.
As it turned out, the name I'd known him under for eight years and his name known in business on large contracts was not his real name.
I fled to Cambodia of all places.
It turned out, I mean, it's a long, as a really stupid story.
Not a very happy ending to that one.
But he recommended I read this book.
And of course, Howard Marx, famous for smuggling huge quantities of mainly marijuana.
And later, ecstasy, I believe, as that started to gain popularity towards the end of his quote,
career.
They would smuggle it in cases for amplifiers with bands traveling around Europe.
And quite interesting, big companies that are behind all this.
You know, hundreds of millions of euros in this trade.
And yeah, it's like, it's an interesting book.
It's maybe a bit of a glorification of the drug smuggling trade.
Yeah, he's a red pill, but I don't know.
I just don't find the story that interesting.
But it is a good read for sure.
If you want to know more about smuggling drugs,
I can't miss their nice.
Ah, you know what?
I'll put a link in the show notes to the book at Amazon.com.
So you can buy that.
I also grew a year older over the weekend.
Or it felt like 10 years older.
My daughter started her first driving lesson ever.
Oh, yeah, boy.
Of course, they don't have drivers at here in Europe or in the UK.
So it's not quite like the States where, you know, 15 or 16.
They're already taken drivers at.
And it's kind of a part of the schooling process.
And here it's a separate deal.
She had a great lesson, though.
She said she's really well.
She used to drive the tractor when she was a 10 or 11.
10, 11, 12.
No, when she was more like, yeah, 12, 12, 13.
When we had the castle, we had a little mini tractor, which is cool.
And she was good.
She could do the clutch and shift and all that.
So, you know, she's got a lot of that baked in.
But still, just kind of makes you feel like, oh, you know, crab.
Get old.
Hey, Adam.
Alan, person's also here.
Okay.
Now it's just on my way home.
Listen to my agenda.
Got to say, together, PG6.
You've got to be drinking.
You'll succeed.
It's got to be the best thing we could get in the UK.
Anyway, try it out.
Well, follow the rectal.
Okay.
Yep.
Cheers.
Well, let's end reference to the conversation.
I have with John C. Dvorak on no agenda.
Talking about what's the real.
I didn't know that he was a big tea guy.
He's just a, anything you can put in your mouth.
He's into.
Yes, that too.
I'm sure.
The wine food, tea coffees.
He loves it all.
And I was saying that, you know, we typically drink PG tips.
But this Yorkshire stuff.
Okay.
I'll try that out.
I presume I can get that at Sainsbury's, which is where we shop.
All right.
Well, you know what?
I'm just going to really slow.
You know, have you ever had those moments where you just like to stop the world?
I think these moments are important, by the way, because we go so fast.
We're whirling around through the universe.
But hundreds of thousands of miles an hour, we're sending our bits, you know,
in packet form across the, the interwebs on an hourly minute, second basis.
Sometimes you're just going to slow everything down and just say,
I need to stop, stop the world, slow down, relax, and listen to a piece of music
from the soundtrack to my life.
Thank you.