Hey, home fries, it's CC Chapman from accident hash, encouraging you to check out
BODOD.tv slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there, and you can only find it at BODOD.tv.
Boy, I learned my lesson.
Don't stick the red pill in the blue pill, in the same pocket.
Especially on the day when it's 100 degrees out, you end up with one purple glob.
And if you take it, it feels like you're on the DSC 648.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I like to think I am flying into the future.
Are you my rally show? Are you the answer to my question? I have always been my time now
Cause if I feel this feeling, but you call out of your footsteps
I call out of my rally show, will you be my rally? Cause I can't see you suddenly
I can't feel crying more, I can't see you suddenly more
Without your mind, you're by my side, I feel fine
Are you my rally show? Are you the answer to my question?
Are you the answer to my question? Are you the answer to my question?
Are you the answer to my question?