This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Time to play where in the world is Adam Curry.
He was in Spain. He was in the UK.
Two days later, he shows up in San Francisco.
He's everywhere. He's like a fugitive. Where is he going? What's he running from? Huh?
Check it out on the DSC. 587.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain.
He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He
was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He was in which there was beer and coffee. He was in Spain. He was in Spain. He is in Spain. And he was in Spain. He is in Spain. He appeared in Spain.
Okay guys, grab your gal and hit the floor because here's that beat you in the way
into swing too.
Along with that beat with the beautiful eyes, one very beautiful like a trinketide,
I just have a baby on swing just with me.
Hope it helps you baby, wanna wing it with me.
I don't have a lot of money, I can do it.
Don't give me what you want, I'll be on my move.
In the mood.
It didn't make my life play a little more now.
And it was my family and I got a job but you...
Dong, dong, dong, dong.
Bleach your mom and cook up
We're all
We're all done
Hey, remember I told you the lady Patricia was working on some special project, there you have it.
The Star Sisters strike back. Better known as the Nilfs. Oh man, if you're into that dancing
with the star stuff, well, this is the kind of music those people love. I gotta say, I kind
of like it myself. It's awesome. I love the military cadence at the beginning there. Now it's
not pod safe yet. However, check this out. And this was something the lady P worked on quite
a bit with her record company or the record company she's been with for 20 years or something
like that. They're going to put it up on the pod set music network. They have a publishing company,
so they have all the rights, all the ASCAP, BMI, everything's covered. I did say to the to the
the record company and said, just send me that in writing. Okay. And then I'll be happy to help you
get that up on the pod set music network. Should be up sometime this week. And she will be performing
that live on dancing with the stars in the Netherlands on Sunday, May 6th. And she's, you know,
I love my wife man. She's nuts. She's really, she's off the race with this one. She will have
video. I'm sure we're going to put it up on pod show when a video of the show. It's going to be a
lot of fun. I've actually been working on getting 30 of the royal Dutch marines onto the show.
And it's just, it's a creative project. And she's completely, completely embedded into this.
And it's cool. I like it. This was obviously a remix of a song that she had a number one hit with.
And I think in 1981 or 1982, they went through so much trouble trying to find the original master
that had been some flooding in one of the studios. And it's like, you know, this is all magnetic
tape days, right? These are big 24 track magnetic tapes. And it's been quite a project.
Anyway, coming to you from Northern California right here overlooking the bay. It is the Curry
condo. This is the daily source code episode 587. Thank you so much for being along for the ride.
I got in this afternoon. Boy, what an interesting trip. First of all, you know, we got back
late. I should say early Sunday morning, really Saturday night. And you're not going to believe
what happened to us. Or to me, really, over the course of two days. So we arrive at like
130 in the morning. And of course, you know, our temporary visas are being turned into permanent
visas. And so I have all this paperwork I have to show from the home office. And it's, you know,
big pain in the ass. So we're like 10 minutes, maybe 15 minutes at immigration. And okay,
so when they stamp everything they'll let us through. And just about everyone's already got
there, their suitcase and they're all gone. And Andy, of course, who would win with us on vacation,
Christina's bow, her boyfriend, which I got to tell you a story about in a second.
You know, he says, oh, okay, there's only a couple left. And here's yours. And he, you know,
I have a really beautiful, to me roller bag, a big one. And I, and I cost a lot of money. And I
said, you know, it's like $700 for a suitcase. But I travel so much. It really at the end of the day
is well worth it because, you know, basically it hangs together. And there's also not a lot of them.
And it's just, it's, it's a, it's a really good travel case. And it's convenient, you know,
it's got a pop-up handle on wheels and the whole thing. And, you know, it might's pretty distinctive.
It's a, it's a standard, it's a standard bag. It's got the, you know, the leather tag on it. And then there's
a gold virgin flyer club card or whatever. And so he brings this over and I'm like, wow,
there's a lock on it. My lock was cut off by the TSA. I mean, how can the lock did they put a new lock on it?
Then of course, I realized that the gold card on the, on the suitcase is not a virgin gold card,
but a British airways gold card. So now it's like 145. It's like two in the morning and like,
oh my God, someone picked up my suitcase. And there's a still here. It's the middle of the night
word, Gatwick Airport, North Terminal. I was like, f**k, f**k, f**k, f**k. I mean, what are the chances,
right, of both the same bags coming in from Tenerife, exact same configuration, the only difference
being a lock. And of course, mine is heavier than all shit. But I guess someone, you know,
this guy's suitcase was pretty heavy too. So anyway, so I take this bag off. I roll over,
there is a baggage services, there's someone there. And right at that very moment, thank
goodness, the guy was in the parking lot. And he realized that that he had the wrong suitcase.
So he found someone on the other side of customs and they communicated with the baggage. And
he was really nice guy. You know, we were both laying out. So we went through, by the way, it's a
great way to smuggle shit. Let me tell you, because when that happens, no one checks you. Like,
oh yeah, let's go find the guy. They forget to look at your suitcase. Nothing I had any
contraband with me, of course. And so the guy was on the other side, you know, really nice thing
was a Scottish. And, you know, we laughed about it for a few minutes and shook hands. And so we took off.
Okay. So just keep that part of the story in mind. Let me just cycle back for a second.
The headphone earlobe for those of you who had not been following along.
Fuck you, already knew that didn't you. I'm so confused with the time you
already talked about that on yesterday's show. Here, oh, he's what I want to say about Andy.
So Christina and Andy, they share their own suite right next door to ours. They're very grown-up kids.
I have to say, you know, that's almost 17. He's 17. So what are you going to do, right?
And everything was peachy keen until he decided to dunk her in the pool.
And I think she had just blow dried her hair or some shit like that. And she, she threw all
his shit in the pool. I'm talking about his bag. He's close. I like, oh, yeah. That's my daughter. I love it.
Okay. So, um, spend a little bit of time at home on Sunday. Of course,
had to, you know, go to the doctor, have the headphone earlobe checked out.
And the Monday morning, it picked up because coming to San Francisco. And, you know, Virgin,
they sent the car for me. So I'm, uh, off to the airport, you know, struggling to be on time as usual.
And it's a madhouse in the Virgin lounge. I mean, it's like there's a, there's a band playing,
there's a million people. I'd never seen anything like it. What the hell is going on?
Well, it's our inaugural flight to Chicago. And, uh, so this is all press. And, uh, it was great.
You know, I was talking to some folks from, uh, Sky News, from Bloomberg.
Um, oh, there's this guy, uh, what's his name? Uh, he does the business travel report on CNN, Richard.
He's, he's a total whack job. If you've ever seen that show, then you, you know, exactly
I'm talking about. Anyway, you know, I went up to him and I said, hey, man, I really love your show.
I got your fucking wacky. You know, come on over to the dark side. He actually seemed pretty interested.
And I said, when he's in San Francisco, he'd look us up right.
Probably see each other in London before that. And, uh, guess who else was there? Sir Richard.
And his parents. So, uh, I went over and I said, uh, excuse me, Sir Richard. Uh, I'm a, I'm a paying
punter. A punter, by the way, is kind of the kind of, is that like slang, I guess, English slang for, uh,
just a dumb, dumb fuck who pays? I'm paying punter, you know, congratulations. I really love your
airline. Man, he was a, but a nice guy. But it was really weird. He shook my right hand with his left hand.
I wasn't too sure at all that was about. Okay. Anyway. So, um, so it was, it was just a mad house in the,
in the virgin clubhouse. Uh, then they got on the plane, you know, by the way, delayed for an hour.
I don't know what that was all about. I came in late from New York as getting out of New York
apparently was a nightmare. So, uh, we left late, um, you know, typical flight. What I watch, um,
the pursuit of happiness, the wheel Smith movie. That was pretty cool. Like that. I've been reading
another book, uh, the third secret, which is, uh, kind of like, uh, the Vinci code type book
and arrive at San Francisco and, uh, everything's fine. You know, I go through, uh, immigration.
I'm there, uh, waiting for my bag and, uh, all the bags go by and, uh, my bag's not there. I do notice,
of course, another two me bag, um, just like mine, but it has a, um, it had a, uh, like a ribbon
tied around the handle. So, like, okay, well, that's not mine. I didn't tie ribbon around it.
And I'm waiting, I'm waiting, then everyone gets their bags. And then, of course, there's like three
bags left. One of them, which is the fucking two me bag with a ribbon wrapped around it. And
exactly, how is it possible that would happen to me twice in as many days? So, I look at the tag
and there's like Amy Frederickson or something and there's a number and I call the number.
Hello, it's Amy. I said, Amy, it's Adam. Do you have all your bags? Yeah. I said, well,
there's one of your bags here and it's a two me bag. Do you have your two me bag? Yeah. Well,
I think that's my two me bag. Didn't you notice? It was like 8 million pounds and didn't have a ribbon
on it. She was already 15 minutes away from the airport. So, she had to turn around and come back to
said, uh, I'm in a BMW X5. So, I'm standing out there by the corner. I got, I swear to God,
a black Beamer X5 pulls up with five cute chicks in it. Oh, sorry, three cute chicks.
And they're like really apologetic and we swap bags and I went to my condo like good married boy.
And my ears, I have I have stuff like all this cotton, you know, padding and wattage because
it's the headphones man. I got to be really careful. I do not want to have a resurgence of the
headphone earlobe. No, I don't like the in ear experience of like the iPod headphones. I really
need to have phones that cover my entire ear. But this is very, you can hear now that the tape is actually
sticking to the headphones. So, a lot of great responses about the, about the first of the savon
series having come extra blogger on yesterday talking about mobile phone industry and about the
French elections briefly. I have to say pretty much everybody was completely positive about that.
So, talking to another savon today, docks or what we're talking about, the death of web radio,
of web casting because I think it's, I don't know. I mean, podcasting, of course, I think is,
you know, huge growth curve and part of that is because the total, you know, just routing around
the mainstream music business and using creative commons, licensed songs and podcast music, etc.
But docks or else, he knows a shitload about radio. He knows about the streaming stuff and
he's just an interesting guy and he's an a-lister. So, we'll be talking to him later as the
official savon for today's show, one in a series of many. Hello Adam. This is Tokyo Dan and it's
been a while since I've given you any feedback. And I know that you prefer feedback from listeners
rather than podcasts these days, but I have something I have to say in this time it's not positive.
Man, what has happened with the pod safe music network? Absolutely nothing. That's right.
It's still in the same sorry beta state it was a year ago. It's like it has been forgotten about.
A year ago is exciting and more than acceptable because it was new. But a year later it's unforgivable.
I mean, have you ever tried to do a simple search? It's almost fucking useless. For example,
I select R&B as a genre, enter a simple keyword such as Love and 62 result pages are returned,
but not just R&B tunes, but songs and every other genre that's on the PMN are returned.
All right, hold on a second Tokyo Dan because I see you got more than a minute left of this rant.
Okay, let me tell you, um, first of all, search your absolutely right, sucks.
However, you can do a genre sort. So if you just select R&B and don't put in a search term,
it will show you all the R&B tracks. I'm not saying that that's right.
But it definitely is one thing you can do. Now, I don't use the pod safe music network necessarily for searching,
but please rest assured. We're quite aware that it sucks and we're actually implementing
a new search across everything. So the search that works and I think the results are beautiful at
podshow.com and podshow.com slash music. You might want to try that. I comes from the same
database for more about that in a minute. So we are implementing a better search across the board.
Absolutely agree. As search, you could even miss, you could even misspell like one letter
and it won't give you results. So it sucks. But, you know, it's like dude,
there's a lot of stuff going on. Okay. Next try the same thing under advanced search.
Nothing is returned. Not an advanced search is just to make you feel happy like you did some like
it did something. That's never worked for me. Come on. I know there are some R&B songs with the
keyword love. No way, man. It's for artists on the PMN. If they sell their music and have some money
in the PMN, there's no easy to find information about how to get their money out of the PMN.
I know the artists have to contact podshow and request a check. But outside of the USA,
a 20 or 30 dollar US check costs more to cash than it's worth. Jesus Christ, why can't you
implement a system as simple an elegant as PayPal? Oh boy. Oh, how I wish we could implement
something as simple an elegant as PayPal. But doesn't quite work as well if you want to have
a repository where you can go back and download the song you want as many times as you want the
song that you bought believe me. And also, at the time when we implemented what is it that
click and buy, I think there were a whole bunch of other huge benefits which really allowed a
lot more people to be able to buy through the system. Now just just to reiterate, we added this just
as an option. We don't make any money from it. It's 99 cents. I think it's nine cents that goes
to click and buy for processing. We take nothing. The artist gets everything. So for a little bit
of extra hassle, I think, you know, we are basically, you know, the fucking you get what you pay for.
But okay, point taken. I think there are better systems now. But you can understand why that was
on a little bit of a lesser priority than a lot of the other things we've been doing recently.
Man, Adam, by the way, there's no reason to take the Lord's name in vain on this.
Really disappointed with the PMN. I used to really go after artists to get their music on the PMN.
I told him it was a new way to market and sell their music. It looked like the wave of the future.
Well, now the PMN is just a ripple of the past. And I'm too embarrassed to ask artists to put
their music on the pod safe music network. I guess the pod safe music network was just the first
stepping stone you used to create your pod show empire. Now that you got all the content,
you need not to generate a profit from advertisers. You don't really give a shit about the artist
that help you build the base of your empire. You know, that's it, Adam. That's all I have to say.
I'm sorry, but that's the way I feel. All right, Tokyo, Dan. Well, that of course is quite
offensive. What you say at the end there, particularly if you know that in 2006, over 250 million
spins were generated through the pod safe music network. So that's just songs that were played
from the pod safe music network and were reported back. And by the way, that mechanism is very
much alive and kicking. Is the pod safe music network dead? No, absolutely not. Have you seen how
many new songs come on every single day? No, it's growing exponentially. Now, the things that
you'd like to see fix, which you say, you know, to say that we don't care about it or that, you know,
oh, we have enough content. Now, fuck it all. No, have you not noticed, perhaps, that we actually
integrated the pod safe music network into the listener side. So podshow.com slash music. Now,
you can access all those songs, all of the charts, all of the plays, also what shows they
didn't play it on. That's not just template work, okay? I mean, there's logins to consider. You
have to, you know, have a universal log in. There's a whole bunch of crap that came with that.
I took a long time, dude. You know, send me some programmers who will get everything done for your
liquidity split. You know, at the same time, we have to deal with bandwidth. We have to deal with
all kinds of stuff. So, a little bit of leniency would be nice, okay? Just give us a little bit of
a break. I understand that you don't like the way stuff is, and we'll try and make it better. But
that type of comment, I think it's just I'm called for. Hi, Adam. It's Matthew calling from Australia.
I was tempted to call and leave a message after listening to the CSV interview last week. But I'm
glad I waited until this week, and heard your interview with him on the Monday show. I really
preferred that. I thought it was a much more interesting, so to listen to. And I encourage you to keep
up with the interviews. I think it's a great idea for a new format. Keep up with the work. Thanks.
All right, man. And I appreciate you calling it and saying that as I said, most everybody thought
it was a good idea to look at the, you know, rehash the format a little bit.
Um, well, I forgot something really important. Okay. Let me, let me, let me play the, uh,
fuck. Oh, I'm such an idiot. You know why? Because I'm looking at the clock. I'm looking like 22
minutes. I'm like, oh, I've got to stop for the satellite window. And then I thought, oh, no,
there's something I had to tell you guys. I couldn't tell you this. You know, I was in New York,
and we have having meetings with Syrius. We've been going back and forth. And I really couldn't
say anything about what has been going on because I wanted to make sure that everyone who's been
contributing to the pod show on Syrius, uh, that they knew what was going on first. And in fact,
let me, um, we sent an email today to all the shows that are participated. I'll just read it to
you for a bit of them because it really does explain exactly what's going on. And a couple of you
already been sending me questions, although not a lot, but I certainly got five or six questions about this.
Okay, this is, uh, from Richard Brueher, hey, and of course, I'm on a list as well. Hi,
guys, as you know, we've been investing in making significant enhancements and improvements to
the pod show network where the launch of our new colo, that's a co-location of the data barn last
week. We've created the infrastructure necessary to take our partners and programming to the next level.
Over the past months, we've begun to develop opportunities for distribution into new markets and
across exciting platforms and network to the same time. We've been reviewing our current relationships
with a goal of focusing our energies where we'll get the most return our investment for pod show
our producers and our audience. As you are aware, the radio market is undergoing a massive restructuring
with the merger of Sirius and XM, the pending rollout of digital radio and the new licensing of
internet radio. We believe it is an incredibly opportunistic time one that we are uniquely
positioned to take advantage of. Our relationship with Sirius was exclusive and although very
positive for the past two years has become less productive for both parties. At the same time,
new opportunities are coming up that are more core to our progress. We have therefore
terminated our exclusive relationship with Sirius and have begun to review a variety of options.
Now, this, of course, frees up producers, PWF, and Brian Know to help drive the production of
some of these great opportunities and to focus on enhancing the production quality of audio
content on our network. We'll keep you posted on all new developments as they come to fruition.
On behalf of Ron Adam and all of us here, thank you very much for your hard work. You've been
part of the first podcast indication to any other platform for congratulations. You help make
pod show and pod casting history. So I wanted to make sure that I told you that.
It would have been nice to have been able to finish up and then have a good buy show,
but that show this folks. What can I say? Okay, so back to the savant segment.
I think I'm going to be able to get at least one savant in episode. Now, the trick of course is
to get all the shit into the show without making it extremely long with the interview.
And by the way, I want you to know that this format change doesn't mean that I don't
student want naked pictures and shit like that. Okay? So a few free to send those. And of course,
keep your comments coming into the phone numbers. Here's the UK number.
7 5 3 plus 4 4 2 0 7 6 8 1 3 7 5 3. So welcome to the daily source code Doc Serals on the
eve of of your trip to Brussels. So I'm glad you could take it just a few moments because you
sir are a true savant in every sense of the word, particularly when you have to cover a few things.
Well, when it comes to web radio, actually, I think when it comes to radio in general, I mean,
I've been reading your weblog for many years. You always have the inside track. You always have an
interesting take. You come at radio from a little different perspective than I do, I think.
And you've been blogging a lot about the changes in the fees to be paid for music.
Is this the copyright royalty board? Is that who made this decision?
The thing is that the, I was a very long story. I'll try to make it as short as possible,
but it started probably before the DMCA, but the DMCA is a good, a good place to sort of,
that's the digital millennium copyright act. Yeah, the digital millennium copyright act, which was
past I think in October of 1998. And a moment of things left unclear was what, what online,
what, what, what U.S. Broadcast, I should say webcasting stations playing,
or I double-A license music would pay to the organization created by the I double-A called
sound exchange in royalties. And let me just stop here there for one second, Doc. Does that mean
it's the only fee you have to pay for using licensed music, or do you also have to pay
ASCAP BMI on top of that stuff? As I, as I understand it, that, that's, that's still owed,
but that's, it's, it's so not a gating factor that it's not really been part of the conversation,
that the, from the beginning, the R I double-A wanted to charge the, the webcasters, the
maximum possible amount. They wanted to do with online radio with their never-letoo, with broadcast
radio, and which is basically set the term by which the music was used. And so they set really
would amounted to pretty heinous terms. And there's a lot of back and forth at the end of which
they're, through something called a copyright arbitration royalty panel or clerk. Originally,
we still, I think, copyright royalty arbitration cattle, but it makes still that out.
That was crap, yeah. Yeah, and so, and so that, that was, that was settled by Senator
Jesse Helms, that he was, it was partying from the Senate, mostly on behalf of the religious
broadcasters who realized that they would be completely screwed along with everybody else.
Okay, so let me, let me just set this doc because it's really complicated stuff when it comes to
rights and royalties. So essentially, now streaming goes back, I guess you're right to 1998,
and it was okay, you know, since it's not a download, we'll, we'll let you stream our music
because what, you know, stream license music, but you're going to have to pay a special fee for that.
Probably not dissimilar to a subscription fee to a music service in a way, like Napster or,
or, you know, one of these other subscription-based systems. And is that incorrect?
I'm not sure, here's what they wanted from the beginning is to charge on a per listener,
per song basis, and they wanted to impose those reporting requirements on the stations, and they wanted
to, basically they said that they're, you know, we, we think this is, first of all, they characterize it as a
performance, okay, and the most of the performance rights goes back to the fees, I think.
That's, you should be asked, but the point is they wanted the stations, they said basically,
here's what it costs, and you guys have to pay this, and you don't care if the place you had a business
or not. And, and a kind of settlement was reached in in 2002, and everybody kind of thought,
well, that's kind of gone away, at least on a listing side. I, I paid very close attention to this
for a number of years, and they didn't pay any more attention to it, until early this year,
when something called the copyright royalty board, which nobody heard of, suddenly shows up and says,
oh, no, you're, here's a new rate, oh, but a winner, a hell of a higher than you've ever seen before.
And this time, everybody got thrown into it, there was a, there was a quiet, uh, what was called a
card of out for the non-commercial stations that were separate deals with the RWA, that that
includes the NPR stations and other non-commercial stations. They got thrown in there too, so everybody
from clear channel to NPR to all the little Pacific stations and ordinary webcasters, and for that
matter, podcasters who are streaming, it's a different set of rules for streaming. All got thrown into
the same pod and suddenly had the same problem. And, and the problem is basically there is,
for the smaller guys, there's, nobody has yet imagined or put into practice the business model
that will allow them to pay these rates. So essentially, it's a debt sentence for web streamers
in the US. Okay, but, but here's, here's what I don't understand. First of all, who is
creating web streams, I mean, everyone, it kind of gets lumped into web radio, and to me,
radio is something completely different than a live 365 channel that's basically a playlist.
The people who are hurt most are the people who are just streaming together playlists,
and, um, and I guess trying to make money with that somehow, or like, is it like Pandora or
last FM? Are these the guys that are getting getting hit the hardest? Or is it a clear channel
who, uh, will have to turn off their streams, boo-hoo, I'm crying? Right, and the crucials turned
them off before. Um, like, the clear channel is a player in this, but, of course, nobody knows
it's going to be behind the scenes there, but the, um, if it's being streamed, if it's live,
then it's considered a performance, and, and the, the IW wants to, wants you as the, as the,
as the medium of that, whether you're a robotic playlist or a live radio station,
but that's, that's, that's kind of my point is, you know, who's being hurt by these fees?
You know, it's, well, there's a people being hurt by the scenes of most are the,
if it's what I'm concerned or should say, are, are the actual, be going, um, radio stations
on the net, that, that people don't, I don't want to knock anybody in live 365,
I don't know, I'm not definitely aware of it, but, but radio paradise, um,
the, I mean, I have about a hundred stations that I can listen to live on my sonos system
here at the house. How many people are listening to the, to these streams,
Doc, I mean, isn't really that, is it really, and, I never hear anything about it. Really,
oh yeah, hell of a, listen, I was, I was talking to, um, at the Brooklyn Center,
we've been working with, um, with, with the, with the public broadcasting folks
coming up with, uh, a model to improve, um, uh, their, their revenues from, from their listeners,
and, and it's talking to a guy with a, a pretty large, well, I can't say what it is,
it's definitely one way to see in New York, and, and I jokingly said, well, I'm your listener
on the list code, he said, well, there are 10,000 of you, and this sometimes 20,000 of you.
It's a rapidly growing percentage of their total listenership, um, and it's, and I had no idea,
and he said, there's much more countable, um, on, um, online, and it is on, uh, through the air,
then you've already tried to go, go back to the, uh, but, okay, so, so for, for radio stations,
uh, that already have a terrestrial signal, um, and they, you know, so they want to expand their,
um, their market, and they're doing so by providing streams, which I understand, they make,
they make, so they're just not just, I mean, it's, it's radio paradise, which is, which is online, only.
Online, but, okay, but radio paradise is, but Doc, is it, is it, is it, is it just the music
that makes radio paradise, so special, is it, oh, God, no, no, it's, it's built, it's built, it's built,
it's built, so, so why, so why would, it is the personality and he's the guy who puts it together, um,
you know, there's a, there's a whole week radio out of Alaska, right?
There are a couple of people who are doing this thing out of a shack and have been doing it for years and they do and all of a good job
Right, but what I mean so they could easily use
a music under different license they could use
Music license on a creative commons they could use the policy using our work that you know garage ban
If you're in authority on music that happens which is I mean 90
You know
90-some percent of the music that's running through most of our heads is you know above a certain age is
Stuffy for the radio and that but bought a record source and to say oh you can't play that at all
You know, it just doesn't work for a lot of people
I mean to be a definitely worship people are dealing only in positive music for example or and you know
I mean look I'm the I'm the first person to say I hated because I really miss playing
You know the soundtrack to my life. I'm
Miss sharing that with my listeners. I think it's a travesty and I really despise the fact that I can't do it
But it's just a fact, you know, this so this this seems to me like this is being blown out of proportion
We're something that we know we saw this coming years ago doc we knew that it would never work
It will be so coming but at the same time everybody again, you know
Clear channel NPR and and the small webcaster and the rest of nobody expected it to be
But the royalty panel to make the decision that they did they heard one side they heard the other side and
They expected the
The decision to come down somewhere in the middle. It didn't come down in the middle out of nowhere and nobody expected it
It came down entirely on the side of the yard of a way and sound exchange and that's
That's been a complete shock and so
I mean for again for people who who you know or for whom it's okay that
That something as unjust as this happens. Well fine, but you know for a lot of people
It's you know who are putting out radio that does play the sound track of our lives
It's this not good. It's you know and and it's not accepted. I mean why should we put up with that?
Why should that be okay? Why should it be okay?
For the you know for the record industry to muscle Congress into putting a an nascent business
Out I mean that that's basically they're doing the killing of business the killing of it
It's just starting out and they're doing it on purpose. I mean, it's just an amazing thing to talk
Have dead. Okay. Here's my take on it. So yeah, I mean, I don't know about the putting out of business
part of it because look, you know, it's it's their property
They've they've had a monopoly over
Remusic in the way it's licensed and how it's used for for many many years
In in podcasting, I think we pretty much saw that there was just no way through it. So let's go around it and
For my money, I think maybe
We could take all this energy and we could create the soundtrack or the lives of our children or something like that
You know, it's oh, it's pretty egotistical at this point. I agree that at the end of the day the listener loses
Because
There's just songs that my daughter is growing up with songs that she should you know that she should know about
She's never gonna hear because they're not played on the radio and they're certainly, you know, not played on podcasts and they're just not available and that is a
Travesty, but
Don't you think we should just
Get on with it and say all right. Well, you know, because I think either the
Obviously, it's not a strategy for the future for for the for the
mainstream
Music industry
I think that they'll either have to come around and and change their views if everyone says, okay, screw it
We're just gonna go play this other stuff or
They'll die
Right, but but that's
I think they can do both. I think on the one hand they can play the other stuff and and on the other hand they can fight
What's happened?
I also think by the way, and I want to completely switch my point of view on this because I think I think I think there are ways of dealing with it
But we can't deal with it
I'm the supply side. That's what I'm working on at the Birken Center Harvard right now is coming up with
With instruments on the listening side there's a whole category of
So after that hasn't been created yet and tools and haven't been created yet that that give
Not just listeners, but but give customers ways of dealing with vendors that they don't have right now and now and you're here's a way of looking at it
So
And I'll just talk about I'll talk about public radio for a second. This is an interesting thing
So if you're in any room with middle class people in the US
It's a family people here listening listening listen to public radio and almost all the hands go up and and you say okay
How many actually pay for it and most of the hands come down 10% go up then you mess this?
How many of you would pay for it? It was easy at all the hands go back up again
The problem is it's not easy. Now a color that with with with
Music is that
With the honor, I definitely want you to what's the station's to charge even the thousands this antipers song
Okay, and it adds up of course you've got four or five 10
20,000 listeners at any given time
That adds up to a lot especially if you're not collecting money for it
But what if you could collect money for it? What if we could solve the problem from the listening side of I
I mean if I want to hear I mean just earlier tonight and I was playing with this thing is playing
Six days on the road by Dave Dudley for 1963. It's part of the centric life, right?
I'm gonna fix it to use on the road. I'm gonna go on on my own
Doc you're dating yourself. Yeah, I just want my voice changed to that very song, right?
So I'm gonna imitate Dave Dudley. So anyway, I
So I'm thinking you know, I'd be willing to pay
19,000 to this set to hear that song and I would like to be able when I hear it to punch a button on the car radio
Or punch a button on the whatever I'm listening on and say you know, I want to throw it right
I would have also a 20 25,000 to the set in their general right
But Doc you come back to it has nothing to do with web radio is just another way of getting music, you know
It's like you pay for satellite radio you pay for a subscription to Napster you you know, you pay for
Subscription to Yahoo music engine, you know, it's like wouldn't it just be a hell of a lot easier just to buy a subscription?
I mean I have Napster. I love it. You know, I was like, oh, I'd love to hear that song
Here's interesting thing. We we got Rhapsody other subtle system. You listen to it
Mostly, you know coming up to holiday is gonna take a little care to go get a Christmas music channels
We play the Christmas music people come over we play the jazz thing and a plane to class
It's really good and you know why they got a really boring after a while
Yes, because you don't have someone programming it for you
Exactly and how much did they say there is and all that but the interesting thing is the real radio stations
I mean I listen to small things is something called care CL in in Salt Lake City awesome freaking radio station
There's a little one in in Fairfield, I like how care you you and you know
They're range on the ground is you know four miles, but I'm in that it's around the world and
And I don't know whether they're playing a Creative Commons music or something else most of it is stuff
I haven't heard before but it's cool shit and and I like listening to it and here
Here's the thing I would like to this is like this is a light and on the one hand
I would like to help the stations fight the R.I.W.A and all that on the other hand
I would like to
Create the tools that make it easy for the listeners easier than ever for the listeners to get money
Directly to the people who are to be artists and for the intermediaries that are doing the job and and through the day
You mean just leaving it up to Napster and
Rhapsody and those is boring. I mean, I would rather have a
You know, you know
And impulse based you know works when I want it to way of doing that. So
Okay
It may be completely bogus. I mean, I work, but I'm trying to make it work. You know, just start about it
Well, when you when you got some news make sure you let me know. I'd love to hear about it
I'd love to have you back on the show to talk about that
Well, I'll be glad to come so just tell me what what are you gonna do in Brussels because it talk what the hell do you do?
I mean you you write you
You're you're an a-list blogger. Are you a consultant? I presume?
Yeah, oh, that and it was the the main thing. I mean right now
I've entered the the academic phase in my life. I've got a of a
I'll fellowship at the Birken Center at Harvard
And that's what I'm working on
You know, I bet I bet you can pick up chicks with that. Hey, I'm a fellow at the
I'm a race of a baby. Come on over here. Yeah
Yeah, no, no, mostly
I don't know what it does. Anyway, so the but it's fun, but the the other one is that I have a I also the fellowship
But you see a speed here in Santa Barbara where I live to work on
On some other stuff which is too long and complicated going to but it's also cool
The big thing about both is that
Is that I get to save a relationship so two universities that never would have let me in a student so
That's that's pretty cool. I was like a straight beast student in school and uh all right, but now I get you
But you got to eat Doc what what are you doing in Brussels?
This is gonna be my dinner. Okay, so so there
Actually, I'm yeah there are cutters a
There's a I'm meeting with some some folks and I'm some business, but I'm also at a
At a conference called inner identity open space that I've been involved with
Online identity
Development for a number of years and there's been some good salty involved in that, but
More importantly, they'll actually manage to move
Individual based identity forward with open ID and the number of other technologies over the last few days
You really turn them out more of the instigators. What's that? You're turning me on now with all this identity talk. It's making me hot
You know good consulting and that course is still right for litics journal. That's my page right right
It's been my day job for many many years and
That that gets me a lot of you know the information that's good to make money in some other way
Okay, well Doc, I I love the stuff you're writing your weblog. I get it through RSS, but I presume is it still docked out weblogs.com?
Yep, I think I've had the
The same address longer. I'm not making the last weblogs.com blog. I think yeah, but the last thing is not just the thing say
So we'll be following you. Thanks for for enlightening us
Somewhat here on on on this whole issue
It's very complicated, but you know, I did keep doing what you're doing. It's all you know that the podcasting
There's actual progress there and and you're not pushing the same rock up. They all look wonderful
Hold different rock. Yeah, it's a rock believe me. It's a rock as well
All right, Doc, I really appreciate have a great trip to Brussels and I'll send you a list of restaurants for for you. Okay, bye
All right, thank you
What we got from the start to the fall
Yeah
The time is out to realize what is to be around you what to decide on this fight
Get like your fate
What's up to what you should know then you will know where to go control your eggs
And don't look on the face
Who wins no one knows back to you all the trophy
And it's all you've got to
Who wins no one knows back to you all the trophy and it's all for that
Oh
This
The time is out, and we don't mind us, but it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's
it's just, it's just, it's just, it's that, it's just, it's just, it's, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just that, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just, the way that we were doing before the game, that's just, yeah, it's just, it's just, it's just it's just, and then parties, just, the way,
I don't know about the fade out, but hey, Doc Seralsman, a bit you like that song, no fees
necessary, crush and soulful battle from the pod tape music network, well, I'm not
quite sure what I learned, but I do appreciate Doc Serals taking the time before his
trip to talk about the death of Web Radio.
Alright, so for tomorrow I'm looking for a savon who can talk to me about the World Bank
and about Wolfowitz, I think it would be perfect for nylon, but I have no idea if nylon
is still listening, haven't heard from him in a while, I don't know what he did while
we're on vacation, but he's just kind of disappeared from the face of the earth.
And of course, I'd love to hear your suggestions for the rights of on to talk about that,
because that's just something I'd like to discuss tomorrow.
It's really hard to do this by the way, I can see where it's 50 minutes right now, and I'm
really trying to keep these interviews at 10 to 15 minutes.
What do we do with Doc about 19 minutes, God's field feels a little bit long.
But of course, I had to do a bit of intro, at least three minutes of talking about
what Doc does.
Okay, so here in San Fran, all kinds of meetings, all kinds of crap going on, so the shows
will be recorded at night, but of course, I know you really like that.
Adam at podshow.com, dailysourcecode.com, hey, we're going to have a fun week, I'll
talk to you tomorrow, bye.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery, podshow
in line light.