Hey, this is Michael Butler from the Rock and Roll Geek Show.
Check out one of my favorite TV shows this summer,
Bow Dog Music Battle of the Band.
It's a competition with Johnny Rotten as one of the judges,
and that is quality television, my friends.
Find out more at bowdog.tv slash battle.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks in.
I like to drink outside, you should drink.
I'll just take this out of the curry.
All right, just don't know if I can spit in.
I've got a lot of things to pack.
It's the ESN608.
If you have to ask, you better listen to it twice.
Here's Adam.
You better listen to it twice.
mash up with Madonna's and ray of light. It's
right of god. Well, that's a classic GHP mash up found just the other day at
mashuptown.com. Hey, everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the daily source code
episode number. Uh, 658 coming to you from the curry manner on the
east side, east side on the west side of G town in the affluent suburb of
Surrey known as Gilford. All right. Uh, okay. I might as well just kick it right off with
uh, with uh, the nylon because he's so right. Adam, I'm alive and kicking it for my
long. Down here, the elder ray, which is the fire island of France. And you have me
crying in my rosé about you giving up the daily source code. Hey, guy, you haven't done a
daily daily source code since April. What's the tears about? You know, it's different.
Your audience is the same. You know, it's changed. No serious and no splendor to pay
you to get up in the morning and deliver or show as you promise on the day you
promised. So don't give me this about your commitment to the audience. The audience
is the same. It's serious that's gone. So let's not all the promise and under
deliver. Oh, nylon, you hurt me so badly with that. How can you possibly suggest that
that my lack of source code has anything to do with money? If it had to do with money by
friend, I would close down my company and I would just do this show exclusively. I think
I could do just fine as nothing to do with money. But your point, your point is made. I don't
know if I've over promised and under delivered. I think I've just promised and not come
through. We'll come back to that. Just go to two shows a week, Tuesday, Friday or three
shows, promise that and deliver that so that when we look for you, you're there. I know
it's good for your download request. There's to be looking for your five days a week and
only show up too. Oh, you doork. Of course, it doesn't do anything for my download
request. If there's no shows to download, hey, football Friday on Sundays, I'm supposed
to be doing the time shifting. Not you. So go to what you can deliver and then keep it.
You know, it's never done a daily daily source code since serious stop paying you to get
up. But the audience is still here. So, you know, make a commitment with us and live
up to it. You know, you're a busy guy. Uncle Don. Uncle Don.
I don't. Hold on, hold on, hold on. Oh, nylon. That's a hardest part. The only commitment
I can make is that I'm committed. My friend, it has been and I warned you. I warned you
this week would be just outrageously busy and it was and Friday. Oh, man. I didn't get
home until, uh, the same as Thursday, really nine o'clock. And I was so tired. I just, you
know, I'd rather not do a show than do a half-ass show. You gotta, you gotta understand
that and you, you gotta appreciate that. Besides, the only person who seems to be crying
about it is me, actually. Anyway, here's your jingle, buddy.
Let's have a word with the nylon spreading and news with the smile on where the roll
all right. Ringo for light. Let's listen world of wild to the nylon. Yeah. I'm not
going to even play the part of what Uncle Don, because I've already been through all that.
Oh, yes. Uh, I wound up with a meeting at six o'clock Friday night in London in the short
it's UK office with Pixie Geldoff. Now, uh, the, the last name, of course, will, uh, we'll
probably ring a bell. Uh, her dad is indeed Bob Geldoff. And, uh, her older sister
peaches is, uh, that's, I saw her, uh, present a big brother, big mouth show over here, which
is kind of like a, right after the big brother show, then they have a kind of a funky, like
talk show thing going on, uh, with guest hosts of scene peaches. And she's, she's around
town. She's, of course, of drinking age, I believe. So that's why she's around town
and in the papers. And Pixie is, uh, I think 17. And, uh, that was kind of interesting.
Uh, I'm like, I'm, I'm sitting here and I think I'm having a business meeting with
someone, the same age as my daughter with, with a, uh, man, I wish I'd taken a picture
of her, uh, her agent or her manager. Oh, my goodness. His guy, uh, he was, he was a, he was
a real one, you know, black slacks, black shoes, uh, trousers worn just a little bit too
hot. He was kind of like an older Simon, Simon call. Anyway, it was very interesting. Uh,
once I asked her what she wanted to be when she grew up, then all of a sudden, then all
of a sudden, like, it's easy and passion. We had some to talk about. Anyway, so I was just
way too tired to do anything Friday. Um, even though, uh, yes, I, I even posted Thursday.
I think the last time I'm going to encourage calm that I was going to do a show. So I'm
sorry. I really do a problem, apologize.
Let me see, uh, good news. Uh, there was a couple of different good things. I believe, um,
number one with the bullet. One, a parsec award at, uh, where's the Dragon Khan? I
think is what it is. Congratulations to a, uh, Mark Yoshimoto Nemkoff. Also, uh, games
Weasel. Now, you've heard games Weasel, uh, promo on this show. It's a big show for us
here in the UK. It's audio only. It's a Mac Cuddle who does, uh, uh, this audio show about
video gaming and, uh, just kind of email, uh, uh, late in the week that games Weasel has
been nominated for the 2007 GMA games media awards, one of the five finalists in the games
podcast segment. How? By the way, there's something really messed up. I, for those of you
in the UK, there's the digital music awards, um, which is sponsored, uh, by BT. I think
maybe even in part by BT Pod Show. And this, they have a podcast category, um, that I'm just
going to have to distance myself from, uh, oh, man. I tried to tell them that it was, the way
for was not to nominate all mainstream podcasts. And I just, this is where the two cultures
just kind of clashed. So, um, for those of you, uh, you know, I, I, we'll get into a deep. I got to
talk to the BT people about it. But I've already gotten several emails of people questioning
what the heck is going on. Uh, so obviously we had no involvement in that. And, uh, I, I don't
think we can, well, I'm excited about the digital musical awards because it gives us a great
opportunity to do some live stuff. Uh, we always have the, uh, very awesome. We last year, we
had a great party. Uh, we were live for, I don't know, like a seven or eight hours red carpet,
uh, lots of celebrities. That's going to happen again this year. It's taking place in, uh, I think
it's, uh, mid October. Uh, so, uh, looking forward to that, but not to the, uh, to the actual
category as a, a four mentioned. Um, the girls are gone. It is indeed Sunday night. It's, uh,
10, 25 tomorrow morning. I leave right in early for San Francisco. Not only is it Labor Day tomorrow,
which is kind of why I chose Monday, no one would have to leave on a Sunday, uh, but since
there'll be no one working on Monday, I figured out it'll be nice to travel. I think it'll be nice
to travel on Labor Day. Everyone just kind of staying home. I hope that also happens to be my birthday.
It was the third of September that day to I was remember, uh, hey, that reminds me that is a
part of the soundtrack of my life. Maybe Yon Polet has one from yours.
Hey, Adam, this is, uh, hit us number 85. Hey, babe. Again, I have, uh, selected three great
tricks from the eddy. So here we go with intro number one.
And number two. Oh, I know that one. Oh, I love that one. That's, um, Ryan Paris Dolce Vita.
God, that's like a summer hit from 1981. I think, for 80 minutes. And the final one is number three.
That's, uh, first win in fire. Uh, I'm going to guess Boogie Wonderland, but I'm not sure.
And I can't figure out the first one. And these are the answers. Number one is Joe Kucker.
Damn.
Answer number one.
Oh, Kucker from 1987, and this is number two.
Yeah, 1983, right in first. This is Dolce Vita.
Oh, man, the spring's back memories of Sarka.
Right, Paris, and Dolce Vita is answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
Oh, no, it's from 1981, earth, wind and fire.
And this is no, no, no, no, no.
All right, wasn't Boogie Wonderland. I can have stars for that, no, not you.
As love goes on, earth would inspire, as answer number three.
And that concludes hit test number 85. Excellent.
Alrighty, three great tracks from the 80's again. Adam, I hope you liked them. And you'll, I guess, the
them all right. Next week, I'll be back for hit test number 86.
And until then, the answers to this hit test. And of course, the links to the music and
iTunes can be found at hittest.partshow.com. Alrighty, thanks for playing Adam.
Until next week, take care and bye bye.
I can't believe I missed Joe Cocker. That's, uh, that's almost unforgivable. Okay, I got, I don't,
I only, I got earth's wind fire, right? I didn't get the song right, but oh, yeah, and I love it.
I love those hit tests, man. It makes me feel good. That took me back to, it was 83, I guess.
I thought it was earlier. The summer of 83, uh, I was on the pirate radio station radio
decibel in Amsterdam. And, uh, that was such a hit. It was a warm warm summer. And we just
played that Ryan Paris Dolce Vita song over and over and over again. That was fantastic.
And of course, you can find links to all of the songs and all of the hit tests. We have 85 of them
now in total. That's been going for quite a while. Hey, y'all, what are we going to do for 100?
We got to do some special dude. You can find all those at hittest.podshow.com. All we're talking
about iTunes. A lot of, uh, back and forth, uh, in the press between NBC and Apple. Uh, it's, it's almost,
it's, it's kind of sad. It's like watching a bad breakup. So I guess what, what's happening is that NBC
and Apple couldn't agree on how they were going to extend their contract after, um, I think December,
where NBC wants, uh, flexible retail pricing so that they can basically, um, and, and I can
understand what they're coming from, by the way. They, they want to package things. I want to put
tracks together. They want to make special, uh, packaging deals. And I can understand because that
is kind of in their blood. Unfortunately, um, not only is that not in, in Apple's blood or
an iTunes, DNA is really, um, it's, yeah, you know, it's, it's, it's kind of, it's not the way geeks
think. Yeah, we think geeks think pretty linearly by one track, 99 cents. Now, everyone has argued
that Apple doesn't make any money off of the actual media sales anyway. And even if they do,
the point is that with mainstream content, uh, you know, the minute you have a great model for
reselling or packaging and distributing it, and you start to make some money, you know, what's
going to happen is they're going to raise the prices on you. They're going to start cutting you off.
That's just the way it works. You know, record companies these days are so desperate, so desperate.
They're there even trying now to get, uh, 50% of all proceeds from, uh, merchandise and, uh,
um, from, uh, concert performances. I mean, the desperate, the model is just over, you know,
give it up already. And so, you know, Steve Jobs, although a fantastic CEO, uh, you know,
no doubt about it. What he's been doing with Apple before he was kicked out of an after he came
back, is just stellar. And he's a very nice guy. I find him to be somewhat introverted and
timid personally, even though that looks quite different on stage. Um, I had, uh, the pleasure of
a, about an hour and a half, uh, private conversation with him before, um, iTunes launched with the
podcast and capabilities in it. And he was really endearing. And I know he listens to this show
from time to time, more at least he's got people who cut out segments and seven to a more
set of a pointer. Um, so here's my advice, you know, Steve, you are not a show business guy.
In fact, I would have to say that you are a several levels, levels higher on the social
latter. And I'll show, although show business seems very sexy. And yes, I know you're in Pixar
and, you know, you're on the board of Disney. And it's different, you know, it's different
down in the trenches where, you know, the asshole of the industry, which is basically with a money,
gets taken in and, and the bullshit pooped out. It's very different down there.
And, um, I don't understand why you, you know, enough already, you know, if they want to go
off and sell it on to Hulu or Zulu or whatever their website is, let them go do that. That's fine.
They're going to do it anyway. And that's probably what's, what's 50% of the whole breakup
is about is they want to be able to just sell it on their site and not have to deal with you.
But, look at the world of independent media Steve. Look at all of the reports that are coming out.
Look at what people are saying that they really want. Look at where they're gravitating towards.
Look at what they're moving away from. They're moving away from mainstream.
They're looking for alternatives. They're looking for new things and new series and, and really
episodic content they can latch on to and become a part of and contribute. And you've got the
perfect infrastructure for it. And if indeed you don't really make all that much money on, on, on,
on the content sales itself. And in, of course, in the future, you probably won't anyway.
What do you have to lose by supporting independent media? Really supporting it. You know,
that was the, the one disappointment, understandable. But the one disappointment when Apple
came out with podcast and capability, they really started to promote a lot of mainstream content,
a lot of NPR. And although it is fantastic content, you know, there's so much more that can be done.
Really, really, so much more. And they would support you. They really, they're already supporting you.
Independent producers, the world over our supporting iTunes with the tags that they put in with
trying to get listed, you know, trying to do a really good job to get, you know, more subscribers
and into your top 10 lists, even though it's kind of fuzziest of how those work,
it doesn't matter. You know, they will support it. Give it up. Let's fuck those guys. Really,
for years, I tried to change the thought of the mainstream until about three years ago. I just
fuck it. Let's just do what our, let's just, let's just show them how it's done. We'll build an
entire parallel industry if we have to. That's the word of the day Steve. Just fuck them.
Fuck them. Oh, my, I think, oh my gosh, Adam Curry. This is Dan Johnson from Cincinnati, Ohio.
You know, I started listening to the daily source code back around July, early August of 2005.
And you were, you were using the rock money now, opening back then, hearing it on DSC 656 from August
27, 2007. Oh my gosh, I just brought you a talk about the soundtrack to your life. Man, I'm just
saying that applies me out so much, brother. You rock, you like the house, man. Thank you so much.
That's nice, man. I appreciate it. Oh, by the way, what while I'm talking about Apple, just a bit
about the iPhone, it has the touch screen is still not come back to life, unfortunately. I think
that is gone forever. So that is a bummer. And that does put me in the middle of a quite a
conundrum. Or should I call it a dilemma? Adam Jason from San Diego. So you lost your iPhone
and you're going to buy probably the new iPod, but what I'd like to know is are you going to buy
another iPhone? Is it worth it to spend the other money? Have it. And maybe you may not use it a lot,
but you know, sometimes you just got to buy something to have it, would you buy another iPhone?
Like, yo, yo. Well, um, I'm the wrong guy to ask that particular question because, uh,
the cost of an iPhone, I just had to be honest. It doesn't make any difference to me left or right.
So I don't make my purchase based, not that type of purchase based upon, uh, do I think it's worth it?
Because I, what I just wanted, I really, really, really love the web browsing experience.
Although I've been hanging with the Nokia's for a moment. What is it now? More than a week, right? Yeah.
It has more, it's, yeah. It's like nine days. And the phone, of course, is working great. I have to say
battery power, far superior to the iPhone. The Nokia, you know, I can be using it for two days and
still going strong. And the 8800, I got to, uh, can't even, and Luke sent me a very nice, uh,
leather at wallet that wraps around it and snaps in place with the, uh, with little, uh, magnets.
And, uh, that that actually gives it a very professional look and feel to it. And I have been using it
quite a bit. Got to tell you. Um, and, uh, if, you know, it's like, I could construct the perfect
device that I really want. I know that for sure. It would take a whole bunch of patents to be matched
up together. Um, but it would be a combination of things. Anyway, um, I'll say that phone wise,
I'm very happy with my E61 India. Uh, and if Apple were to come out, uh, on, uh, was it Wednesday,
September 5th, they have some special announcements in Cupertino and everyone's pretty short
about iPods. But what if they came out with the iPhone, with the phoneless iPhone,
you know, if it was an iPod that also had the Safari browser and it and Wi-Fi and, uh, man,
would I dig it? Yeah. Would I buy it? Definitely.
Sugar, sugar, sugar, Adam here, the sugar, sugar. Stop. Just for a moment.
Imagine that you're wife and mother who has been manipulated or experienced physical or emotional
abuse. Imagine the concerning half for your kids because you hope that they are not next.
Well, maybe you've seen a progress to your child and it hasn't get come to you.
Imagine all the times you've heard your partner say he wants to change,
knowing that he hasn't. Imagine trying to muster up the courage to get out of this situation.
Imagine the anxiety and fear you feel as you look around your home,
because you know you're going to leave so many things behind.
Maybe it's hard for you to imagine what this is like, but maybe you certainly can relate
with the feeling of being powerless. My name is Daniel Johnson Jr., and I produce a podcast from
Cincinnati, Ohio. Even more importantly, I'm a person and a member of the community.
The same way victims of domestic violence and abuse are. I know I'm not alone and wanting to do
something about it. Here are two things you can do. Number one, on Sunday, September 9th, 2007,
people all over the Cincinnati area will be joining together to raise one voice for domestic violence
awareness. Please come join us as saw your point along the Ohio River. Money's raised will help
families leaving the local battered women's shelter to start over. Find out more information
at onevoicewalk.org. Number two, become part of the growing online community that is raising one voice.
Check out myspace.com slash one voice walk for more information. Thank you very much.
More than welcome my friend. This morning my inbox was filled with two types of email.
One was an apparent invite from all of my friends to join the social network catch-up
spelled in a rather peculiar manner. Quebec Uniform Echo Charlie Hotel Uniform Papa.
And the other half of the contents of my inbox, at least the visual part, was apologies from people
saying, oh man, shit, I can't believe I signed up for this and it sucked out all my email addresses.
Need mail down my friends. It's like double the amount of spam. Wow, what a virus, huh?
A awesome, awesome, awesome social virus. Very, very simple. All the did was, is it just kind of
didn't tell you that, oh my second, was that the, I'm looking, I waited for a text message from my
girls on a batteries full, charging the Nokia. Yeah, you know, so if you, if you run into
some kind of social network that you're going to sign up to and by the way, all these things are
viruses as far as I'm concerned, if you know how many invites I get to Twitter is now gone,
pounds, how many friend requests I get from my space, how many friend additions from Facebook,
how many people are asking for connections on LinkedIn? I'm sick and tired of it. It's just annoying.
It really is. And now this ketchup thing, which I guess you sign up for it and then it says,
oh, you know, we're just going to check and see if any of your other friends are already on,
and then we'll like hook you up automatically, which is also just fucking annoying. It really is.
I do not want to be your friend. Stop sending these invites. I'm not joining. You know,
I don't have time to do a show. Let alone manage my friends on all these different social networks.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's see what else was there. Oh, so the wing commander did I even tell you
the story about, I don't know if I told, I'm blanking for a second. I don't think I've told the story.
So I was supposed to get the the Delta Sierra. I don't know,
yeah, I think I did. No, I can't remember that I did I talk about it with Patricia on Sunday,
show anyway. I was supposed to get the Delta Sierra last weekend, but they needed a flying
station wagon, which is declassification of aircraft we own. The 182 retractable. Because the 182
they had set up to do, I think it was, if it wasn't the make a wish foundation, it was comparable
to the make a wish foundation. We're going to fly some kids around Rotterdam last Saturday.
The plane that they had set up for that, they were, they had just rebuilt the engine. They had flown
four hours. This is the wing commander William. And he was a parked at grass field eating muscles.
The only plane on the field except for a glider who was pulled up on a cable. And I guess he
went off the center line. So he kind of veered off and then he dropped the cable and the cable
came down and sheared the wing. So they needed the Delta Sierra to to cover. So not a problem.
And so this past Saturday, the wing commander showed up right in early and brought it back. And so
had a nice flight taken him back to Antwerp and then solo back over the channel, which was,
oh, it was so nice. I got to tell you, I'm at that point. Do you remember when you learned how to
drive when, you know, and it's usually after just time. And in this case, it's also time. It's just
hundreds of hours of flying. Where you feel like, okay, you know, lots of stuff can happen.
And there's all kinds of things that have to be aware of, particularly other drivers and conditions.
But I have this vehicle under control. And that's the way I feel now about my flying. You know,
and I'm at the point where I feel just as comfortable in a helicopter.
And the fixed wing is I do in a helicopter. And it's really, it's, it's, it's almost like it's
invigorating. It's like a drug. You know, you just, I get so psyched up. Oh, yeah, I'm going to fly.
And just, and everything is always different. But I know I've got this thing. You know, I know how
this is my plane. It's wrapped around me like a second skin. And it's just nice.
So, you know, that was beautiful doing the crossing the channel solo on the way home. Then this
morning, I took the ladies, the divas, Patricia and Christina, who are at a fashion show or
word of fashion. So earlier this evening, I probably outhang and then drink and whatever. And
the two of them, you know, oh, man, they look like total divas packed in the back of the Delta
Sierra with the, they're big, big aviator glasses on lots of hair flowing. Flim over to Hilversum
and dropped them off. We had a nice, quick little lunch, saw taxi Eric. And of course,
I was with Captain Dan, as you know, Patricia won't fly across channel with me without a safety pilot.
And so we had a nice flight back. You're kind of unadventful. But it was nice.
Kind of good time. And I've had my fill. Thank goodness, because it's going to be two weeks
as of tomorrow, two weeks on the road. First to San Francisco, then I'm somewhere near, I think it's
San Diego for some, uh, what is it? I media. It's I media conference where I'm a lunchtime special speaker.
Then a quick stop. Uh, I'm actually I'm hoping to take a virgin America from San Francisco to Los
Angeles and then fly back from from Los Angeles. Really? Because I just want to fly
virgin America. They say it's like a flying iPod. I can't wait to try it out.
Hey, uh, what is it? 30 minutes? I got some songs I got to play for you. Hold on a second here. I got
Jersey Todd, which of course was a Fubar Friday special edition. Something we haven't done a long while.
What's playing on?
At this first, and I find.
Yes, we have not played something from the first gen iPod in a long time. I'm no longer
gonna put it on the summer selection since the weather is a little bit variable now. So I'm taking
off of the summer playlist. I'm just, uh, getting either rammed in here.
All right, it's queued up. Let's find out what's playing on Adam's first gen iPod.
What's playing on Adam's first gen iPod? Okay, you never know. Oh boy. Oh no.
Oh, I'm not embarrassed to say I've got this on my first generation iPod. It's the captain and
to kneel everybody.
This was, uh, takes me back to the windjamer club in Amsterdam in, uh, late 70s and do that to me one more time.
I can never get in. Oh boy, I'm like you. Oh, kiss me. Like you just me. Oh baby, do that to me once again.
As if I may want more time, once just isn't it for my heart to hear, well tell it to me one more time.
I can never hear in. Oh boy, I got you. Oh, say. Oh, kiss me. Oh, kiss me. Oh baby, do that to me once again.
Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again.
Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh boy, do that to me once again. Oh
do that to me once again. Oh baby, do that to me once again. I was 15, I think she was 16. Snuck into the win
in jammer club underneath the uh... what is now the uh...
yeah
there's now the marriott hotel news was the marriott then too
but dance the night away
to captain to kneel it takes all the boxes on the soundtrack to my life that's for sure
uh...
you know this is happening all over the place people are hearing old songs and they're
saying wow that is definitely a part of the soundtrack to my life and that's
why we have a upsell the organization for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives
at um...
to listen to sixty six and you're playing your original theme song music and
man that's great you talk about the soundtrack to your life
i remember driving with my brother from where we were getting gone a power plant
actually
and we're driving from the hotel over to the plant about a thirty minute driving
you got to listen to things about the podcast
he's ruined is like first gen iPod
how did i started playing it that came on and followed by you in the daily source code
and i've been listening to that plus about a half a dozen to a dozen more podcast
ever since
and that was a real blast so that was pretty cool thanks for playing it man
not until further and uh... i don't know what else
Steve jobs Steve jobs listen these are people who buy your products listen to what they're
saying please
you're under i'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out
you're under please don't bang that gavel you can try this cowbell out
let's all give up night
to the hardest work and lawyer
you
yeah
how's it going out of it's jersey time the official musicologist
of the chacha
have i got a band in a story for you tonight
the band is the stone coyotes at a Massachusetts
i am loving these guys and i love their story
barber key through here in a second is the uh... the amazingly singer this band
and the thing about her is that she started her whole career as a folk singer she was actually
playing grenadier village in the in New York city she was signed to an am she was signed to
warner and and she had some pretty good songs and scum covers
uh... some people covered some of her stuff including barbers dry sand and tanya
tucker
her husband on the other end was in l.a. he was a writer for bewitched
happy days the end of the show but you know neither of them were entirely satisfied
doing those kind of things
so they moved off to western massachusetts they taught their son to play bass guitar
and they formed the stone coyotes
now this band we had been playing around in fact they got back out to l.a.
and when l.a. more Leonard was looking for inspiration to get shorty the sequel
that came out be cool he found the stone coyotes and in fact dedicated be cool to them
I know why because this band absolutely kicks ass in fact it's one of my all time favorite songs
on the positive music network it's called back to New York and I know you're going to love
this check this out
this is just one of the best songs ever
I climb to the top of the mountain
I went to where rivers were born
I threw three coins in the fountain
sail to the eye of the storm
I sat across from a wise man
he said I'll tell you what is true
I said excuse the interruption
if it's all the same to you I'm going back to New York
back to New York
yeah yeah
I found the moss city of Atlantis
I slept in the Taj Mahal
walked through the garden of Peter
I saw Adam and he'd take the fall
I hit the ride on a spaceship
I hit my crew out to Venus and Mars
I said oh well I like the view
but I thank my lucky stars
I'm going back to New York
back to New York
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh oh oh oh oh
I hung around with Pandora
she said don't open that box
I said too late the deed is done
she said she would have showed her change
the locks
I was crying across the Sahara
in the middle of New Man's land
so for a second and Broadway
she learned that deserts
and I'm going back to New York
back to New York
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh oh oh oh oh oh
I'm going back to New York
back to New York
yeah
Todd no joke man
Stone coyote is your final
on the pod save music network
at music.pot show.com
or of course direct links
in the show notes at daily source code.com
whoo
going back to New York
now I don't feel good about going to California
back to New York song
that just doesn't feel right
we got to rectify that
let's break the law on this
food bar for Sunday
who gives a shit
his guys are all rich anyway
you sure are a pretty man
at him if I was woman I'd have
been for you
music
On a dark desert highway
Cooling in my hair
Once we'll complete this
Rising up through the air
Up ahead in the distance
I saw a shimmering light
I hit the heavy on my side who damn
I had just enough for the night
There she stood in the doorway
With her mission bail
And I was thinking to myself
This could be heaven
And this could be heaven
Then she lit up her candle
And she showed me the way
There were voices down this morning dark
I thought I heard them say
Welcome to the hotel California
In the place that you love, in place that you love
Your face
Ready and rule, let the hotel California
In the time of year, in the time of year
You can find it here
When I just dip in it twisted
She got the Mercedes fans
She got a lot of her pretty pretty boys
She got friends
How the plants in the courtyard
Sweep in summer's way
Something that's doing over
Something that's too forget
So I call her the captain
Please really remind
So we haven't had that feeling here
Since the 1960 night
And still those voices are calling from far away
When you have been better than night
Just now you have been saved
Welcome to the hotel California
In the place that you love, in place that you love
Your face
Ready and rule, let the hotel California
In the time of year, in the time of year
You can find it here
When you have been better than night
In the time of year, in the time of year
You can find it here
in the time of year, in the time of year
In the time of year, in the time of year
You can find it here
in the time of year, in the time of year
In the time of year, in the time of year
You can find it here
You can check out any time you like
But you can never leave
You can never leave