Find this podcast and others like it at the number one new media network.
Potcha.com.
Better faster.
Strong stronger.
And now with new mini fresh sent.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present Potcha's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Rose is our man.
My sweater is beige for your domain name needs.
You should go to this page.
GoDaddy.com.
Potcha is pleased to bring you the following killer content.
Direct from the all new feature rich Potcha.com.
Get it.
Play it.
Dig it.
Welcome to the robot weather in Celsius for the Guildford region on Tuesday the 13th of February.
Today chance of rain with a maximum temperature of 8 degrees.
Tonight chance of rain with a minimum temperature of 5 degrees.
Tomorrow rain with a maximum temperature of 7 degrees.
Tomorrow night the temperature drops to 1 degree.
Thursday scattered clouds with a maximum temperature of 9 degrees.
This is the robot weather.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery.
Potcha and line light.