It's time you've got in the game.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get a domain name, free-click blog, and complete email.
Get in the game at GoDaddy.com.
Hey there Adam, this is Earl over in Rawland North Carolina.
You were down over in Wellington, though if you were still there may we get together
and do the DSC 5601.
I think that'd be a lot of fun, and I bring old Bruce with me.
You remember Bruce, he's gotting on new teeth.
I ain't still whizzing really good, and he ran like that cowbell you play.
I play for Marcus, we have a so little band.
So with the DSC 5601, let's get it going.
With $60 million worth of air playing strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing this battle curry.
All my slides are in the yard.
This horse code.
I got it.
Body,oustic Cleanser, forensics.
That's right I got it.
I got it.
doinn the basketball.
Get out of the game.
I got it.
I gotstring beard I got it.
I just got it.
I got it.
I have on the hook as I was right there.
I had a little bit of the boost.
I got it.
Gosh, you know, it's what's happening. All right, so maybe it's a little softer in one year now for some reason
It's been one of those weekends. It's been one of those days. It's been it's been just crazy
Man, this is really gonna this is gonna bother to shit out of me if if you guys can't hear properly
Hold on, let me see let me just try something here hold on bear with me
Okay, that was an interesting experiment now. Let's try the other channel
Yeah, okay
Well, hopefully you hear me in both ears anyway, so let me let me just prep us a couple things. So yeah in New York
How should I maybe I should take it back to Friday? Just to make it easy on myself to do it in chronological order
And then I'll and I'll get to all the other stuff that's happening right now. So
Fluida New York on Friday last Friday food bar you remember I did the food bar show and everything was all messed up and the life was food bar in general
And okay, the flight was on eventful got in state at the we have a corporate apartment here
Which the sales team in New York actually kind of managed the apartment
So it's their office and when the guys come in from out of town they stay there and and
Some of our production people also use uses it's like a crash pad. It's very much like the shortage office in in London
Only we didn't get the same interior decoration done imagine a two bedroom New York apartment
Fabulous view of the Empire state building
You can you can see right up to Broadway from from I mean the view is just spectacular
It's a great building it gets a nine on a scale of one to ten for location
But when you get guys who do the interior decorating you get pretty much what you'd expect
It's like a dormant with guys who had money
They've got these I stayed in one of the bedrooms and they've got this
One of these posture tetra pedic thing mattresses that's supposed to form itself to your body
Well that's basically for me. It was like sleeping in a slab of clay
That was not
Not my cup of tea to say the least
And the living room has no couch. It has we have lots of desks and and plenty of wifi access
And then and I don't know how big this TV. There's a TV in there that it's like it must be like a 70 inch television
You know like rear view projection whatever
It's crazy
I was one there for one night and then the next day left for Wilmington North Carolina home of port city pd of course
one of the
One of my favorite shows on the the pod show network you can find the port city pd
podshow.com. It's a cop show. It's real simple and the production value of this thing in the story and the editing is is top notch
And you know we're a winding down series one and I can't remember exactly how they came about
But we agreed somehow even in the contract
This is something you know I told you before that podshow contracts are all the more unique
And in this particular one part of the contract was that I would appear in an episode of port city pd
Now we tried to do it for episode six
But it didn't work out schedule wise and so then we did it with that episode seven and I had a you know
I play an FBI agent agent Quinn no less and
So you know I go to North Carolina and I kind of forgot in the North Carolina is not it's only like an hour and 15 minutes away from from New York
You just hop on the shuttle. You know, it's it's really convenient and the weather is beautiful
You arrive there and like oh man of course
They've got beaches. They've got you know colleges universities is beautiful people walking around
It's historic at the same time and
You have to know
that North Carolina is is
Has recently I don't know not only recently, but I think maybe they did they read it their tax code again
and it is without a doubt one of the most
financially
Attractive states in the union for television and film production
And right next the airport that's a huge MGM sound state it says about
$300 million worth of productions taking place already in in Wilmington
Dawson's Creek was shot there one tree hill
This you know several
Major motion pictures that are being being done there and
What happens when you have that type you know on the way in the talk to the the guy at the shuttle bus driver for the
Yeah for the Hilton
So yeah, so I tell me about Wilmington. Yeah, he says well, you know basically we're tourism here and we've got great beaches and and of course
You know the entertainment industry that's really big for us
And so when you have a community that you know that gets all this money ported and also it gets ported into the local community
Of course when to film and television productions come the town you get something that in LA has existed for many many years
But it's so fresh and and new in Wilmington. It's really it really turned me on you get a whole subculture of
People who like video and now that the tools have changed and and this generation in Wilmington has grown up
really with
necessity being the mother of invention
What they've done is instead of just you know only trying to scam jobs on on these big productions
They've started doing their own productions and that's where this whole port city PD thing came from these people who are professionals
Really know what they're doing and
You know sometimes they work on big big budget productions and lots of other times they don't and so
they all kind of get together actors
directors of photography
Directors producers and they all have you know day jobs and and either they're waiting on tables or or you know
Some of them auditioned in New York, but they all there's a really beautiful culture of hey
Let's just make some cool ass shit
And I was blown away by first all the way
You know the professionalism of all the people who work on port city PD
It's a you know big crew when you think about and if you ever seen the show you'll know exactly what I'm talking about
And everyone has a
Everyone has a demo DVD of some short or movies full-length movie
like unbelievable motion pictures
shot all on HD
HD cameras you know an edited and final cut pro or premiere and I'm so excited and I really really and it hasn't
I mean it's been a long time since I pulled almost a virtual all nighter
But we were really
You know we we met with the producers we were not to dinner and then we went hung out and then of course
You know lots of people from the cast and crew were dropping by and everyone had a cool interesting story and everyone's working on something before you know
It's like two o'clock which of course sat at a night was not two o'clock. It was three o'clock and then before you know it
It's four and you're in bed by five and I had a a call my call time was 8 a.m
For my scene and port city PD and you know and everyone was there man even though we were all and you we all only slept a couple hours
and
And it was very very invigorating to be in such a creative community
With so many people who have so many interesting ideas and things going on and just really messed up stuff that they've made
Which I'm so happy to see and and we're gonna try and get as much as possible on the on the network
You know the little that's just lots and lots and lots of business to be done very excited about that. It was a great trip
So was it Sunday came back to New York
Crash real hard Sunday night, you know, I I luckily had already done my serious satellite stuff and
You know, I just had to sleep. I just couldn't do a show because we had a full day today and right now
New York time is also
We'll just call it Tuesday if you're in London
It's almost midnight so
Basically Tuesday if you don't mind me calling it that and
You know, I got everything set up. It seems to be working reasonably well
This is the the mobile kit that I put together. I was able to get the right
adapters and plugs and cables
by the way, it's a personas is this
Compressor limiter than I'm using it's a real sweet
You can hear some of the New York street sounds out there. It's a real sweet box. Um, I love this box. I love sweet boxes
Speaking of sweet boxes
If I'm not gonna get the lady Patricia on the show
I'm gonna get her on the show. I really am maybe you could descend in a voicemail comment
Because maybe if they hear from you, she'll believe it
Tell her she had needs to come on the show
There's a whole part of my life the ones that we share together that she knows
About you know you should send her email you really should you really should
Patricia Curry dot com
Lady Patricia's outside of course
She said why why should she send this to the old new show?
Why? Why why?
She has other things to do. That's so sad. I can't coordinate with her
Maybe you could descend in a voicemail comment
You know you should send her email Patricia Curry dot com that's a sonder from
Podcasts studio.nl
Trying to motivate the lady Patricia to come on the show of course
That's kind of tough me being New York and she's an engineering a good time, man
They're having the girls are having some fun back in in old blighty
I'm kind of jealous of that
But I did say I forwarded her the link
So I and I know when I forward it to or she's kind of click on it and she'll hear it and she'll probably get it and
Hopefully by the time I get back we'll have
Yeah, you know
We'll have a show we will make show together
A practicing my German accent
Big big pod chill meeting with some
Big marketing mux and in Germany on or Friday and Hanover
Hanover of course the home of seabed
Now I won't be going
Ron will be going and
Executive sales we Zola
Chris will be going and I'm gonna cover in New York because
Lots of stuff but this whole week is just chocolate block full
Hooking up with the Mary Claire folks Mary Claire
Of course we you know the mast head which is the the show we do behind the scenes of the making of Mary Claire every month magazine
And so meeting with Joanne the editor and chief and meeting with the publisher and yeah
I know that if Patricia knew that you know she'd be here and yeah
I think she's secretly quite jealous that she's not here because this time around
We are meeting with lots of lots of cool people and it's just been back to back
Advertising agencies
Some of the clients directly and I got to tell you the buzz is big and really is and and what you're seeing is that
Everyone is starting to understand
This stuff about advertising that you know that we've been talking about that they're you know the first of all that there's an audience that is
You know it fits somewhere between
mainstream
television and radio and and like my space
virality and and you know it seems to be you guys
Congratulations
Advertises want to talk to you
So we'll hold auditions for them shall we
And then who's got the New York hook up?
That's the one thing I've never quite completed in the past two years. I need a new York connection
No, what I mean
Thank you
Hi, this is Peter Tlothero from the Suffolk and Cool podcast with a very brief and special invitation to you
To get involved with an experiment in networking
What is there's a couple of guys in Australia who have come across somebody else's blog
And they want to make contact with that person
But they don't want to go direct to them what they want to do is to try and use the blogger's fear podcasters personal contacts
Anybody who knows anybody else to find really secure it is rude to this person
So if I tell you that the message is coming from a couple of guys called
Dave Wallace and Mike safefang in Australia
And they're trying to contact
indirectly
GP Rangaswami who in fact is the CIO for British telecom's global service
And he has a blog at a confused of Carl Cutter
And so what they're trying to do is to find
a bunch of people to connect through personal contacts to eventually find their way to
GP Rangaswami
So it's arrived with me
I'm actually based in the east of England in the UK
And I'm passing out to you and I'm inviting you in fact to pass on this MP3 if you would to anybody
You think might even be a connection
Or even if you don't think there is it's it's incredible how the connections do crop up
So if you could that would be really good and you'll find information about exactly where to contact
And who to contact let us know how the the space telephone is working
In the Suffolk and Cool show notes for the podcast number 55
And you'll find that basically get the Suffolk and Cool website which is all the dumps
Suffolk and cool
dot com
things very much indeed for your help
It's fun this I tell you
All right, I mean I could pick up the phone and just call the guy
Really I could
But I guess that's not the point space telephone. Okay. I'm in. I'm in. There you go
We see a couple of things. I just want to talk about the came in over email. Yeah, this was a quite a shocker
James
He sends me a link to
BBC new story. Yeah quite disconcerning
Hold on here it comes. Soul band the drifters have been involved in a serious car crash on the M1 in South Yorkshire
Which is nasty, but I hadn't heard about this. What did this come out this came out to
uh
Yesterday the accident happened near ratherum ratherum ratherum ratherum ratherum ratherum
ratherum
Happening the early hours of Monday when the bands car hit another vehicle that had crashed after swirving to avoid a deer
Patrick Allen joined the band the 1990 suffered head injuries and was being treated at ratherum hospital
and the other three band members Peter Lamar Victor
Beno I think it is by no Beno and Rowan turning escape with less serious injuries
Wow
Oh man that really sucks guys I hope everything everything works out particularly
With with Patrick James thanks for sending that one in
I really should have had some drifters ready to play for you in hindsight
And of course boy did I get a lot of email about the conversation
That I started about the channel for fill which of course now you've probably seen on curry.com or maybe you've sorted out yourself
He's available both on google video and and youtube
Of course I'm referring to the great global warming swindle and
I got a lot of comments and I haven't even gone through the all throughout the voice mails yet
I just wanted to read part of this one. This is from Thomas crossland of course to call my eye because he starts off by saying as a
former aerospace engineer now an environmental scientist
I always cringe when you start talking about science topics
That makes me feel all warm and fuzzy on the inside while I generally enjoy your show
You are very susceptible to media washing of various topics
First of all let me just say
You should go back and listen because
I didn't say that I believed in and I said it was very compelling and now I said the same thing about an ink and being in truth
You know, I'm just the messenger in this case. I don't know what the hell I'm talking about
But yeah, of course I'm susceptible and I'm a smart guy. I think so imagine what it does to the masses
Which is exactly why I wrote to these topics
The channel for video I went and dug around in there is supported by the Kato Institute
Which is a right wing think tank that was founded by Charles cock
Cock cock cock cock
Charles cock co-owner of coach industries the largest privately held oil company in the US and heavily funded by Exxon
The three scientists at the Kato Institute have been trying to tear down climate science and helped and helps from the
And helped form the Bush administration's early policy framework
Regarding climate change
They've been doing a good job of creating a veil of debate and confusion about climate science
Which keeps the public not knowing which way to turn when people are in certain they won't act
This is the goal of the Kato Institute and people like them and and the email goes on and
There's explanations and
You know
Well, here's the question. Do you really believe Thomas?
How am I doing on time here?
Let me see how I'm doing with the satellite wind up fall shit
Almost there
Thomas, do you truly believe that the Bush administration
would
harm the environment purposefully? I for profit. I guess that's what you're saying
only because of oil. I mean
Do you really think that?
And you may and and and and if you have any reasoning behind that, I'd love to hear it. You know, it
If it's just money and it really is that bad
Man, then that would be incredibly evil
So this week is a little difficult for me to really hone in on
On this issue if you have a comment about it, please send it
You know, call the voice mail line actually. Let me just give you a reminder in case you forgot the number
I
We'd be highly appreciated so that we can just keep this going while I am not able to spend as much time as I'd like to but
I have been I have been reading up on on the plane as I promised I bought a book called a globalization
Which if you're listening to serious satellite radio stars one or two you won't be able to hear
Talk about that because we're about to cut off the source code for today. Well, let me just grab the book, okay
It's over here
What is it it's uh written by who wrote this?
Alex McGillavry McGillavry Gray McGillavry a brief history of globalization
Because of course the hypotheses of the movie the great
Global warming swindle is that it's really
Being perpetuated by the anti-globalization movement and I'm interested in that because what exactly is globalization and when did it start and
You know there's different theories about that
Some say it started in 1950s some say it started in
19 even as late as 1980s something 85 and
In this book, there's an example cited from 1870 and even earlier
So I just look in here. I'm looking at the the bookmark. I'm on page 24
So I got a little ways to go
Man, I think if there's anything else
We got to talk about that is do more more
No, I think that's kind of it
It's gonna be a nutty week, but I'll definitely have some some things to talk about
Every single day so Monday was I hope really the only day that it just kind of got out of control
I just couldn't do a show should be okay for the rest of the week though
Coming to you from New York as you know and I went to the PM and
You know punch at our comm slash music. I searched for New York and came up with two pages of just awesome stuff that
Really
Really kind of maybe feel like I was in New York City
Michael the Thomas fan is going to New York City you won't find me in Boston
My New York City
I've been to Richmond and Phoenix too
I've been so many places with nothing to do got my ticket
The call I'm going to New York
We do a planter and watching tour
You know my M.M. show was long
But ain't nothing ever so pretty like New York City
I've been to Brussels and London too
Well, they're fast and mine's me of you
Nipples, they're still your heart and that's a star
Yeah, I won't be in Boston
No LA
Sweet home Chicago
It's too far away
I got my boots on walk out the door and I'm gone
Yeah, I've been to Richmond and Phoenix too
I've been so many places with nothing to do got my ticket
The call I'm going to New York
I've been to Atlanta and watching tour
You know my M.M. show was long
But ain't nothing ever so pretty like New York City
Hey
It ever so pretty
But New York City
The Michael A Thomas fan going to New York City coming to you almost live from New York City
Yeah, I got to tell you one day in the city. I'm already. I'm grouchy. I'm angry at everybody and I feel energized
It's what New York does to you
All right, everybody daily source code dot com item at podshow.com
That is actually working again the atom at curie dot com email. It's a whole another story for a whole another show
Maybe tomorrow to care yourself and
We'll talk you tomorrow. Bye. Bye. Bye another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery podshow and line light
Or