Ladies and gentlemen, I present Padshal's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Roses are wed, my sweater is beige. For your domain name needs, you should go to this page. GoDaddy.com.
Time for an extra special bonus! That's right, because I'm a passionate guy like that.
So as a sit here, touching myself, I thought to myself, I should call Mark. I should tell Mark,
do you love what you're doing with a chacha? The chacha has never been so fresh, so invigorating.
So, um, turning it on. I sit here every night and the doctor said it's my homework.
I put the iPod into my ears. I grab the Vaseline and I turn off the lights and I crank up the chacha with Mark.
You'll show more on him, cough. It makes me happy. It makes me giddy. It makes a mess of my sheets and my socks, but that's okay.
Thank you, Mark. Keep up the good work.
First, there was brain twisting, jallin jipper, together, the principles of mathematics and cross-all puzzles.
From Japan, the country that brought you suitable.
Come! Bookaku!
All right, let's see, seven, one. The four goes here. Wait, no damn, that's not right.
Holy shit, dude, you just jacked off on me.
I'm like regular Sudoku, where you can make mistakes and erase them with pencil.
Bookaku is much more challenging, because if you get even one number wrong, you will find you and jack off on you.
Oh my eye!
Bookaku is fun for parties, national parties, retirement parties, and the occasion in perfect time for Bookaku.
Today, Little Schmolikko, Bergonia 13, birthday you are a man.
My Little Schmolik, somebody get a towel.
Idiot, days no 13, in Bookaku!
Get Bookaku today! Before Bookaku, get you!
Bookaku!
You're listening to the daily source code with Mark Yoshimoto Nenkov.
Welcome back, my friends, to the show that never ends, coming to you from Gilford, somewhere deep in the bowels of the UK.
And the bowels are pretty deep here.
Yeah, guess what, it's me again, and I'm here at Adam's house, where something in the attic smells like corn chips and feet, and Adam is still unconscious.
You're listening to episode 5-8-2 of the Chacha.
Tell you what, let's start it all off with some really kick-ass shit from Kevin Reeves.
Now I'm on my way.
So many dusty roads have run down.
Switching for this place, without a chance of miles and face the trials.
No matter what it takes, gotta try.
Before I die, gotta fade.
The love I'm searching for, so leave it away.
The things that make me feel so lost in play.
Now I'm feeling I'm running out of time.
It's not going to work.
What is this?
You've never keep a damn.
Yeah, good boys, the gun recovers, gonna glued out on the land.
I saw the road ahead of my own.
I feel so handsome around, but all I've found were just sections born and new
I'm so tall
Oh, I'm so tall
It's now I know
I can't think it will with me when I go
Now I'm the rethink what I saw
I'll get my life up there in tensions
Now this is my journey for protection
Oh, I'm so handsome around, but all I've found were just sections born and new
I'm so tall
It's now I know
I can't think it will with me when I go
Now this is my journey for protection
Oh, I can't think it will with me when I go
Now I'm the rethink what I saw
I'll get my life up there in tensions
Now this is my journey for protection
Oh, I'm so handsome around, but all I've found were just sections born and new
I'm so handsome around, but all I've found were just sections born and new
Kevin Reeves with redemption, fuck yeah man, that's on rocks like a mother fucker
So hey, welcome to the daily source code, I'm Mark Yoshimoto Nemkoff
You know what, I'm declaring today, Bong hit Tuesday
I found some Adam's stash here at the manner and I'm a dude
This is some Primo Primo shit, hold on
Oh fuck, oh my god
That should make Willie Nelson blind, oh my god
I have no idea where he gets it from, but so today, yeah today is, I got to do another one hold on
Oh shit
Okay, so today is Bong hit Tuesday
And, oh fuck man, so if you're in your car, if you're on the subway, I don't care
Fucking, I pull out that Bong, I want everybody doing Bong hits right now
Even, yeah, okay
Oh, right, right, right, so Adam, right, right
So yeah, yeah, I was going through his underwear drawer
And it's all thongs, it is, it's all thongs
And thongs and bolo ties, I swear to god
So I'm going through Adam's underwear drawer
And I find his stash, this beautiful, beautiful stash of, well, I found that stash too
But we'll talk about that later
But I also found I swear to god, you got to see this, it's the most amazing thing
It's, basically, I found his show formula
This is one of the most highly guarded secrets in all of podcasting
The recipe for the daily source code that he kept hidden in his underwear drawer
Right underneath that turtle shape vibrator that was signed by Kurt Loader
I don't know if it was actual signature because the turtle face on the vibrator actually looks like Kurt Loader
Anyway, so this is the recipe for the daily source code
Item number one, play series of repetitive opening jingles in order to get those last 20 drags in on the blunt
Number two, for five minutes line about my internet connection in my new house
I'm be sure to give specific details on download and upload data rates
Number three, spend 10 minutes delivering soliloquy on geopolitical landscape
And partying opinions and expertise gained from years spent introducing the latest music video from CNC music factory
Number four, playback message from multi-lingual vampire from the EU
Number five, fantasize about girls would call into the show
Number six, play cold pod save song
Number seven, ruin cold pod save song with cowbell and or singing
Number eight, flick lighter, set man or on fire
Okay, yeah, I think this is all going to be useful shit
So, hold on let me ask Adam what do you think
Dude chill, okay chill, alright look you want you want to bang it
Dude, you're going to whip the duct tape come on, dude
Fuck hold on
Oh fuck, I think I set the cattle prod too high
Oh man, he's probably going to crap himself now, odd cheese
I thought that you said about piracy and the statistical information about the boss
It may be thick about the whole concept of being born to run
If I had an endless word to have phrasing, let tell the format
I truly wrap your legs around these velvet ribs and strap your hands across my inches
Is that what you had in mind when you mentioned that M's could stay
Well anyway, just some thoughts to ponder
Goodbye, Mr. Namca
Oh, and please still Adam, I put the victory set me on the medicine chest right over the Tylenol PM
Bro, I think pro grammar at your command is the melodic pro grammar program
Oh man, that is oh fuck, what the fuck is that in there?
Oh, it's like kitty litter
Oh shit
Oh my god, I think he's lacing his stuff with cat shit
Oh my god, oh, I don't care whatever it is man
Anyway, so
So I know Adam hasn't really talked about second life a whole lot lately
But you know, kind of got me involved in it and I think a lot of you too
And something that's actually happening in second life
CC Chapman sent me a press release his company crayon
They're this cutting edge marketing company and check this out. They're working with Coca-Cola
So let me read this press release Coca-Cola launches competition to design online
Virtual first Coke machine open competition invites in world second life residents and the public
To imagine a virtual vending machine with a limitless possibilities
Check this out check this out
Imagine a vending machine that dispenses entertainment adventure or happiness
A device that satisfies curiosities and fulfills virtual wishes
Coca-Cola is launching an open contest for second life residents and the general population
To design a virtual experience machine through its virtual thirst competition second life is a three-dimensional online digital world
That enables user residents to explore digital universe and blow lives, you know what second life is
So let me hold on
Uh, scan up
But simply we've invited the world to use the second life platform to design and prototype the ultimate Coke machine
Something that delivers an innovative engaging experience in second life as defined by its community of residents
Says Michael Donnelly director global marketing global interactive marketing Coca-Cola company
So for example, I guess it could play music from a jukebox or display fun animation in video
Or transform the user's experience and capabilities in some positive way
So that's pretty fucking cool
So you design this virtual vending machine right that can dispense
Um entertainment and Coke and whatever right I mean it's totally outside the box kind of thinking
And it's not about second life, right?
It's it's about imagination and the thing is you could submit apparently you could submit your submission
Man, that's it. I'm smoking is way too fucked up. You could submit your submission. Yeah, good job
So you could submit your prototype
Um, you know, either through audio a video or whatever
So it says right here go to virtualthirst.com
That's pretty fucking cool. Now
I don't know about you
But my my idea for the perfect Coke vending machine involves you know
I put in my dollar. I get a ice cold coke, you know chilled perfectly and I get a blowjob
Now, you know the machine doesn't have to give me a blowjob
I mean there could you know be a someone there hopefully a pretty young girl
I
I'm not picky though if I'm getting a blowjob for a box and you know
Who am I to pick and choose but that's kind of the concept so you could design your coke vending machine
If you want your coke vending machine to you know
Dispense coke and play music and and spread sunshine and happiness across the globe
Then you're kind of fucked in the head, but no, no, you know what I'm saying
Then it's it's a great idea. It's a grand idea
You know, I'm definitely going to enter my a blowjob coke machine prototype though
So I way I can go in second life when they prototype the thing and I can stand there with my avatar and get blown in drink of virtual coke
I think that'd be fucking awesome. That sounds like Saturday afternoon to me
And I'm doing this my online avatar and second life
Doesn't have a dick
Yeah, because barely you have to buy a fucking cock for your online avatar
There are shops in second life. I swear to God. I didn't know this right and
True story when Brittany Mason was showing me around the town of Shadow Falls what when they built the town of Shadow Falls
We did that whole thing
She was showing me a bunch of other places in second life and I was I was really like amazed by
How creative people got with their buildings and their little islands and stuff
And she took me as a place and it was actually a pretty big ad agency that had a office in second life
And so I was running around naked. I just I hit the button that said take my clothes
I'm running around naked and you know and she said you got no dick
And I was like, oh check that out. She's like, I'll buy you a dick
And I felt kind of weird. I felt a little weird having a strange online woman buy me a penis
I don't know maybe something I just have to get over
But I know one way to make my inhibitions go away hold on
That's definitely catch it. Oh fuck
Common strip
Is a club called the man bar and eighty two great suffix street in London
WWE dot man bar dot info
They do have a good two for one decorate night on Tuesday
But I do not want to meet Adam's hair
Anyway, Markio Shomodonemka fuck you
I have to go now and pop a hemorrhoid
Not one of my own, but this none of your business
Common strip
Hey Mark, I've got some feedback for you
When you started talking about the RIA it really got my blood boiling
Because here's the deal
The RIA can win and moan all the wants
But reality is it and the companies represents our scared shitless
They are falling way behind as they stick to their old models of production and distribution
Sort of like how Adam's remote control sticks to his inner thigh
I think you understand me
Point is before the internet sharing was negligible
And even then it's still encouraged people to go to concerts and buy merchandise
Of course this is still happening
But back then big labels had the power to produce very few acts and promote them excessively
Because we only had so many ways of accessing media
In fact, they would sign good artists and then bury them in the vaults
In order to protect their big cash running acts
This model is fucking dying
The internet has retribulized the world
And people are getting sick and tired of the same shit on the radio
And on the Rax and ATMP
Or whatever other shitty records store this, drop it
The labels are convinced that they have to keep a few huge acts and earn all their cash from them
And as since they are creating the piracy that they claim is hurting them
By over saturating us, the listeners
I mean, do we really need another Britney Spears album?
We have no choice but to pirate
If the labels would pull their heads out of their asses
And promote a wide variety of good artists
It would dilute musical tastes across the board
This would make piracy irrelevant
Because the labels would need the social aspect of the internet
To get the word out on their artists
This is what the positive music network is doing
And if the labels don't get their shit together
They're going to get their asses kicked
And I for one would love to see that
Oh, and by the way, I hope you remember to poke some holes in the closet
Or something so that Adam can breathe
Take care
Hold on, hold on
Fuck you
Travis, thank you
Travis Martin
With that comment, thanks Travis
And thank you for reminding me to actually throw some holes in the door here
You gotta hope it's not too late
Anyway, you know what Travis, you have a really good point
The record companies, I've friend to work in the music business
Over the last five years
So many people who work at record companies
You know, we're talking suits and our guys
Whoever have lost their fucking jobs
Because these record companies are failing to make money
And they blame it all on piracy
But one of the things that has always struck me as being fucking ironic
Is that throughout the history of maybe the last what?
20, 30 years
The record industry
Has spent a fortune
Baddling piracy
Whether it's a battling real-to-real tape
Or cassette
Or dat
When dat recorders came out
Which was the first actual consumer model
Digital audio recording medium
When dat recorders came out
The record companies
The RAA
Went fucking insane
Spending a fortune
And having hearings
So that they could enforce
What was I think was what was it called at the time
DCMS or whatever digital copy management system
So you could not actually hook up a CD player
The optical output of a CD player to a
Consumer level dat machine
And make a perfect digital copy
They spend millions of dollars
We'll fuck do you think those millions of dollars came from
That's right
They came from artist royalties
So instead of taking the money
That they were making from the artists
And putting it back
Into the business
To invest in new artists
Or even fucking pay their artist what they're actually worth
They took this money
And they've been doing this
They took this money to fight piracy
But they've done the same thing with cassettes
With CD recorders with anything
I mean you look at the history
They've spent a fortune on this
And then every few years or so
Another medium comes out
Another way to copy music comes out
And then they spend another fortune going to fight that
That's just the way it has been
Since the fucking invention of any sort of home recording
Right
And you know who's fault this fucking is
I'll tell you
It's the fucking lawyers
Because some lawyer basically says
Hey, you know what we need to fight this
And they find a way that their firm
Can make millions of dollars
And I'll tell you why that's not bullshit
Going back like five years
Actually more than that
Going back a few years
I had a literary manager here in Hollywood
His name is Daniel Alter
And Daniel told me the story one day that his lawyer
Was the same lawyer who handles Metallica
And basically the lawyer went to Metallica one day
With this whole story about what was going on
With this company called Napster
And the lawyer said to Metallica, hey look what's going on
I think we have a way here that we can make millions of dollars
That is exactly what happened
I am not fucking making this up
The idea to sue Napster was not Metallica
It was their fucking lawyers idea
Oh shit hold on serious 102 listeners
You're going to have to go to dailysourceco.podshow.com
To download the rest of the podcast
And hear me say fuck a bunch more times
Catch you later
Okay
So yeah, the whole thing
Was cooked up by a fucking lawyer
And I'm sure it's the same thing
At the record companies
With how the RAAA manages to
You know spend their fucking money
Badling piracy
Now
Granted
If you go to a record company
A lot of times a lot of the suits there
Are lawyers
Because they come up in the entertainment ranks
They know the business
They know the finances blah blah bullshit
Whatever
A lot of the suits at any major record company
The major suits
We're talking the guys who run the fucking business
They're all fucking lawyers
I'll tell you what with the exception
Of this fucking douchebag
That runs the universal music group
This fucking Doug Morris guy
Now remember this is the guy that called
All iPod users
Pirate
And we said all iPods
Are full of pirated music
You know that Doug Morris guy
Doug
Doug Morris
You music.com
That Doug Morris guy
Who I think is the biggest fucking scumbag
In the music industry
Doug Morris
If you can hear me
Fucking blow me you fucking piece of shit
You know what
I swear to God
It's like
The fucking bullshit
That the universal music group has perpetrated
On their artists
Their listeners
Is a fucking sin
And here's a guy who started his fucking career as a songwriter
And this guy doesn't give a fuck about the artist on his label
Again, here's a fucking company
That is spending countless millions of dollars
Fucking fighting piracy
Right?
You know they're trying to eliminate all their videos
Off YouTube and all that
I mean come on
Do you honestly think that anybody
Is fucking copying the audio
From the video on YouTube
And listening to it on their MP3 player
I mean a video
A music video
They're all created as a fucking commercial for the song
Right?
Remember MTV when they used to fucking play videos
What do you think all that content was?
This is freebie shit
MTV was not paying
To fucking play these videos
So in the same way
It's like how is how is YouTube
Showing these videos
Anything other than a
You know a way to market this shit
That otherwise people would never see it
What the fuck is the difference?
I don't get it
Okay, maybe I'm missing something
Maybe I'm fucking taking too many bong hits
And I just don't fucking get it
But anyway
And the other thing Travis, I think you totally nailed
Is that
You have these record companies
And same thing with the movie industry
Or the book industry or whatever
They rely on a blockbuster release
To fucking pay for everything else on their slate
That doesn't do so well
And when you get into that kind of mentality
Where you rely on the blockbuster
Then you are going to go after it
The easy fucking sell bullshit
And you're eventually going to say
You know what?
It makes more sense
To fucking promote
You know 10 Britney Spears clones
That we know all
You know sell a few hundred thousand units
Then trying to promote new artists
That may only sell 30, 40, 50,000 units
Their first time out
You know nobody wants to develop a new artist anymore
In the same way that media
A television, especially
Doesn't want to give a television show
Any sort of chance to build an audience
If you don't fucking build an audience right away
You're gone
And that is exactly
The kind of fucking mentality
That is going to fuck the record industry
Right in the ass
Unless they're into that kind of thing
And then
You're regardless
The mentality of the record industry
Has always been to protect
What they fucking currently have
And not evolve
Which is why they're fucking dying
Which is why the record industry
Is fucking hemorrhaging right now
And they sit around
And they have no fucking idea
What to do?
It's it's sad and pathetic
So here we go
Record industry
I'm going to tell you what to do
First thing you do
It's called a PCH comment line
At 1-800-875-099-5
And I'll set your shit straight
Because the new methods of distribution over the internet
Are slaying the record companies
And what you're going to see is that
As record companies
Have fewer
Resources for distribution
They're going to rely on
Basically they're the top few distribution outlets they have
And of course
You know what scares the fuck out of me
Is the number one distribution outlet for music in the United States
The number one distributor of music
Wal-Mart
Conservative fucking Wal-Mart
Okay Wal-Mart who basically says
Oh no we want to distribute that because it's
It's too controversial
Okay
So Wal-Mart
Sounds more records than anybody else in the United States
So what you're going to see are fewer choices on the racks
And as a result
The record industry is going to have to rely on
More and more blockbuster hits
And when they don't have them
Because their audiences are being drawn away
By more and more choices
Guess what's going to fucking happen
So I feel like Nikita Kruzchev banging my fucking shoe on the podium
You know we will fucking bury you
But guess what record companies
RIA
We're going to bury your mother fucking asses
And it's going to be fun to watch
Hey questions comments
Let me know
Send me an email
At where is Adam Curry at gmail.com
Or you can send one to Adam Curry's gay
At gmail.com
Mark Yosin Mode and NMK
Well my god
I was being a daily source code
Look now
I thought the point of this whole Adam going away
Saying was to reduce the almost factor on the DSC
Well anyway
I guess he'll do
Let's go on on man
Then that is what I'm going to do
Let me show you
Nice little surprise
Kind of the DSC this morning
And find you co hosting at door
Substitute hosting at home
Anyway
Calling in regards to your RIA
Major record label
Inquiry
Pun intended of course
Anyway
It seems to me like
Although we end up talking about this in great detail
These should seem to be becoming
More and more muddy
As time goes on
And here's a deal
As you know
Because you want to create this for the show
Talking about
Major record labels with me not so long ago
Or some major record labels are screwed anyway
Anyway
It seems like there are two components of this
The date although they are not defined
One is a legalistic component
The second is a moralistic component
And more realistic component comes from
The legalistic end
That is to say that
This technique is technically illegal
To quote unquote pirate music
However
And the RIAs
Justifications seem to come from
While this is illegal
Therefore we have the right to do
X, Y, and Z
They're being resisted
However because of the moralistic end
Which comes from the legalistic end
Although it is technically illegal
It is due in part to the lobbying
Of the government
We are a double way
These people have much more leverage money
And power
Than the other side
Being the end user
The consumer
New and me and all the other cool people
Actually pay for music
And
Dan
Where'd you go?
Dan Patterson cut off there
I don't know
I'm thinking he might have been silenced
By the RIA
He knew too much
They had to keep him quiet
Dan Patterson
Are you on the bonnet Tuesday?
On the daily cold sore
Yeah
And
Oh we got another comment
Hold on
Similar to Adam Roger here
I was going to be in the Guilford
I was wandering by the
Curry Cottage
And I was wondering if I could stop
In for a
Jolly Good Rogering today
Anyway
Goodbye
Fuck I don't have Roger Smalls
Is a jingle
Here I can't find it on Adam's
Laptop
Hold on
No
I can't find it
So I don't know
I don't even remember how
How's it go?
Roger Smalls
You really creepy guy
You want to lick Adam's balls
I don't know
Something like that
What I did find on this laptop
Oh my god
There is so much porn on here
I can't but
Panda
There are pandas fucking
That's the kind of shitties got here
And it's
Hold on
Oh no
Haha
My bad
Those aren't pandas
That's actually
Ed Asner fucking Rosie O'Donnell
Hey Mike
How's it going
In Adam's attic there
Causing too much trouble
Inviting the Guils around
I hope
Anyway
Jeff
Yeah
Can you cue the music?
Moving forward
Going on into
Everyone
besides
It's coming
I'm for assault
To see
Smith World
Biggest clinical
Your now
Come with me
Good morning
Dominive
Children
feminine
Yes
Good morning
You can't
You're so cute
Dominive
Gonzard
How would tic-d motorcycle
Did you sit on it?
He just he
getting any of the things and you just can't pump it out, oh it's crazy. Anyway this is
Derek from Sydney Australia and if you remember that jingle from last year that's the
potty for cancer jingle and you know we're getting excited again because May is when we're
having the world's biggest morning tea. What it is is we're raising money for cancer and it's
it's been, it's been affected by this lately and it's just crazy that like people should
be able to get on with their lives and do pot casting and anything they want with having to
bother with some crazy disease so we're donating money to cure it basically and well not
basically we're going to cure it it's going to be great the day we see it on the front page
on the newspaper but at the moment we're just donating money for the research so you can donate
money by going to potty for cancer.com or you can you know get some out of it as well if that's
enough for you by buying a limited edition mug or stine from my cafe press store which there's
links on potty for cancer.com and they're really limited the ones that were available last year
can't get him anymore this year 2007 mugs only get him this year and of course all the profits
from their sales are donated to the cause then on the 24th of May the official day for the world's
biggest morning tea you can join me on Skype and we can have a massive Skype session as we
did last year it was great and we can just have a morning tea and a matter where you are in the world
it's going to be morning here Australia but it might be like midnight where you are so it can
be exciting have teens, scones and stuff like that you know some big ease we're really exciting so
check out potty for cancer.com and try not to get too addicted to this song. Catch you later
the pride of Sydney Australia Derek J. Steen it's also the host of a show called the
pot show about nothing which is at nothingpot show.blockspot.com or the pot show about nothing
pot show.com so yeah potty for cancer definitely check that out thank you Derek really appreciate
you sending that in Derek's a great guy Derek really is a fucking amazing dude and he's doing
some really cool shit in Australia. Hey real quick before we go on to talk about one last thing
do you know what a stumble squad is? I learned this from Chris Penn from the Financial Aid podcast
Chris Penn evil genius Chris Penn and I don't know if you've hooked up with stumble upon
at stumble upon.com it's a really cool way to actually find new websites you kind of put this thing
in a toolbar of your browser and you click on it it just kind of randomly kicks out a website based
upon you know your preferences the things that you like so if you click that you like
books or movies or fisting boom it'll click out a website based upon like something that you're
interested in and you know basically you give it thumbs up thumbs down whatever or give it a review
you know that kind of thing but it's a really it's an amazing marketing tool as well because what
you do is if you are inclined to right you get a bunch of friends together and you help each other out
like if somebody says hey check out my page and give it a thumbs up then you know apparently the more
thumbs up response is something gets the more frequently it's delivered to anybody who clicks on
the stumble upon button in their toolbar so check it out stumble upon.com and I was thinking you
don't be amazing we should create a big stumble squad and all help each other out promoting
you know our shows or stuff or anything crazy you're doing on the web so I don't know
shoot me an email fuck maybe I'm just some kind of crazy optimist maybe maybe it's the shit in
Adam's Bung I swear to God this stuff is amazing hold on one more
fuck oh so I'll tell you what let's get out of here with a song and nothing could be more
appropriate on Bung hit Tuesday then a little Lewis Taylor somewhere right now Andrew Grummit's going
fuck yeah courtesy of our friends over at Hacktone Records from the album of the same name
hey are you having fun how you've made a mess like this just don't know did I crumple
who you start into baby and I won't think I'll have a recovery now
Who you and when you're storming I get so clever Don't ask me how
Who you and when you're storming I get so clever
I became so nice with you I wait for part two
Better get just one you can before I get wise
Go you and make me come to be a nice
Who you and when you're storming I get so clever Don't ask me how
Who you and when you're storming I get so clever