This is the first time I've ever seen a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever
seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a film that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that you've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that you've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that I've ever seen in a movie that
It's not something that you just do something on.
It's not a big track, right?
It has series of tools.
It's a joke.
Time to love jokes.
I just the other day got in an era that was set by my staff.
The 10 or 5 in one in the fight. I got it yesterday.
Time to love jokes.
You're so amazing.
Because you got time to love with all these things.
Going on the era and commercially.
I think that's it.
Absolutely essential.
This is an interpretation of my streaming.
You can go on the other side of that.
The chase.
The fiber optic, the network shows.
I don't have to have that kind of speed.
I don't think anyone here is to find one.
That control of the is.
It's not a big track.
I think there's a series of tools.
And here we have this one situation.
The channel is streaming.
I can't.
Let's take it on.
I think it's absolutely essential.
And the center of whether you realize that you're asking for regulation.
But for massively invading this world of the internet.
It's determined how.
Yes sir.
I'm sorry.
Not to decide.
But when we take the tip of the end.
A fiber optic.
It's really.
Medicaid that.
Anyone who wants to use it.
This system.
For massive.
More people think it's over.
Commercial purposes.
Those tools can be killed.
Time for that chose.
The internet is not something to do.
Why did we do that?
Why?
And enormous tools.
That's the series of tools.
Massive tools.
It really is.
The internet consumed in my life.
Because it got tangled up alone.
We say it going on there.
I'm actually.
The world has turned against this.
It didn't be wrong.
Personal.
And that.
The world has turned against this.
It didn't be wrong.
Personal.
The world has turned against this.
It didn't be wrong.
Personal.
That.
You.
I'm perfect for a Monday.
Perfect.
To bring back a series of tools.
DJ Ted's techno tubes.
Coming to you on the daily source code episode number 605.
Hey, what's going on here.
I'm still at the curry man.
I should be in San Francisco.
New York.
Or Austin.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm here.
And I should explain why.
First of all, did you hear that opening?
This is something I.
It's called Let Them Sing It For You.
I don't know.
You've ever seen this.
I got an email from.
Yeah.
Robby Williams, which is R.W.
Robby Williams at Google email.com.
Yeah.
I'm sure that's.
I'm sure that's someone's really email address.
And essentially you get a little player and you can just type in words.
It goes out and finds portions of songs or songs that let's see if a series of tubes work.
If you put that in.
Hold on.
It really helps if you read along with at home.
Let's see if I can do comics, strip, blogger.
It doesn't of course have songs for everything.
Let me see if this works.
Okay.
All right.
That just sucks.
When I was a boy, my mom was drunk.
She used to kick my ass.
It was probably knowing so much like wish.
So maybe that's why I treat folks, especially women a little harsh.
You were the one that was drunk.
That's why she kicked your ass.
How about you're the most pompous self-centered.
Full of him, Saul.
As whole.
Oh my God.
Deep down inside, Johnny.
There is something about you, we love.
Really?
Okay.
So we dig your sorry, Saul.
What?
That's why we love playing bone.
And of course we all love prizes.
Who doesn't?
So find out who wins.
And who gets the backhand, Johnny Todd.
I'm show four with us, the rumor girls.
Don't touch him.
Johnny.
What are you laughing for?
Bone.
Don't touch him.
Thing is off the hook.
It's just out of control with a number of people downloading listening to this game show
where you can win a fabulous Nokia N 800 tablet.
Internet tablet.
Tablet internet tablet. Karen and Carla. Is it Karen and Carla? Yeah, Karen I think it is. Karen and Carla from Rumagirls
Yeah, that's right. They're on episode number four bone check it out bone dot podshow dot com. So
Let me take it back to
Friday word came in a pay attention people to the east to the east of me now
Podshow is coming to Germany in fact. I'm coming to Germany tomorrow
I'll love the the whole idea is to fly the delta Sierra to my own aircraft to I think the meeting is in
Darmsh dot so if I were to fly commercial
Which is very well could happen depending on the weather tomorrow although today even would be pretty much flyable
We got ceilings of 3000 feet so no problems little bit of rain. That's just liquid sunshine
Normally I'd fly to Frankfurt now I can go direct to a small airfield
Not relatively small airfield within the same zone of right near Darmsh dot and
We got some meetings going on and I need some help. I need to now I've got a couple guys who are on the
On the network who already are in Germany
But if if you've got some some ideas about what could be done in different regions of Germany mind you
Is the big ass country compared to the little island we're sitting on here
Drop me an email at him at podshow.com
So that's that's why I didn't go to the I media conference because word came in that we're taking over
We're coming in we're coming into Germany and I have to admit to you
I know frightfully little about what's going on in Germany in general. I mean of course
I know lots of podcasters
Lots of shows I have some idea of the marketplace we've been in touch certainly when it comes to the pods
If music network we've had some great conversations some great back and forth discussion
But I mean is there is there a certain
Social network that that is big in Germany is the a B-bo here in the UK what's being used in Germany?
I don't know yeah, I mean everyone has a story and everyone will point to something
But it's kind of hard to figure out exactly
You know
Who's right or just getting enough information in general because if you look at iTunes
At the podcast chart for the German store
Yeah, it's like it doesn't really corroborate with the information
I'm getting about what the really popular shows are which of course would
All right kind of make sense
So please if you got any good intel you want to send my way I do it today
Those of you in the US and even on the on the European side of Laplandia time I'm not leaving before tomorrow afternoon
I'm gonna take it nice and easy and then when's they I'll fly back and I'll be back here
So and then from the I don't know what I'm gonna do I might be I might go to San Francisco next week
There's a lot of stuff happening in the in the UK crash pad office. It's just busy man and on top of all that today is day four
Of AC completely smoke free
Hate and people's like around me and so every like me person to stop smoking
Could appreciate it
It's probably not gonna be easy
I'll be worth it. Also your shows and the last two shows have been fine
You're on the ball too far out. I'll probably prefer do you think has been more with it?
I've been watching this wicked. I'll keep it up. Good luck. Bye
All right, Ben thanks. Well, you know what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna just say just to keep track. I think this counting thing does help me in many ways like we track episodes
So we're now 605 why don't we just say?
That ever since show 600 I've been smoke free not entirely right me on and instead of counting days let's just count
The number of episode starting at 600
It's kind of sad to hear that you think this show was it been sounding better. I don't know if I don't know that makes any difference whatsoever
But I've been getting through. I've been getting by and then I feel that the thing to do is just keep busy
If I sit down and just like do something like hang out and listen to something
becomes very difficult then that's the only time where I start thinking
Oh, man, yeah, like something then I usually jump up and do something else like what I do
Saturday
Oh, man, I flew to Bembridge
Bembridge is on the Isle of White a solo flight mind. You was still at a good win 2025 knots
It's about about 30 miles an hour
I must end that right and yeah, and it's really cool because you go down to the south of the south of of the country in fact
You're about to fall off so you you fly it over the over the ocean and then just a little off to the right
Is the Isle of White and there's two airfields and this the Bembridge you literally come in
I think the the cliff is probably about a hundred feet far maybe it's 70
Well, let's just say a hundred feet high from the water and you're literally coming in over this cliff
Before it's almost like landing on an aircraft carrier to be honest with the wind blasting from the side
Of course because only one one runway and this thing it has like it's like a dip it has an elevation
It kind of ramps up from both sides so when you land you want to kind of you know pay attention to
Landing somewhere a little bit before the middle of the runway because then once you've landed the runway, you know ramps up
So that could get kind of tricky
Just getting your wheels on the ground, but it was great, man. I felt really energized
Had a cup of coffee there. There was no one flying because it was too windy and then I I hoofed it back
Here's a cool thing I gave
So I bought a VHF radio
So you can you could use that as a backup in place of an electrical emergency
I got to get one for Patricia for full time, but I gave it to her and she and just put it downstairs on the squelch
And I put it on frequency one two three decimal four
Five zero which is pretty much the standard frequency when pilots want to talk to each other in the air
You know, it's like I want to three for five and everyone knows you can switch over there. It's not by any means private
But I was flying over the over the manner and
And I tried it out and I put it on the second second comb box and I called that asshole one to asshole two
And within like four seconds production of flight asshole two to asshole one
It was just it was fun, man. It was totally useless, but it was fun to just you know
She was waving and and
She could hear me. I mean she could communicate with me all the way back to home base
Of course, I was paying attention to air traffic control on like the other frequency at the same time. It was kind of busy
So we didn't have a long conversation, but it works. I got to get her own radio
So whenever I'm coming home, I can just say that I'm on my way and
Get dinner ready to here
I'm more about my non-smoking and that would let up to it
Hey, Adam. This is Dean. I'm down here in Houston, Texas and I was the daily source code every day and I love it
And I was listening to
The first they show I forget what number it is, but
Hey, please don't let some guy look in at your palm decide your future that's all bullshit
Yes, you can quit smoking. Yes. You should exercise. Yes. You should eat a healthy diet, but
Don't base your life off some guy looking at your palm and doing what's called a cold reading
on you and let it influence you in what you think you're doing
Who's talking to you from the great beyond
What's all bullshit just eat healthy quit smoking kicks and exercise and keep kicking up the daily source code
I love it. Thank you very much. Goodbye. All right, man. You know
Basically it's cold reading or not. He got me to do the exit those exact same things
I've already been eaten healthy but today. Yes. I pulled out the rowing machine
I know that some of the excess boxes have been moved out of the house still from the move and I sat down when I rode
I rode that sucker as hard as I could
email from Maurice
Remember he did the
Podsafe sack
Back with episode number two. Let's see how hard it is today
Hey, and I'm so here's part two that Podsafe sack
Okay, so he thought it was a little bit too easy last time make it hard and fix that of course
And I'm glad jumplet get on this. This hit that's great to have him back on the scene as well. All right
Although I must admit that my production work doesn't really has the flashes like
But anyway, yeah, I'll try to make the best of it. So why is it that all the Podsafe production
Coming from the Netherlands. I love the one that young politically recently and I think he'll be coming up with more and and I think we're just gonna
Forge ahead with this stuff and say hey, it's all under the
Under the banner of education because we need to know about these songs our children need to learn for the future
Oh
Planet of women do waking up the neighborhood
Anyway, I think you took number two
That's uh, thank god. Jones. So they still think it's too easy. We'll get an harder. Let's go to clip number three
All right, let's go to the answer then this was clip number one
Planet of yeah
This I need to reward myself
Wow
So onto the next clip this was the number two
Got that new york
Thank you Jones with first date. Oh, yeah, and I still can remember
Physically today. I first heard his song
I thought it was the
See you're something like that. I'm not sure
I'm a breacher. Yeah, I'm breacher
There was a last problem in the memories. Let's go on to the third answer. Okay, third team
Oh
Yeah, see the sun that we'll know black lab from the their Russia-jard days
Oh, those days
Oh, so it was so long ago the three answers and you didn't find it too easy
I'd like to like the second episode of the pot safe second you can go over to www.potsafesec.com
And subscribe to the show for a non-admvision of it and for all the pockets out there
You can use it in your podcasts about so thanks again
My name is Maurice and I'm signing off
So you know, I'm thinking about doing all these
mashups and the hit tests and and what the fuck am I worried about? I look at the Hillary Clinton dot com
And right there on the page. This is amazing
Choose our campaign song
Listen to the following nine songs and choose your favorite or if you have your own suggestion
Write in a song an artist in the space provided
I cannot imagine
That the rights have been cleared to put these songs up to be played in their entirety now
You may not be able to download them. In fact, let me just see if I can view so I was a flash player doesn't mean we can't
Can't get it done hold on. I mean they got you two in here
We've got a
City of blinding lights suddenly I see
I'm a believer get ready temptations ready to run the Dixie chicks rock this country
Should I attend beautiful day that you're here now in its entirety?
And right here right now Jesus Jones and I'll take you there the staple singers
Which I think every single one of them sucks as a campaign song
You should go check that out Hillary Clinton dot com. We'll put a link in the show notes
So you know and you know exactly what's going on here. What's happening is all the the record company
I presume record companies maybe you twos down put
Yeah, the record company owns all these rights and they're just like oh, yeah, please play it over and over make it the campaign song totally totally bogus
Maybe this should just go sue Hillary Clinton. I think it would I think that would be just if not
Long live the hit test and the mashups
on May 29 unwind with Angie B will present an artist spotlight on love spirals and love spirals
a lot of it has to do with
Time that was where I was in the 90s with with the low spoused downs and and those spouses were I am
Now and with Angie hold different person band founder and my musical partner Ryan Lomb
joins me in the studio to discuss the band 16 year history during one of the most
Revolutionary periods in music history and I just amazed like wow you could get all the songs on your computer
And you can like move the tracks around is blew my mind how many knew what I wanted to do
I wanted to like produce in the studio. I just have didn't have access to that technology now
Anyway, can buy an apple and have garage band built in plus the world debut of a brand new track from upcoming third album
Check it out and unwind.podshow dot com the cool thing is unwind is there
Oh my go is it unwind is sponsored by a Tylenol PM and I've been looking for great testimonials
And finally Robin got his uh his stable of divas together to come up with something for me
Hey Adam it's Julie from the diva cast and I'm here hi Adam
World timing in but I hear you talking about Tylenol PM and I wanted to tell you about my story
I've always used Tylenol PM and I love it
And I did there's a few reasons but my latest story I wanted to tell you about is I was in the yard the other day
Worked in the yard finally it's getting pretty down here and got some weeding done and I went to bed and my back was killing me
Took a hot shower that didn't help got in bed and took a couple of Tylenol PM and got the best night's sleep
Now here's a catch being a mom. I have three children and my son my youngest had a bad dream and I
woke up in the middle of the night and got him settled down and putting back to bed and I know with sleep aids
That's a big fear being a mom that if you take something you're not going to be able to wake up for your children
Right, and that's why I like Tylenol PM
Because I was able to wake up. I was very alert. I wasn't out of it at all and then the next morning when I woke up
I wasn't fuzzy or some of that like you might get with cold medicine or some of your sleep aids
Right, you were still functional. I was functional and I was clear so
I'm a believer and I think more moms out there need to know about it because the divots know about it
And it's definitely a divadue a divadue definitely. That's a divadue. Hey, you know that's interesting
I hadn't thought about that but I it makes of course total sense that that moms would love to have something to help them get to sleep or leave any
Any aches pains, but they still want to be able to wake up should there be a reason for it
Oh, that's why it's a divadue. You know
Robin who who produces the diva cast
He left the recording running and he came up with some more interesting divadue. She might want to listen into
So this is a voyeuristic list. Yeah, I'm serious. Check out what just sucks
Yeah, that would be that go well. That would be underwear that is regular with that's not thongs
You're gonna get so much trouble Robin. Don't work for Amy
Really
If you're crack anyway, no matter what my dog and
But, but is made wrong then it is
Maybe you need to go for an underwear fitting because you go white. It's not supposed to go be by no in my Dap
In mind don't either okay, I'm always having all my life
problem
No
Alright, this enough of them.
And more women clutch.
You know, I listen to the showgirls, and they really went overboard now.
And the most recent episode, talking about Adam moments.
I was pretty frightening.
I finally, Angie B has mastered up the time or courage,
or maybe a combination there of to send me an audio comment.
Hey, Adam, it's Angie.
So, we girls got to talking about you on showgirls this week.
I just thought I should mess up now, you know, you'll hear it eventually.
But I don't know, I somehow started getting really mushy and reflecting on just how wonderful you've been for me and my career and how great pod show has been.
It's been awesome working with you guys on and wind.
I've received so much support.
And the listeners are really into the show, and it's just been a really good experience for me.
I just wanted to thank you.
Sorry, I missed your 600th.
I really meant to send you some audio feedback.
But anyways, we all kind of shared our Adam moments.
Only four of the showgirls were in this week,
but we had special guests Natalie Del Conti,
and she shared her Adam moment as well.
Oh, I didn't hear that.
It's like warning.
We went off on kind of a crazy tangent of naughty words
that were found on the urban dictionary.
So, I don't know.
I think you'll get a kick out of that.
Anyways, great to talk to you as always Adam.
Thank you.
I'll check them out, showgirls.potshow.com.
Art from Mashup Towns been sending it in again.
He's back on the beat for short.
DJ Peking, warning, rush where it's at.
It's a whole bunch of turns.
It's a matter of distance.
The president came back.
It's like you told us.
Man, man, you're open and ready to open.
It's like you're ready to get away.
It's like a church.
It's like me.
Look at me, that is
Did you remember that I feel like you're telling
God, I should believe that you better not cross
It's the God, poor, poor, poor
That you'll endanger us, you'll tell us
That you'll encourage us, you'll take
God, I shouldn't refame for sure
God, I'm the mere victim of the poor
That you'll encourage us, you'llæ€
Don't Anfangour, it's the god and
That you'll encourage us, you'll
What you buy, not stop
You're leading in above you
What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up
What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what
I said it's no good, I said it's no good
I said it's no good
All right, let's go.
I never saw it.
Dr. Art from mashuptown.com definitely enters the stable of the Savon.
Savon specials.
Okay, it's time for our Savon from our series of the Circle of Savon.
I'm the Sultan of Savon.
Savon.
I think I'm going to be able to get at least one Savon in episode.
There's a fast forward button on that forward for a reason.
And I hope to be able to talk to Savon every single day, Savon.
And by the way, I want you to know that this format change doesn't mean that I don't
want to make a picture by the southern of Savon Savon Savon Savon Savon.
Mashup by DJ Peaking from down under you heard Green Day's warning versus Bex
Where's it at versus Big Audio Dynamite's Rush?
Man, I love that stuff.
Link, of course, at DailySourceco.com.
Let's get from the boat ridginspotcast.com, which I hosted the pod show.
And I keep having a problem over and over and over again.
When I try to log in to my page to upload another show or work on my profile or whatever,
I enter my ID and my password and it sends me back to another login page.
Try to get in, it sends me back to another login page.
I send air message to your tech support.
They seem to fix it and it will us another month or so and then it happens again.
Did you find out from your guys down there, what the problem and fix it?
Once and for all, that's it.
I do.
It may be the decaf.
Folders would be better for you.
I'm not quite sure what's going on with that, but shit does happen.
And part of what we're doing now is trying to understand exactly what you do and how you use
pod show programming and the network and the pod save music network.
And then give us some answers to some simple questions help us suck less.
I understand if the login doesn't work, we got to fix that.
I'll take care of that personally, I promise.
Probably just one server in the cluster going, hey, why are you know?
I've got all that techy experience.
I'll fix it for you.
Help us suck less help us suck less.
Go to suckless.potjo.com
I want to tell you something, okay?
And I want to leave a message for you right now.
Because again, it's getting 30 here and you're going to win day.
And once again, I'm in an ass of myself trying to get to a phone to call you a specific time.
Where are you?
I called you 20 minutes ago and you never called me back.
When the time comes for me to make the phone call, I stop.
Where are I'm doing?
And I go when I make that phone.
You told me I did it that you were going to pick me up at 11.
It's like, I would have made other plans.
I wouldn't have that phone turn down.
It was the third time recently that you promised to do something to me dad.
I'm completely freaked out on me.
I didn't know something, okay?
I'm tired of playing this game with you.
I understand you have to work in your busy, but I'm your daughter.
When you promise me something, something is simple.
I'm going to pick me up when you say you're going to pick me up.
And you do it.
I am being in a plane.
And I'm going to come out there for the day.
And I'm going to straighten your ass out.
When I see you, you want to stand up.
I'm so not fucking standing here in the middle of the night on the sidewalk.
Like some crazy homeless person.
I have the point where the decent man has a human being.
I don't give a damn that you're 12 years old or 11 years old.
But you're trying your father.
There's a father standing in the ass.
Who doesn't care about what you do.
I'm right.
I'm getting sick of these children.
They're all in trouble.
And I'm like, they're probably one of these people.
You are really comfortable.
Just have to support to do what you have.
And I'm very ironed.
You're telling me you've got a real little stone of fire on me.
Oh, my God.
I'm not fucking fucking hot.
I'm not hot.
You better be standing out the day.
There's enough money to pay for this guy.
I know.
Really make sure you get it.
I'm a choreographer.
Come on.
You fucking better be wearing men's clothing.
Oh, that's Matt from the Daven match show at DavenMatch Show.com.
It'll make stuff like Baldwin with Christina's rant.
I went pretty well together, I think.
I don't know.
I think they have a career possibly.
All right.
This song I'll mess up my kid in yours for sure.
Of course, it's from the podcast and music network.
So do enjoy safely.
I was sitting at home the other day.
Here in hand, pizza on the way.
The turner, classic room.
It's not turner, huge.
First of all, even Michael came.
We're driving Diane, Canada and St.
But after the killer, I saw the two of him smooch.
I haven't felt so weird since I was young.
I'm not sure, but I think there might have been children.
I didn't understand.
They both were men.
Men of voice in my head said, yeah, so what?
And I know his Chris had a real nice button.
I knew I was never going to be the same again.
Well, I walked straight in narrow.
But now it's a little bent.
I used to be full head or roll.
I wonder where that went.
After quit being a scout master.
And I have to leave my wife.
Two guys kissing ruin my life.
I should my head not change the channel.
Saw some guy in a cap of flannel singing.
He was a lumberjack and he was okay.
But he was so good.
I kept on surfing.
Got broke back.
Mountain Rocky Horn.
The bird cage and I stopped counting when I got to gravel.
And the whole damn network was gay.
I sat in that square with the funniest feeling.
I figured I'd need some sexual healing.
But that was my Marvin Gaye on my aching head.
I'd have sworn I was straight to I saw that kissing.
But it showed me something.
But I had been missing.
I'd ruled out half of humanity.
Sharing my bed.
The techniques all look normal.
But the details are kind of weird.
Doesn't much cash act like Velcro.
When it runs into a beard.
Agonized and re-affraised.
As caused me endless strife.
Two guys kissing ruin my life.
The internet and magazines and every film and book.
This slashy stuff is all I'm seeing.
Everywhere I look.
Went football players watching each other.
It seems more intense.
And all that hairy, drag-o-stuff is starting to make sense.
Each time I thought about it.
I wondered should I try.
To have a close encounter with another horny guy.
Because it would still be cheating on my wife.
I'm pretty sure.
I could tell her in any other woman.
But it sure is heck ain't her.
Then my mouth would have checked.
I couldn't afford.
We were watching the People's Choice Awards.
With Hugh Jackman and Hugh Login.
Touchy feeling.
I said, yeah.
I bet they're the People's Choice.
Even I'm like kissing to one of my boys.
And my wife said, and a self-revoiced.
Really?
Since then, our love life is freaking unreal.
We weren't sure.
And say what we feel.
She tells me your fantasies.
And I tell her, mine.
It's more romance than we've ever had.
But there is one thing that makes me mad.
I got addicted to queer eye and top design.
My next car, but you shut me.
And my hair is set goodbye.
But the girls down at the office.
They got me they're kind of guy.
I lost all my machismo.
With acceptance I am right.
Two guys kissing ruined my life.
Little bit, little bit of constant.
Tom Smith from the Phump project.
Which we haven't had.
We haven't had great success with playing.
Several of their tracks.
They're all on the podcast music network.
And of course, a link to Tom Smith's.
Anthem.
Two guys kissing ruined my life.
All right.
We're just under 40 minutes.
Perfect timing.
I have no idea when the next show will be.
If I do fly to Germany tomorrow,
I will be recording the entire track.
Track, track, track, track route.
Flight planned, et cetera.
And that will be part of Tuesday's show.
So stay tuned.
DailySourceco.com.
Adam and podshow.com day four.
Smoke free.
Thank you.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.