This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
Come on, come on.
Hi, honey.
How's it going?
I'm beat.
This city just keeps getting worse.
It's like I'm driving a bus full of doghermins in my ass.
It's made out of dog biscuits.
I'm sorry you had such a rough day honey.
Put it for a little help.
I loaded you up a bomb and downloaded the DSC675.
Alright, so you can listen to it while I fix your supper.
I don't feel like it.
But it's full of our Friday.
No, sweetheart.
How can you be so nice to a mole-plack me?
Don't, it's just because I love you so much sweet.
Baby, fuck you, Adam Curry.
Silent Library
I got it.
There was $16 million worth of airplane trapped by us.
Since the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm smiling each of these insurance.
I'm justing his bedroom curry
My pride ain't
I'm getting out of the house
I'm getting out of my room
It feels like it needs to be
You can do it
When you grow, it's okay
It's not to do it
It's just so ahead and feel your man
Here up, and do your back
And go to be a shine
It feels like it needs to be
I'm getting out of the house
And we go wrong
Just because I'm on
Don't take the time to jump a heart
Just because I need you
What's in there, what's up, what's in there
Just because I'm on
Don't take the time to jump a heart
Just because I need you
What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up
I need the time to jump a heart
Just because I need you
What's the theater Livestzenie I'm Gonna Let her Out
Seunu's Say Yeah
What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up
Yeah, what a song I'm about to say, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it,
you say it, say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you are, you say it, it, you say it, you say it right, you are, you like it, you say it, you say it, they say what you say, you say it, you say it, you say it, it you say, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you say it, you tell me it is, it, you say the song. I'm looking for it, down, am I yourself, one say the song as a 3-time singer, I that also give All the name.
I'm so mad, all of me, my pussy, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me
it's me, it's me,
it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, just me, just me, and even me, I'm willing to become crazy up back then I'm willing to love more
Change and everything seems like it's up and down
With this wave and to the moon and to the moon
Everywhere you look, it seems like it's been five
Like to be trying to find a rainbow
No one's ever found, just don't you think
But it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
Everything you need, five by your feet
The miles touch, everything I touch
Once ago, before you look at my heart
The miles touch, you'll never let me touch
I'm fighting, I'm just so old
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
The miles, the miles, the miles
You want to be a finger-finger for my life
It's all things, but the little thing
I found on your feet again
I think you always bring it up
A week and a day
It's all flower stones
You know that I might not have to be
Who's right, I'm just wrong
You got me, yeah
Take over, you take it, it's in me
And when it goes, that's it
It's all flower stones
You know that I might not have to be
Who's right, I'm just so old
A week and a day
It's all things, but the little thing
I think you always bring it up
A week and a day
It's all things, but the little thing
I think you always bring it up
Okay, evenly endorsed by the organization
To the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
If you weren't alive in the 80s
That's pretty much a good portion of it right there
That you've mastered it up
In the mix up old school style
From the bond from door starters
A fine Dutch group, a loose-knit group of
Mixers, remixers and mash-ups
Who've been at this for a long, long time
I think for the radio program very much
Soul Show
And a link was sent to me by Marlaine
Who said, Adam, do you remember these mixes?
Boy, do I ever?
What a way to kick off the footballer Friday
I'm almost afraid actually
To put a link in the show notes
To this fantastic resource
Because I'm afraid that
You know, their server may come crashing down
Or whatever
So I've got to think about that
So there are fun veils, synths, synths
Is the one who mixed that one up
It was Mixed Number 207, man
All right, everybody, how you doing?
It's a footballer Friday
It is not entirely a maximum music footballer Friday
Because there's just too much incoming
Too much inbound, too much to talk about
And I gotta hurry up today
I have a photo shoot here at the curry manner
Coming up a little bit later today
Between one and two, a player magazine
Will be here
Yeah, because I'm such a player
And I'm still in the, this is actually the backup bathroom
That I have on today, it is
It's kind of like an Indian vibe
Not as an American Indian, but as an Indian from India
Of course, still sporting the black egg boots
I gotta tell you, I am excited
Yesterday, confirmation came through
And of course, we'll be talking about this today
Confirmation came through that
Republican presidential candidate
Dr. Ron Paul will be appearing on this program
The daily source code, this coming Wednesday
So the way it's gonna work is
I will be speaking with him at 10 a.m.
Washington time when he is still at his condo
Because after I think after 11 he has to
Be somewhere to vote
And he could only use his cell phone
Which apparently is an iPhone
Plenty of you have been sending me pictures about that
So that's like 3 p.m. London time
So actually I'm just gonna not go into London
On Wednesday, just stay here and get the call going
And you know, I've got at least half an hour
And had a great talk yesterday
With the communications director of the campaign
So we'll be talking about that later today
Of course, some awesome music
As you can expect, Sir Jersey taught us here
We've got youngplets hit test
And of course your calls coming in in great volumes
I'm sorry if you're not getting on the show
It's just too much
And even I wouldn't want to listen to the show
Was over an hour long
Hey Adam, it's Jerry from anapolis
And at this point whatever I say regarding the whole
We've got issues and the freedom issues and all that
Probably we're just piling on
But I figured I have to add my two cents for us
I have the freedom to do so
I think it's unrealistic that change
I get that and I get that
And it's an emotional thing, emotional debate
But you've got to understand that
While you might be a world citizen
You are also a citizen of the United States
And you're a story
Your angle is gonna have that bias
And I think that's reasonable
Just as it is
You know his approach to life
Probably has a bias from wherever he's from
So I think it's unreasonable to expect to adopt a
Generic vanilla approach to all problems
I mean if there was a suitable solution to all problems
That was agreeable to everyone
That we'd be doing
First of all being made
Because no one in terms of everyone
Can agree on everything all the time
So you're gonna make somebody unhappy
And oh well
So I think you know
Plus the way you said you know enjoy your freedom
I think it was well understood
Anybody's listening to your podcast
Clearly has some freedom
You know
And I think the point was enjoy the freedom you have
And I think change might be in the minority
To have misinterpreted that
Guns well you know
I'm not a gun fan
On the other hand I do believe if you take away the guns
Then you end up with bad guys with guns
And no good guys with guns
And that's not a good combination
I do believe that if you've got a gun
And it's loaded you better be prepared to kill somebody
I think there are a lot of people who have guns
Who don't show proper respect to the weapon
And when they end up
Using it they end up with consequences they were not intending
And my feeling is if you've got a weapon
You have to understand how to use it
And understand the consequences of using it
And be prepared for all possible outcomes
And that includes enforcement
And the crimes that you may have committed
And using the weapon
So I think if we just enforce our laws
To the letter and not do this plea bargaining business
And people who use guns
And the commission of a crime
Got what they deserve
And it would do to be at least more deterrent than we currently have
So anyway I could go on and on
That's some of my two sims for us
Folder
Boopill
I'll see what else I'm supposed to say
Fuck you at a furry
You know
I wanted to play that for you because
Essentially you know
Yeah you piled on but you piled on with some sanity there
And I've been listening to a number of comments coming in tons of email
It's really it's really quite amazing
How the shift in topical discussion here on the Charlie has
As caused quite a bit of a bit of feedback
Lots of new listeners as well
People who are checking in that they've
What about the conversation going on so welcome everybody
For those of you who are brand new to the show
Please note that it is okay at the end of your comment
In fact it's encouraged to tell me go fuck myself
And
Who sent this to me?
Shit
I don't know who sent this
Here it is
Swaring at work boost team spirit and morale according to research
Here you go
You're Huda Baruch
Professor Management at the University of East Anglia and graduate
Stuart Jenkins studied the use of profanity in the workplace
And assess this implications for managers
They assess that swearing will become more common as traditional
Taboo's are broken down but the key appeared to be knowing when
Such language was appropriate and went to turn a blind eye
Employees use swearing on a continuous basis
But not necessarily in a negative abusive manner
Said Baruch who works in the University's business school in North
Banning swear words and representing staff might represent strong leadership
But could remove key links between staff and impact on morale and motivation
How interesting is this?
I'll put a link in the show notes to this study because you definitely
Have to read it and I agree
For some reason it feels really powerful
Doesn't it just to be able to say that?
Particularly you guys seem to really love saying it to me
But the quality of the content of what you're saying just before that
It's improved dramatically
I have to tell you I'm the guy that gets all this shit coming in
One other thing I realize is that
EI is an American actually know very little about the constitution
And Angela Thornton sent me this fantastic link to
series of videos which are on Google video and this one
This is homework between now and Wednesday when Ron Paul will be on on the show
It is what's it called?
It's called constitution class
And it's eight hours okay
So it's this is no joke
There's eight different videos eight hours in total
But it really takes you through the entire concept of the constitution
The Bill of Rights
What is a right?
What is a privilege?
What is property?
What responsibilities come with rights?
Very very interesting stuff if you want to understand about the
Workings of the Republic of the United States of America
And if you're truly involved in what's going on
I encourage you to take a look at that
I know it's it's a big assignment
And I'm only through our three right now
Because Christ where do you find it?
It's not easy to find the time
But I think it's fundamental if if you're interested in the topic
If you're an American citizen you are almost obliged
You know you have to take a look at this
Now if you're a citizen of the world and a citizen of music
And you love the 70s 80s 90s
Shit sometimes the 60s
Well young palettes your man
I'm counting casting with Adam Curry
Hey Adam, are you ready to be stumps
Because he used the hint
Bring it on mate
Hey Adam, it's time for another hit test
On this week hit test
There's number 92
Okay, I'm ready
And this is intro number one
Uh
Stand up, stand up
Meet Jagger Peter Toss
She's going to walk and don't look back
Yes, I'm sure of that one
Bring on number 2
Number 2
Police
Is it a little thing she does as magic?
Easy this week young
I think
Which is when getting them right
And number 3
Please
Now you're insulting my intelligence
Brick ass, we never gonna give you up
Don't tell me it got three stars today on
And time's up
And these are the answers
That's right
The answer number one from 1979
Nick Jagger and Peter Toss
Yes
Got to running from
There is no one
No one
You can't
With you just
Put your hand in mind
We're gonna leave all that troubles behind
We're gonna walk and don't look back
Don't look back
Nick Jagger and Peter Toss
And you got to walk and don't look back
As answer number one
And this is answer number two
From 1981
The police
Thank you
Here we go
You know the words
Sing along now
And everything she does is magic
The police and every little thing she does is magic
Yes number two
And this is answer number three from 1987
This is Brick Ashley
Sorry
We're gonna let you down
We're gonna walk and don't look back
We're gonna go
We're gonna let you
We're gonna make you
We're gonna see you by
Answer number three
Rick Ashley and ever gonna give you up
That's been great
It's number nine
Thank you to you.
Again, they were not very difficult at him, I think you had them all.
Yes, finally.
The answers to this hit-est, and also the iTunes links can be found at hit-est.bacho.com.
Next week I'll be back with Hit-est number 93, so I don't thank you for playing.
No, thank you for making.
And everyone else, thank you for listening.
Until next week, take care, and bye-bye.
Those of you...
Excuse me, let me just wallow in my glory here for a second.
Three out of three.
Feeling good.
And the sun is shining today.
Lots of requests to see young-pullet studio.
He's posted them now on his weblog, young-pullet.com.
And you can see young there, and his full glory in front of his...
No, no, no, it's not his studio.
What do we call it?
The lab.
It's the hit-test laboratory.
Amongst many of the comments coming in as we've kind of shifted the focus.
And by the way, it's impossible that I'll be able to be talking about politics
and candidates and amendments and constitutional rights
completely until the 2008 elections.
So please, I know that as this show always has, it will shift course, shift focus.
And for those of you writing and calling and saying,
Goodman, you've changed, man.
The show is all different.
I think the only thing constant about this show is that you can always expect change.
Here's a comment relating to it.
Adam, it's Mike from Windsor, Ontario, Canada.
I was looking to show 73 today a lot work on the assembly line, making many vans.
God bless you, man.
Bless you for being on the assembly line, making many vans.
And I think it was Parkie who called when you referred to your listeners
as part of your family.
I have to admit that when you don't talk to your family the same way
that you talk to other people, I think I've seen me on text dry,
listen to him, tweet, and I've seen you on cranky geeks.
And when you're talking to those people or when you're on,
I guess you'd say with those folks,
it's nothing like when you're behind that mic either at the condo or at home in England.
It's like you're very personable when you're talking to us,
but when you're not in that situation, it's a whole different story.
Also, no matter which direction you take the show, things gotta evolve.
Everything's gotta evolve. It doesn't matter where you go.
Your family will follow you, no matter what.
And how we put up with your second life,
excursion, we can put up with anything else.
I guess it's it for now, you look good work, and I'll talk to you, Adam Curry.
And you know, I only accept that from my family.
Yeah, appreciate that.
And you make a very good point.
One of my wife makes all the time.
And by the way, why isn't she on the show anymore?
What's going on with that?
Next week, I'll wrangle her in, it's time.
It's way overdue time to have the lady pee on the show.
So Patricia will always say, you know,
when you do interviews and when you're on talk shows and other people shows,
how come you're not yourself as what she says?
I say, well, I'm trying, you know, I am myself.
I'm myself in that moment.
I don't know.
Yeah, but you're much looser at home and funnier.
And I think it has to do with the number of things.
One, and this is why I've always liked radio over television.
I have complete control over this program.
Every single thing that happens are at my fingertips.
My hands are running twice as fast as my brain sometimes,
just in making things happen.
And every single piece that goes on,
I'm in control of a very difficult with video.
You just need other people really to pull it off.
And, you know, if you have other people, you can't control it all yourself.
That's why I need a great team.
Very, very hard to put great video or television teams together.
When you got it, you know, then shit really sings.
But anyway, so that's one small part of it.
But also, you're in my home right now.
Wherever my home happens to be, at this moment, it's the manner.
I'm the west side of G2.
I'm in my bathrobe.
You know, I look like shit.
I'm on shaving.
My hair is all messy.
But I have this tool, you know, this microphone.
And it's funny, because I was thinking yesterday how wonderful this attic is.
Because when I'm talking, I'm literally looking over the mic.
I mean, when you talk into a microphone, you got to look somewhere, right?
Now, sometimes, of course, I look over at the screen and I'll read something.
Or, you know, I have my notes.
And, you know, of course, I've got lots of, you know, cast blasters up and running.
But most of the time when I'm talking, I'm kind of in a Zen state staring off into space.
I'm actually looking out of the beautiful bay window here in the attic.
Looking at the trees, the colors, the blue sky, which is why you always hear me talking about the weather,
because that's what I'm looking at.
And when you're talking to someone else, it's, uh, it's sometimes just not as beautiful to look at.
It's hard, but I'm very conscious of how I can zone out when I get into, uh, getting to a vibe.
And this microphone, um, all my life, and I've been on the radio more than I've been on television or done anything else.
This microphone, it's, um, it's everything to me.
Um, I travel with it.
I travel with my microphone.
It's my pen.
It is my, uh, it's my weapon.
It is, uh, it's my love stick.
Connected to my love tube.
Can you feel the love flowing through my tube into your earlobes?
Hmm.
Push those birds in deeper.
You know, Adam Curry's Chris Taylor from the Comprehensive Ania.
I'm still on wall between this run point.
It's a barricard bomber guy, but I'm starting to lean toward ground ball.
If you get it on the radio or on a video on the podcast, make sure you get some information from him.
If you're a folder or a scruncher, that little blue pill.
And if you get a good fuck you, Adam Curry, Adam.
I will talk to you, Adam Curry.
Yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
You know, um, so when I was talking to Jesse, the communications director, yes.
So I called him yesterday.
And, and I, and the first thing I said, hey, man, you know, I just got to tell you.
I really impressed that how fast this all came together.
And he says, and it was a silence.
And he says, are you being facetious?
Did nobody talking about it?
I mentioned it last Friday.
On Monday, I already had people reaching out to me getting in touch with you.
And I was amazed.
Oh, oh, I feel really good about that.
Because I, we were feeling really embarrassed here about so many people had been writing and calling and saying
Ron Paul has to be on the daily source code.
That they felt they'd actually been lagging behind a little bit.
And here we are exactly one week later after I said, you know, if this guy's campaign really is as together as it is.
And if he's really, um, if he really knows how to use, you'd lies the internet and this campaign understands it.
It'll happen.
And one week later, I am well impressed.
Well, impressed, I have to say.
And so I, you know, I'm like, all right, how are we going to do this?
So I've come up with a format for, um, for the conversation, which I think will work.
Now, I have some general questions and there's some stuff that is well known about Ron Paul,
but, you know, I'd like to ask further.
Here's an example.
So, you know, he writes five million dollars.
He's, you know, once a raise, I think 12 million for, you know, by the end of the year.
My question is, how are you going to spend it?
Now, of course, we know, but, you know, who's actually in charge of the media by?
Who creates the, the commercials?
Of all the things I've seen on YouTube and all the Ron Paul videos, the weakest by far,
the crappiest are the commercials that the campaign is putting together themselves.
You know, so I got questions about that.
I want to know why, if, I think I know the answer, but, you know, he's stated several times.
And this is what I hate about mainstream.
You know, so the mainstream, oh, man, I hope that's not the photographer already.
He's too early.
What time is it?
No, it can't be him.
Mainstream, well, it likes to ask questions.
They already know the answers, too.
And I think partially to just, so they can slot it into the time available.
And so they look smart when they ask the question or whatever.
But, you know, well, Ron Paul, if you don't receive the, the Republican nomination,
are you going to run as an independent?
And I've all known as the answer.
His answer is no.
Interesting.
No one's asking why?
Why won't he?
Again, I think I know the answer, but let's hear it from him.
But I also wanted him to understand the show and the community that surrounds it.
The family.
We, oh, fat, man, they.
So I said, you know, please Jesse, make sure that Ron Paul hears a show or at least part of a show.
He's got to understand what he's walking into because the world at large
that large and the daily source code audience, in particular, needs to know if he's a folder
or a scruncher.
I had to explain what that meant, of course.
I said, Jesse, communication is due.
You need to listen to the show.
Please.
And I said, you know, we're kind of crazy, you know, and people say fuck you to me, you know,
I didn't, I didn't go as far as to say, hey, I hope Ron Paul can give me a good fuck
you at the end, but, you know, if he really listens to it, then he should maybe catch
on.
We'll find out.
So anyway, the format for the questions, I was thinking, you will take like the top issues
we've been talking about, right?
So we have a second amendment.
We've got to follow the money, so that would be like our IRS Federal Reserve.
I think that we probably want to spend a little bit of time on the first amendment, which is
free speech, because I believe that he has actually, this is another, I'm going to suggest
something to him as well, you know, in all these,
interviews, you know, it's the same stupid story.
It's like, well, you've got a lot of support on the internet.
And then Ron Paul kind of in a doofus way goes like, ah, it's amazing.
We didn't know we don't know how it's happening.
Stop.
That's dumb.
If I can make a recommendation, which I'll do, he needs to be saying, we've cracked the code
of the internet.
Can you read the headline?
We've cracked the code.
We've figured out how to communicate through the internet.
Because that will scare the bejesus out of every other candidate.
Oh, shit.
Those guys figured it out.
How, how, how do they do it?
You know, they're doing them.
You running around trying to figure out how to, how to hop on board this internet thing.
And it's really simple, the well, why I believe, why he's cracked the code of the internet
is because the internet is a huge first amendment machine.
If anything, it's that, you know, it's where you get to say whatever you want to say.
And you can pretty much do it without any repercussions, whether it's in text or audio or
video or, you know, and, and, and hello, damn, I'm in the middle of it, leave me alone.
It's an amazing first amendment machine, freedom of speech machine and freedom and speech.
Well, if you speak to people about those things, that machine's going to start working.
Anyway, so what I'd like to do is I'd like to say, okay, please walk me through the second
amendment and how the second amendment, how you interpret that, Dr. Ron and how it fits into
your campaign, into your strategy and what you're going to do if and when elected.
So instead of saying, you are programs and have him go through the trouble of explaining
it all the way down to the constitution, since he is a constitutionalist and a libertarian
and a Republican man.
He's a lot of things.
I'd like to see if he can explain it from the ground up.
That will probably help.
That's why I'm giving you a homework assignment to learn a little bit more about the United
States constitution.
You won't be disappointed.
The guy that does this is pretty interesting.
It's literally a college classroom class and you're just kind of sitting along for the ride.
And I found it quite enjoyable.
Almost as enjoyable as the multitude of languages in which I'm learning to say, fuck you.
Hi, Adam.
She's my role.
You're an listener.
That's so cool, Adam.
Nah, fun cooler.
It was coming regards of your fuck you experiment.
I just remember that in Italy you have a competitor.
Oh, no.
You have somebody that I'm sure that your sister will look at the test more.
Is that a great law in Italian comedian who's been thrown up a lot of shit around the town.
It is a fun cooler campaign, which of course is fuck you in Italian.
And it will be interesting just to give a listen to and see how it is.
But for me instead is going to be the fun cooler.
I'm cool all.
Nice.
Well, there is no such thing as coincidence as also in the voicemail.
My darling little sister checking in from Italy.
No, bro, it's your sister calling in from Italy.
Oh, first of all, welcome home.
Yeah, I knew it.
I knew it.
You're a bit lost there with your iPhone, but you came back.
You came back.
Anyway, I've been listening to all your episodes.
Had a hard time though, because my drive to work is only 20 minutes.
Had a hard time getting all the stuff in.
But finally, I'm out today.
And I really enjoyed listening to all the comments and you endorsing Ron Paul.
And I've been looking things up.
And I like it when something gives me a push and start, you know,
getting more interested about something.
Yeah, and that's exactly what Ron Paul is done.
He's cracked to the code of the internet.
We all know how it works, obviously, but he's coming in.
He's cracking it.
What I thought was interesting is that we coming out of the same nest.
We have some reviews are just opposite.
And I know you keep saying, yeah, but Ron Paul and his ideas is not this or that.
It's just he doesn't want all the laws made by central government,
made by local states, local laws, and I fundamentally agree with that.
Because I think there are lots of things that are much better done and decided
at a local level or a state level could be schooling and that kind of stuff.
But there's so much stuff that's just shifting the problem.
You know, like, and I agree, like the drinking age, that's locally now.
I mean, the states, okay.
So that's what basically he would be doing by overturning the, what is it?
Rovers' weight thing.
Oh, excuse me.
Yeah, I think that's a big misunderstood part of what he's saying is how a lot of the things
that we regulate at a federal governmental level should be regulated by the states.
And I think that's really good.
We should probably talk to him about Rovers' weight because I got a couple of comments about that.
And again, I think I know the answer isn't I think I know how it is supposed to work and how it
probably could work.
But again, we've got to delve down a lot deeper because it's not just about
changing or abolishing one piece.
There's all all these pieces fit together.
So like national health care, you know, maybe that's something that shouldn't be
regulated by the government.
These are the things that we've got to figure out.
So yeah, I'm sorry, I didn't interrupt.
But he'd be doing just shifting the problem, the problem.
Yeah, the problem is, and look, first of all, no one's going to solve anything.
Not, or everything I should say.
That's just not possible.
We're a diverse group and humans by themselves are just when we never mind.
The problem from central government to the local government, what's going on?
What's going to happen?
Okay, one state allows abortions.
The other one doesn't, you know, I just go to the other state.
Yeah.
You know, to get an abortion.
I mean, I really think, you know, certain things.
Why not?
You don't solve the problem at a local level.
You're probably going to even solve them at a central level either.
But anyway, but I think he's sort of like, yeah, well, you know, the whole idea that he wants to
shift where the laws are made.
But he is pro-life, I'm pro-choice.
I mean, are we getting too long?
The biggest socially men, I don't even know what being pregnant means.
All right, let me just try and address this really quickly.
Because, of course, I have no fucking no idea what it's like to be pregnant.
Of course, I don't.
I'm pro-choice and I'm pro-life.
I guess pro-life means we also don't execute people,
which is kind of the whole craziness about this pro-life pro-choice.
Of course, it's your body.
You should be able to do anything you want with it.
What's so ever?
This is really a philosophical question because the first right you have
as an individual is your own body.
The question that is being raised is when are you an individual?
Correct. That's, you know what?
Let's stop killing it.
Let's stop shooting hot-letter each other in fucking deserts.
And then we can get around to this one.
I think that might be a larger issue.
Not trying to downplay it, understand everything,
have no answers, not running for president here.
These are, he helps to give him birth to 4,000 babies.
Anyway, and the second amendment, oh, I thought there was very interesting
that the listener who called in with the context,
because I really didn't know that.
And, oh, lots of stuff to say there, too.
I'm definitely for some control.
Um, just a quick fact, uh, let me ask you a question.
Uh, you live in Italy, different country, different politics, different system.
When the, uh, covering the area or whatever the hell they're called,
you know, the guys in the motorcycles with the white helmets,
covering, covering the area, covering for whatever their name is.
Uh, when you're driving down the road and you see those guys in your rear view mirror,
do you feel safe and think, wow, you know, that I feel protected because the
carbon area are behind me and they've got their guns and, and I'm safe.
I know that this is a safe country, or do you think yourself,
crap the carbon area behind me?
I hope they don't fucking hassle me.
I think I know the answer will, though.
I have lots of, uh, friend, mom, friends, as we call them in the states.
And once, uh, we, we were in contact by email.
And this, and this topic came out like, oh, do you let your kids go over to
a friend's house where you know, uh, they have a guns in the house or do you ask?
And I was like, why don't we tell them they're talking about, you know, it's just a reality.
It's something that doesn't exist here for me.
And I feel good about it.
I mean, you should hear them, you know, going about, oh, yeah, no.
First I call and I, and I ask and I say, do you have guns in the house?
And yes, and then some, some moms would let the kids play there.
Some wouldn't some.
Yeah, okay.
Um, um, that's, you know,
I don't want to piss off a whole bunch of people.
But that sounds to me like very typical.
I'm going to generalize if you don't mind.
Very typical suburban American housewives, soccer moms, uh, who are completely infiltrated by
fucked up media and get freaked out about every fucking thing that's been on this on the news.
It's freaking these people out.
That shit's got to stop.
It really, really has to.
I can give you a checklist.
Here's a checklist.
Do you have any guns? Do you have any drugs? Do you have any alcohol?
Do you have a swimming pool? Do you have a trampoline?
Do you have anything at all that could hurt my child when they're, uh,
it's crap. What is this?
No time for you.
That's the checklist you can go off.
And it's because of fear.
Willow.
It's fear.
These women are scared to death.
They're being scared and they're very on homes by television.
Let's see how it was like, you know, and, and, and, oh, yes, it's true.
Guns don't kill people.
People kill people.
They only promise what happens.
If it's little people who get their hands on the gun,
I mean, little little people.
So anyway, that besides getting into that,
no, just thought it was good for you to endorse Ron Paul.
If he feels he represents what, you know, you want.
The the candidate might, will be, uh,
Barack Obama, because he just does more whatever.
He's just mad.
Oh, that's the pleased.
Crikey. All mighty.
Fuck off.
Leave me alone.
Hey, if you can't articulate, why you're going to vote for Obama,
and what he stands for, you might want to reconsider.
He represents more of my ideas.
And then what I also thought was the thing was that people said,
or you were saying that people are saying that you've changed.
I don't think so much you've changed. I mean, just, no, you never pointed out
your views on certain things.
Oh, I didn't even know you thought about certain things in a certain way.
But that, well, I believe me.
Most of the time, I'm too stoned off my ass to think about anything.
So don't get worries.
That doesn't mean you've changed.
I think you're just mentioning things that you haven't mentioned before.
So anyway, lots of things to say on this topic,
and I would be, you know, I could talk about it forever,
but I see that I'm already going on way too long.
Uh-huh.
Looking forward to hearing him in an interview on your show,
and uh, that's it.
And now I'm supposed to say, uh,
fuck you into you, but it doesn't seem moral to say to my brother,
so I'll just say it in a time, it seems like a fancy.
Now that's fun, cool.
Fun, cool, though.
Mala, fun, cool, oh, y'all.
Hey, man, I know that was long, but it's my sister, you know?
This is how we communicate through the tubes,
through the tubes on the internet.
I need a break.
Oh, let's second down to it.
It is, of course, through our Friday,
so we got to bring in the official Music Colleges
Sergio, the Todd standing by,
with a really rough throat.
But still, man enough to bring us the pot safe.
You're not to make a motion.
It's my sister, my heart.
Man, I'm sorry, I'm just a child.
Today is Orlando, Um-hum.
It's time for your home.
And it's a football Friday.
With Josie Todd on the Charlie.
It's a football Friday.
Well, have some fun out there,
Yo, how's it going Adam and Jersey Todd, the official musicologist of the Chacha?
Hey boss man, I gotta apologize right off the bat, because for the last couple of days
I've had the worst cold, in fact, for a couple of days I was going to court with no
voice at all.
I know, a lawyer without a voice, what good is that?
But telling me to shut up is like telling Lance Armstrong to get off the damn bike already.
Besides, I had to have to get out of football Friday for you, because I've got something
amazing.
Yeah, you might even remember it from your past.
So get out some hairspray, get out the bedazz or get out the ripped jeans and have a ball
with some of the other headbanders, because I'm bringing you a wasp.
Yeah, that's right, they're a pot safe now, and they've got a brand new album out calling
Doc called Dominator, and this is the song Mercy.
I know you're going to dig this, check it out, it's a wasp under through our Friday.
I'm going to take you there face down my bed, I'm really rules to see you smile.
I know you're going to dig this, I know you're going to dig this, I know you're going to dig this,
Cause man, when we're rolling out
You know we're making clouds on the sand
When we're going here, you know
I'll make it round for the sand
I'll roll
Gotta roll
I'll round
I'll roll
I'll make you cry for the same
I'll make you cry alive
Don't go to the line, cause man
I'll make you cry for the same
Nobody, nobody in the hell
A la la
That's why I'm talking about
Wast
Oh man, going back at time
Mercy, it's on the positive
same music now where they got another track up there as well.
You can check it out, show notes, at datingsourceco.com.
We'll contain links to everything played in this episode of the program, the football
Friday edition, DSC 475.
Ah crap.
Now I could do three hours of this with you guys.
Well actually, I can't because I just don't have the time with other commitments and I don't
think anyone could hang in that long.
That's the big difference between radio and independent media like we're doing is like, you know,
those guys got to do three hours to get one point across because no one tunes in for three
hours. And here I've got to get all my points into, you know, really I try to do 40 minutes
I'm already at 48. So yeah, go ahead. Look down at your iPod. You can see it's 48 minutes.
Hi, yes. Hey Adam. Yeah. I heard you yesterday talking about how a Gabby was a fruit.
Do your research. It's a fruit. Oh, fuck you. Okay, that's the route from which the Kila is derived.
Check out on the KilaTrail.podshow.com.
Hey Adam, this is Tony from San Diego. Thanks for turning me on to legacy of ashes and zeitgeist.
Both of them were really eye openers. But now what do I do? I feel like I'm trapped by all the messages
that are in this is life. There's no way we can overcome it. Yeah, I understand my friend.
And that's the whole point. I think that really is the point. You know, your brain's working.
Congratulations. You've just witnessed your brain going into overdrive. Now here's what you should do.
Take the other way to work today. Turn left instead of turning right. That's really good to
break your routine to get your brain juices flowing. The synapses are all firing in different
different patterns. Do everything you do today. Do it the other way around. Go left instead of
right. You still have to get to your destination. But, you know, pick something up with your left
hand instead of your right hand. It's really going to help your brain focus more. And please go check
out those constitution classes. Link at the show notes. Daddysourceco.com. Now I have,
let's see what I have lined up here. Another rovers is weighed. Another two second amendments.
I've got Derek from the UK. I just think it's I want to play one more song. I want to do the final
thought of the week. So I'm just going to do this one last one if you don't want to. I'm going on
with David from Jersey column and again. I've got six words for you. November, remember, remember
the fifth of November. Gunpowder translated into class. Some of your British listeners,
remember that as a guy for something. But this year it's going to be something a little bit different.
It's November, fifth, 2007. The Ron Paul campaign has set aside that day as a day of donation.
They're trying to achieve something along the lines of you and some of the other podcasts
did with bummer's the charts. But obviously for his political campaign.
A good idea. Now for all the you run all supporters out there if you have donated already
that would be great. If you could donate again, if you haven't, wait, wait for November fifth.
Because Ron is trying to look to gather news and my and all sorts of good publicity with this event.
So I've already signed up. I'm on the list and you can go to this November fifth.com.
That's the number five to eight for VV.
Victor. I signed up for a list so they can get an idea about how many people are actually going to
do the same. So anyone that wants to get them in there, let's do it. Take back America.
Nice. Fuck yeah, I'm good. Yeah, fuck you too. Hey, that's a good idea. Although I'm not quite
prepared. Everyone's saying, you know, happy to see you're endorsing Ron Paul. I haven't actually
endorsed him yet. In fact, the campaign sent over, you know, it's a real deal when you endorse
someone. It's not just saying I endorse him. There's actually a legal document that I need to sign,
which I haven't done yet for the Ron Paul campaign, which says I Adam Curry endorsed this candidate.
And you may use any quote I make in any campaign announcements, in any materials, etc. You know,
that's kind of like a like a movie endorsement. You know, it's like two thumbs up. Adam Curry,
Daily Source Code. A big fuck you from Adam Curry, Daily Source Code. So I have not done that yet.
And I'm not going to help with the bum rush the charts just yet until I feel confident I can
endorse and second. I do want to talk about the money and how it's being spent. It was going to be
spent on crap advertising. Well, shit, pod shows good at that. We expect much better.
So, but in all likelihood, yeah, I'm pretty sure I'm going to endorse this guy because, you know,
look at what's happening. This is the, this proves that this campaign has cracked the code to the
internet. What could be more viral than taking something that already exists. Remember, remember,
the fifth of November, the rest of the sentence has gunpowder, trees, and and plot. And I forget
all the rest. But yeah, completely a bum rush the charts. We know it's going to work. And I will get
behind the, of course. Now, you need some assets for that, which we'll talk about if, if we're actually,
if, you know, if I'm going to participate. So that's stuff to talk about. Let me just check my,
uh, my Google notebook here. Uh, a BBC in the news. I would be quite a miss if I, uh,
if I did not, uh, tell you that the BBC, now, the director general and the board of Grand
Pupas have announced that there has to be a 20% cut in the workforce over the next three years. And
the country's gone apeshit, apeshit, I tell you. Because, of course, although I haven't seen it
much, it would with my own eyes, uh, what's being said as well, you know, the cuts are the deepest in the
news department, the documentaries department, all the places where, uh, that the BBC is appreciated
for so much, you know, people are fighting for their existence, for their jobs, for what they believe
in, for their vision. It's on talk shows. It's all over the place. I just paid my 135 pounds
for another year of the TV license fee. Uh, so I'm, you know, I feel very much in control,
although, of course, I'm not because it's the government, essentially, that's making the decision,
um, about how much of the money is is going to be given to the BBC. It's pretty fucked up
situation, actually. Um, and of course, uh, you know, when you, when you try to organize your money
into to pay a resource, so it's our money here in the United Kingdom, we're giving it to the
government. The government then turns around and gives it all of it or maybe even more than it. I don't
know, uh, to the BBC, they decide how much goes in there and they're deciding, uh, what needs to be cut.
Um, I don't think I was asked. I was asked to pay before any choices were made, interestingly enough.
Um, it's just like government, public broadcasting. It's just like government. There's,
and I know how it works. I've worked at public broadcasting corporations and it's, uh, there's a lot of,
well, you get in government bureaucracy and pencil pushing and, uh, believe me, all this money is not
directly going onto the screen and into our ears. It's just not happening. So it's probably a good thing,
but, you know, you know, then you get like a Jonathan Ross who is a huge celebrity here. He has a
Friday night talk show. He does, uh, a Saturday, uh, talk show on the radio. Um, he does a movie review show.
He's entertaining, very popular. And you get six million pounds a year. And of course, that
pisses everyone off. You know, you could hire a lot of, uh, reporters for that money. But, you know,
it's always brought down to that level of, you know, one to one. And then I don't even know if the
cuts actually are taking place in people who are directly responsible for making programming or
reporting news or making up the news for that matter. All right, one more, one more before
we get the final father day. Hi, out of my name's Gorn. Um, I'm, you know, one kind of listener, I guess.
And, uh, I don't know, I've kind of been holding back listening to all of your shows about the, uh,
the essay and, uh, and it's just the ongoing of, uh, the American government for the,
so organizations that are quote-unquote really the American government. Uh, and basically,
uh, you made a comment about, uh, something, uh, the 72 hour notice before you can fly and you
have to be free of food to get your boarding fast. And I, uh, this is, uh, a new regulation that TSA
is proposing that, uh, for any travel to the United States or over the United States, excuse me,
that you would essentially have to book 72 hours in advance so you can be screened and approved
for this type of activity for sitting in a chair full of beer farts eating fucking peanuts.
I say, let it happen. I mean, really, um, maybe for once, you know, there'll be something to push
and track or some other train, train company to fill their own train tracks so people will stop,
uh, you know, well, basically fly because they'll have to, you know, because, you know,
you know, who the hell, you know, if you go through 150 steps just to take that an hour flight
to Chicago or something like that, um, I live in Ohio, I drive 45 minutes to and from work every
day and I would love it if there was a train that I could commute on through, uh, whatever.
So the point being, uh, it's ridiculous, uh, as a United States citizen, I have the right to travel
and that, uh, sounds to me like this right is being taken away. I can't travel when I want to.
I know where does it say you have the right to travel when to prove. You have the right to travel.
Man, these are complicated issues. And, you know, and my brain is so tiny just by being a man
first of all, much tiny than a woman's brain. It just hurts. One more, you've got to read just
of while we're on the TSA and again, this is just another link in the show notes, uh, screeners at
Los Angeles International Airport, uh, according to USA today who did an under-covered covert study
failed 75% of, uh, oh, no, they didn't do the study. The TSA did the study themselves. USA today
got the leaked story or the report was leaked to them. Screeners failed 75% of all bomb detection tests.
Well, gee, there's a surprise. You read this. You're just going to be laughing. So what I've always
been saying, you can get any kind of shit you want through TSA. It's horseshit. It's, it's trickery.
It's mockery, really. It's not based on reality. However, I hear they do have a
100% hit rate at finding my KY intrigue lubricant. It's Friday.
Yeah, and of course, I've, uh, resorted to using KY intrigue lubricant, uh, ever since
Sir George W Bush has been fucking me up the ass. Mine's won't make it a little bit more pleasurable.
All right. They're really poor, Bart. I got to get out of here. I got to get to take a shower.
I got to get ready for my photo shoot. As a final thought of the week, well, you have homework.
The final thought is, please, please, please. I look at these constitution classes. It's
really interesting. It'll enrich you as a human being. It'll give you a history lesson you've never
had before. Even if you are a United States citizen and was schooled in the United States,
uh, it's certainly something that I am completely engrossed in and loved watching and
and I can't wait until I finish all of them. The final thought? Well, I think,
you know what? I'm going to say it in a song this time. Let the organization for the preservation
to the soundtrack of our lives give us the final thought of the week.
What is segregation? I don't know what generation is. Uh, what is big injury?
I don't know what degree it is. What does, uh, hatred me?
Uh, I don't know what it is. Uh, what is prejudice?
Um, I think it's when it's in my thick.
I don't know what I think. I don't know what I think. I don't know what I think.
Anybody?
See my old friend John. Can you tell me where he's called?
We're at the trademark. The motor case is coming by here. I can see many motor cycles coming by
and I'm police motor cycle. Just have to come on the radio. Oh, goodness, so long and tough to know.
So take up the motor case, something is happening here. We understand it is fishy.
The presidential car coming up now. We know it's the presidential car. We see Mrs Kennedy's feet still.
There's a secret service man. Let's go over the top of the car. We're at the top of the car.
We're at the top of the car. We're at the top of the car. We're at the top of the car. We're at the top of the car. We're at the bottom of the car.
We're at the bottom of the car. We can't see who has been hit.
If anybody has been hit, but if there's something is wrong here, something is terribly wrong.
I mean behind the motor case, we need to follow the motor motor cycle. We're going to park on the hospital.
The interruptives programmed to bring you a special bulletin.
Dollars Texas, the flash, apparently official, President John F. Kennedy, died at 1 p.m.
Central Stanford Times.
That's your cold days ahead. But it will not matter with me now.
Because I've been to the mountain top.
Like anybody, I would like to live.
No one can be certain who next was suffered from some fenced black of bloodshed.
And Bobby, can you tell me when he's gone?
There, your audience just said he meant that we've been here too long already.
So, well, my thanks to all of you and I'm going to Chicago and that's with me.
Senator Kennedy has been shut. Is that possible?
Oh my God. Senator Kennedy has been shut.
There's a lot to say about hold of a man.
Oh, apparently. That's part of this guy.
That's a guy. That's a guy.
There away from the guy.
That's your guy.
His hand is frozen.
Take a hold of his arm and break it if you have to.
It is so.
All right.
I can't break it.
That's a guy and break it.
That's a guy.
Hold him, hold him.
We don't want another off-road.
Like it or not, we live in times of danger and uncertainty.
That is the way he lived.
That is what he needs us.
I'd rather need not be idealized or enlarged and dead beyond what he was alive.
Be remembered simply as a good and decent man.
So wrong and try to write it.
So are suffering and tried to heal it.
So are war and pride to stop it.
Those of us who loved him and who take him to his rest today,
pray that what he was to us.
What he wished for others was someday come the past for all the world.
As he said many times, in many parts of this nation,
those he touched and who sought to touch him.
Some men's seat things as they are and say why.
I dream things that never were and say why not.
But for him we come.
What is segregation?
I don't know what segregation is.
What is bigotry?
I don't know what bigotry is.
What does hatred mean?
I don't know what is prejudice.
I think it's when it's in my seat.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery.
Pajo and limite.