Hey Peyton Manning, that you won the Super Bowl, what are you going to do now?
I've all listened to the DSC 530 now.
A $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking trees, man.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing this out of the curry.
Where is he scenario?
You're not just now right out the window.
I have to hold my head just like this.
Even I won't go while I'm sinking.
Down in slow, there is only one thing you know.
You cannot beat the bad guy standing till two.
Where is he on the Super Bowl?
When you don't want to survive, it goes going
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, you, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah
I'm gonna get here that bass line. You know that driving fun's got to come from one man.
Munk, brand new.
Here in it, before it's even on, the podcast music network.
Awesome.
It's your daily source code coming to you from the Curie Manor,
from the affluent suburb of Suri known as G-Town, West Side, represent.
It's Monday, everybody. How you doing?
Oh, man. I cannot believe it. This free Trinity thing.
I have so much material.
And it's not just people calling in and writing emails about Trinity.
It's all kinds of stuff.
And it's just like, all right, boom, all of a sudden we've got a whole bunch of
what we call this audience engagement.
Yeah, that's it.
You know, I had the perfect, I could do three shows actually.
At three hour show is what I'm saying here.
It would be a different type of show.
And I play a lot more music and no one has time to listen that crap.
But that's how much it's coming in.
You know, I had a perfect, perfect weekend.
And let me just tell you about it, brief.
Before I get into that, do you hear that little, like,
horrible in the background?
Part of my weekend was getting most of the, of Adam's attic all cleared up and
and all the wiring done, etc.
And I still have this just minor minor ground loop.
And it's because of the second monitor that I've plugged in.
That I'm now using because it's a lot better than the ground loop noise was before.
I think somehow it's, it's interacting with the docking station for the
creative labs card that I have plugged in.
I think it's just too much, too much stuff strapped on to the, to this poor
Vio.
But anyway, I do enjoy having the secondary monitors, so it doesn't bother you,
doesn't bother me.
All right, perfect weekend.
Let me tell you Saturday, wake up, Patricia and I were really early,
like it's 630 and was just a beautiful day.
Five knots of wind, just blue sky, nice and crisp.
And not a cloud to be seen anywhere.
It was, it was just one of those fantastic days.
It almost felt like it was, you know, like we're on a ski vacation in Austria without
the snow.
And Captain Dan and Hyde and I had agreed to do some instrument training.
So I went to Farrowks rolled out the Delta Sheriff.
Of course, he would call it in, said that she was looking pretty lonely and pretty
sad.
And we flew for about an hour.
Now instrument training, it's really all about training your brain to
rest your instruments.
That's probably the best way to put it.
And of course, learning to focus on these instruments and translate what you're reading on,
there's basically four major dials that you got to look at.
But, you know, focusing on that while you're flying the aircraft and while you're doing all kinds of
other things like switching radios and checking your fuel, your engine, you know, all these things that
just have to have to take place as you're flying.
And it's really, it's really millimeter work.
You know, every little input you make makes a big difference.
Because, you know, when you're looking outside and you're flying the plane, you know, it's kind of like
and high and high.
And I coordination.
Yeah, it's more much.
And you know, you can, and it deviates a little bit.
But when you're doing some precision flying, it's, you know, it's a, it's a whole different
ballgame.
So what you do is you get these, they call them foggles.
It's basically like safety goggles, except you can't really see through.
Like a little portion down near your nose, a lower part of your eye is, is actual into
the rest is all frosted.
So you can only see your instruments.
And even that's not not that easy to look at them because, you know, you got sunglasses on
and then you got the foggles on.
But you cannot see outside.
And, of course, Captain Dan acted as a safety pilot and instructor.
And then, you know, you know, make you do all kinds of things.
You know, turn and laugh.
You have to do a standard rate turn.
It's like 15 degrees.
And it's really, it's a big challenge.
I caught it on pretty quick, but still, it's just going to take a lot of practice because,
you know, that's basically one part.
But then, you know, you got to be changing radios.
You got to be paying attention to what vectors you're being given.
And it's all kinds of stuff that, that, that goes on.
Very, very heavy workload, as we say in the, in the aviation business.
So that was a lot of fun.
Of course, it was nice move there, which is great because it's much easier to learn new things
instead of fighting the elements to keep the aircraft.
Basically in the sky.
And then we stopped, you know, before even went up flying,
I had a big, big breakfast, which is the fair oak's airfield version of,
the full English breakfast.
And it just, it was perfect.
You know, like, oh, I feel great.
I slept great.
I was up early.
Go flying.
We came back.
We had a coffee.
Then we went back and we did another hour of training.
You know, went home.
It was, you know, it was nice.
I had, oh, Christina was staying over at, at Indiana's house.
So Patricia and I had the house to ourselves for the first time.
So, you know, we watched television.
We laid by the fire.
You can use your imagination.
But it was really, it was perfect, you know.
And then Sunday, oh, I spent a lot of time cleaning up the attic.
And I have, what is it?
Probably about 15 boxes left.
We'll really get in there.
And you'll see it.
I'll take some pictures.
I'll put them up when I'm, when I'm ready.
And today, it's, well, back to the old, back to the old grind, which, of course, is,
got that, I don't know about that ground loop noise.
It's pretty irritating.
Maybe it's, it's not, you can't even hear it.
Maybe it's just in my headset, who they'll know is.
And of course, last night around 11 p.m.
The Super Bowl kicked off, which was being carried live by ITV in the United Kingdom.
And I have to say, ITV completely fucking ruined the whole experience.
You idiots.
Ah.
They so misunderstand what the Super Bowl is about.
It's not a sporting event.
I mean, this is really Yang's versus the Brit stuff.
We got some more of that coming up too, by the way.
It's not just a sporting event.
You know, it's like, who, and the UK gives a shit about the teams.
It's a show.
It's a whole freaking show.
And please, in the show, you need to include the commentary by the American commentators.
You need to include the American commercials.
That's part of the show.
And so they have like their own guy.
And yeah, yeah, it's, you know, two American guest hosts on.
But, you know, it was silly ass lame set.
You know, a lot of, a much more background noise than any other booth.
You know, just a little puny chairs and just dumb chatter, you know.
And jokes, you know, and kind of like Terry Wogan.
Yang's you won't know who he is, but Terry Wogan makes kind of like,
you know, comments about the Eurovision song contest.
Yeah, it was a little bit of that vibe.
I was like, oh, man, you're fucking ruining the whole show.
Did you see how that thing started?
I mean, to have Billy Joel go into the, or as the UK ITV1 presenter said,
Billy Joel.
And you can tell really bothered me.
And it really ruined the experience.
A lot of the experience.
Billy Joel finishes the, the anthem.
And was it five jets?
Fly right over the stadium right on cue.
I mean, that's masterful, man.
That is only, that is show business the way I think only Americans can put it down.
It was, that was awesome.
And then the half time show with Prince.
And I got to tell you, I've been a huge fan of Prince for many, many, many, many, many years.
I've met him, he's an awesome guy.
And, you know, he's, he's one of us, man.
He's against the man.
You know, he, he told Warner Brothers records to shove it.
That was that whole, the artist formerly known as Prince thing, you know.
And he went out on his own and he, and he, and he does his own thing.
And he's very successful.
And he kicked ass and to sing purple rain in the rain.
It was just awesome, man.
It really, really was.
And I love the, like the, the phallic, good, well, like all guitars of phallic, of course.
But, you know, with the shadow and all that, that was pretty cool.
I presume they showed that in the U.S.
But anyway, so actually watched that this morning because I was so fed up with, with the, with the ITV1 coverage.
You ruined it.
You completely ruined it.
It's a whole show.
You can't just take one piece of the show out.
That's not the way it works.
I understand, of course, they have to sell their own commercials.
I'd rather watch some stupid extra commercials just to see the commercials that came out in the U.S.
Which apparently I haven't seen any, you know, any blog posts about anything spectacular or fascinating.
I thought, I did Apple doing ad.
Someone told me they were doing an ad.
Go daddy ad was okay.
I think the outtakes and the legal stuff or legal stuff, the band stuff that didn't pass.
I thought that was better than what really made it on the air.
So anyway, so as I said, perfect, perfect, perfect weekend.
Hennem, this is Chris Christensen.
I wanted to send thanks to you and to the gang at Potcho for the sponsorship from Sheraton that I had for my show, the amateur traveler that happened in December.
I just spent the money and I thought you might be interested in knowing that I did two things.
One is I gave an iPod shuffle in a contest to my listeners to thank them for their faithful patronage.
And the other one is I just bought tickets to Istanbul to go visit a exchange student we had from Turkey who lived with us for a while,
who has been bugging me to go and see him for quite some time.
I'm told his father keeps saying that my brother is coming, my brother is coming.
So I thank you all for enabling that trip to happen.
I hope that we can manage to support my travel habit and the fashion to which I'd like to.
In the future, thanks again, or as I hope you say interchish.
Saloon and host Chikolene, or thank you and goodbye.
Excellent.
Yeah.
Well, you know what?
You don't have to thank me, man, because you're building your own property there.
You own media property.
That's what we're trying to do.
And I love the fact that you reinvested it.
And I'm sure you're going to do not just the reinvestment on the iPod shuffle that you gave out,
but I'm sure you're also going to do something with your visit to Turkey.
You know, I'm just hoping that I sent an email to Barbara, the Polo Alto podcaster.
And let me see.
Okay, yeah.
I was supposed to call her at 2.30, but man, it's already 3 o'clock.
I'm telling you, it took so long to prep this show.
Because of all this awesome stuff that you guys have been sending in.
And not just about Trinity, of course.
Dude.
Greetings from Finland.
You asked about how to pronounce Nokia correctly.
Yes, usually it's almost right.
It's Nokia.
Not Nokia.
But Nokia.
Simply.
And easily.
It's from Finland.
So am I.
So this is Hessu.
What's faster himself?
Long time Charlie.
Love her.
Finding up.
Bye bye.
Nokia.
Everybody say it now.
Damn, as you could paid for saying that.
And now we're from our sponsor.
It's the Yanks.
Versus the Brits.
We'll drive each other crazy.
But everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let's just like you and me.
It's the Yanks.
And the Brits.
The Yanks.
Versus the Brits.
Mind the gad.
And this is Nick from London.
I've been listening to the show for about 18 months now.
Quietly.
Without engaging or providing feedback.
Normally because although I have an 8-erge,
pedant that I am, to correct you on certain points or engage in debate.
There's usually another pedant out there who's far more able and keen and willing to do so.
But something's been driving me nuts that nobody else has picked up on.
It's that letter of the alphabet that comes after G.
For some reason, you've got to the deer head that was Brits say,
H.
Well, you know, and I'm so happy we're going to,
Would you someone picked up on this?
You Brits do say H.
I hear it all the time.
In fact, I've heard it so much that I decided to adapt to it.
Particularly now that I have a H.D.
Because even when I called the Sky People,
The Sky Satellite people, you know, when I said,
I got an H.D. by what kind?
What?
An H.D.
H.D.
Ah, you have a H.D.
So a lot of use are saying it, okay?
And it's it's H.
You're right first time.
Clearly you've heard some people say H.
And assume that we all do it.
Well, we don't.
Or if we shouldn't.
Well, but, you know,
I hear a lot of television too, man.
And if it's on TV, I'm going to presume that everyone kind of does it.
It's the same as, um,
Well, I know this is wrong, but the TH here in the UK.
Oh, man.
Doesn't that drive you guys nuts as the originator of the language that you continuously pronounce it as an F?
Yeah, if I hear Keith one more time on East Enders, I'm going to kill myself.
People do I admit, but it's just plain wrong.
But there is something slightly odd about the way we tend to use that letter in words in this country,
this country, in my case, being Britain.
If you're desperately portion, perhaps have a received pronunciation,
you would generally drop the her sound from the start of the word,
only when it's prefix by the word A, or as it would become Anne.
I was staying in an hotel, or you might describe
Trinity's room across America as an historic event.
But curiously might celebrate the event by having an extra portion of herbs on their pizza, not herbs.
That said, if you have a bit of an extra accent, perhaps you're a cocky, or for less.
Wait a minute, I'm confused now.
Is it the holy herb, or the holy herb, or the...
What am I supposed to say?
You might naturally drop your hues anyway, regardless of whether it's prefix by A or Anne.
For instance, you might stay in an hotel, Danny East End, and perhaps if it's a particularly historic event,
have some herbs on your pizza, night.
Where, of course, I would stay in a hotel, and even if it wasn't a particularly historic event,
probably still have some herbs on my pizza.
Anyway, glad we got that straight, so it's hd from now on, please.
Well, okay.
Hd from now on, then, if anyone disagrees, let me know, okay, because I want to do it right.
But there is one slightly more serious thing I'd like to pick you up on, and that's your friend Trinity.
Now, I really don't want to piss on your chips here.
That might need some explanation, and he acts for us as the Brit's moment.
But this idea of taking Trinity across America is, in principle, great, but you need to be very careful about how you portray this.
Particularly if you start shouting out about Trinity's green credentials.
The green thing to do is not to drive her anywhere, because as soon as you take her anywhere, she's producing green house gases as she burns fuel.
Sure.
I'm not necessarily trying to play up the green thing.
I'm not even against big oil.
In fact, I think big oil is doing a fine job at getting oil, keeping those running.
Again, those profits, they're reinvesting them. They really aren't. They have to.
But that'll be it. You know, that's for the next 50 years, and then we're done.
It's more about independence, freedom, free Trinity.
She is producing less of a negative impact than the equivalent journey in a petroleum diesel or petrol based car, because she's not as dependent on petroleum.
But nonetheless, she is producing greenhouse gases.
Is that true?
Does the vegetable oil produce greenhouse gases? I'm not so sure about that.
Same don't do this, but just during the trip, don't proclaim some great green credentials, which really don't bear close examination.
For instance, you might want to promote the idea that by drying Trinity across America, you've converted a number of people to buy a diesel.
And thereby reduced overall a dependency petroleum based car.
Yeah, I appreciate it. I appreciate the pronunciation, correction, and the thought about Trinity.
No problem, and as you'll see here, coming up, it's not about the greenness. It's about the independence.
Now we're from our spine here.
It's the yanks versus the brits.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
Let's just like you and me, it's the yanks and the brits.
The yanks versus the brits.
Mind the gap.
I'm just looking at, oh man, I'm looking at all the Gmail.
It's too much. I'm telling you it's too much. This one's awesome.
This came in. Who's this from?
Sinclair.
Sinclair says, uh, perhaps this is a true metro sexual moment.
And he sent a link to an article, which I've got to put into the show notes, a daily source code.com.
A new product is enough to make your hands stand on end.
It's a new hair product. It's bullseeming.
An upmarket hairdresser is taken a leaf out of Cameron Diaz's book.
This is from Metro. This is a free newspaper, Metro.co.uk.
Of course, making the comparison to something about Mary.
They give you a 45 minute intense commissioning treatment used using
Thurabred Seaman from Aberdeen Angus Bulls at a farm and treasure or the Cheshire.
I'm really, I'm really worried. Now I'm at pronunciation.
Hey, it's said to offer the ultimate shine for 55 pounds.
Uh, Harry's H-A-R-I.
In Night's Bridge, London is the hairdresser who is offering the streamer's combined.
The organically produced Seaman with the root of protein-rich plant Katera.
The mixture is massaged into the client's Othsexy.
The mixture is massaged into the client's hair after it's been shampooed.
Then the customer has put under a streamer.
So the treatment penetrates the hair.
Finally, it's blow-dried.
This is supposed to be really good.
Let me just copy this link here for a second.
Send that to Patricia.
Hello.
Adam.
Is your drugs London correct?
Oh, man.
It's him, Charles. He's calling in and he's drunk.
Uh, hello.
This is Charles, your drunk London.
And I am.
You said the other day, Charles, why don't you find out, don't I?
Been at the waiting to unleash the drunk in the...
Oh, yeah.
Here I am.
Sydney at home just got off the tube.
And I am drunk.
And I'm happy for it.
And I've got so many barking, barking, so many topics to come.
You know, this is what I love.
They say children and drunk people tell the truth.
This is what I love about Charles.
He's not afraid to experiment.
I mean, I've been taking notes.
Like, um, five, three, five.
Jade, goodie.
She says, H.
Uh, no, no fucking, no one says H.
It's not an English thing.
There's a H.
Now I'm completely convinced.
It's not H.
Fuck that.
H.
H. D.
Not H.
But who says that?
A horrible, yeah.
Who's used me on burping?
I'm burping.
I'm just saying.
I'm probably saying, I'm just saying.
Oh, I dropped my snooze.
I'm a London man who's just about to...
I don't smoke, but I take snooze.
When I go to Sweden, I love the Sweden.
I'm a Sweden file.
I love the Sweden.
Anyway, yeah, H.
No, but that.
Some people say H.
If you want to hear more from Charles,
the drunken Londoner, and you're listening to us now in serious stars.
So, uh, 102.
You'll have to go to dailysourcecode.com
and download the rest of the show.
The horrible, not H is what it is.
Um, look, I go to one of those real quick.
Go to Australia.
It's fucking amazing.
Go to the Witt Sunday.
Really.
There's a fan features.
Beautiful crystal clear water.
Oh, it's still out on the boat.
I see what he's doing.
What he's doing is he's going through all the shows and he wrote down notes when
everyone was listening and now it's all coming out.
Okay, I gotta go to Australia.
Let's clear.
Go Anna?
And I big, big fucking Lizard.
Amazing.
Okay.
Next.
Well, you know what, I could just round the line.
It's boring.
You're listening to me.
You're going to blah, blah.
That's it.
You're playing the comment.
Um, so, you know what, I'm just going to all write an email
or I would call you a comment, lots of video comment or something. But, um, food
congratulations on becoming a homo, uh, homo, no. Um, coming down.
Sounds very London. No, man. A boy, son.
I fucking miss a regular more man and now bitch. That's not good is it.
I mean, he sounds London. They were sound like a queen.
He sent, he oops. He sent something wrong there. He sent in an anecdote, which I'll
say for another day, unless you luckily broke it up into two parts. Lots of people
who haven't heard from in a while are calling up, uh, member, uh, Pablo called in from
Ecuador. Uh, and I said, you know, how are things over there? And, you know, how's the
government and how stuff going? And, here he is, uh, Pablo Ecuador.
Hi, Adam Davis, Pablo from Ecuador. I'm going to some terms that bathrooms, especially from
government, uh, places. I really, really nasty. People here is really, really bad.
I guess that's just from here, but from all around the world, people are really,
really nasty. They do really bad things in bathrooms. Uh, just to say hi, I, um, my wife called
last time, but she had problems meeting the message. Uh, she is her name is also Patricia.
So, bye. Guy, Pablo Ecuador, everybody. Kind of like that plan words, Pablo Escobar,
Pablo Ecuador. Yeah, man. I, I think I might be missing some, uh, some voicemail messages,
because Rosie, uh, said she phoned in with the report on Trinity, and I haven't seen it anywhere.
I usually that stuff comes into my, uh, into my Gmail, and I all, well, I, I know what I'm
going to get next from her because she said, hey, man, I got to go to, I don't know, it's San
percent of Barbara or Monterey. I don't know, she was driving somewhere, like a 500 mile
round trip. And I think she left yesterday and it's coming back today. And she asked if, uh, you know,
that, now the Trinity was back up to cruising speed. If she could take her on this, you know,
more or less a test run. And I said, yes. So, you know, we're going to have a, uh, a little chat
about Trinity in a couple of minutes here on the show. Hopefully, she's still doing well. And I said,
well, of course, I said to Rosie, I said, well, of course, you can borrow Trinity, uh, under the
condition that you do a video podcast. So, we'll have that to look forward to. For sure.
Um, okay. Let's see. Oh, yes. Oh, this is also, man, people are really digging this thing.
Thank you, Jeff. Let's see. Yep, it's, uh, it's definitely catching on. Brian and
Nigmas says, hey, Adam, I'm writing to say that I totally agree with you on the subject of
posh pigs in the potty. But I do have to draw your attention back to the century thing. One of the
colors and DSC, I heard talking about the phantom shitter, you suggested posting a century outside
the bathroom. Well, that's exactly what some of the poshists of posh bathrooms have. I bet you've
been to a restaurant country club or nightclub. Uh, let me see. Yes, no, no. Uh, I don't go out anywhere.
Uh, uh, where there's been some dude standing by the sink ready to hand you a towel. Sometimes
they even have mince hair products. Uh-huh. I got some great hair products for you now.
Shots of espresso, even. Well, middle class folks like myself are left scratching or heads
wondering, should I have tipped that guy? The club owners are left happy with the satisfaction that
this guy is the bathroom police. It's hard to take a dump in the urinal. P on the wall,
string up toilet paper streamers or etch your name into the mirror with that guy there.
I'm not that I've tried or anything. I'm just saying. And honestly, I've seen the same kind of bathroom
monitor station in restrooms of even more shady night clubs, presumably to ensure people aren't having
sex or using drugs in the bathroom because no club owner wants the publicity or legal hassles
of someone ODying in their club. That's right. Now, I'd rather have people shit on my walls.
So it does appear that there's some habitual shit here. So to speak that we need to talk about.
Did you dare in the office? Laurius even? A beautiful place. Going with the buildings completely
full and sitting all detail. I think it's sort of same from the yellowing gulfed. And I'm just
calling him with another comment on, apart from how it sits, he may be crisped out with by now,
but here's his on the me, right. So I still work for a national news paper, the broad tea variety
and instrumental stable. And for me, first news is developing a nest. The old building
grazing rate, in a converted sort of way, I'll say, all one is to keep sleeping prisoners or something
in many years ago. And in the ravages there, over the walls, at a fairly rough surface. And there's
one person who has to stand up, right to lose the content of his muscles and leave it stuck to
that. Speaking of that, it's under wall and everywhere, a week and a month that grew into
a lot of things. It's so totally, totally nasty. And of course, the next part of our discovery
into the topic of our posh people, pigs is, is this a male poshness thing or a female poshness thing?
Hi, Adam, it's CG here with a report on that are people, posh people, potty pigs. I've just talked to
the contracts cleaners of the place where I work and got a report from them that women are the
worst, especially those in the fancy mull gowns. They're a report state, but as well as the usual
vomit and two smears on all surfaces, these women leave the nicarus or panties, if they're
in the American, it must not be hindering all over the place and right to read messages with
lipstick on the mirror, etc. Which brings me to another point that James from Newcastle was saying
that men are the worst, actually reminded me of a story about German block of flats that was
being refurbished and many of the toilets the pipe work had to be replaced because they were
corroded, but not all of the pipes in all of the flats were affected. After some investigation
was found that in flats where women only lived, the pipes were not corroded. It was mainly due
to men and after the pipes had all been fixed and redecorated, the men were asked to sit
to pee and this became a movement in Germany, forgive the pun, called sit-son, pinkland. There's
a sign which can be seen in many guest houses and hotels in Germany now. Gentlemen,
can I suggest that in order to save some of the mess that's created in the bathroom,
a new probably will notice it unless you've actually taken the trouble to clean up the bathroom,
much of us can be avoided by sitting to pee. I know it sounds a bit girly, but there you are.
Go to hell. There you have it. Holder. Uh-huh, of course. Excellent bathroom habits.
All folders have them. Well, this is fascinating stuff. I'm very glad you in lighten us with
this bit of information about sets in tinkland and I think I might give it a go. At this point,
we have new toilets in the curry manner and two of them have not have to be re-adjusted because
the lids fall down which is a real pain in the ass and if you don't watch it, you can be a pain
somewhere else. It's like it's a two-hand operation knowing when I go for a slash.
So I don't have an extra hand to hold up the lid. And now that I know this,
maybe a Petr- the lady Petrish has been asking me to sit down when I pee for 20 years and I just-
it's hard, man. It just doesn't feel right. It feels- yeah, girly isn't the word. It just- it feels-
I don't know. It's like unnatural. I haven't been doing it that way.
But I'm willing to give it a try now that I hear that because, well, clearly, we'll keep the value
of my home up there. Hey, it's not just in Europe in the United States that the
posh people seem to have issues. Why it even takes place in Asia.
Adam, hi. It's Melvin from Seoul. You're also about the Asian men rooms habit as well.
Asia's a big place but here in South Korea, let's go get used to the cleaning lady,
wandering around where you're standing and studying the quality of the tiling.
Which fabric would come at her? You don't start to wonder. You think Korean men have a size problem
because it's all over the floor. You get so close that I haven't taken a leak and they back away
to give her a shake and it goes everywhere. Oh, right, mess. You could do a whole pod show,
literally a whole pod show on the ins and outs of Korean men's bathroom habits. If you want to
know more, give me a call. Take care. Oh, man. You gotta give us the ins and outs of Korean men's bathroom
habits. Are you kidding me? That's awesome. This is this is fantastic news. They step back and
give it a shake. What's up with that? I think we have a lot of investigating still to do on the topic
of our posh people, potty pigs. Our posh people pigs by godly goshit is a fine question. Yes,
it is our posh people pigs. Sorry, little miss fire there.
One Jess Smith after another.
All right, finally sorted it out.
Trinity Trinity. Oh, yeah, baby. Check this one out. I am pretty much convinced that any egg
non-colored Mercedes diesel has been at one time a taxi in Germany. This is still the default delivery
for taxis and I often asked myself how this particular shade was picked, surely not as the
result of a popularity contest. Be that as it may, since the free Trinity project may well be
crossing the bomb to blighty. I'd suggest you think about going a bit further to Germany in fact.
Trinity comes home. I think the idea would resonate with the German media.
It's Trinity's tour, it'll cut down the boulevard of Berlin. The ranks in the DSC audience could learn
a little bit about how the German greens rose to exert influence on society and the government
as far back as the 80s. German fans of the Charlie, and I'm sure there are a good number,
would certainly welcome the possibility of participating in the Preternity Project.
We bridge will inevitably laugh ourselves silly when well-wishers in Germany shout out.
Good to fart. It's just an idea from welcome in Abu Dhabi.
I put an incorrect link to the Trinity Google group. It's since been corrected so you can
get it now from the DailySourceCode.com show notes.
Hi Adam, this is Mark from the North. Quite so I've fluent suburb. Sorry, don't just woking.
Woking, by the way. I heard that it used to be London's graveyard
until some German bombed woking in World War II or a couple of Germans I guess.
And there's like bones and bits everywhere. But I drive through woking all the time. I'm away
to a ferroaks to the airfield. So nice little places I sit by.
Suggest something for Trinity's World Tour. Well, two things actually.
Firstly, if you don't have any listeners in Iceland to drive for us, you make
away over the Atlantic. I'll gladly step in. I spent six months there last winter.
I would love to go sightseeing again, but this time in the baby poo,
colored station wagon, as I believe she's now described. But more importantly, if you thought
about going on top gear, this round the world challenges exactly the sort of wacky cast stuff
that they love. And frankly, I can't get the image out of my head of the stick driving around
the circuit in Trinity with you cowering in the passenger seat. It takes us course.
Well, that new towering over Richard Hammond, even more than Clarkson usually does.
Oh, one more thing. What ever happened to the Flying Fools project? I was going to volunteer.
I'm learning to fly out of ferrocs at the moment. I'm about 10 hours into my PPL.
So I think I could probably qualify as both flying and, well, a full
I'm sure I can sign off with tailwinds though. Yeah, let me know what you think. Absolutely. Thanks.
Bye for now. Yeah. I just got to have time, man. It's like, you know, this Trinity thing is
taking over the world now. And what an excellent idea. I think you're right. I think that we actually
can get pretty far with this. Is that I've got people working on the case? Let's see if we can
rile this puppy up, spin it up big time. Although I can just hear Clarkson now, you know,
it's like, of course, it'll start off by taking the the Mick by taking the Mick out of podcasting.
As Adam Curry does some kind of a radiate internet radio show. And a couple of his mates across
the world, I've decided to send this biodiesel pipe piece of junk around the globe.
That was a pretty shitty Clarkson I admit, but working on it. Adam's guy here with the Alaska
pod show. Do you have any idea? Well, yeah, you do. How great the daily source code is.
Do you realize? Yeah, if our world leaders had their own daily source code, how productive
this world might be how we think. You know what it is? It's not that we need our current world
leaders to start doing podcasts and start really writing web logs. Someone who does a podcast or
who writes a web log will most likely be the next leader of the free world. That's or maybe, yeah,
it could be in 2008. It's going to be someone like that. So I think it's going to be the other way around.
It might get solved. Well, you know, I'm really excited about this Trinity thing,
because this is just another great example. I'm just thrilled about this project and I'm behind
110% or more. I don't know. Is there a percentage? You get my point. I, you know, Alaska is
and has become the poster child for global warming here in the states. You know, we want to start
tapping into more oil drilling up here, natural gas. We've got all kinds of things going on. We're
still not moving forward as far as looking to the alternative fuel. So in that, I'm really
supportive of Trinity's message. And I think how great would it be to have her start her journey
from Alaska and maybe we could get a Canadian neighbor involved. And, you know, I could drive to the
border of Canada, Canada, take over, head on down into the states and then on across the United
States. I mean, from the far west to the far east, you know, there goes Trinity. And so I'm
all for it. You know, we have a healthy network of bio-fuel states. I should say actually backyard
bio-fuel stations, a healthy network of guys and girls that are producing some great fuels.
In fact, I got an interview I'm trying to nail down and I'll share that with you if you're just
it. But, uh, yep, Alaska welcomes Trinity. And, you know, it'd think it'd be fantastic and
just some organizations would definitely get behind you up here and helping you promote this. So
thanks for everything you're doing. Thanks for your daily source code. Take care of yourself again.
All right, bye. Thank you. Thank you, Scott. Yeah, of course Alaska's on the list as this
Canada, but I think we're going to have to do her on the second tour around. What we'll do is kind of
like an orange peel. We got to start with the states first. No doubt about it. So we'll go to the
states. Then we're going to start going around the globe and we'll go up and we'll come, oops, sorry,
hit the mic stand. I'm actually using my hands to show you this. And that's when we'll come through
Alaska and we'll go through Canada. Something like that. One more on Trinity. And, you know,
again, this is just about the whole thing you said about the backyard biodiesel. That's exactly
what I'm looking for. I'm looking for mom and pops. I'm looking for people. Just people who are
doing something independent. And in my mind, completely revolutionary. Hey, Adam,
right Adam's here. I love the free Trinity idea. Maybe you can refer to Washington, DC,
and make a stop by the Pentagon, where there's an alternative fuel station that sells both ethanol
and B20, 20% biodiesel. I film my jet of TDI there whenever possible. On DSC 537, you
made some excuses for the excess profits of big oil. I agree that they will need tons of investment
dollars if they're going to keep us supplied with as much oil in the future as they are today.
It's getting harder and harder. Translate that to more expensive. To find and produce
a massive quantity of oil that's the economy demands. My preference will be for oil companies to
invest some of their cash into a tonnek power, or the technology offers huge room for improvement.
As I told you on DSC 367, I spent a few years driving around a few hundred feet underwater
on a zero-heemission, a tonnek submarine that ran for about a decade and a half without any new fuel.
The boats at my friend Rirem and Willie Colardis is building today will operate for a full
30-year lifetime without any new fuel at all. Just imagine what the world could do if we would
do a better job of harnessing the incredible power of the atom for peaceful purposes like electricity
and maybe even airplanes. If you want to hear more about a better way to produce power,
check out the Atomic Show at Atomic. That's the podcast network.com. You can also find out
at a really cool engine technology company at AtomsEngines.com. Good luck on the free turnity tour
and think about getting more power from Atoms. Oh dude, I'm telling you, if you could put an Atomic
engine in Trinity, absolutely, I'm all for that. I don't know much about it and you know,
I don't want to sidetrack the free turnity project with a whole bunch of talk about Atomic Energy
and the pros and cons and what you do with the waste and all that, but I'm totally into it.
I want to try all that stuff and maybe that is the next step, but still that's not something
you can really do in your backyard or can you? Is all that it really takes is just a flux capacitor
and then and you're set? Please don't send anything about Atomic Energy. Let's just, you know,
definitely go listen to that podcast, but let's keep it on track here for a free turnity.
Okay, I got a hurry up the show because I've got a barbro standing by. We're going to talk
about putting the whole project together.
Right on, thank you Jeff Smith for the go to thejessmith.com. If you want to have all kinds of
cool songs and jingles and stuff for your show. Just a little, uh, I got to finish up because I got
to finish up the tube, the TLA noisy tube topic. Otherwise people keep sending me stuff about that.
Here's one from John Glasscock. That's something to do with different tubes, tubes of a different
sort. Hey, Adam, what should be done to support breast cancer research is to have a calendar of
young women's breasts with the proceeds going to the appropriate philanthropy. It would be a good start
to have a pod show count. Scott, what is it? John, what is this? It would be a good start to have a
pod show calendar with the top podcasters offering breasts shots to propel the calendar idea at
10 bucks a pop. You could raise about $1 million and also diminish the anti-topeless anxiety of
US women to sun themselves. We as men need to get our hands on the issue and make sure that our
women are not lumped into the gross statistics. Man, that's a lot of subjective, a lot of
interesting words you use there. Well, dude, you know, I mean, I don't want to start this project,
but I would obviously support it and I think that, you know, I'd offer my breasts to the calendar.
I mean, we're going to mail breasts in there too, can't we? I mean, we can't be hypocritical about it
and, by the way, you know, men suffer from cancer as well. Maybe not, well, maybe we have a
female show breast and male show prostate or something like that. Yeah, you're right, maybe not.
I want to make sure you're again with a note about vowels. You mentioned that you were getting
some noise from your valve amp. This is possibly due to the valves themselves. They do wear out
though, if you haven't had it long, then I'd go to that fact, actually, because the greatest
cause of noise in amplifiers is actually a warm potential, the volume control, as the wipers
scratches across the surface, eventually wears it away and that can introduce noise. So, that's
the first thing to check. If it is evolved, then gently tapping it with your fingernail using
the most important one hand behind your back rule, because you need to do this while it's live,
you can tap about the glass part of the valve and you should be able to irritate as enough
to produce more of the sound that you think is part of the fault. If you cannot identify it,
there's a number printed on the valve. It's fairly easy to type that number into google and find
a replacement. Hope that helps. Cheers. You know, it helps if I open up the mic.
So, here's the good news. I figured out what's wrong with my TLA 5052 valve processor,
which is what gives me the big gehonus, soon to be seen on a calendar near you.
With the move and repatching and rewiring the studio, one of the plugs became a little
either corroded or corrupted or not quite sure. One of the main ones that goes in from the output of
the mixer into the TLA. So, that's what was just on one channel. That's what kind of gave that same
type of impression. There's a noise gates and all kinds of stuff. It would cut in and out.
It was a little tough tracking down, but once I figured out, it turns out, I think the tubes are
just fine. But it is eventually going to happen because I'm a big proponent of leaving the tubes on.
I also leave all my computers on, you know, yes, it consumes more energy, but particularly with tubes.
And I don't know, I've just found that my computers last longer and I'm old enough to have had a
couple of computers and other components. And see, I think there was an email, uh, yeah, Franco from
Rokostitalia. He says I should turn it off. But I, I think keeping it on is better. I really do.
It's just my, my real world experience. So, anyway, when the tubes do start to go,
certainly know what to do. Hey, they're Adam. This is Andrew from Montario, Canada,
giving you a call about your TLA stereo valve processor. I just thought I'd let you know about your
tubes or valves as you call them on that side of the pond. You usually change your tubes every
couple of years or whenever they start sounding bad, they don't sound as silky. So, if you think
it's time to give them a shot, uh, just it's 12x7 and an ECC 83. It's a very common tube pair.
You replace both of them, plug them in, let them warm up and give it a shot and see if it sounds better.
Now, about to, uh, it'll help out. And if you let me for a second, I'd love to promote a podcast I love.
It's called a project studio network. They talk tech sound, all the stuff geeks love to talk about,
uh, big owl and Mike are fantastic hosts and they line up all sorts of great stuff every week. So,
I recommend everyone go over to the project studio network.com website and download a show and check it out.
That's it. Thanks a lot, and folder. Yeah, thanks man. Okay, so now even know what to get. That's fantastic.
So I'll keep that comment because, uh, invariably it's going to happen. The tubes are going to go.
One of these days. Who knows? Maybe the next, uh, the next dwelling we have, you never know.
By the way, you can kind of tell that I've got a new format going for the show, which will help you in,
because it's going long. I just, there's nothing I can do about it.
Excuse me and say I was splendying. Go daddy. Go go daddy.
So I'm trying to do new stuff at the top, uh, you know, personal stuff at the beginning and then
Trinity kind of knew the end. And then topics I want to wrap up after the after Trinity.
Because Trinity is going to go on for a while. That's clear. So I'm wrapping up the, uh,
I'm wrapping up the tubes and, uh, what else is I wrapping up? There's something else.
Okay, although we might want to bring the calendar back. I still like that idea. Okay,
I'm going to play one more song for you.
As suggested by Sir Jersey Todd, as Bordaud would say, she's nice. I like.
Mhm.
Hello, Bob. Like you're moving on.
Moving on.
Fun, Sandoote-Toga auto home.
Hail, there's nothing you can do.
He watches all while I'm still,
How I feel in this way, as a knee,
Can I lay and tear my roads alive?
Can I roll for me a little more?
Can I roll for love to you?
Oh,uke Hello Weir
Weir Weir Weir
I meant so about lots things now
But I know it's right this is true
Something's got me getting down to you
Here's my family room
I need watching you while I stay
And while I'm feeling this way
And I'm going to love you
And I'm going to feel in the way
And here's the world I'm feeling
No, my miss, no
Yeah, yeah, no
And I want you to see me
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey
Much of you I don't stay here
I'm feeling this way
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
And I want you to see me
Hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey
I'm back here, but they're here and they're all around
Him, I roll to love you
Him, I roll to feel in love too
Just from New York
Her name's Laura Lamber, I'm crying for loving you
Find the now on the Pods and Music Network looking for the link
Well, just go to DailySourceCode.com
And that's what you'll be able to find out
Exactly all about her, who influenced her
Why she's called the Pop Rock Maestro
Ah, yes, all that wonderful stuff
All right, I would love to hear from y'all
Even though there's plenty of stuff coming in
I really appreciate it and remember
Link in the show notes to everything including the Google Group for free
Trinity, join up if you want
I still have to parse through everything that came in over the weekend
I'm actually a little bit behind today
Just I got to start my day with less messing around
I guess, I got to get right to it now in the morning
At P Dobs, wait in the satellite windows
Close all kinds of shit going on
So anyway, DailySourceCode.com
Adam at podshow.com
It's going to be a great week everybody
And really excited what we're going to find out about free
Trinity, it's going to be a good time
Please join me here tomorrow
Bye bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best of the brightest
Saved up Daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight