Daily source code listeners, you've got it, the best of the Charlie.
The 60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
The following is an actual pod star conversation. May 1st 2006.
Pod star emergency. This is Adam.
Yeah, I'm stuck at a stop wait.
And the guy on the car next to me is listening to corporate radio so loud.
I can't hear my favorite podcast.
Okay sir, try not to panic. I've just called in an air strike from the pod father.
Bad things happen to people who listen to bad radio.
Is everything alright now sir?
Yes, yes, thank you. Oh, bless you.
Pod star. Tell us where bad radio lives.
And we'll make sure it's gone.
His name is Adam Curry. He's always in a hurry.
No man will write up stories.
Through us from three to three.
His name is Adam Curry.
And both his vision's blurry.
The old song.
Dog that furry.
And deep three.
Then say hope for his name is Adam Curry.
His name is Adam Curry.
Hey, Daily Source co-listers.
This is happy from bedtime stories my kids love.
And welcome to the best of the Charlie.
Let's spend through some of the best stuff that's ever happened on the DSC.
Well, Adam's moving to the new Curry, L.A.
Or whatever he decides to call it.
Well, as you all know, this year Adam got voicemail hotlines.
And as soon as he installed them, he started getting some really, really cool calls.
Like this one from Chino.
Adam, this is George from Chino, man.
I'm doing time up here in Chino.
And we love to listen to the chop chop.
Especially when we're having sex with each other after lights out, man.
You know, I even downloaded a picture of you on the internet.
That I came to my cellmate back when I preached him up and writing like a wetted new old man.
So hey, keep on the good work.
And hey, if you're ever up in Chino,
so we're going to buy for a conjugal visit.
And if you didn't do much trouble, maybe you can smuggle a file in your ass.
Hey, that would be a big help to him, man.
He's out.
Okay, Mark.
I got it.
Over the weekend, I did show Patricia a second life.
And I was a little wary to be quite honest because, you know, she's so smart.
It's like online game.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Okay. What's it about fucking?
I said, well, there's that.
And she said, well, just don't let anyone see you.
Okay.
This is why I love my wife. She's so incredibly smart and with it.
But she was actually fascinated.
And she's been asking a lot of questions.
And she has some pretty good insights.
And we've been talking about business opportunities for second life.
And, you know, people keep asking,
When will we see Lady Patricia in the castle?
I said, well, that could be one hell freezes over.
But her characters are so character-so to your copies.
We have no situations.
If you're inside the way, you're a second life property.
Help. Help.
No, just kidding.
It's your neutral neighbor, comic-stable blogger,
known in second life as comic-signor.
So it was nice meeting you in second life, Adam Kerry.
Thank you for teaching me how to operate Bazooka in second life to shoot down a star ship.
Anyway, I have a question. I have a question to everybody interested in virtual realities.
How to be sure, how to be certain if anonymity must be granted
that the other person in virtual reality is female
and not male who is just pretending to be female.
Maybe your listeners could help out.
So, so, see you in second life neighbor.
Yeah, okay neighbor, that's right, next to the castle in second life.
And if you're just joining, you know, please check this stuff out because
it really will mess with your head.
I mean, I'll be the first guy to share it to point out some really good drugs that won't kill you.
Okay, that's what second life is, secondlife.com.
And so, comic strip blogger purchased a parcel of land right next to the castle, the curry castle.
And he put this huge lighthouse on top of it.
And now, you know, and it's like, okay, when I first moved there, I bought the land.
It was almost no one around.
Now, there's a couple other castles.
It's getting pretty crowded and I have to make some decisions here.
But, you know, I'm trying to be good neighbor.
So, I flew up to the top of comic strip blogger's lighthouse and he was unpacking.
It wasn't a bazooka, it was an atomic RPG.
And it's kind of like the unique, of course, second life is all based on hackers and programmers.
So, it's very common to help out new people.
And, you know, show them the way around.
Because there's always someone who showed me and showed everyone the ropes in the beginning.
And so, I showed them how to unpack it and how to shoot it.
I think, actually, CSB, since you own that spaceship, there's a preference you can set,
which is make, was it make damage permanent?
Something like that.
I think that's the way you can blow stuff off.
Because in the damage, actually, we'll take place and you'll have to rebuild.
You can't just restore it.
Something like that, I'm pretty sure.
So, I was hanging out in second life quite a bit over the weekend.
And it was, once again, a mind-bending experience.
Oh, let me answer that second question, a comic strip blogger.
It's very, very easy.
Now, the way second life is currently run or large portion of it is girls who are online.
Typically, they become an escort.
They make themselves really pretty.
They get hit on all the time by guys.
And then the sooner or later, the pimps come out.
And they say, hey, you know what, you can get hit on by guys in second life all the time.
But if you come over here and dance in my club and if you want, you can become an escort.
You can make money and then you can go shopping.
And there's a lot of shopping in second life.
It's very hard to find male clothing for your avatar.
But there's lots of stuff for women.
I've just tons and tons of stuff.
You can't, in fact, I think this will be hugely successful with women, although probably
you're right comic strip, probably a lot of the cute women who are in there are guys or
young boys trying to make some linden dollars to go and build stuff that can shoot other
people out of the sky.
So there's only one real way to know.
And I've done this myself.
You go shopping with her.
Go shopping with her first.
And that's how you know if it's really a woman or not.
You can just tell.
And so I went shopping with a couple women over the weekend.
Actually, Angie B. She went with myself and I have a business partner in second life.
This is really cool.
I don't want to say her name because I don't know if she wants me to mention that or how
silent or upfront she wants to be about the partnership.
She's an ex escort.
She's stunningly beautiful.
And she really wants to have a purpose in second life.
And I've had some ideas for a while and she's been on for a couple years.
So she knows exactly where to go to get stuff.
She knows all the great designers, all the great engineers, programmers, developers.
We're thinking about sitting up our own sim, which means we even run our own server.
I'm confident we can we can make money out of this.
And you know me, I'm always the guy was looking for a way to commercialize because that's my life.
I like doing things that I have fun doing and make money out of them.
That's kind of what I've always done.
So, and I went shopping with her and with Angie B.
And they bought me some new hair.
And I could tell, you know, it's like, no, I know Angie B is Angie B.
So I know that she's a girl.
And, you know, she shops like a girl.
It's obvious.
So that's the way you tell.
See, as B, you don't need to know anything else.
Just go shopping.
See how they react.
Usually that'll be a dead, a dead giveaway within the first three minutes.
Good morning, Adam.
This is Logan from Southwest Florida.
I just got through listening to you Charlie from fighting.
Well, it's morning in my part of World Anyway, buddy.
I wanted to ask you a question.
I know that you're a person who enjoys the herb.
I'm a few years older than you are.
And I just recently changed the job and changing the job.
I had to take the usual, you know, drug and alcohol tests.
So that then I had to study for the test and had to abstain for like a month and a half or so.
Which is really a pain in the ass.
But anyway, what I would like to ask you know, you smoke.
Oh, who told you that?
So you require the employees of Pod Show to take a drug and alcohol test.
Dude, if I did that.
We'd have no pod show.
That would be a question.
Yes, okay.
Very much respect to you and your family.
I enjoy it in listening since February.
Don't have any intentions starting on old podcasts.
But I am a listener and my right time.
The only thing, buddy, is what someone do the best of the week of the Charlie.
So people can download it, stay on Saturday and get all your highlights of the week.
You know, maybe a hour, hour to half long.
But just raps it all up and cut that off a little.
Oh, you know.
We have no show left over.
Anyway.
It's a good idea.
That's a very good idea, Logan.
I like that a lot.
Did he say the best of the Charlie?
You know, that is a great idea.
Somebody really ought to do that.
Well, the Yanks versus Britz conversation begins to heat up.
And then we hear an interesting song with an interesting requirement.
Hi, Adam.
It's Glenn from the Zeta Show in Cape Town, South Africa.
I thought it sounds engine or your comment regarding your Yanks versus Britz segment on your show.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on a second.
Let's do that differently then.
Let's do it this way.
Let's do this.
And now a word from our sponsor.
It's the Yanks versus the Britz.
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's apparent to see.
They're just like you and me.
It's the Yanks and the Britz.
The Yanks versus the Britz.
Mind the gap.
I had him at Glenn from the Zeta Show in Cape Town, South Africa.
I thought it sounds engine or your comment regarding your Yanks versus Britz segment on your show.
I've got to say that I'm with the Britz on this one.
South Africa and although we have our own cultural identity, we do follow mostly the European trends.
Although we cannot ignore the fact that in some ways the Americans do have an influence on us.
Well, a lot of our programming on TV in the movies.
We watch originates from the USA.
Of course, there is something that the rest of the world likes to mock the Americans about.
I've been to the USA before in one thing that it's me every time.
I go there was how Nationalistic the Americans are.
If it is in American, it isn't good enough.
Ooh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Dude.
Whoa, that's a shot across the bow, my friend.
Particularly from someone coming from South Africa.
I don't know if you will be able to do it by the way.
Quite simply I was quite surprised when Colt played it very well.
Whenever they come in, man English music has always done great in the states.
We love it over there. The thing is is the last lit of the alphabet. The rest of the world pronounced it as stayed.
Yeah, well, you know, that's just silly. Okay. Z is just dumb. It's not a zebra. It's a zebra.
Where does that come from, by the way? Why is that different? Why do we say Z and you say Z? Could someone please enlighten us?
And we know about Z. But we're, uh, they only know it as Z. And hearing Z just confuses them a lot.
One thing I've noticed too over the years is how ignorant some Americans, as well as other foreigners are about South Africa or Africa for that matter.
Meach in the word Africa and connotations negative, although, uh, like poverty, HIV-AIDS, civil wars, etc.
Spring to mind. I think the funniest question that we get asked is where the wild animals, like elephants, tigers and lions, roam our streets.
Where as the reality of that is that such animals are actually roaming in wildlife reserves around the country.
And where our cities are booming metropolis with skyscrapers, tide roads, suburbs, etc.
There are a lot of positives about South Africa and I think it's time for people to take some time out to see them.
And see what a great country South Africa actually is as well as Africa.
Well, Adam, you said you wanted to come to Oswonday, but how about coming to Cape Town and hooking up with a flat around the peninsula?
And instead of drafting dots, we can do a lack of brine instead, or if you guys know it as a barbecue.
Well, and before you come, you can take a listen to the Z.S. show at the Z.S. show.com, search for us in iTunes. Cheers.
Dude, if you said the Z.A. show, you'd have more subscribers.
Thanks, I appreciate it. It makes a lot of sense.
But what you're saying about South Africa, I live in Uganda as a child, not quite South Africa, but yeah, I wouldn't mind going back.
And people do have a wrong perception. It's like a rack, you know, I went to a rack and it was like an eight-lane highway.
From, you know, all the way from Kuwait, from Kuwait, past the border, all the way up to Baghdad.
So I do have something that Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff sent me from Pacific Coast, Hellway.
It's a video, and I'll make sure to put a link to the original source into the show notes for today, dailysourcecode.com.
It's not entirely about masturbation.
Well, my father says you're nifty.
And it's nice.
You've put a photo layer, and we both agree that human rights abuses are unfair.
You understand your feeling, and you're not afraid to share.
And I think I could do something with your hair.
You smell nice, and you'll grow the end.
We both like foreign movies.
My mother says you have that touch of glass.
Well, I can see a shining future where we'll die a log and nurture.
But there's one last thing I feel I need to ask.
Do you take it in the air?
Because you're beautiful and curvy, but unless you're kind of worthy,
There's no way you and me are gonna pass.
Do you take it in the air?
When it comes to brands, you've got a button, but unless you play the bottom,
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to take a pass.
Well, you're adorable, reliable, but is your in-as-playable.
And that's the information that I need.
But you would do it if you love me.
If you're nervous, what about me?
You'll be able to control the death and speed.
Do you take it in the air?
Because I voted in a shipment of the relevant equipment.
I got lubricant and poppers and some brass.
Do you take it in the air?
If you need more information on this type of penetration,
We can always take a course for this class.
You see, I'm not the kind of fellow who can get up on the nail
and know I know I get a little color in my sex.
Well, how they find just so happens that I've brought my nails
wrap on and some meds go into height in the effect.
Ready?
Do you take it in the air?
The wet spots.
Do you take it?
Thank you very much, Mark.
Yoshimoto.
Look at the video.
Actually, you heard the audio only.
Wait until you see the video.
It's fantastic.
Where have these guys been, huh?
Everyone in second life is going around having cyber sex with each other.
Oh, that is so sad.
Please, don't tell me that.
That's sad.
It's not sad.
Oh, I was afraid of that.
No, it's not sad.
I think it's either a...
It's a human thing.
Yeah, I think it's a human thing.
It always ends with fucking some reason.
For some reason.
And I've talked to a couple of the escort girls.
In fact, just about every cute girl in second life
has it one time or another worked, quote, worked.
Well, they will love you Adam Newman.
Yeah, if I give them a thousand lindons.
They love me a long time.
Lindon.
There's a lot of really twisted fantasies.
Yeah.
Oh, that I believe I know about that.
Oh, yeah, really?
Yeah.
How do you know?
It's been, you know, it's been for years and years and years.
And yes, people, it's very extremely strange fantasies.
Yeah.
Yeah, some definitely weird stuff.
But, you know, I think the brain is still the largest sex organ we have.
So if you're stimulating the brain based upon some visual images,
I have to say, I can see already because I've seen the figures
that those men have in second life with those big baskets
and, you know, walking around with...
Boring, boring.
Big muscles and everything.
Yeah.
Well, that's a part of it.
Oh, the guys want.
Well, of course, mine is a true representation of real life.
Yeah.
Particularly my arms.
I have arms like tree trunks.
It's second life.
It's an expensive skin.
Nathan Tacos.
Tentacles.
No, I think that...
I think there's not an area that I'm interested in delving to deep into,
but I think that the way people have sex in second life is something new.
It is definitely something new.
It is something...
I'm very safe.
Very safe.
Yes indeed.
Yeah.
But it's fascinating.
And so anyway, so with the palace, which...
They're building it.
Now, I'll put some pictures up somewhere.
I want to show you that this morning.
It's phenomenal.
This is going to be so beautiful.
And we have actually...
We hired people to work in second life.
We had a meeting on our land.
I mean, if you're getting...
Of course, it's all...
It is a game, but then again,
isn't all of life a stage.
And each of us must play our life.
Life is a game.
It add them.
This is George Ramchino, man.
Hey, there are these two guys who are working in the prison laundry.
And they say your hair wasn't as cool as Ricky Rackman.
So I stabbed them in the exercise jar.
With a knife by me from a spoon handle.
Hey, just one man.
There were a couple of the new guys on a said block.
And one of them kind of looks like you.
And from behind, if you know what I mean.
He lets me soak his hair, which is nice,
because it reminds me of the chop chop.
And man, you know what's crazy though?
His thinker looks just like her loader.
Uh-oh.
Oh, man.
I got a goal.
I think one of those very enation guys just bought me for a carton of lucky strikes.
I'd better go do my stretchy so I don't pull a hammy.
I'll catch you later, man.
Mr. Chacha.
Be out.
Oh, yes, our friends from prison.
Glad that we're making a difference for you guys on the inside.
I was made aware of the fact,
just two days ago, right here on the Daily Source Code,
that it is national, may is national masturbation month.
And go figure.
Wouldn't our buddy Jess Smith just love to hook into that?
You've been a naughty monkey,
but I'd really have to thank you.
If you hadn't been so naughty,
I'd never have to spank you.
A naughty naughty monkey,
I'll really have to say,
you've been so bloody naughty.
I'm spanking you today.
Here we go.
Oh naughty naughty monkey,
I'll really have to thank you.
If you hadn't been so naughty,
I'd never have to spank you.
A naughty naughty monkey,
I'll really have to say,
you've been so bloody naughty.
No spanking you today.
Here we go.
Oh, okay, Belly.
A naughty naughty monkey,
I'll really have to thank you.
If you hadn't been so bloody,
I'd never have to spank you
A naughty naughty monkey,
I'll really have to say,
you've been so bloody naughty.
There we go.
A naughty naughty monkey,
I'd really have to thank you.
If you hadn't been so naughty,
I would rather spank you.
A naughty naughty monkey,
I'd really have to say,
it's a bloody naughty.
It's spanking you today.
Yes, the fabulous Jeff Smith available for Wedding Sparmitts was, and Spankin.
And actually, for some good-ass tunes, the JeffSmith.com, that's G-E-O-F-F, the JeffSmith.com.
He can also do all kinds of stuff for your show if you're a podcast or if you're interested.
Well, this is happy, and thank you for hanging with us on this episode of The Best of the
Charlie.
You can check out Bedtime Stories My Kids Love at BedtimeStoriesMyKidsLove.com, hurry back at him.
Be Jay Zerubut.
Get this piece of the show, and more great ones like it on the BT Pot Show Media Network.
Control your part in the show at btpotshow.com.