Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah
You said you'd meet me now it's harder to do
I know I'm hiding but I'm still on you
And I get to fact it talking to you
I tell my family and you may sit around
I'm not in a jealous piece, I'm not looking like a clown
I think of you every night and day
This is my one, I can't think of my brother
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I guess myself from the middle
Can I break free from the things that you do
I want to walk, but I got back to you
That's why I ain't myself, but I ain't you
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I'm not looking like a clown
But I'm dreaming about the love I knew of you
I'm only in vain, I'll be happy with you
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
But you can't keep me right
You just don't know what you was missing this night
I want to see you play, you said, but get it just goodbye
I think of you every night and day
This is my one, I can't think of my brother
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I guess myself from the middle
Can I break free from the things that you do
I want to walk, but I'm only in vain, I'll be happy with you
That's why I ain't myself, but I ain't you
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I'm thinking of you every night and day
Keeps up my heart, and it's a part of the way, yeah, yeah, yeah
I sell for loving you, and bring free from the things that you do
I wanna walk, but I run back to you, that's why I hear myself from loving you
I ain't no better way to kick off a brand new week
Brand new week of the Charlie Hey everybody, hi, I'm Bill and did you sure start episode number six one six
Joan Jett and the Black Hearts clearly follows the golden rule meaning if I have a golden record of the artist
I can play the song on my podcast. It's only fair
I think I've done my part of the equation on it's in
I hate myself for loving you
Joan, you don't need Joan, you don't need Joan, you don't need Joan, I wonder how she's doing
She's just on a picture not too long, I look pretty good
Everybody how you doing, this is a whole week coming to you from the Curri condo in San Francisco in
No Cal, it's of course it's Sunday night, it's Monday more more eastwards
So it's already Monday morning, by the time the UK is up and of course down under it
Australia, we know that till you already celebrating Wednesday afternoon
But Sunday night for me late, time to to catch up a little bit on what happened over the weekend
Of course, I still spend most of Friday in New York
And yeah, I just I just got done watching the
Season finale of the sopranos
Much, much, much, much hyped
Yeah, this was supposed to be the hour of television that everybody was going to watch tonight in America
And I'm sure everybody did watch and let me tell you because you know traveling back and forth between the UK and
New York and San Francisco I really haven't had time to catch you know to really follow along with the sopranos
For some reason they're on a delay, I think they're on delayed schedule on sky or whatever
But I can never figure it out, I set some of those you know like a record the whole series and I wound up
Recording all of last year's series or the series five or whatever it is
Now luckily Comcast here in in the condo has then on demand service, which is where they call it the
I don't know if they even call it the catch-up service, but it's on demand
So I was able to catch up during yesterday and today I watched
Seven episodes of the sopranos back to back because I wanted to be able to be completely up to speed with the whole story
For the finale this evening. I saw I watched four episodes yesterday
I were just I was a three or four that I watched today
Yeah, so it was almost like like this massive massive movie that I watched a big big mob movie
Which was only interrupted every 60 minutes by the necessity for me to find the next episode and for a quick bathroom break
And so I was ready for it ready for the big season finale this evening
I don't know if you saw it or not
What kind of ending was that it was like the most disappointing thing I've ever seen in my life
I'm sorry if you're in the UK
You know you should turn it off now or skip ahead if wherever you are if you haven't seen the
The ending spoiler alert here
It was that I mean or to speak with the sopranos the fuck was that
I mean you want to end the gangster movie you know you
You want to you want to be something like this
That's what you want say hello to my little friend
I don't know man. I think what they just trying to leave room for uh for you know to come back anyway
And next season. I don't know it was completely unsatisfying to me. I
I really didn't do much much else this weekend although I have been looking out the window. It's I'll see if I can take a picture of that
y'all on the on the
You know in the upper 20 floors on uh in this building here the curry condo and I have a 180 degree view
So I have a view of the bay the bay bridge and of course the tower of death which by the way
I now actually have to
Squat down to be able to see the top of this thing through my window which is a ceiling to floor window
This is out it is literally the towering in front of I was been built next to the condo
On the other side I can see a straight down. I guess that's the moscone center which I never really realized because I see this huge
Apple logo. I believe it's the worldwide developers conference
That is taking place. I guess this week and so there's lots of people in town have been receiving emails from people
Who know I'm in town and want to hook up and so it's gonna be a pretty busy week. That's for sure and
I believe they're not once again. It seems like that just might be a Los Angeles trip
Got to go to show biz town
So I'm hoping to be able to hook up with with a couple of people
While they're here and I wonder if there's anything exciting going on at the
Is there a Steve Jobs keynote? Is there something planned or not? You know, I should actually check that
Usually apples pretty good about
We just say so you don't have to do it at home. I'll do this for you apple.com
and let me see
Anything about to
Introducing iTunes Plus once the do ads. Yeah, man if you've seen the iPhone and
I gotta tell you
Even though I've been a windows user fork or I keep what isn't now the better part of a year
I'm still at heart. I'm a I'm a Mac fanboy. No doubt about it
Here we go. WWDC 07 June 11th 15th San Francisco Explore new highlights
Excuse me unwind from Angie B brought you by Tylenol PM
You know, did I am I like completely stupid or am I just now figuring out that the PM
In Tylenol PM doesn't actually stand for post Meridian like you know like like evening time like sleepy time
I think I finally figured out it stands for something else than that
And I'm not kidding you. It really took me a long time to figure this one out
The best laid plans
Sell them become the desired outcome in a perfect world of business
Alex controls every situation
But when agreements fall to pieces and associates are winding up dead and new world emerges and the bitch within
I'm new life to complete the final plays of the game
Relying on the pure powers of sexual persuasion the rules have changed and the lines are crossed between business and the art of
Sex and the realities of bitchiness from the imagination of Terry Woodard
ASB the art of sex and bitchiness
We're nothing is safe and the easiest way to be friend of foe is absolute sexual enticement
Coming exclusively to pod show this summer the art of sex and bitchiness the erotic murder mystery
That will make you second guess who you get into bed with
I can't wait for that a lot of these a lot of these audio novels are just so awesome
There was another one. I'm sending these all to Mark Yoshimo to name cough
Because although it's not officially announced yet. We're coming out with some very cool
Podshow press
That's all I'm gonna say about it, but this format and this is a format that is very very specific to what we're doing
It is not all like audio books like audible by the way
Autable who have closed down their pay for pod casting service. Gee guys that was a great one
I'm not forget Doncats that you tried to weasel me into that trying to endorse that
So that didn't pan out
But this is you know it's it's this thing is it's exciting you know I'm I'm listening to these
Books and I'll listen to a chapter and only they're only released a chapter at a time and it's almost like sticking the needle in you know
Because what is a chapter like five minutes maybe ten minutes you know it's like I want more
I want more than you have to wait until the next episode and by the time the next episode comes you know you listen to that thing
You're hooked and then you're hooked to this whole thing and then of course you want the book
It's as very exciting to me. It's very much the same principle as the pod safe music network and I am loving it
I got a lot of email from people
Telling me I was pretty stupid about saying that
Let the sunshine in
It's from the soundtrack to hair not the Jesus Christ Superstar
Was that last Friday that I said that now that that wasn't indeed pretty stupid
But it came from the first gen iPod, you know, so what can you say?
Friday before I left New York, let's see
Oh, yeah
So I had a nice well of course I did the show Friday morning
I was relatively early and then I had a lunch and this was really nice. I had a lunch with
Brenda Brenda was one of my mom's best friends who I remember
I think I must have been maybe six years old or something like that because they both grew up together
They they grew up in in Rhode Island
And they went to a barrington high school together and so I do remember one time going back visiting with my mom and
And I was playing with Brenda's daughter
Sarah I believe and
I remember Brenda was hot. I can't even then I was looking at all the women and
And you know she was very kind she sent me a nice nice postcard on May 21st
It would have been my mom's birthday and
And so I was in New York I said you know what I'm gonna look her up because I'd always promised my mom would do that
And I did and I got a hold of her and she said well why don't you meet me Friday at noon at the Harvard club
Now the Harvard club is a a private club
And so I actually dressed accordingly no tie that I don't believe that's necessary anymore
As a part of the dress code
But I did have a I had a jacket on and it was weird Max. I you know
So she's same age my mom 68 and so I didn't know what to expect but
Walk into the Harvard club and you know stunning platinum blonde beauty
with with the you know just exactly the type of
And you it she fit perfectly in the Harvard club absolutely fantastic very chic
Yeah, you know had kind of a little bit of that that Providence accent that my mom used to have
As you was trying to hide it, but you know you really can't take Providence out of the girl
And we had a great great lunch for
About about two and a half three hours and it was fantastic because she was able to tell me things
About my mom that I you know stories that I hadn't heard or you know just other sides of stories or
Maybe even were telling something that I remember differently and I was able to do the same for her and we had a really really good time
And oh and and I remember you know, I was like you know this I was trying to fit the Harvard club and everything into it
Her first husband
Was the family that started macy's
So that would explain the bling but it was it was really it was really
What's the word for I don't know I felt much much better after after after talking with it
I felt a yet a little bit more enlightened as we're coming up on the first
anniversary of my mom's passing on that July second
So and then just to make it complete a complete
Personal day on Friday ahead dinner with Steve leads
My buddy who I've known for how cricky what have I known Steve for 20 years now
He was the one that brought me to MTV
Steve of course works at a serious satellite radio
And so you know been in close contact with him throughout our contract with serious and
We met it. What is it uncle Uncle Nick's Greek restaurant on night Avenue between 50th and 51st
We sat outside between the fire escapes it was it that by itself was almost a very surprised moment
And we talked some industry shit and he had some pretty good ideas about some things and and some some folks who we could
Work with the pod show so that's stuff. I'll be working on this week here at HQ
Let me see a little ketchup here on some other email and then of course I flew
On Saturday morning. I flew with sales weasel Greg and I took the early morning jet blue flight
From JFK to San Francisco
I have to say besides the back pain which I just get because I get it back pain from sitting too long anywhere
Even in my own plane
Jet blue's got something going for it. I've said that before and and I figured out what it is first of all
There is enough room and it took out one row of seats. So they only have 25 rows now and for those of you fly jet blue
There is a little bit more leg room from exit row 10 for or exit row 13 and exit row 10
Forward. That's where there's a little bit more room
So the whole whole point was that we were gonna fly you know, I was gonna fly back with him
You know instead of flying two separate flights. I was booked on jet blue anyway
So so let's try and sit together, man, and we got to row 25 last seat by the lavatories next to a
Lady and a baby on our lap
We were really expecting the worst, but it was not that bad the stank was okay
Well, you know, don't you just hate it when people will stand next to you in the aisle and you're the
Basically you're putting your their ass in your face. Oh my god
The baby was adorable though. All I did was a gurgle and smile throughout the entire trip
So happy about that, but what really makes Jeb Blue cool is
The live television and there is a distinct difference between you know 20 channels of movies
Like you get on virgin Atlantic now. That's great. I have to you know
I'll tell you that I really love their selection. They refresh it every single month. There's plenty of stuff to look at
But live television. Wow. That's a real time wester at the flight just goes by in no time because you know
You get hooked. We were watching the this was so this was so typical
It was the VH1 classic highway a top 20
Road song countdown and it was sponsored by Lexus and clearly I think what they did is
Lexus said okay, we want to we want to advertise but you got to make up a show for us
Which you know, it happens all the time and and we do some of that too at Pod Show only with these guys came up with
The brought out Mark Goodman to host the show was it was kind of fun seeing Mark Goodman on the tube doing that
But the choice of videos man, so the the first one was what they have
Man Gregson kick my asset for God already but you know they had like
Steppenwolf born to be wild what was the first one though?
Yeah, it was all off because all of a sudden you got like rock set
It was all kinds of really you know pink Cadillac
Free way of love. I think and I know exactly how this works. You know of course VH1 being basically
The same company as MTV the same folks who work at MTV will sometimes produce on VH1
You know all they do is think okay, we got to highway songs
They don't really give a shit about an order
Which song is supposed to be number one? It's just okay. Let's just make sure we play videos that they either mentioned
Cars in the title you see cars in the video
And we were just guessing which one come next and it was it was a pretty fun list and before you knew what we were there
And I stayed indoors all day today as I said watching you know all that soprano stuff
So I'm ready for a full week. We kick it off tomorrow morning eight o'clock. I am so ready
But go to LA if I stay overnight. I might even try and catch the jersey boys again
You know the San Francisco cast is now in Los Angeles
Oh and homeless second where is it?
Alison Eric Bergen's mom you know Eric of course is is my buddy you hook me up with tickets to the show
He got a review man. This is the Los Angeles times
So you know I love the show and I thought Eric had a fantastic job and I love Eric even more now
That I know who his girlfriend is who of course is incredibly hot. She's also in the show
Now check this out. Let me just read you a little bit about what they said about Eric. This was fucking awesome
Here we go. This is the Los Angeles Times calendar section
Ehh
An odd development
Why is that the one I'm supposed to say?
An odd development is that Eric Bergen who plays Bob Godeo the songwriting genius behind the four seasons and the band member who claims to be more comfortable
Working behind the scenes is the show's breakout star
Is charisma feeds off the spotlight and with this lanky good looks and vibrant intensity and fucking hot girlfriend
He tends to eclipse the others in the musical numbers which are choreographed by Sergio Trujillo
Trujillo Sergio to evoke the old sixties moves
That's pretty good man and it goes on and on actually to say here just as the four seasons
Probably wouldn't have made it out of Belleville New Jersey without the hitmaking of Godio
This version of the band almost certainly wouldn't have gotten much farther than Newark without the charm of Bergen
Who fills the void left by Jones is amiable though low wattage valley
Oh man what an endorsement congratulations Eric. I couldn't be more happy for you man
That is so cool. I'm telling you this guy you brought way dude. You're totally gonna do the Broadway version
I hope you do at least. I think you'd be killer without a doubt
The opening of the show you heard
A nice promo from Jones yet
Now normally it wouldn't take away the magic of this and you know so you probably think wow that's a cool
John Jets and Adam
You know like a cool jingle
In reality
Do you remember when I for those of you who have been listening that long when I left the curry castle in Belgium
when we moved to the United Kingdom
I took the box now I've been slipping around a box of air checks of radio shows of
Basically cassettes and a couple of real-to-reels that is you know it's been my history and I sent it off to the official
My official biographer Tom Scrooting clog walked down under
And he's been digitizing old radio shows and stuff he's been you know just been going through this box
I thought the box was kind of empty but apparently he still has stuff and
He found something from me. Well, this is from I it's got to be 1989
Let me just play with that thing again. Hi. This is Jones yet from the black horse and you're listening to Adam Curry on z100
See that part I cut off
Hi, this is Jones yet from the black horse and you're listening to mad cap Adam Curry on z100
It sounds like it came from a cassette done it anyway
So Tom sends me something else. He sends me a picture of a video cassette
Let me just see the subject of the email
Is a proof oh oh home on for some reason
Well, that's kind of weird
Google notebook didn't quite keep it the way I want here we go proof of your early programming skills he sends me a picture
I got even it's so I got a zoom in here. It's a it's a fantastic. It's a it's a Sony cassette
And he yeah, he literally scanned the cassette and it's great because you can even see I should put this up somewhere
You can even see on this picture that it puts scotch tape over those two plastic things
The edge of the cassette you know if you want to record protect it you'd have to click that out
And that was so typical. You know, it always just put tape on it so that we could re-record anyway
And it says on this cassette it says basic programs
in Vic 20 basic
Now the geeks out there will remember this if you're old enough now have you ever heard a modem
What a what a modem sounds like when when it's trying to connect I mean these days
It's it's almost like how many people still know what a record scratch sounds like yeah
My daughter has never heard an actual record scratch
I know how she ever heard a modem connect because uh, you know, it's all uh Wi-Fi and broadband
There's no more audible dialing through a phone line
But back in the day the way you know before uh well
When we couldn't afford floppy disks those really with these first consumer grade computers
So before the Commodore 64 you had the Commodore Vic 20
Victor India Charlie 20 and
It was basically a keyboard it had a little TV RF output you could the
Shove in big ROM modules and you could connect the cassette recorder to it so you could write your programs to the cassette tape
Which would basically save the program this was basic so it was you know it was like lines of well
It was lines of code only very very rudimentary stuff and you could also read in
That information
From a cassette and you could then use the program you could load the program and you could send these to friends and you could share them
In fact the BBC at one point had the BBC a corn computer very similar concept and they would actually broadcast these programs over the air
So you then record that signal just a regular FM station
You would you would record the single onto your cassette tape and then you'd put it into your deck of your computer
And you could load up the program and it was it was the
Met with the most it would think about how cool that would be if we could still do that today. It was massive massive bandwidth
Massive multiple
You know like
You know it's like one stream and everyone caught it at the same time. It's a mine trip when you think about it
And so what Tom did
Is he of course he digitized the program so if you have a a Vic 20 laying around
And because I don't have mine anymore. I had no idea where that's gone. I wish I still had it because it would certainly be in my my collection
Then please load this program up and tell me what it does
Here it is
Yeah, my yeah my ears hurt too. I have to admit that did kind of suck
Hey, I want you to give me a call. I could look forward to
Like I picked her on week
I
This is what it from glad it's cost. I want to make pot show suck less, but I can't I'm from another country. I have to wait
Help
Don't worry
You'll be able to help us suck less very soon. Hey a castmaster Mike sent me an email looks like
Actually, I'll read it to you. Hi vid blaster version. Oh dot one six beta is now public just put a link on the form at vid blaster dot com
Thanks for all your help. I sincerely hope you continue helping me test all those versions to come
So this of course was to the close beta test if you're at all interested in
quick easy publishing a video
vlogging
Being able to use multiple cameras this thing is is awesome you can plug in you know two three four five as many
USB cameras as you want and you can switch between them
It'll actually switch the the devices use for audio as well so you can have you know
It do you know if you have a web cans with built-in mics you can load up video
Just you know
Maybe just something you shot and you want to do a quick intro to it. It's it's a phenomenal program and
It works out of the block out of the box with the pod show all you have to do is fill in your user name
Which is typically the email address you use to sign up and your password and your video will be uploaded
Automagically just like cast blaster does to check it out at vid blaster dot com it truly is very cool
Okay, let me see
I think I'm gonna leave it at that for for now of course not a hell of a lot going on
But this week will be
We're all the good stuff comes from and we'll be good to be back in the office as well, man
I haven't been here for it seems like ages. Of course. There was a lot of stuff
You know it's planning out coming back a while ago before the whole German thing happened
So it'll be again, I'm probably not gonna know half the people in the office. Oh, it's kind of scary
So the final track this will be on the pod safe music network sometime this week. This was a tip from from Steve leads
I'm not quite sure what the connection is or
Maybe it's his brother Harvey who's working this record, but anyway, there's a lot of people really really excited about it
Yeah, you got to wait for it. You're gonna like it
All the nights we spend
Oh
It's
You
Whoa
I promise you when this thing hits the pot safe music network it's gonna be off the hook everyone's gonna be playing
JTX
It's got a my space page so of course I'll put a link to that in the show notes a daily source code dot com
Got a party like a rock star
I'm gonna wrap it up for today
And of course
Well, I'll be back tomorrow. Please check out the show notes daily source code dot com if you want to send me an email
Let's add a met pod show dot com. I want you to have a great week
And we'll be back here tomorrow
And we'll compare notes