It's time you got in the game.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Get a domain name, free quick blog, and complete email.
Get in the game at GoDaddy.com.
This year at Charlie, 5-2-Niner.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
It's time you get in the game, I can't fall asleep in this race.
It's no longer for me to be.
It's become routine, the better it's you.
It's somewhere in the world, where I don't rest, I don't have to deal.
Never be given, never be a song, I can move it through the back home.
It's time to try and get me in the back of my mind, and I just lose straight from time to time.
I'm worried that I can hold on me, but we'll all sign right on us back for free.
It's time you get in the game, I can't fall asleep in this race.
It's time to try and get me in the back of my mind, and I just lose straight from time to time.
Last week there was an email that was circulating the Potio mail servers.
I think the title was vagrant effen records.
The lemon heads indeed are now on the Potio music network.
Thanks to the label vagrant records, they put a whole bunch of stuff up there, including Paul Westerberg.
That was no back bone, and of course you'll find a link to that in the show notes.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Daily source code episode number five to nine are coming to you from the Curry condo.
It's Sunday evening, and when I say evening, it's 10 minutes to seven, and I just had a great day.
I was charged up.
We got up reasonably early for a weekend for me before nine o'clock, because we had a photo shoot going on at the office between 10 and 1230.
I wanted to go over there and check out how it was going.
So it was beautiful outside today.
It was just a very nice.
The wind was calm.
Oh for four bay area statistics.
I would say reasonably calm.
Sun was out in shining.
It was just nice.
After the session was over, locked up the office, and I walked around a bit, went down to the water's edge.
And I got myself a sandwich and came back.
And I was, and there's a whole bunch of things we got to talk about.
But now that I have some version of connectivity and internet bandwidth in the condo temporarily, again, I'll get that in a second.
I was going through, you know, I had the computer open again, because without an internet connection, the computer is just useless.
It really is, unless it's a specific task you want to perform, but I'm always popping around.
And I forget about the net being even connected until you have to do something.
I think through voice mails, and I came across this one.
Hi Adam is talking checking in.
From a rather grey, cold and miserable London.
So there you go, that's life.
Just quick question.
Where haven't you occurring some twin?
I was really looking forward to that.
I appreciate an update.
Check it.
Bye.
Thank you, parking.
I don't even know.
Did I play that on Friday?
I might have.
So I remembered.
And it was, uh, or wasn't, you know, it was like two o'clock.
But a quick Gmail search, search for Leo Tweet.
And there was an email thread because we had gone back and forth on me joining on, uh, on Tweet.
He wanted to pay me 20 bucks.
I said, I, I do it for free.
As long as he kissed the ring.
And, um, so I sent him email, you know, I said, hey Leo, you know,
and this whole thread is probably seven or eight emails long.
And of course, Gmail nicely tracks that for me.
And it, uh, it didn't work out because every single time they,
they would be taping, it would be taped on Sunday around, uh, 11 30 p.m.
Uh, UK time.
So, you know, I typically travel, uh, from San Francisco to London on Saturday arriving Sunday.
You know, I'm in the house around 12 noon.
And I just didn't think I would be coherent at all by that time.
So it didn't work out.
And I said, this is perfect.
They, oh, all set of an email.
And Leo said, yeah, man, no problem.
Come on over.
So, um, Barkey, there's your answer.
Uh, it's on the next episode of Twitter.
I think it'll be episode number 85.
And I gotta tell you, I really thoroughly enjoyed myself.
It was a nice conversation.
It was a lot about the technology news and stuff that I'm very interested in.
And it was, uh, it was just a good chat, you know, it wasn't an interview situation,
which is what I, what I despise most of the time.
When you go on these shows, this was just really, um, just a couple of geeks hanging out
talking on us on day after noon.
So, uh, be sure to check that out.
It may even be up by the time you see it.
So, as I have a, you know, connectivity and, and of course, having gone through that, you know,
you do, the creative juices are just flowing.
And, uh, and I'm, and I'm thinking about, I'm writing stuff down.
Or this is going to talk about tomorrow.
This is going to talk about tomorrow.
So, you know, screw it.
I'm just going to do a show right now.
Uh, and then I'll have all that extra time tomorrow morning.
I can sleep in a little bit until like 7.
30 if I really want to.
Uh, so, um, it may even be, um,
Monday evening by the time you folks know Australia here, this.
I don't know.
Anyway, um, it, uh, going back to the, uh, to the weather.
So now, of course, it's dark outside, but just imagine here,
if you've never been to Northern California, uh,
these are these are the nights that I really love.
It is so clear.
You can see stars.
You can see aircraft.
It has that crisp, cool kind of feeling to it outside.
It's just nice.
And I've got the, uh, the baker's rack all stacked up with the equipment.
Uh, I have no light over here.
Usually I'm doing this in the morning.
I even have to, uh, draw the blind because of the sunlight coming through.
So I've got candles lit.
I've got a little incest go incense.
Hello, Adam.
Mike Turner here from Central Bristol, the thermo show podcast.
See, about, um, vote a phone of 3G broadband and then hit a one gig a month.
I'm actually by extra bandwidth if you need it just to let you know.
The egg gonna suddenly cut you off.
You possibly speak to them.
Or you will just get build for the extra bandwidth.
Anyway, just let you know, uh, choose for now.
Yeah, that was one of the things that happened on Friday.
Uh, you know, the first thing I did when I got up is I called the, uh,
customer support to get my, uh, my line re-provision, you know,
I had to wait 15 days before some other service disconnected real hassle.
And so because they closed, you know, of course it like six or seven o'clock in the UK,
the, the help desk.
Or at least you're gonna get the second string team, you know.
So I called in went through the menus.
You know, you have to re-explain it every single time you call in and I got disconnected twice.
Cox, it made me so angry.
Uh, so but it's working for the girls.
Uh, I'm gonna, can I not gonna, would there?
I'm not gonna this candlestick. There we go.
Uh, it's working and, you know, I had it hooked up to a Mac.
It was really good I went through that exercise because I went through quite a bit of exercise
myself here in the condo.
Let's get into it. You know what actually I think this we see if I can find it here
Here we go it qualifies
104 104 104 you'll have moments 104 104 104 104 104 104 and moments
And now it's time for the 104 you'll have moment
It's not about conspiracy theories. It's about geeky stuff
So this that's a let it be fair warning for you that this is a geek moment here
So I've calm cast in the condo calm cast up generally been very happy with haven't ever had a real problem
I have their cable television service. I have the on-demand service. I have pretty much
All the the basic super packages you want. I don't have the sports package or anything like that
And I have their high speed internet and it's work pretty much show okay for me
Now what went wrong and you know that since I arrived Wednesday in the condo
Conactivity was out
The the cable TV is all messed up. I
Think I know what happened and of course is very difficult when you have a building situation like I have here with a condo
Where there's also work going on inside the building and I guess somewhere there's some company in the middle because
Comcast keeps talking about our building using a new provider for a
Blah
You know it's you're not really getting the technical information out of the people who are to customer support
Now I can recall
When setting up my cable set up here that the engineer spent quite a bit of time in the telco
Cable TV cabinet which each floor has one and and going through all this I recall him saying that something was messed up like my my
apartment was a rewired to the wrong junction box or something like that and took him a little bit longer to find action
You know to actually find the the cable that fed into my apartment
So I think that what happened is if indeed there was some kind of provider in the middle somewhere
between Comcast and my building that someone probably reinstalled something and said oh this cable belongs over here
And that's probably why I lost all my servers because Comcast can't see my mode
I mean I literally have no connection to Comcast. I'm getting just some kind of
Basic channels and a lot of stuff. I'm just not getting it. I don't know what's going on with the digital box
So I pretty much know what's going on and and you know go through a lot of back and forth on customer service and trying to figure it out
And you know they're blaming the building the building is saying it's the provider no one knows what the provider is or does
So I'm a little bit frustrated and finally I get an appointment for Monday between one and three in the
afternoon. How fucking convenient is that not?
And this I was throwing some trash out and as with the most buildings you know you have a little room
In between the elevators and it's the trash shoe
And I see there's a door there that says telco cable TV and it's a jar
You can of course only understand my delight. I
Open the door. It's not and it's real sticky. So I guess that the whoever was in there probably the provider and
Just you know let the door shut and thought that it would close all the way but it didn't so immediately
I got a piece of cardboard and devised that so I couldn't get locked out and I
To make check to make sure that I couldn't get locked be locked in
And I'm taking video of all this. I want to do a video podcast of of what I set up
So anyway, so I go in and I it's very clear you know I see all the the the big cable stuff coming in the thick black cables
Which are for the the distribution system which is opened by the way this distribution cabinet
And then I see all the white cables for each individual apartment going into kind of like a
A mov colored box and like right that's where I got to be so I try and open it and has this real funky like
26. Allen key wrench lock on it. So
And without breaking the thing off the wall I'm never gonna get into it. I'm like, oh, I'm not gonna do that
And then I see something very interesting
I see a cable running up through a duct
Connected to an ethernet switch and that's switch is connected to I think I'm like a say which apartment but it's uh yeah
Actually it was like 25.05 or something. I don't know which apartment but I can see it hooked into one of those
Wiring bays, you know the ones with the plastic on it
So
So I'm like wow, you know, could it be so I
I grabbed my am I laptop? I plugged the laptop in and
I'm telling you I had like super fast internet. So then I'm like, all right, this is awesome
All I have to do is create is get a cable connect it to that to the switch and then connected to one of the ports that come into my apartment
And I have
Five different wall plates with a and b and they're both RJ45 connectors so they'll take an ethernet jack
And I figure one is for telephone and one is for whatever you want to put on it
And clearly you can you can connect an ethernet cable into the that wired plastic wiring bay. What does that call by the way?
You use a punch-down tool to connect wires to it. I know that after some experimentation which we'll get into
So I spend
Man, I don't know when when when was this was this Friday? Yeah
Friday evening I spend the entire evening trying to wired up and of course I didn't have the proper tools
So I was using screwdrivers and all kinds of stuff and I just gave up and like this is not going to work
So what at the next best thing, right? I get my my de-link Wi-Fi. It's a links this makes this a Wi-Fi access point
I take it in a plug it in and of course now I'm broadcasting from the
From the telco room next to the trash shoot and I'm broadcasting my signal. So you know, I take the laptop and of course
As I walk into the door
Of the condo the signal pretty much dies because it's going through elevators through all kinds of walls
I mean Wi-Fi the distance is not that very far but Wi-Fi does not like to travel that way in fact when I open the door
It's like Wi-Fi was whafting in because then I could actually get it all the way into the hallway of the condo
So clearly and I tried all kinds of combinations and settings in place
But it's just a little 80 bd antenna and my laptop of course has to communicate back through it's little 80 bd antenna
So there's way too much going on and by the way what happened to humanity?
No one's leaving their Wi-Fi is open anymore. Oh
That's so sad anyone can suck off my pipe anytime
Oh, that'll make a nice outtake for someone somewhere
Okay, so I pretty much give up on this because you know, it's it's just not happened and I'm frustrated
I'm using the the internet tablet for just to check my email and it doing it through
Using the my cell phone to get a
Singular edge connection which is of course is really not not great for everything
I get a lot of practice on the on the internet tablet though, which was good because I'm starting to
Back out of my opinions on an on-screen keyboard, but that's for another day
So I know I need I I'm thinking it's gonna be
The way I've put these wires into this connector so I need some tools and I go looking around
Comp USA Radio Shack and you know, and it's just so iffy and you got to go in the sitting you don't if they'll actually have it
So I decide to make the trek out to Concord, California home of I think it's the original
I don't know if it's the original fries electronics with the one I've always been to and this is like mecha for geeks
Imagine a store that has everything from the single individually packaged transistor all the way up to high and flat screen
El see plasma displays everything in between you want a hard drive
I mean you want a camera you want a particular piece of cabling you want a punch down tool for one of those
Wacky plastic wiring blocks they got it 69 bucks by the way. There's not inexpensive tools and I figure I also get a wire tracer
How smart am I now? So I've got a little transmitter that can plug right into these jacks and then with a little probe I can go and see if the signals come in through
And I figure you know what just on a whim. I'm gonna grab one of those
High gain antennas for the D link as well because it's just a backup plan
So all right
There's a whole piece in the middle that I'm just gonna skip which I want to talk about in a second after
After we get through this story and I'm back and I'm
Doing my probing. I am probing around turns out the B is connected nowhere
It does not show up on that great A does but only two wires. So I don't know who did the wiring in this building
But someone cuts a major corners and in order to connect all what is it to eight is it eight?
Eight wires for pairs. Yeah, I think so. Yeah, I'd have to know how to
Pull this plastic wiring block apart and I'm like now. Okay. This forget about it
That was really upsetting because I had some awesome tools and I did all the tracing but it's just their wiring is all messed up
So then I hook up the antenna thinking that this will do it. Well, it didn't really do it. It did however bring the signal probably
Five feet further into the hallway
with five bars on
On the eye Mac actually because that's what I wound up doing so now I'm figuring out okay
It's not very convenient to sit on a chair in the hallway. I just want to be able to roam around
You know I need my I need my laptop in the bathroom when I'm listening to something while I'm taking a shower
I need it on the couch and you didn't the kitchen
I need to be able to watch my porn and bed. You know I need the bandwidth coming through
I can't be restricted to one spot. This is the sucks
So I had another linksis router. Oh, man. This is where all that experimentation with the a vote of phone
USB dongle thingy comes into play
So I am receiving the deal link on the eye Mac and then I'm using I'm sharing the internet on the Ethernet port
Which in turn is now sharing that connection with any with my laptop through Wi-Fi internally
So I had to rename
This because they were both named curry condo so I had to make one curry condo to I had to
Manually configure all the IP addresses and it's and it works. It is so so amazing
I probably could have done it without the without the handy system tool for
Sharing your internet. I probably could have even figured out the routing. I haven't done it in a long long time
But it was so much fun and so incredibly rewarding that it actually works the only thing I had to do
really that was out of the ordinaries. I had to
Enter in a manual DNS server for every client that is now accessing the internal network
But I'm just so incredibly pleased with myself that I've done all this and tomorrow between one and three
Of course, I'll have to dismantle at hence the the need for taking video of it tonight
Because the calm cast engineer will be coming and that was
What not fun
Sometime later this week I'll delve into all the fantastic ideas you've given me for naming the the new cottage the new curry cottage
I think I actually have one of the many many entries this really caught on for you guys
It's almost like we're talking about splendor go daddy or something like that because it's everyone's all over this
And yeah, I'll leave that for tomorrow
But I don't want to withhold Mark Yoshimo Nemkov's entry
Play to stay and down there on the third floor. You'll visit sex dungeon today
Whips and chains and loop and lots of ass play
That's what you've come to expect and Adam Curry sex dungeon today
The hunky garden has been missing all week
Maybe he'll turn up today
I got a feeling he just hanging around and Adam Curry sex dungeon today
Adam Curry's got a secret door that he'll go through so he can play
And if you win a really bad boy, it's time for a sex dungeon today
Adam Curry's got a black leather pink bonfaddle
And if you ask he'll grease you up and ride you around on a great big saddle
All the guilt for town tongues are widen about a place that's happy and gay
And now they're all lining up for Adam Curry sex dungeon today
Six dungeon oh yeah
Oh Mark Mark Mark Mark Mark
No one more thing about the
The entire Comcast experience
Their support number is 1-800-COMCAST
That's easy to remember right
Now do you realize that there are many telephones the E61 from Nokia included that no longer have the actual digits on the phone pad
Or then the the the letters associated with each individual digit I had of course I couldn't get on to the internet because I had no cable
I had to call someone and take a please look at your phone and tell me what comcast spells out it was nothing as simple as this
3-4-7-1-1-1-1-1-6-2-5-6-3-1-7
Hey Chris it's CC Chapman one take a minute to welcome you to the pod show family
You probably saw him hanging around at podcasts but take in all these amazing pictures
Hey Chris it's Kelly from geek brief TV welcome to the pod show family
Hey Chris this is Trucker Tom welcoming you to pod show
We're all looking forward to seeing what you do this year
No pressure though. This is Julian from and over your head
You got them tips
Welcome to the cult I mean the company
The German man
See now I'm really excited because you and Franklin McMahon can have like the photographers death match
Just make sure you video podcast it. Welcome aboard
Congratulations to tips from the top floor from Michelle at whisper prayers
Welcome aboard baby
Hey looking so much forward to shaking the world with you guys tips on the top floor dot beaty plachio
dot com
I'll tell you man. I think Julian Smith had it right welcome to the cult when I hear that it's like wow
Everybody
I have some bad news my friends. I'm sorry that I must tell you the Trinity
Has had her three strikes. Yes, this is a one piece of the story
I didn't tell you about my trip to fries and all the gear. I bought to fix my internet's
internet's situation
until we read love
On the way back about
4 miles outside of Concord on route 24 west I lost power
It was pretty clear it was once again fuel starvation
I could just tell by the engine
and
I tried to turn over a couple of times I pulled right over on the just before the moraga exit
Lafayette california on the shoulder very very narrow shoulder by the way
Try to a couple of times and no good so once again. I was determined to get my money out of the triple a
I was guys are so great man. They were there within 20 minutes loaded Trinity onto the flat bed. I think what's happened
Then I discussed this with Chris who was the driver of the flat bed
I think that because he was not only interested but seemed quite knowledgeable of biodiesel
Because you know what happens is with any diesel really but also with biodiesel
Maybe because there could be some more more sediment and other stuff in there that just burns away with normal use
But only cranking her up once a month. That's not gonna work stuff is settling stuff is clogging up
I'm pretty sure that this is a filter or another fuel pump issue. I just had the fuel pump replaced
Or at least they say it's replaced. It's been replaced. It's 200 bucks worth of something they did
So
Unfortunately the science project is just not for me. I do need reliable wheels when I'm in San Francisco
But of course I feel really bad about this because I only have one parking spot. I can't keep her
But really I'm doing the car no justice by you know by just having it sitting there and not being driven so
I want to give it away and I want to give it away to
one of you loyal DSC listeners
But you have to really promise and maybe that's I haven't figured out how we're gonna give it away yet
But she has to have a good home and
She has to be well taken care of and I'll make sure that she's in running order. I'm not gonna give you a busted up car
I'll make sure it's repaired whatever needs to be done
But this is what I did this with another car when we moved from New Jersey
99 after Ron and I sold the previous company think new ideas
And we retired and moved back to Europe had a Rolls Royce Silver Shadow 2. I had driven that thing 85,000 mile
I love that car
Brewster green classic car just fantastic and I gave it away to
Fred the fireman who was a volunteer fireman and in uh I think it was a ball he lived in Brona, but it was a monk layer
Volunteer not volunteer
He worked for the fire department. He also
Later
Played a pretty significant role in the Twin Towers 9-11
And his wife, uh, Lordist, Lou
She was our housekeeper in Jersey and
Patricia and I were good friends with both of them and so I said Fred, you know, would you please just take care of the car
Just take it off my hands and they call it the Duchess and they still drive it, you know, at least twice a week
They take it out on Sundays
So that's what I want, you know, I just I don't need anything for it
I just I want to come for the fun way to to give it away and to make sure that she has a really nice home
Hey Adam my here from the Fishball Acoustic Showcase podcast at fishballacoustic.btpotshow.com
Just wanted to say that we're really excited about fishball
Being on the BT Pot Show network and uh I wanted to let you know because I know you're a fan of these guys that the shakes are gonna be a long to play
A rare Acoustic set at the fishball which is gonna be at the white heart in wadhurst
So pub in wadhurst in East Sussex on Sunday the 28th of January and we're gonna be recording that set
For the the fishball podcast so hopefully that will go out
Within a week or so after the show itself
Now
This is what we do at the fishball we put on live shows of
Generally Acoustic artists
We do previews of tracks from the the acts who are gonna play and then we record the actual shows themselves and put them out as
Exclusive live performances on the podcast
So if you and your listeners want to check out some excellent acoustic live music
That you won't hear anywhere else
Then check out fishballacoustic.btpotshow.com
Nice to see the BT Pot Show family growing. That's a great show by the way if you'd like a acoustic
You know unplugged stuff and totally for you
And the shakes also did another unprecedented unplug performance on who's on it?
I don't think the show was up yet. It'll be up tomorrow sometime
UK time
Probably in the evening
Who's on it dot btpotshow.com
They performed on some rather interesting instruments that we had laying around for him
I also wanted to talk about
What's going on with big brother in the UK, but we'll save that for tomorrow
by now I want to roll out the marauders
The Pot Saved Music Network of course. It's kill pop radio
You don't have to the bank for me
Going to put a fist in my hands TV
Down in the base you got to be a family going to plug it into another thing saying
Can't say I saw a normal joke
All around the band ready to go
I want to kill pop radio
music
Life's best for the past and so
I got to feel it and have your last control
All little edge girl moody
When she just a flavor of the month in a magazine
Think I know time you'll see me solve
Play bad, it's a real thing so
I want to kill pop radio
music
You don't have to be the bank for me
Going to put a fist in my hands TV
Down in the base you got to be a family going to plug it into another thing saying
Can't say I saw a normal joke
Play bad music music music
Shea marauders I want to kill pop radio and there was another song I really wanted to play for you today
I heard it on I love the company
Which of course the David Baleito from New York now with his phone. He's got the hot hot toast
Oh, baby keep played a song today, man
crap. It was
What was it called? I'll be your bitch or something. It was hilarious
I was it to David Schwartzman. I think who
Did the Bill Clinton got a blowjob and of course the song is available anywhere so I'm gonna stay
But if you can get clearance when to play it
I'll see if I can play that tomorrow again. I want to talk about this whole flap of in Britain over big brother and racism and
Have some have some views on that
But that's for another show. I liked it today. I hope you guys liked it, too
I felt really good. It's it's much nicer when I'm awake. You know when when I'm not dead tired from
Getting up at five thirty in the morning. Maybe I should do these things in the evening
It seems like I'm much sounded principal. Anyway, Adamertek
Potcho.com love to hear from you send me your send me your stuff and of course all the show notes at
DailySourceco.com. I'll talk to you tomorrow everybody. Let me find a lighter for the signature sign off
Here we go. Bye bye
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery
Potcho in Lightlight