In a world where women were comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you
get your entertainment.
This is the pod show network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
Delta share Charlie's 631.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass, in the next generation radio content
in my ears.
Napier bro you don't need to rest.
I like to tick up something.
Fantastic.
You're a bloc carie.
Clap your hands.
Pull form a pile.
I can't let you know if you've all like you can't hurt it to rise
Early in a sack, thank God
Once or twice, when a single man alive
doesn't give me no harm or anything
The family working on the phone
Days are all filled, they don't need to come back down on the phone
Really got you here, I might've got the old riddle
When the sun's coming up, you can't sell the riddle
I can't let the money go to buy the riddle
Back now, I've got the old one
When the words are all done and done, said go
Pull up, come in, I'll never cross and let it go
It's on, it's been so keep a pedal
And back now, I've got the old one
Night plays, I like the poor old days
You can't put it back on, they're my wife
But taking a very good thought, it'll be an idea
You can't let the money go
Back now, I've got the old one
We'll look at the media, I might've got the old riddle
When the sun's coming up, you can't sell the riddle
I can't let the money go
Back now, I've got the old one
Now, I've got the old one, my dad is in the big heat
I've got the old one, my father and the old two
I can't live a good life, make a little cry
Make a bad old one, come on
We'll look at the media, I might've got the old one
When the sun's coming up, you can't sell the riddle
I've been, I've got the old one, my dad is in the big heat
I've got the old one, my dad is in the big heat
I haven't seen the old one, my dad's in the big heat
Oh, thanks God, I'm an HRful boy
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, thanks for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I
I'll food art is that party band mixed up John Desperes thank God I'm a country boy the city boy remix
saw it out by a massive town dot com a place of link a daily source code dot com hey everybody how you doing how you doing it is monday perfect way to kick off a
Monday it is uh well it's uh about 50% beautiful today here in the UK and 50% really crap Christina called from new key where she's still on her
her um um post graduate getaway it's pissing down all day they're at the beach so they're basically indoors and having a horrible time and it's cold
we feel so bad for those kids
uh boy anyway um the my weekend was pretty food bar didn't really all was because of the weather
uh it was just a cascading series of horrible events dominoes toppling over and it really was because initially
I was going to pick Patricia up in Rotterdam on Saturday the weather wasn't all that hot
in fact it really sucked over there even though it was much better in the UK
and so we decided to do it on sunday um so you know of course I did my my food bar catch up on
Saturday so I knew that I would have time Saturday and uh you know there's something really weird with
Casplaster which I don't think is Casplaster's fault by the way but sometimes um either when the computer goes to sleep or it shuts down
it basically messes up the dot i and i file of Casplaster and then it can't find things
and even if you restart it the file is then I think saved in uh in a food bar state
uh for those of you new to the show food bars and acronym for fucked up beyond all repair
or recognition your choice
you know so then you have to basically create a new i and i file for Casplaster and it's a it's a
it's a pain in the ass and it could be something that's loaded on my machine that is messing
that up I had no idea but I would suspect that the way it shuts down or goes to sleep or if it's
something exits abnormally then that's when Casplaster doesn't get all the way through writing
its file something like that and I have noticed by the way sometimes it seems like my what I'll just call
the finder so my desktop sometimes not often though but maybe once or twice a week an application
can't find a file until I like click on that file or click on the desktop it seems like maybe
something's going to sleep somewhere and it can't find its file path so I don't know it's uh
it's not really horrible but what does happen is you know then Casplaster has a problem
then I got to go reconfigure things set it back up copy a backup i and i file it and you all the
stuff has to take place and then I test it and I tested you know you know how I tested i tested
by doing test one two one two in fact the only thing I haven't done yet is test test test
to call but essentially I'm testing and then I always forget I should have a checklist but I always
forget to stop and actually no I hit record but if it's recording already and you hit record it
doesn't do anything it just keeps recording so I should hit stop and then record and so I apologize
and and the clues are there I just sort you even hear me in the show say damn I can't believe
you've been recording for like over an hour now it's going on with that well of course 15 20
minutes was all that checking stuff at the beginning so I'm not doing it on purpose I'm just a
doc I apologize and so then Casplaster fake you know faded out again or my computer messed up
and you know then I had to upload through the to the web browser upload not a problem then
podshow crashed oh man you know halfway during the upload and so I couldn't upload for a while
and then I did and finally it was upload and I had been deleting you know the wrong episode
went up I don't know how that happened I I'm sorry it was it you know so all of that's taking place
finally everything's you know is all steady didn't secure and everything's working and then the next
morning I got to get a burly to go get Patricia knowing that the day after she came home
we were going to go to the Genesis concert we were invited by my friend Gavin and his wife
Gavin is a marketing market to British telecom by the way we hang out privately he said you know
shit we've got two tickets for the the BT box for the Genesis show we're like shit yeah we'll be there
so um flight erotic am where there's not brilliant in Holland but it's okay great flight by the way
just great to be flying again had fantastic landings everything was smooth it was nice it was really
great to fly again picked up my lovely wife who I hadn't seen for for over a week
and flew back and then I'm like so okay you know so tomorrow night Monday night the the night
after you come back it'll be uh we're gonna go to the Genesis show and then I read my email this morning
and Gavin's like are you okay we were worried it was of course it was if she'd come home
Saturday it would have been the day after which would have made it Sunday so we completely missed the entire show
completely so I'm like a triple dick so well once more consolation prize we did have
awesome sex during the same time when we would have been at the Genesis show i don't see it again
yes i'm leaning back because i had a feeling that the first comment on that there yesterday the
Adam i love america i do i love america i'll be twice and if i was young free and single i would live there
i would live in New York actually manhattan island that's where i live i'd just if i could what i call
i love america and i love you my dear friend and glad that we can talk sensibly
it's sort of shitty the dsa i just couldn't appreciate that one the dsa is fucking amazing
thank you really have a fight it's fokane amazing i thank you so much this of course in
reference to the year 4th of july show a couple other uh bits of feedback that came in and here's
one more and i'm how's it going this is your podcast you're listening here wanted to just
give you the thanks for making me such a proud american after listening to the 4th of july special
you did because you know what you finally made it clear to me what it is to be an american
american i'm a first generation american board mexican and you really summed it up to me by saying
that if you're willing to work hard for yourself then this line for you the really is no limit
what you can achieve if you're willing to work hard at it and after watching that movie about the
health care system and all the fokk up things that the president does you know the war in
Iraq letting levy go free i started to think that maybe i should go vote with with my feet and
move to another country but after hearing about your grandfather banging away at his
typewriter writing to his congressperson i realized that i have no reason to go you know i always
get upset when people don't tell me my mistakes and therefore i'm unable to take corrective action
yet isn't that exactly what i'm doing with america i mean i just got to speak up
so you know what i'm gonna do i'm actually going to write to my congressperson and tell them
that they need to support the internet equality act you know hr2060 or else i'm just not going to
vote for them next election and i encourage all your american listeners from all nationalities
to be proud stand up and speak up for your rights right to your congressperson
about whatever matters most to you well and um thanks for your wise words and making me a smart
proud american citizen all right my for now wow that's really nice man the anonymous podcast
listener the music he used by the way was from the podcast music network the cats in the hats
with their rendition of the battle him of the republic that's it's that simple man all you
got to do is write your congressman i think you don't have to be around the bush we don't have to
do that it's 2007 just say look here's what i think you should vote if not i'll never vote for you again
done it's a very simple effective message done don't need any eloquent language don't need to
set it up it's just this is it done it's that simple and yes that's that's how the italian
america works so you know everyone could sit around complaining but uh you got to you got to go
to the uh to the root man you got to go where it all takes place you that's where you make change
all ready a lot of change made look at what happened in congress look at uh look at who's
come in look at who has the power now that power has to be exercised and i think we're kind of
resting on our laurels a bit not everyone's resting on their laurels hey adam it's me and from
London just figured i'd give you a call about uh you're a kid formation uh well i've been
collecting uh kid batches for ages uh because i can get it work and i figured out the best time
to enter the cage is either searching in the morning about seven a.m. or really late at night you can
like now and uh i just want an ipod uh yes i i won two free songs and five minutes late
i got an email for you to say i wanted to get an ipod so definitely work just wait and do it late
in night and you'll be fine awesome you have a good work Adam yo i got to tell you that i bought a
bottle of koke yesterday i did some shopping so we would have a little more in the fridge when
Patricia came home because believe me that's on the wife comes home to checklist you better have
that box ticked off get some stuff for the fridge and you know cat and dog food and all that
said does it doesn't matter if you've been feeding like scraps and shit all week but when your wife
comes home you want to have uh everything nicely stock so she thinks that you've been taking care of stuff
um yeah but i i i too was like oh you know i should actually take a look
i haven't redeemed the code yet but so there you go do it early in the morning or late at night
and you have i guess i don't know i don't know that makes any difference if you really have more
chance of winning it seems like it wouldn't matter for their systems uh but you know ever since
we've been talking about this now people are getting into it and a lot of interesting
information is coming back uh coming back about this promotion um and how it works
hello Adam you are asking for some feedback with regards to the uh kokekota promotion
that's currently running and um i have to admit that there's so many different promotions that
go around these days that you tend to ignore them but do people realise they could be throwing
away iTunes songs um i was actually prompted by your call on the 4th of July to uh to have a
look at the bottle of coke that i just finished and peeled off the label and um inside that
give you a code now you can do two things you can either send that code off um using a text message
which apparently only charges you the price of the text messages not one of those that charges
you a premium rate so if your um if your normal plan has like 12p for a text message then that's
it you just you just spend the 12p i don't think that this kind of call um is covered by any free
text messages that you might have in your package so you will be paying at least the price of
a text message to get this uh first one i sent off it get the uh text message come back saying sorry
you have one nothing uh so it's 12p that's a bomber there's nothing next one i sent off it
came back with a text message saying congratulation so far it's a nice word to get in a text message
although it's normally followed by congratulations you've won something you really don't want
in this case it's a congratulations you've won a uh what you can put a read it from the phone congrats
you have one one three song on iTunes and still have two chances to win an 80 gig iPod not
quite sure what that means i'm not really been able to find out the the full terms and conditions
it's has here to claim your song visit coca-cola.co.uk slash music
and go to entered by SMS well um i actually did it exactly as it said entered into my
internet explorer coca-cola.co.uk slash music and it threw me up my ISPs search engine cannot
find this domain so we've got a bit of problem there within marketing perhaps you can feed that
that back to uh to coca-cola how awesome is this so guy here's me talking about the coge promotion
is drinkin' a coge starts looking at the labels wins a song finds out
that sounds messed up and now he's telling us about it i'd say that's pretty you know
something about this advertising thing i'm podcasting is working um but when i stuck a WWE
WWE in front of it it then redirected me to music.coca.co.uk and everything from then on was
was quite hunky-dory um it then gave me a link into iTunes and gave me another this this is something
i liked it gave me the option to buy either a 79 or a 99p track. i think the 99p tracks are the
ones that are DRM free so that could be interesting um unfortunately the track that I
toes wasn't available in DRM free so i'm tied into the the Apple player um well i don't know
how how geeky and science fiction you are but i'm sure a lot of your listeners would have
watched the recent Dr. who end of series and i absolutely fell in love straight away with the
scissors sisters track and of course that's what i download with a little help from pocher
thanks very much all right all right man awesome thank you all right so you're thinking if i
actually win something if i win an iTunes song for the coge called promotion what kind of songs
could i go and download for my tunes well here are some suggestions
are you ready to be stumped you are he used with y'all all right y'all y'all
y'all we later one new hit this it's episode 77 this week i'm warmed up and ready of course
you know how it works so here we go this is number one so please easy easy bump bump bump
earth wind and fire boogie wonderland okay wonder man number two
oh man i i didn't get that one at all you're probably sitting there with you we do earbuds and going
this week's final clip number three
pat bantar love is about i know i have no idea what the second one is first and third i'm pretty
confident though let's hear the answers y'all hit me and times up it's time for the answers this is number
one earth wind fire
from nineteen seventy nine answer number one in this week's hit test earth wind and fire
and boogie wonderland and this is answer number two from 87 it's level 42 and it's over
because it's over all right you got me on that one y'all
i get it's not really on my way to and it's over I'll answer number two
and this is a third and final answer from 1984 bat bantar love is a battlefield
we step forward no reason bad of you bad bantar and love is a battlefield as answer number three
and that concludes hit test numbers 77 so until next week and hope you got them all at them
the answers in the items links are to be found at hit test dot bar show dot com
and that's uh about all i have to say this week so until next week
until then take care and bye bye
hopefully go accommodate two out of three ain't too bad
i'm so happy we brought this feature back of course completely sanctioned by the organization
for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives and brought to you by koko kola
hey Adam it's Craig myr calling uh there's a new release of your note nokie 800 firmware
it includes a hook for the Skype client interesting one side installed the Skype client
here's my stop working who would say i think i preferred gizmo
but anyway i thought it was a two-note take care i'm thanks yeah i got a note from the candyman
that there's a indeed a new operating system for the nokie 800 internet tablet you know i love that
thing although i have to be honest i've been using the e61 i almost exclusively as of late
and i've really been looking for the right combination of tasks to use the the tablet for
and having Skype on it will be a huge one i'd love to just have one device that has Skype on it
not you know Skype popping up on a million different computers something i can carry with me
slipping my pocket when i'm talking it has they have a great earphone microphone set combination
that's kind of weird though maybe when you reloaded that's when it blew out your uh your gizmo
settings when you when you reloaded the OS or whatever i mean i i'm always afraid of doing that
stuff i really know i got to take at least two hours to sit down and prepare myself to go through
it usually it's fast you know ten minutes i'm done but i always want to have enough time because
i know that i can't put something down if it starts to you know freak up then i got to
i just got to focus on it make it work but it's been pretty seamless with the with the tablet
and it also does flash nine now so and and also what was Luke emailed me that uh it also does
windows media wmv files and they have a media center so we're trying to get our podgeos stuff on there
i and maybe it is on there i have to check it uh okay one more comment then the last song of the
you know Adam is different southwarder man this nylon i did what the fuck man i you got to
just stop playing his shit man i'm back i'll come back in the gun range right now and i feel like
going in the back of my car and grabbing a 50-count he's blowing my freaking brain
clean for looking at his guy please it'll love a god stop playing his shit
uh dude no i love the nylon there's nothing like someone giving me shit
and then all of you sticking out for me it's heartwarming
i can do it all again yeah maybe i could be better there's the things that i would change
if i could do it all again i'd start off for Christmas i'd focus right on you
i was afraid the thing would change now i'm afraid those days are saying it's such a shame
i can't erase i want to decay if i could do it all again yeah maybe i could do better
but those things that i would change if i could do it all again if i could do it all again
yeah maybe i could be better there's the things that i would change if i could do it all again
i've got been a fear of down because i'd tell like no one else i was afraid that i would change
now i'm afraid the state is saying i'm afraid i can't explain now what the hell i'm gonna try to say
i'm afraid the state is saying i'm afraid the state is saying i'm afraid the state is saying i'm afraid
i'm afraid the state is saying i'm afraid the state is saying but i'm afraid
the state is saying i'm afraid the state is saying i'm afraid the state is saying
if i could do it all again well maybe i could do better there's the things that i would change
if i could do it all again if i could do it all again yeah maybe i could be better
if i could do it all if i could do it all if i could do it all if i could do it all
i'm on tarry okay i have Rob Sabo that's a pronounce it that's kind of love song i
like man there you go i'm sorry baby oops i wasn't doing it on the speakers yeah i messed up
if i could do it all again i would do it better there you go that's it hey those of you out there
who are making songs and putting them on the pod safe music network have an idea that i want to
propose to the lady Patricia you know she's really been thinking about what direction she wants to
take and she's really excited about singing again and doing stuff and the things she loves the
most by the way is the entire process of making music making records and i'm thinking if you're
out there and you've got a song that you think might fit for her i think that i can probably
convince her if if i had the right material and i could say look here's a whole bunch of songs
and these are you know and these folks are fucking serious and professionals and they want to
work with you we could put something pretty interesting together just the thought
and with that thought i will say talk to you tomorrow bye bye
another pod show pod guest stick it in your ear
the best and the brightest sub duct daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show
and limelight