Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony
ear buds were styled meat sound.
This year at Charlie, $701.
The people people say they're clean, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up,
they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling to turn back the war, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling out, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling up, they're calling, 4, these are calling up, they are calling, they're calling up, they're calling, they are calling up,They are calling, but they're calling, they're calling up,
Oh, what's good for saying?
You're getting a new male.
Now pop in my eyes.
Cause all of you get in jail.
I'm gonna pop up.
Oh, I'm gonna pop up.
They're gonna pop up.
Now I'm gonna pop up.
Let's pop up.
Brought to you under the very new doctrine.
courtesy of the organization
to the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
I continue to turn our nut board city limits.
Kicking off daily source code episode 702.
I guess.
Yeah.
You probably have the same reaction
to my wife had when she heard me playing the song.
She's like, why are you playing that song?
That exactly is exactly the voice she used by the way.
I say, well, because he died a couple days ago.
And an honor of like Turner.
I'm gonna play one of his biggest hits.
In this case, happens to be one with Tina Turner.
He's had a lot of hits with other people in his own band.
And of course Patricia said, but he was a real asshole.
I know he wasn't asshole.
Of course he was.
You know, we all know that he abused his girlfriend slash fiance slash wife.
That's been well documented.
Pretty much from one side only,
but it's been well documented.
But that doesn't mean that we can't honor the guy for what he did from music.
I mean, come on.
He was probably the first guy to really bring this genre of R&B
and rock and roll together at a perfect time.
And he really, you know, he was a musical visionary.
And I have, even though I cannot condone,
of course any type of violence, as you know,
I'm a non-violent man.
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
I think he did pay the price.
For the abuse.
Because everyone thinks he's an asshole.
And he died a slow and horrible painful death.
So there you go.
I just can't deny the musical contribution that he made.
It is Thursday.
Big apologies for Tuesday and Wednesday.
I'd already forewarned you.
Once again, we're in delayed source code mode.
It'll be another three show week.
But it's had to get some stuff done before the end of the year.
And of course, I hadn't really been in the office properly for a while in the London office.
So it was a good hangout with everybody and catch up and see where we're at.
And we're doing quite well.
I'm just really pleased with how things are going.
Met with a couple of content partners and producers.
That was fun too.
Oh, I recorded my Ron Paul endorsement video yesterday,
which I guess they'll put up on their site sometime.
I'm not quite sure when they seem to like it.
You know, they're pretty, I'd say I did a pretty,
actually I'll put it in the daily source code channel.
If you haven't seen that, go to atom.podshow.com.
Check out my channels.
You'll see their DSC channel.
And if you subscribe to that, anything that any media that I have,
I think is worthy, will pop automatically into that channel for you.
And you can have it go to your iPod or whatever.
Your iTunes or just have it sitting there and your channel to play online.
But I had turned out okay.
I thought I was, the message is really what it was about.
It's funny because I showed it to Patricia last night.
She's looking at it very intensely.
When she looked at it intensely, I know that she's really enthralled.
But I think after 21 years I can tell.
And she says, yeah, this is very good.
And when someone says, this is very good.
And I'm like, all right, what don't you, what is wrong with it?
She says, well, you know, I would have, you know,
I couldn't see your eyes as well as I wanted to.
I would have had a little bit of light underneath to light,
to lighten up your chin.
Like, did you hear what I said?
Oh, yeah, I know I like the message.
Oh, my wife, bless her.
Oh, I also had a lunch yesterday with Simone of Altafa.
Dutch listeners will remember who she is.
I was hoping to hook up with her again in Amsterdam for that,
that kind of reunion party, relaunch of decibel radio.
The pirate station that it all started at for me and for a number of people,
including Simone, because she was there back in the day.
She's an original pirate horror.
And in fact, she succeeded me on some of my TV and radio work that I did in Holland
when I left to go to MTV in 1986, 87.
And she became quite successful.
And she met a guy, got married,
and decided to talk it.
I'm giving up.
I'm going to go do something else.
In fact, I think she was thinking about how to save the planet at the time.
I don't think she's changed much nor as Clark, her husband.
They've been, they must be married for a good 17, 18 years by now, I think.
And so they're wrong around the country.
Her husband is Clark Dachler.
He used to be a Johnny Hates Jazz.
If you remember them from shattered dreams,
that's probably the song that you remember.
And he's done a couple of album since then.
And so we had a great conversation as a new record out.
In fact, he re-recorded shattered dreams.
I probably couldn't, you know,
couldn't get the rights to the master.
I'm sure some fucked up radio record company owns that.
And I don't like 10 or 11 other songs.
I saw some of them.
I really like.
And so they actually she asked me if I would, if I would pick what I thought was,
you know, the best or, you know, my favorite track from the album.
So I'm not quite sure I can make the choice yet.
And she said that she'll put, she'll make him a pod safe.
So that's cool.
But it was just nice to catch up with her.
We had a lunch at this place called Shish, which is kind of like a Wagamama or kind of a,
it is a chain I believe, for Shish Kabab, which was kind of fun.
And as we're talking, she hasn't changed.
You know, we've known each other 25 years.
I said, hey, you know, I guess she remembers all this shit from back in the day.
And stuff that I was like, huh?
I really, hard for me to travel, you know, get that recollection back.
I said, do we ever fool around?
She says, no, don't you remember?
No.
I said, don't you remember when I came back to your place.
And I just started living on my own in Amsterdam.
And you said, hey, you know, let's just go to sleep.
And let's just sleep because I, you know, I like you so much.
And sex will just complicate things.
And so we slept together.
But we really just slept.
And I guess she never forgot that.
And I was like, wow.
Oh, imagine me.
Maybe I still just wasn't sure about my sexuality.
I don't know.
Oh, no, it's because man, she's beautiful.
Anyway, looking forward to those tracks coming up soon on the podcast.
Music network.
Let me see.
Got a lot of email.
Of course, you know, I'm catching up myself.
Oh, by the way, damn you, John C. Devorek.
He turned me on to this book by John Perkins called Confessions of an economic hitman.
Oh, oh, man.
I'm just getting more pissed off now.
Now that I'm really starting to understand how the American Empire was able to expand so drastically.
And what we're really doing in all these Middle Eastern countries.
And you know, in other places as well, don't forget there are other countries where the United States
is adequately represented.
And why?
And how it has basically built up the corporateocracy and the military industrial complex.
And it also sounds like really, really big words and, and really tough concepts.
But it's really simple to understand once you get into it.
So I'm sure talk about that a little bit later on today.
If not on the No Agenda podcast.
Hey, Adam David from Delaware.
Hey, David.
I was cut to listen to your DSC71 straight.
And I've been inspired to call you.
And even though I've been a listener since the wired interview I haven't ever called.
Oh, man.
That's a 2005.
Well, thank you for hanging in there.
And to give it a little hint to the cinematographic.
So the listen to I just passed my 56th birthday.
Nice.
It's past Sunday.
Congrats.
I'm also an owner of the business.
And I really could relate to your comments about the.
Listen to what's that show.
Of course.
You don't want to miss the your your own company's Christmas party for Led Zeppelin.
I don't give a shit.
Who?
Well, no.
That's not entirely true.
There would be circumstances where it probably forgot.
But this was just not anywhere near.
Yeah, there's just stuff you had to do.
That's all there's to it.
I'm also on the No Fly List, which I just found out on the recent.
Uh-oh.
Houston.
And they're a cooperative continental agent.
Let me know.
That's the reason why I couldn't get my freaking morning boarding pass.
I couldn't have done anywhere.
And I had to go and see the people at the corner.
Inspires with TFA people.
I would make a suggestion.
You've asked for people from Iran to call in on your line and talk to you.
Give me some comments about what it's like living in Iran.
How about even closer to how much get some TFA people to call in and say just what
the hell is in their minds when they're screwing us up.
Are they being instructed to just be in assholes or is it, you know, the civic constructions
about how to do that?
Let me just jump in here for a second.
You know, I do not.
But first of all, I'm not on a no fly list.
I'm on a lookout list, which is an entirely different department.
So the TSA is not alarmed about me at all.
The customs border protection, both by the way agencies that fall under homeland security.
They're the ones that are concerned with me.
So let me just say something about TSA and about airport security in general.
The people working at airport security are the same people who work with Donald's.
And although I just about barely trust the people working at McDonald's to give me a germ free hamburger,
I do not trust them to understand the intricacies of a screening out.
Maybe even sophisticated ways of hijacking an airplane or blowing something up or whatever.
I don't expect them to have that training.
I don't expect them to be listening to the show.
And just next time you go through a US airport security, look at them.
And in fact, you can just say, I'll have a happy meal, please.
They'll probably reach around and want to give it to you.
So they're just following orders, which doesn't that sound familiar, just following orders.
To the best of their ability.
So I don't think that, you know, and probably there's, you know, the same thing that you'd get in a McDonald's.
And by the way, I'm an asshole at McDonald's.
When I walk up to McDonald's and someone doesn't say, hi, welcome to McDonald's.
How may I help you?
I always say, hi, helping to McDonald's.
That's the way your commercial portrays your company.
I'm not getting any love from you.
And I feel that I'm a dick about that.
I really am.
Let's go.
I say, hi.
Welcome to McDonald's.
How may I help you?
You know, if I would get that from the TSA, hi.
Welcome to the TSA.
We're here for your security.
We're just going to, you know, and sometimes you do get a guy or a gal who's, you know,
shepherding the line and they'll be making jokes and kind of make it fun and funny that happens
in New York.
I've had that happen a couple times.
You know, and that's kind of making light of a quote unquote dire situation.
But at the end of the day, now, man.
These, these, these people are.
They just don't care.
And I think they, they have as, as little pride in, they would have given you a hamburger
and they can the perfect burger as they would getting you through security securely.
And so of course you're going to have people who just don't like you, you know, because you're not working
for whatever they're working for.
And of course, you're going to get people who want a little bit of a power trip because they have some.
But, you know, you can't generalize that everyone's evil.
You can generalize that the people who are working there are of a,
a, boy.
Maybe you should just shut up before I get in trouble.
Because by the way, I like going to McDonald's.
And I have nothing against the people there.
But it just seems like they're in a fucking McDonald's job just, you know,
getting through and not really caring.
And that is not the point of security.
Which is exactly what's kind of trying.
Of course, we won't get any of that.
And we'll, we'll call you to know TSA.
If people would be calling, listen to your podcast anyway.
And by the way, if someone from TSA wants to call, I mean, they'd be more than welcome to.
I like, and, and I do get emails from people who just don't want to be on the air because they're
afraid for their own job security, uh, advice.
And I've gotten this from investment bankers, people who understand, you know,
I've been talking a lot about the federal reserve and how, um, how they're just printing money.
And basically, uh, enslaving us in debting us for good.
Uh, but they don't want to come on the air.
And I can understand.
So I can only kind of pass along what I've learned, uh, in the back room conversations.
Uh, one quick thing, I also want to mention this,
and this Thanksgiving holiday to this past,
there seem to have been a complete change in the, in the whole travel, uh,
issues and then in America, at least.
And it kind of was revealed that there are flight paths that are designated for commercial
aircrafts and vast majority of the airspace is controlled by the military.
Um, and maybe that's really what's been screwing everything up since September 11.
And there's not really been four fluid ounces of stuff that we can't bring on the planes and then TSA people.
Yeah, that's not true.
I can tell you categorically that has nothing to do with it.
Absolutely not.
You know, there's, there's no reason why, you know, if commercial air traffic would be flying
through some supposed military zone, uh, which, by the way, is not necessarily a flight path,
but it's really, uh, it's a zone.
Um, that, that would, that would have nothing to do with it.
So I don't, I don't think that change anything.
I think they just implemented some new systems.
That's all I think.
Um, I actually didn't get my checklists.
I guess red pill, my piece smells, my eat theparagus.
Nice.
Oh, sir.
And, like, oh, no.
You love you, pick.
Yeah, love you, man.
No, homo.
Get a lot of those.
That's pretty funny.
And of course, more, uh, on the TSA and more, uh, Tales of Terror.
Hey, Adam.
Uh, it's my concept.
Just go.
I, uh, which is going to sit at my nephew is also on this list.
And, um, she does a lot of traveling with his folks.
My sister and my brother-in-law, and she's on the list also.
Um, problem with this is that she is, um, seven years old.
And they constantly want to take him to the back room and, um, my brother-in-law.
So, you know, I have to go along.
Yeah.
And, um, it's a more lettering thing when they go flying around.
They travel a lot.
And what a great station for him.
Yeah, really.
Travel the world.
But, um, yeah, we're teaching him something now.
And, um, why they're, um,
He's on the list where, um, he's kind of a shady little guy though.
Anyway.
And, um, he was looking at the PME well back.
So the stream pod guys.
Yeah.
Anyway.
I'm sure you had a good time.
Bye-bye.
Yeah.
I had a great time.
The full shizzle.
Yeah.
And again, you know, it's like if a name pops up that, uh, could be an issue.
Nothing wrong with checking it.
You should be able to take people off the goddamn list.
That's, that's a stupid.
It's irritating.
It's unnecessary.
And it shows how fucking, what are you using Microsoft Vista?
What the fuck is that?
Hi, Adam is John Quirk.
Um, just a couple of things.
But maybe relate to your extended interview with US Customs.
Um, it's pretty well known.
I don't think he's any secret that you like the early herb.
Which may not go down well with some people.
We're on drugs and all that.
And the last thing is at one time on the S.
You did actually say something along the line that I can get any contraband through.
They won't stop me.
Maybe somebody heard that and decided to put your name on the list.
And I see what you're carrying.
That made us be something to do with it.
I don't know.
Anyway, keep fighting.
It's the worst fight before.
Yeah.
All right.
Happy Christmas.
Now, you know what, uh, I don't think so.
And I'm, I'm deriving this or concluding this just from the,
what's happening in secondary screening.
They're just interested in me.
They're not interested.
They're not really doing a contraband search.
I can tell because I know when people are looking for contraband.
I know what that looks like.
And by the way, you know, that's when they'd bring in dogs and all kinds of stuff.
And if they really thought I was smuggling contraband,
I'd have a much more thorough search.
And of course, I'm not because I'm not stupid.
I'm not stupid.
Uh, no, I think it's much more likely that someone put me on this list to fuck with me.
Um, and of course, I have some indications as to who that might have been.
Uh, which, of course, is highly legal and just as messed up is if the government themselves had,
you know, had some reason to think that I needed to be screened.
But again, it doesn't matter.
It just doesn't matter.
Once I'm cleared and clean, no, once I'm clear, once I'm clear, I should be just fucking clear.
You know, and I really am going to find out.
I'm going to, I'm going to ask these guys about this clear card.
If I fill out the clear card, if I give them my retinal scan and fingerprints,
does that mean that I'm cleared through customs?
If not, then you really know it's a bunch of bullshit.
And it's just another version of the National ID card.
It's just another way to register you.
Essentially to fuck with you.
So now, I think, I think the issue is, um, I'm on checkmark somewhere.
The new systems went into place.
I got the new passport with the RFID chip.
So now they can actually scan me in the new system and Bing.
Shit's popping up.
What was it?
Did I see a fantastic story the other day?
Oh, please tell me.
I put that in my Google notebook.
A girl from Iceland, I believe.
She went through a horrible ordeal.
I'm just recalling this from memory.
She and her girlfriends went to New York to have some fun for a couple days.
Do some shopping and hang out.
And she was stopped at customs.
And they said, oh, at the border, basically.
And they said, well, you overstayed your tourist visa in 1995.
And we're going to deport you.
And she said, well, wait a minute.
You know, I've been to the States a couple times since 1995.
And no one ever mentioned anything.
And so, you know, what's the problem?
She was detained for two days, put in shackles, subjected to all kinds of searches.
Couldn't make an international call to anyone.
You know, just really fucking lame.
I'll put a link in the show notes of that web blog.
I mean, that's, um, uh, bummed I can't find it now.
I can't, I'm, I was sure I would have, almost second.
I'm sure that I would have booked Mark that or put that into my, uh, put that into my notebook.
It was essentially, it's a translation of a blog post that she wrote.
And she's hot, too.
I wonder if that has anything to do with it.
She's blonde.
Maybe it's just against blonde, huh?
Hold on.
Let me just see if I can find it.
Hmm.
No.
Oh, thanks.
All right.
I'll look for it.
I will put a link in the show notes of daily source code.com.
Hey, here's a sabanta who has, has a very good solution for me getting into the United States.
Hey, here.
Hello, Adam.
Here's some fairies.
Hey, buddy.
Long time, etc.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, certainly sympathize with you about the issues with the US immigration.
I've had my moments there.
But nothing is severe as you're getting.
And it's particularly calling since you are a citizen.
And I am not.
Still, I can understand the problem.
I know where the problem lies.
And I know what the answer is.
Yeah, you need longer sleeves.
Because each time you reach out to become a finger on those in scanner,
the man behind the desk sees that your watch is worth more than his house.
He's all in, that's all it is.
No, no.
Anyway, um, I, of course,
the public detestations for you.
Yes.
This is a potential exotable way.
Yes, I've got it.
Yes, no.
Thank you.
Thank you, Hugh.
No, man.
You've got it all wrong.
Americans are not like that.
Americans see that you're successful.
The only thing in American citizen will think is,
damn, I want to be that successful.
Congratulations, dude.
I'm glad you made it.
That's what the American citizen thinks.
Seriously, it's part of the dream.
It's what we all work towards.
And of course, it's, you know, it's very materialistic.
But it's, uh, it's just the way it is.
No, I don't think so.
And by the way, um, you know, the TSA,
and I was equating them to McDonald's workers,
and they should, uh, they should have the, you know,
nice, happy attitude.
I really do miss what you used to get, uh,
years ago when you'd come into the United States,
they would, the customs and border patrol.
They would say, welcome home.
They would say, hi, how you doing?
Welcome home.
And you know what, even if they said,
now, hey, welcome home.
Uh, we just got to check in a few things.
It's, uh, it's for everyone's security.
Just come on back, you know.
Ah, fuck it.
I can't, uh, I'm not even angry anymore, barred.
I'm just not.
I thought you were based in LA.
Oh, like, are they?
Yeah.
LA is, oh, I'm up.
So I'm, so I'm just going to go out now.
Oh, they gay.
I'm going to think.
God.
I bite the hand of feet.
Haha.
It may be a limp hand if we don't know.
If they win, if they win, LA, I'm going to go to their offices.
And I'm, I'm going to have a few strong words.
It's Adam in.
Yeah.
Oh, he's curry.
Over here.
You want it.
Haha.
That'd be quite a laugh, actually.
Just strolling and pick pair of scissors.
No, right, they can curry.
Let's sort that fucking barnet out, shall we?
Haha.
It didn't work for John Bongeau, because whoever him.
Well, it didn't work for John Bongeau.
What, bonnet?
The hair.
It didn't work for John Bongeau.
I didn't think he was a pink.
She was a superstar and all the ladies loved his hair.
Wow.
Well, Adam Curry, that worked.
Just looks like a girl.
Haha.
Oh, he's, they're sending this.
See if he fucking pays this out on Daily Source part.
Haha.
Ah.
Now who were these guys?
Ah, damn.
Let me see.
LA is somewhat, some, some, some, some, some, some.
I bet you they have no hair.
That's what I usually find.
people who make haired jokes have very little hair themselves. Sorry, boys. Anyway, nice to hear
the Brits kicking in. You got a lot of British phone calls this time around. That's good. You guys
are back home. You're getting ready for the holidays. You've quit working. You've got time to chill out
to listen and buy stuff. Hey, Adam Mike here from the southernmost reaches of Canada. Listen to
show 701. And you had asked listeners if they had picked up any new Sony headphones. And I have.
And I love them. However, they're not the headphones that I was actually looking for. I was looking
for the sleek metal housing noise canceling. What's this? Show up on the page when you punch in the
URL that you gave the ear listeners. Sony dot com slash headphones. Those aren't available until
actually today. But I bought my headphones last week. You couldn't wait. And they actually replaced
a set of fast text T50s that I had bought in the 80s and all the black stuff that holds a
phone. And that's all coming out. Yeah. And the cable shows some intermittent noise. So I wanted
to replace those. So I said, well, I'll just get some nice Sony studio installed kind of headphones.
And I have to tell you these units are so light and they sound very good. Awesome. The other thing
is you were in New York. And I also listened to, I love the company with David Epilito. And there
was a time there. Right when he went from five shows a week down to, you know, a shortened schedule,
I guess you'd say. And he sounded somewhat disgruntled. I'd have to say about, about Podio. Without
actually saying anything nasty about Podio, he compared doing the podcasting and a monetary
sense to having a paper route. That's how much money he felt. Like I feel like he's putting a lot
of work into it. And, you know, he wants to see some returns or something. I'm not sure. And he's
not sure either. So he really wants to talk to you. It sounds like he says, well, if Adam's ever
in town, I'd really like to go have a cup of coffee with him or something. And it's too bad that
he were there. And you guys didn't hook up again. But anyway, that's it. I've been rambling on too
long already. And I love you, Adam Kirk. Oh, I love you, too. No, home. Yeah. So first of all, thanks for the
thanks for the feedback on the Sony headphones. We got a couple pairs here. I like him very much.
I've been using Sony's for a long time. Before that, I was pioneers. No way. I think first
it was the it was actually Dave Clark conversion. So the helicopter headsets converted to
to real audio headsets. Those are the because they really were tight. And you couldn't get any
feedback from the headphones to the microphone because I like turning up the cans really loud. And
then it was the pioneers. Kind of those those black half coconut shells. And from then on in,
I think when Sony came out with their kind of collapsible soft foam yet completely closed and
I don't think I ever look back. Really, really like him. Regarding David I believe, of course,
that guitar man from Central Park, I'm a big fan of his music, I'm a big fan of what he's doing in
Central Park, I'm a big fan of his show. Unfortunately, you know, the only way you're going to make
money is by having an audience that is big enough if you're in the advertising game. And I'm not
kind of discuss David's audience size, but he knows what's looking delivering to an audience
size of a paper out. So it's like there's no magic bullet here. There really isn't. He needs to go
on a campaign. You know, he needs to get people listening. His listeners need to get people listening.
That's what you guys do for the show. And he's got to find his niche and maybe his niche is just
really small. However, I have to say that in 2008, Pod Show is going to have a number of other ways
for people to make money with their own shows. I'm really excited about it. We're calling it seller
Tainman. And it's very much the go-daddy system. You have to know that whenever someone
uses a domain name promo code or a coupon or whatever it's called, the show and question who's
who's co-use, you know, they get a hit. They get a bonus. If you're a new customer, they get
you know, a substantial dineros. And just think about why, you know, every company that's really good
and has a product or service. You know, they know what their customer acquisition is. They know what
it costs to get a customer to join the program by their product. And if they're a company that
you know, that has follow on products as most do, they know what the lifetime value of that
customer will be. They know how much money they can get out of that customer in the life
lifetime of that customer being a customer. So it's what they call customer lifetime customer value.
And it's a real simple equation for them. So let's say that they can get three to $400 out of
someone. They're pretty happy to give up 20 bucks. You know, here's $20. Thank you for the customer.
And I believe, or I think we've proven time and time again that it's very, very effective
to talk about products and stuff that you like on your show because if you don't, you're not going
to sell that anyway. And you'll see that your audience will buy into that. So if you have only,
let's say you only have a thousand listeners. You know, that's basically in the advertising business.
That's one CPM. That's one million, one meal. So 1,000 people. And the going rate is anywhere
from $10 to $35. So, you know, if you have a show and a thousand people listen to an episode,
you know, if we filled up the inventory there, we could get you, you know, at minimum 10 bucks.
However, if you, if you sold a number of domain names or how about a Nokia N810,
you might be getting substantially more. And I mentioned the Nokia N810 specifically
because I believe the codes are now finally being made. I have a feeling that we, we probably
are not going to hit it before Christmas and I apologize and everyone apologize. Finland,
fucking apologizes. San Francisco apologizes. We, you know, just, there's a number of reasons
while you just couldn't get it together. Quickly enough. Funny enough for the U.S. promo codes,
I think we're taking the longest for some reason. And as you know, a big fan of this device,
it's made in Finland. I might want to point out. As far as I know, actually, all the parts
are made in Finland. That would be interesting to find out. Find country, part of the European
Union. And, you know, it's a great company. They started making rubber boots and paper products.
And they've, they're a manufacturing company. And a damn good one. And they make good shit.
And I like it. And I love this device. And hopefully I'll be able to get it to you at a good
price very soon. Um, okay. So now I'm segue, segue from segue, segue, segue. segueing from that
into, uh, into this whole, uh, wow, study I've been making really about, you know, what makes
the U.S. economy take, what makes it turn, what makes it churn. Um, seeing is that we're completely
being ripped off by companies who are in Kahootz with, uh, I would say the parts of Congress and
certainly the federal reserve and the world bank, um, who, you know, essentially had been, you know,
if it's all, it's so hard. You really should read this book. Of course, I'll put a link in show
notes to, uh, to the confessions of an economic hitman. Um, essentially the way, you know,
the way it's worked in the past is, hey, um, leader of a foreign country, uh, either in the Middle
East or perhaps South America. Um, guess what, uh, we're going to come in here. Uh, we're going to,
uh, you're going to borrow, uh, $100 billion from the U.S. And this $100 billion is going to
get you infrastructure. We're going to build power plants and and refineries and all kinds of, uh,
power related industry is going to come in and we're, uh, here's the economic models and here's
how that's going to boost up the economy and make your country fantastic. Uh, the world bank will
lend you this money at a very favorable rate. Of course, there's no way in hell, they'll ever be able
to pay it back, which is part of the trap. Oh, and here's $200 million for you and your family
in this black bag. Of course, if you don't want the deal, then I can always send it to jackals,
meaning the CIA, essentially, and you know, they'll probably kill you if you don't participate
in our little program. And so that's what's been happening in all of these countries.
And the way to slow that down, the way to say, hey, hold on a second,
when it's not going to take this anymore, because you know, these these big companies that
be companies. And if you listen to this story from this John Perkins guy, you know, he didn't even
realize what he was doing until, won't tell essentially it was too late and he had to get out
while he still could get out. Because he was just getting richer and everything was great and
fine, and then he kind of woke up to the reality and saw what was really happening and he stopped.
And we can do the same thing. And you know what? It's not going to take a lot. I've been doing
more research. First of all, I'm going to play this little bit from the New York Times front page,
which is a it's a podcast where James Baron usually reads the front page, the highlights from
the front page of the New York Times, which is a great show because, you know, gives me the highlights
of the day. And it also tells me if I want to go look at New York Times dot com or if I even want
to pick up a copy of the paper, there could be a reason for that as well. So I think it's a fantastic
content. And it's the New York F in times. So I'm going to play this bit from a couple of days ago
and it's basically a financial report and listen to what they're talking about, what the story
is about, it's about consumers, about our shopping habits, about our buying and who it affects
and then listen to the percentages. Okay, let's just play this little bit from the New York Times front
page podcast. Hey, Adam Mike here from the, what a great set of. Let's try that again.
Inside Fridays times a dilemma for the federal reserve. Retail sales rose 1.2% in November.
That plus a jump in wholesale prices and a decline in new unemployment claims pointed to resilience in
the economy even as the financial system and the housing market continued to weaken. But the new
data conflict with other reports and that's the problem facing the Fed. Investment strategist James
Swanson of the mutual fund company, MFS investment says we'll model through. He says there's not
going to be an all clear or a big collapse. All right, did you listen to that? Did you hear?
So they're talking about retail and wholesale prices. Basically about what's being spent? What are
we buying? How much are we buying? So let's just, let's just pick through this for a second.
Here we go. Inside Fridays times a dilemma for the federal reserve. Okay, first of all, a dilemma
for the federal reserve. Remember, the federal reserve is as governmental as federal express. It is a
private commercial company who has the exclusive right to print US dollars. They print money when
they feel it is necessary. Therefore, they control the supply and demand of dollars,
which means they control inflation. They control interest rates that banks can borrow and of course
foreign countries as well and of course that all eventually trickles down to how much your mortgage
rate is. So these are the guys who really control a lot and the consumer purchasing habits are
causing them a headache. So this is good news. We know how to cause headaches for these guys,
which gets attention. Let's listen to what the headache is. Retail sales rose 1.2% in November.
That plus a jump in wholesale prices and a decline in new unemployment claims pointed to resilience
in the economy even as the financial system in the housing market continue to weaken. Okay,
so this is very interesting. 1.2%. So in essence, by all of us,
purchasing 1.2% more than usual, we made the federal reserve happy. 1% just one little percent,
a little bit more. That made them very happy, meaning the engine is still working. It's still firing.
Maybe not on all cylinders, but it's still working. We're still spending. Now, I believe
and it's even hard for me to understand this next bit. I believe that the concern for the federal
reserve is that they think this money is coming. Well, let's listen to it again. You can,
but the new data conflict with other reports and that's the problem facing the Fed. Investment
strategist James Swanson of the mutual fund company, MFS investment says we'll model through. He says
there's not going to be an all-clear or a big collapse. Okay, so what that basically means is yes,
consumers have spent more, 1.2%, very happy, but no, all the other data about the mortgage rate,
the prime, the structured investment vehicles, the subprime loans, that, you know, I think Morgan
Stanley now announced another five or six billion dollars they're writing off. That doesn't
seem to be over yet. In fact, I think it's far from over. I think the problems are going to be
much deeper with that. So the Fed is worried about that. So let's just forget the second half
and concentrate on the first half. If all we have to do to make the Fed happy is spend 1% more,
we can probably really get their attention and piss them off by spending a couple percent less.
So think about it. It wouldn't even take that much. Let's just forget all the types of products
and services that we buy for a second. Forget where they're made. That's a whole other issue.
But just to get the attention, the Federal Reserve, if all we always have to do is spend 5% less.
5%, what is 5% of every hundred dollars you spend that you know how fast that goes.
Keep five bucks in your pocket. Don't spend it. Save it. Put it under your mattress.
Do something else with it. But don't buy stuff. If we all did that,
we all did that very simple act of saving 5%. Can you imagine what the, I mean, it would be
consumer spending down 5% Fed freaking out. And we could say, hey, just want to show you the
power now. We've got some demands we want to make. At this next comment has another great idea.
I really like this. Hey Adam, the vermilion support Pennsylvania. Listen to you talk about sending
a message and listen to show. I think 700 tried calling in about not buying fuel.
And they just make an important other day or whatever. Why don't we all just want to fill up
fill up with six dollars in 60 cents to the bunch of six sixes flying on. You got to get
some media recognition. I would thank you. Yeah. I love you Adam.
I love you too. And I think this is, yo, I think it's a great idea. I don't know about six
dollars and 66 cents. I think it would be more like 66 dollars and 66 cents. But yeah,
right on. Let's do that. I'm going to start immediately. I'm going to try and round off everything to
six six six. The mark of the beast. Great idea. Yes, if you fill up fill up $6 and 66 cents
or $66 and 66 cents. That's really cool. So essentially, yeah, we should do maybe we should drop
consumer spending by six point 66 percent. Be nice if we could do it. So just spend six
percent less, six and a half percent less, and then maybe if we're really good, if we really
work on it, we can get that report on the New York Times to say consumer spending drop by six
point six six percent coincidence, you'll have to read the book. And lots of people sending me info
about Reverend Billy. This is the movie, what would Jesus buy for Christmas? And I didn't realize
that this Reverend Billy is actually is a real guy. And this is more a documentary than a film.
It's kind of a combination where it gets thrown out of the Mall of America and thrown out of Disneyland.
Got to be bad to be thrown out of Disneyland. And the guy is an actor. And obviously it's a protest
of sorts. And I'm really starting to like it. And I thought it was, you know, I thought just thought
it was a movie period, but it's a little, it goes a little bit deeper than that. So the concept of
Reverend Billy is a shop, a stop the shocker, was he called shop, a shop, a shop, can't say it.
Shop, a colism. Stop the addiction to shopping, essentially. Stop the corp, the corp talk.
So he has a similar message. And if you combine the two, if you say, let's stop shopping and show
them the mark of the beast by spending six point 66 percent less. I think we could have a real
good brotherhood here between the two of us. And on the site, there's a great song about stopping
shopping with Reverend Billy's choir that I just wanted to share with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Lord I love the little we already got a love love yeah, yeah
Stop, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, follow me,
yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, oh, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, ah, follow me, he, he, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me, yeah, follow me,, follow me, do me, listen, follow me, follow me, follow me, I follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me, you, follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me,
Live on summer day
First up before 1,1
Show one of the people
From what's wrong with girls?
Oh my god, what's wrong with women's son?
You overshot the people
Don't do it Let's get up, do it!
Give it up, C-5 you have to go C-5 and let the man
Wake up, Sonic!
We got a little sister
All right, we need to stop our shot again.
We're gonna back on with you.
Back on with you to that tonight.
Tell me.
Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me.
Back on the way from the front.
Back on the forward.
Time the power.
Stop.
The Reverend Billy and his choir stop shopping.
You can find them at RevBilly.com.
That will work the look.
Mainstream media is paying attention to this guy.
So I like that a lot.
All right.
One more comment.
Do two more comments.
And one more Christmas song to play us out for the day.
Hi.
I'm sorry for making you play.
I'm the not-so-referent county of Essex.
I don't know.
I think this is your podcast for a few months.
Why?
Call in and say hello.
You show really gets me from the day-art work.
So I keep doing it.
Take this really cool.
What you doing on this long haul dude, as well.
And he's campaign.
And you're absolutely right.
No one over here.
No two of the hell he is.
And it was cool.
Did you use it with his little ideas.
That was good.
You should do more stuff like that.
That was really cool.
Anyway, just saying hello.
So good luck with the show and Adi OS.
All right, man.
Thank you very much for listening.
family. Hey Adam, it's Mike from the UC radio pod show, which you can find 24 seven and
bite me FCC dot com plug. You know, I was listening to the DSC 700 the other day and you were
talking about the TSA and all the trouble you're going through and you know what, I feel your
pain. I lived down in Belize for seven years in the 90s and about a year into that I got
caught bringing Cuban cigars back into the country. They made me stand there and break them all in
front of them and then throw them right into a shredder, which just fucking nice me to do. But
I dealt with that. I figured out it for the next five years. Every time I came back to the
States, which was about once a month for business, I was basically strip searched. They went through
all my shit destroyed my bags. It just sucked. So I do feel your pain. But your suggestion, I went ahead
and bought you a domain and unfortunately I didn't use your promo code. I used my own UC radio three
but right to go daddy and I got you don't send Adam to getmo dot com. So now the domain don't send
Adam to getmo dot com points right to your site. So that's it. You have a good holiday. I'll talk to
you soon and what am I supposed to say here? I think it's I fucking love you. Yeah, because I'm confused.
All right. Thanks Mike. Of course you really wanted to use DSC3 to get that domain name for
695. Let me see. Don't send Adam to getmo dot com. Thanks man. That's pretty cool. Let's see where
it points to. Okay. It doesn't say. You've got to look at this. Very funny. It actually before,
nice. Before it, before it sends you to curry dot com, it sends you to another domain which is
called Adam Curry is a fucking homo dot com which has a roof. I can't really see it long enough
because then it it forwards to curry dot com. Thanks Mike. Nice man. You know what? What uh,
how many guys do they have to have to feel you up when that when you're going through that?
Mike's a really big guy. You know and did they, did they lose any any bracelets or or watches
while they were at it my friend? I'll play this one for you Mike. I really appreciate the love my
brother. Nice little piece. Forget about the true meaning of Christmas. Get us in the mood.
Love, friendship and spending time with the family. Mama would be inside,
fix and turkey and dressing and me and my brothers used to play outside and snow for hours. Throw
and snow balls and I'll never forget my daddy coming outside and saying, hey,
I hope that they're going to snowman. I think I risked the fire on the lane.
You could have used the ball, but I keep going. Marara's zucchini.
But the stadium used a symbol. Something you did barely say. I hope that they're going to snowman
and maybe they may look like me. You boys been talking to your mama. I got your Christmas
back. All right. That's it. Daily source code 702 from the west side of G-town in the
Curry Manor. Adam at potcho.com is where you can reach me through email daily sourceco.com
for links of stuff discussed on today's program. And tomorrow we'll have a proper food bar
Friday. I don't have to go into the city. We have some other off-site stuff happening, but I'm
going to participate from home because it's in San Francisco. And that'll be the last one I
guess before Christmas. So join me, will ya? And remember, enjoy your freedom and live life with passion.
Imagine headphones without wires. Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset. A rechargeable
listening experience with 11 hours of music playback. So you and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com slash headphones. Sony wireless headphones. Your music are unplugged.