Ladies and gentlemen, I present Pod Show's poet laureate, Melvin P. Louis-Buff.
Well, this is our red commercial's all-name for the main names in hosting. Go Daddy's the name.
In a condo, in a city by the bay, with a sun is blocked out from other skyscrapers under construction, and no two SSID names can be identical.
There sits the Baker's rack where Adam Curry creates his masterpiece.
It's the DSC V53.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
It's Adam Curry.
A world where the good-dead-doing naughty photo-dabbling one leg at a strange wife of an agent pop star is among the illustrious group of sea listers that ABC has lined up.
For the next edition of its hit competition series, dancing with the stars.
This is the Daily Source Code, number 553.
Thank you very much.
We will be with you.
So I'll come home to you this evening.
No one will be glad to see me too.
I'm inside the fans, and I'm very with you.
I've got you on my mind.
But my thoughts are at a side of the field, but you, every hour, every day of the week.
Well, and imagine I will feel the next to you dancing slowly on a cheeky cheek.
That's why I'll come home to you this evening.
No one will be glad to see me too.
I'm inside the fans, and I'm very with you.
So I'll come home to you this evening.
No one will be glad to see me too.
I'm inside the fans, and I'm very with you.
But we're all the good times.
And say to you, say, I'm making the right choice without a doubt.
We've been together for quite a long time.
Where it seems like forever.
Girl, that you are mine.
Well, and all the time, may you give me pleasure,
but you must never take it all as deep.
And when all of those balls and your faces light up,
we'll never be there to have a back again.
The twilight come home to you this evening.
No one will be glad to see me too.
I'm inside the fans, and I'm very with you.
Baby for you.
Suggested by the official Music College of Surgery, Josie Todd.
Right once again, you are, Todd.
Damn.
Good. Hey, everybody. How you doing?
Daily source code 553 coming to you from Northern California, from the Curry condo.
It is just Tuesday.
I once again am I on my west coast schedule,
and the show is at night, so you can have me in the morning all over the world.
Tomorrow in Australia, which is today here on the west coast.
I did not have a very good night's sleep last night.
After I did the show, and of course I do some stuff for serious satellite.
After I had dinner and everything, and you combine all those things.
It's 1-1-30 in the morning.
So I went to bed, and around 4-30 this morning.
You know, I keep the cell phone next to the bed.
Well, I use it as an alarm clock, because I find I really trust my E61's alarm clock.
And I know it's going to wake me up, and it works exactly the way I want an alarm clock to work.
Very simple.
And of course, if there's something going on back at the manner, if they need me,
I want them to go to reach me, and all this time zone stuff makes it really complicated.
So I just keep the phone near me.
Um, a text message.
Around 4 a.m., 4.30.
I can't remember exactly.
And it was a text.
Actually, I have the, uh, I haven't just grabbed the phone.
I had the text message.
I'll tell you exactly what it said.
And I can also tell the time when it came in, of course.
That's nice.
Yeah, 4.45 a.m.
From Paul Fenton.
I'm waiting for the voiceovers for today.
Can't do squat until I have them.
Now, of course, Pdub's in Florida.
It was, uh, quarter to eight where he was.
And I woke up and like, oh, crap.
Of course, I had done all the work, but I don't know if for some reason,
didn't transfer to the server.
I don't know what was going on.
So out of a dead sleep, you know, like, come on.
I'll just retreat transfer.
And then I have to text him back and forth.
And okay, he got him.
And then I was like, you know, 5.30.
And yeah, then the jet lag, the confusion hit me like a ton of bricks.
But I'm so tired.
I've only slept 4 hours.
And then I don't know.
I ate like a whole plate of Oreos and drank two large glasses of milk and,
and that worked.
Excellent stuff sent in by you guys today.
I'm really proud of you.
And I, and I, and I, I sit at my desk during the day,
and I just smile.
I just smile to myself as stuff comes in on voice mail,
stuff comes in, um, through Gmail.
I just love it.
It really motivates me.
It really makes me want to do the show every single day.
I'm telling you.
Thank you so much.
And Mark Yoshimode Nemkoff and I have been trying to see.
We can revive the art of guitar whanking.
See if we can get people to send in their favorite solos.
Done by themselves.
Hence the wanking portion of the title.
And he sent in another, um, another example today of an excellent guitar whank.
Quite a surprising one I have to say.
Hey, Adam, I got another guitar solo for you.
And this one, you may be surprised, is from the one and only PW Fenton.
Oh, that guy.
Now, a lot of people don't know this.
But before he became a podcaster and an integral part of the pod show family.
Pointing.
PW was a well-known blues musician back in the 1930s.
Um, back then he used to go by the name of blind Willie Lipschitz and, you know,
he'd play around the cat scales and stuff.
I understand he was very popular with the ladies in being uncut and off.
I'm just reading from his Wikipedia page.
But the great depression ended blind Willie Lipschitz's music career.
And it wasn't until decades later that PW Fenton resurrected himself as a blues artist
and formed the band PW Fenton and the second ward named after the wing of the hospital where he stayed at.
I believe it was the sex offender unit.
Or maybe that's the first ward.
The second one being the mental wood.
I'm not sure.
But the one thing I do know.
Let's wine it.
Is motherfucking play.
Ladies and gentlemen.
On guitar.
PW Fenton.
TWAPAH.
Oh, yes.
PW Fenton.
Spiel Fenton.
see listeners out there. If you play the guitar, you got tone. We want to hear it. Jazz
rock, funk, bluegrass, whatever it is that you play. Send it to us. Send me a clip. You
know, like a minute, you playing guitar at House of Tone House of Tone, all one word at
gmail.com. And remember, Adam, next time you talk to Pete up, respect him for the guitar
playing God that he is. And also because he gave me five bucks to say that. Yeah, I know
how to pick him, don't I? Yeah, that was pretty awesome, Pete. I can always, I always
know when when it's time to give Mark a new project, because he starts emailing me with
a million ideas. And actually, I selfishly, I'm thinking, keep sending in stuff like that.
That was awesome. Very surprising. I did not know that when we, when I hired Pete up,
and I'd never met him. I didn't, I didn't mean to for a year until, uh, I was working
with him for a year until we finally met. That's right. Once in a while, now we do, we
should do that again, Pete up. We need to do another, uh, an 800 Nokia video phone call.
I'd love that. Pete up's God one. And I think he has my nav kit, because I was supposed
to receive the developer, uh, an 800 device, the one that is going to spread reports,
wide open for, uh, some SSH action, hot SS on H action. And of course, uh, the point being
that, uh, the developers who have already signed up, and there's a couple of them, can SSH
write into it. It's a Linux machine. It runs a version of Debian, all the, what is it?
Amo. Yeah. So you can SSH in, and, um, it has a VNC server. So when you're developing, you
can actually see what the screen looks like when, when you're, you know, when you run
something, it's like the user interface as an example. And you can control it exactly the
way you would, uh, as if the device was right in front of you. It's kind of virtual development.
And, um, obviously, having the GPS nav kit along with it, which is a big part of what Trinity
's supposed to have, uh, to be functional. That's kind of, that would be kind of handy, wouldn't
know. Uh, so I think P.D. I've got my kit, or some kit is stuck still at customs. I did get the
N800, the new one. It's still on the box. I, I'm not going to have time to set it up tonight, because
you know, I got to install the VNC server, I got to install the, uh, was it bare drop share SSH
demon? Whatever the name of it is. So there's still a little bit of work, and I'm going to
set it up and make sure the, the ports are routed when you SSH. I'm going to set it up here at the
condo. So when you, when the developers SSH in, uh, that we routed to the proper IP address, which will
be the, uh, the IP address of the, of the, of the N800. It's going to be cool. I'm really looking
forward to this experiment. Uh, and of course, I still have to wrap my head around the whole Trinity
thing. Wait, wait until you hear what I've got in the update for today. It's really going to
bend your mind. And you just, uh, I'm, I'm so not sure where we're going to take this, but she's still,
she's still riding, um, Rosie's been driving around, everything's still fine, uh, and there's
still a conversation going on at the Google group. So, um, I just got to wrap my hands around how
we're actually going to execute on this, because it's just, uh, it's, it's a big one. And I just want
to add that I'm having a nice find cup of, uh, fold your coffee year this evening. Uh, just the regular
blend, no, uh, no flavor for me, just with a little bit of milk and a little bit of sugar.
Do you recall, uh, I think it was a comic strip blogger who called it, a good friend C. S. B.
Talking about the U.S. wanting to deploy, um, I guess medium range missiles in the Czech Republic,
in order to, uh, to target Russia was, was not the deal. And, like, some controversy going on with that.
Well, I asked if anyone from the Czech Republic could call me and give me their feelings about,
you know, the whole thing of basically being used as a, as a, as a launch pad for the U.S.
and kind of sitting in the middle. And, uh, low and effin behold, we have a daily source code listener
in the Czech Republic. Hey, I'm, uh, I just finished listening to DSE5551, where DSEB talked about, uh,
those stations that Americans want to build, built in Poland and Czech Republic, those anti-mission
missile silos. Um, I am from Czech Republic, and I have just one thing to say, I don't want any
fucking American radar in my country. We are small country, and we mind around business, we don't,
the mess with, uh, and a terrorists, and we have never, ever had problems with them, and I don't want
to make our country target just because some American radar, which brings completely nothing to our
country. Um, Russians, you know, you should mind your own business. Yeah, that's a lot wanted to
say, take care of them. If right, I'm in, yeah, we don't want no fucking radar activated, the anti
missile shooting down devices in our backyard. I'm down with that, man. Absolutely. And if there's
anyone who thinks that it should be there, let me know, too, but I'm pretty sure we're going to
get the same type of response. You know, it's just so good to hear a human voice, put a frickin
face on these people that we hear about in the news. And you know, uh, uh, I mean, what kind of,
what kind of visual do you get when you think of someone from the Czech Republic? As an American,
please, I just want you to think about it for a second. What is the vision when you think of the
Czech Republic? Do you think cell phones, iPods, uh, BMWs? Do you think that? Exactly. You'll see
that the world is kind of caught up with a lot of this stuff. Hey, there's a new, uh, in the
attic of which, of course, uh, is the show with Pete Townsend, his beautiful and jealous voice,
girlfriend, Rachel Fuller. I'm so in love with her. She's so cute. She's wearing a really cute
outfit in this episode. There's a new episode up which would have been the last episode of
in the attic, but, um, the show is so popular and so successful that we're going to do some bonus
episodes while we work on another series. It's really awesome. And in this last one,
which Rachel actually even announces as the last one, but, you know, then we're able to cut into
a new announcement of her saying more coming soon. Yeah, that's one of those deals. Um,
Tracy Alman stops by and I was just dumbfounded about how cool this is. So they're the back of
their air stream trailer and Pete is fantastic in this episode. Uh, he plays a number of songs
and he's out. They're signing autographs. And so now they're, uh, they're in the, in the air, uh,
air stream with Rachel and Tracy Alman drives by and they start talking about, uh,
wankers. So this is really for our, for the UK listeners. Uh, they also start talking about Pete
from Big Brother and his, uh, his wanker to ret moments. Check out. Check out. I love the
role in the attic. It's making boys. You get you as a lot of boys, boys. We're a bit
smelly. Yeah, I know. I couldn't talk about what they talk about willys and stuff.
Wanky and a little wanky, wanky, wankers. Yeah, I'm, if that's like on, uh,
they call the Pete a lot of Pete or Pete. So as I'm in England, I'm totally, and I still
come back just to want to watch the original song contest. But that's been hijacked by the
Stan countries. What about the book? What about the book? What about the staff has
extent and stands and it's like the stands. Who's the biggest song? Yeah, the stands.
Strictly girls don't say. I love, I like Big Brother. Pete's from here, isn't he? That
blood were to rest. Yeah, yeah, he's from Brighton. Oh, and he's that fancy and he's nice. He's got
yeah. He's got a little bit wider and he's got to rest, which is very trendy now. It's got
to rest, which is very trendy now these days. And everyone's in a while. He says it a really appropriate
moment. And he goes, yeah. And I like Nicky that go. They just talk like this. I am so
poor. I'm worried. And then I think Brava, I've got to have lots of water. Now,
you're the winner. She's totally doing an awesome Nicky. Now, if you haven't seen the UK
big brother, this won't mean much to you, but it's very, very funny segment. And then I'll just
play the little piece of this because this is actually a song on the Podsake Music Network.
Uh, by Rachel Fuller, you can look her up. And it's a life performance with her and Pete.
Let me just, uh, fast forward to it. And I didn't realize that this is the actual recording from the show
that she's put on the PMN. And it's beautiful. It's just Townsend with an acoustic guitar in the
foreground and Rachel in the background. Listen, that voice, man. And you got to see Pete.
It's just totally, totally into it. And the way you can see him is the fantastic. It's just
fucking genius. Oh, okay. So that's a shitty, uh, shitty quality. So I don't want to play that for you.
Um, you know what it's time for? Hold on a second. I got a little bit of music here.
I thought I had some music. There we go. Uh, it is time for Adams, a track from Adams first,
Jen iPod. I knew segment we're trying here on the Deadly Source code. Uh, you might have one of these,
you know, the very first iPod you got. You filled it up to the max. And instead of managing your, uh,
your tunes as you would supposed to be doing, you got another one. So I gave you one. And you
start filling that one up. And so this is from 2004. And it has, uh, just tons and tons of stuff on it.
And it's not all just music. And what we're doing is, uh, let me just grab my wire here. Hold on a second.
I've got to put it. I'm literally, oops. Hold on. I've got to put it on pause.
Okay. So now it's set up. Let me, uh, go to the next track.
So you have no idea what it could be. It could be anything at all that pops up. And hopefully
I'll be able to put it into some kind of context. Yesterday's, uh, song, uh, was its swing swing swing.
I had no idea why that was on my iPod. I don't remember recall putting it on.
I've no idea where it came from, uh, but a lot of people recognize it. And as I saw in the,
in the comments in the show, no, it's a lot of people liked it, too. So let's see,
what does Adam's first gen iPod bring us today?
It's something called star-frosh. Revolution something or other. It's a first gen iPod.
You know, I got to wait for this thing to scroll by, so I've actually see what it says.
I don't know if I like this.
I was going to drive me up to freaking wall. Okay. Uh, one of the rules of another track from
Adam's first gen iPod is if I hate the track, I get to choose another one. So it's on random.
Let me go to the next track. Let's see what we get.
Oh, man. We look out. We get some friends. Yeah, some cinnamon girl.
From Adam's first gen iPod.
Never before that day.
Tell him the same light.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah
From Adam's first gen iPod, it's Prince in the Revolution.
No, it's not even where the Revolution is, Prince,
from musicology, cinnamon girl.
And, you know, you can really tell the difference between a quality recording
and the one that I have on the first gen iPod.
So, in fact, I don't even recommend you buy this track from iTunes.
I recommend you go out and get the CD.
I'm played on a CD player with some decent speakers because, you know,
it's really going to really going to be worth it.
Let me just grab the, uh, you'll plug there.
Okay. Interesting. Interesting with popped up on Adam's first gen iPod.
I hadn't expected that one. There's a lot of old stuff on there too,
just we haven't gotten to it yet, I guess. Remember, it's on shuffle.
So, it's all, uh, well, being done completely fairly.
Well, we've got some good calls today.
Time once again to get the old girl rolling.
Driving across the USA.
Open and make a good time today.
I feel like I've better watch a girl letting everybody know
that this is going to be the better way.
The Trinity, Trinity, the Christmas Central Luxury, Trinity, Trinity,
left the bio diesel set you bring, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity.
Well, we have one Mercedes 300 turbo diesel station wagon that runs on vegetable oil,
better known as bio diesel. You know, the kind of stuff you're making garage,
or the bio fuel-oasis and Berkeley, California, where I have been before.
And we want to drive her across the USA.
And why, well, first of all, because we can and secondly, because we can do it all
without the dependence upon the big oil companies and it's damn fun.
And we're going to make it a kind of a technology project and a friendship project.
A community project, if you will.
Yesterday, I received a call from someone who I called an echo terrorist
who called himself a nylon being from New York and London.
I didn't know that that was an actual, uh, an actual description of someone who
commuted back and forth, but I guess it makes sense if you're in banking or whatever, nylon.
And uh, I came down pretty hard on him because I felt that he was accusing me of
making this whole green thing. And of course, it's not. It's about independence from foreign oil
and from big companies and, you know, I think Trinity somehow is, she's a symbol, not just the
car, she's, why she's an icon. Anyway, dude calls back. Here's what he has to say.
Hey Adam, this is the nylon from Wilburton. And in fact, that is a common term,
you wouldn't get New York magazine here. I want to appreciate to play in my message,
but a couple of corrections for you. Um, I happen to be welcome with the walk as I was.
That's why I should listen to your shows. That's why I may have found it like I was in a hurry.
A couple of corrections, one, one year old show you told everyone that you're going to be in
Twitter and encourage them to listen to you. So I listen to you and Twitter. That doesn't
make me a Twitter listener. Of course, they. Okay. All right. I'll give you that one.
Or someone going on a course. Indeed, I'm over in this country because they used to work for
the beloved oil company. In your native land, well, I guess, nevertheless, if in your native land
and approve it, I can still mispronounce, they would make it. Yeah, that would be safeening it.
Okay, interesting. So the guy either worked or works for big oil. Well, okay, the plot thick
I'm so quite out of the environmentalist. I, in fact, can give you some geophysical aspect of the
industry that you're trying to free yourself from. So that's wrong. Two, I would hope that you're
more inclusive and that just because someone has a different point of view point than you,
that you don't label them as part of some environmental backlash terrorist group. I'm into it.
Well, first of all, as nothing to do with inclusion, I included you. I'm including you again.
I'm just calling you a name. That's all. It's cool. Who has happened to listen to your show?
And so that the bio diesel was kind of a walk like a dot, talk like a dot sort of thing,
that you're in fact work promoting environmental agenda, which you still really are.
And finally, I do listen to all your shows. So this was not a one-off. I fused a
get into this kind of logical habit of what I do in the toilet. So that would have given
a different clue. But anyway, I appreciate you playing it because that's a lot. But I think you
did make some think of the assumptions because I disagreed or had a different perspective from you.
See you soon. So I listen to that and I'm thinking, okay, I still don't get it. Where did the green
thing come from? I've never, I've never talked about this as a green project. I just haven't. So
yeah, okay, apologies. But I just understand. Here's a guy who clearly listens to the show.
He listened to me on Twitter because I told him to listen to, you know, to go listen to me
on Twitter. I appreciate that. So I must be mistaken. Somehow I'm coming across
differently than I intend to, that the free Trinity project has something to do with greenness.
One, you know, I agree. There's a lot of reasons you can say this is not a green project at all.
And then it started to kind of become clear. It started with this voice mail from the UK. So
get ready to switch your gears and tune into a English accent.
At any point where you might ever be confused, there's a thing to admit. You said, just say the world,
say the world and that. Are you getting this? I know it's really hard and it's sometimes very
hard to go from an American accent to a real British accent. What he's saying is he feels that
people may be confused by the theme tune, particularly the ending. Well, you know what, let me,
yeah, let's do it officially then. The ending would just go something like this.
Trinity, Trinity, because essential luxury, Trinity, Trinity, let the bio diesel set you for your
country. Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, free Trinity, save the world, win valuable prizes, Trinity.
Right. Save the world. Okay. So now it's starting to make some sense. All righty.
Okay. So I apologize to the nylon. But, you know, the theme tune is so good and this saved the
world thing. Maybe we should specify. Save the world from, save the world from scrunchers.
Yeah, I'm stuck, Pilgrim. Listen to how it changed to pick a baron. I don't want to play that one yet.
Yes, it is. No, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, pilot error again. This is what I wanted to play.
Hey, Adam. This is the nylon from mumble to. And, in fact, that is a cough wrap. That's not the one. Oh,
no. Well, on a second. Oh, I'm so sorry about this. Here we go. This is the one I wanted to play.
It's awesome. Check it out. You're a lad. I'm the slave from the York. How you doing? Hey,
uh, okay. I was listening to the DSC 552 when I heard the audio comment with a guy derived
into the free Trinity project and you personally about not being green and I had to call you.
After I was wondering too about how all the drivers were going to get home and how the whole thing was
going to look while we tried to make a statement about alternative energy. Well, check it out. I think I
found a solution. Look at terrapast.com and tell me what you think. It's a program where you could buy a
pass that can't so that your personal carbon footprint by funding renewable energy projects.
Kind of like a Kyoto protocol for you and me. I think we should get one of these terrapastes
for Trinity and have anyone who drives a vehicle connected with a free Trinity project. Get one, too.
Shit, maybe we should try to get all the DSC listeners to get one, huh? That would show him how green we are.
I mean, if you're not part of the solution, you're part of the problem, right?
Okay. See ya. Love ya. And, uh, though I swing both ways, it's more fun to say.
Scruncher. Oh, girlfriend, please. So, I don't know if you know about this or how this works.
But it is indeed a fact that I believe it's countries and the countries and I'll
turn that over to companies. You can essentially, you build up a credit of points and these points
are for CO2 emissions. How many emissions you can throw into the air? And this thing has become
a tradable commodities. It's fascinating is what it is. It's so, I mean, I love it. You know,
you watch, you'll be trading water before too long. Uh, we already are. I'm sure we're already
trading water. But anyway, um, I received an email from Doug Pilgrim. And I remember Doug is the guy
who wanted to come out to San Francisco with his son and drive back to Boston with Trinity,
which got this whole thing started. And of course, we're coming a little bit full circle.
Back to the original idea, just for simplicity, sake, and for quality of programming, sake,
and uh, and also quite honestly, for some green sake, because it's, what a, what a nightmare
trying to, uh, have a different driver every 100 miles or something like that. It's, it, it just
will not work. Very, very difficult. So anyway, Doug Pilgrim sends me an email. Good morning,
Adam. I bought Trinity a gift. Seems like everyone wants valuable prizes from her. I thought I
would give her something. This is an energy REC or renewable energy credit for native energy. This
will compensate for any CO2 that might be emitted on our voyage when straight 100% biodiesel is used.
This covers two tons of CO2 or 4,467 miles worth of petrodiesel or 22,337 miles of B20 diesel.
Please place a copy of this with the car before she drops lines. So, and he sent me this,
this printable document. And it's absolutely true. Trinity is now green for 22, well, more.
But I'll just say, since we're doing 100% biodiesel. And, you know, there's a pretty high number
for the B20, which means 20% biodiesel, 80% petrochemical based biodiesel. Let's just say 25,000 miles
of credit. What a fantastic idea. And, Dave, New York, you guys are all geniuses over there on
these coast. You and Doug is fantastic. I love this. So, of course, this is, this is, we're going
to incorporate this into into the project. And, let's promote the purchase of this. This is great.
And, I know it sounds kind of like a mathematical trick. But, you know, you couldn't, you
couldn't basically buy yourself greener. It's very simple to do. You buy one of these renewable
energy credits. And, you, and somewhere in the world, less CO2 will be emitted into the atmosphere,
into the air, because you put down your money for that, because you bought that, you bought that
right to reduce CO2 emissions somewhere. And, of course, you don't have to have a car to buy that.
So, we could, that's, that's a metric that's interesting. How many thousands of miles
we have made CO2 free or how many tons of CO2? I mean, this thing that Doug bought is two tons
of CO2. That sounds pretty impressive. I'm really, really liking that idea. So, give me a few more
days to flesh this out in my head, but I'm getting pretty close. We're getting the technology
piece together. I still haven't even gotten back to Paula Walter, podcaster, Barbara,
for figuring out what role she's going to play and how we're going to manage this.
But, I do know that I'm really leaning towards the friendship love ankle of this as well. I'm
such a sucker. Listen to what Doug Pilgrim sent in. You remember, he came up with this
cock-a-ma-ma-ma idea while his son was off at sea. And his son, Brock, came home. Well,
I'll let Doug tell you the story. Hey, Adam, it's Doug Pilgrim. Listen to how it changed to pick
up Brock. Yesterday, my son, he just got back from two months on board his ship down the Caribbean.
And, uh, played some excerpts from all of the free Trinity discussions that have been going on
the daily source code. And, uh, I got in very interesting, uh, candid reaction from the kid afterwards.
And I thought I'd share that with you. No way. What's, what's the deal? What do you think of that?
I think one, what, I'm, I'm, wow. Well, I just think about doing something. Go on a San Francisco,
I'm picking up a car and driving it back. That's, that's completely awesome. I think that's
incredible. The miraculous, for example. We're all astronauts at the interspace. Why don't
pursue it? Yeah, they drug test you. Oh, did he call back? What do you say? What do you say?
What do you think about that so far? So far, you're on board. Yeah. So you can imagine the reaction here
at home. Uh, and I kind of, uh, understood it coming from a kid who's been hanging out with the
Rostafarians down the Caribbean. Mom wasn't as understanding though. She, uh, she immediately ran
out and hopped in the car and drove down to the local pharmacy for a drug test for the kids. So,
um, it was interesting times here, uh, back at the house after that one. Hey, teenagers, what are you going to do?
Yeah, I know. Tell me about it. But, uh, I think your wife probably went to get the drug test for you
dug your idea. Okay. You know, that really seals it for me. I got to have you guys driver across
the USA. There are a couple of spots we got to hit though, uh, because we do have, um, a lot of different
spots on the map. And I, if you guys only have a week, it may be too short. So let's see if,
how much time you actually, um, you actually have. And we got to put some time in there in case,
uh, something happens. And did you show your son a picture of the car?
So, um, once she's in Boston, I think we have, uh, aren't there's, remember the two girls who, um,
who want to see each other, the two girls with, with no man?
Right. We definitely got to send her up there. You know, and, and then all podcasters,
and so everyone will be able to make some good shows and send it back. And, uh, yeah, yeah,
I, okay, and even so, um, there are a couple of cities. I want to, I wanted to go to Seattle.
I'd like her to go to Portland. Um, I don't think we'll be able to go into Canada, but if we
get her around the world, we're coming back through Canada, that's for sure. And of course,
the intent is to get her over to the, to the UK after, uh, after the East Coast. Uh, let's see,
we'd probably want to hit Chicago. We'd probably want to hit, um, maybe Dallas, Dallas, Chicago,
or something like that. Okay. So it's starting to form in my mind, but I, you know,
really the whole buddy movie idea, father, son, uh, girlfriend girlfriend. This is tournament.
I like this. This is going to be cool. Okay, everybody. Uh, that's it for today. If you're in the UK,
I would certainly appreciate it if you gave us a call, or if you're close to the UK phone exchange.
Lock this in your mobile.
Plus for four, two, seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
So we put that plus in there because you're supposed to store this number in your cell phone,
or as we say in the UK, your mobile, your mobile. So wherever you go in the world, the number will always,
have the right, uh, and correct prefix and dial without adding any additional numbers. If you're in the
U.S., be prepared to lock this into your phone.
God, that's annoying. I have at least you remember it, right? Okay, uh, plenty to do tomorrow.
So I'm going to get out of here. I'm going to go to bed and you all have, uh,
yourself a fantastic Tuesday. DailySourceco.com, Adam and podshow.com. Take care of yourself,
bye, bye. Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest, served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery, podshow and
lightweight.