Well, Adam, with the addition of John C. Devorek to Pod Show, I am assuming that the DSC will
get a little extra techie. So, you know, the man that gets no spam, the man from devorek.org
slash blog, why had that techiness to Fubar Friday and will that work? Exactly what will
that mean? Because with all the music, you're going to go techno pop, or you're going to
go synthesizers. I guess we'll find out in the DSC 608, but welcome aboard, John C. Devorek,
adding that extra techie.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A
A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, B-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-S, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B, C-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-D-B-C, A-B-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A-B-C, A
You got to meet me, you see, it is the accord to you, I'll say, well, let's go, rain me, A, B, C, one, two, three, baby, you and me, you see, you see, it is the accord to you, I'll say, well, let's go, rain me, A, B, C, one, two, three, baby, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me,
on the branches of a learning team. And builden with all our fruits and my metal,
material, education, acheically, T, T, T, just gotta show you, A, B, C, E, B, C, E, I come, these things, all same, will
like always, me, A, B, C, I'm 23, baby you and me, you and me, you see, it's the accord to you, I'll say, well, let's
I'll see, but as though it'll rain me
ABC, one, two, three,
Baby, no, I'll be girl
Tell me, girl
I'll make a love, girl
No, yeah, girl
Show me what you do
Take it, take it, take it, baby
Come on, not shake it, shake it, baby
Oop, oop, shake it, shake it, baby
One, two, three, baby
Oop, oop, ABC
ABC
I don't know anything
Baby, no
That's, I'll eat, love,
baby
And Disney is like how
Jing果可以
Zing a ship on my property
Stopface dog, you bring it over
енно, pois alright
Bring it on
You young girl, call me
pouce in when it's coming
baby, c'est Disney
To you go
Go, go, go go
Psh
See that seam
I'm so mad at me
Can't I wait, be sick
I'm in the apartment with you
I'll see you in the apartment with me
A, be sick
One, two, three, baby, you and me
In the apartment with you
I'll see you in the apartment with me
A, be sick
One, two, three, baby, you and me
In the apartment with you
I'll see you in the apartment with me
A, be sick
I'll have to say that it's one of the most musically challenging methods I've heard in a while
Of course courtesy of matchup time.com
DJ Morgol
Shout-A, B, C, consisting of a course
Michael
Shout your name
Tito
Yeah
And it disturbs cover of shout-outs
Shout-outs
Massive for your convenience on a maximum music group
Our surprise
Shout-outs
And then he starts goes six
Zero
Eight
Come on
Shout-out
You want it?
Come on
Now you are getting it
Shout-out
Got some awesome tunes from the podcast and music network today
Most of them sent in by a recommendation suggestion
You might like this super-loss
Ragnum
Citywagon
The villager
This isя
Citywagon
It's not me, it's not me
It's not me, it's not me, it's not me
It's not me, again, without long awake
I'm scared about anything, find more
It start all around, without you
It's all around, why do you need harm
I am scared about that, I'm sure my chuckling
That's why you're a man, you're a face to be her
And you're a woman
You're a woman
That you're getting along
You're a man that you're saying your thoughts
You're a woman
You're just a woman
Suggested by everybody's favorite rock and roll alien
Mark Bob the alien
Superlaks
Run, rabbit, run on a maximum music
Food Bar Friday
It's a muggy here in
Guilford
On the west side of G-town
At least in the manner
Windows are open
It's definitely going to rain a little bit
This afternoon in the general London area
But I'd kind of tell you this global warming
It's you may think it's bad
But before you know it
The United Kingdom will be the new Bahamas
Here I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
You're on her
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work in law here
It's just a tiny bag
Yeah
You're on her
What do you say?
You might even end when this case
You're a zeta
What's up Adam
It's yours you taught
The official musicologist of the
Chacha
Dude except no substitutes
Except for Splendop
Dude, did you there?
Dude, are you with me man?
I've got something
Absolutely, absolutely fantastic
Freaking fantastic for a fantastic
Food Bar Friday
Dude
The Munisizuki
Around the Pod Safe Music Network
You cannot beat this
Dude, if you don't know the Munisizuki
They're one of my all-time favorite
Hard rock and bands at a New York
New York, the city's so nice
They named it twice
Dude, this song is unbelievable
I am so thoroughly psyched up
They're on the Pod Safe Music Network
They've got a brand new album coming out
Called Have Mercy
And this is their new track
99% dude
This just rock
I know you don't love it
Have a great football Friday everybody
Have a great football Friday
You've had it with me
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. doin' like that, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah there we are, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah just yeah it, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's that, um-huh. So yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah,
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Come on, okay, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on rolls on, come on,
Don't let me think, leave it, don't get your way
It's not enough, but it's enough
Let it out, put it down, put it down, put it down
Oh, not enough, put it down
Oh, not enough, put it down, put it down
No, not enough, put it down
Not enough, put it down, put it down
Oh, yeah, Sergio's a top scores, big time, the full bar
It's a multi-moony Suzuki man, I like these guys
Definitely the kind of two of them that I'm into
You can find them at the pod save music network
Just go to potchot.com slash music, or of course
You can always go to dailysourcecode.com and check out the show notes
For the appropriate links
For New York
And they're good
Mooney Suzuki
Jersey Todd
Thank you, man
Hey, now I really picked a fine week to quit smoking
Particularly with all the humidity in the air
I have night sweats have come back again
And I don't know if it's a
It has to be some part of physical thing
That's taking place, just my body saying
I don't want to make a meme
And just the general fact of it being warm and muggy
Water water helps could give me night sweats
John DeBorick with potchot
Unbelievable, totally cool
Could be
Hey everyone, this is John Misselli from the Dawn and Drew Show
And the other day, Drew and I got to interview world famous
Reggae legend Ziggy Marley
And he told us some secrets
If you don't believe me, you should check this out
Yeah, I mean, I think this is for a seminar
I told anybody that
Exclusives
Yeah, you guys got the exclusive and that
For the rest of this exciting interview
Head over to Dawn and Drew.com and June 1st
I got to tell you guys totally rock that you got that all set up
Seriously
And I believe this is going to be a tune on the podcast music network
I mean, does it get any better than that
All right, here's something that will be on the PMN tune
It's from 1995 and it's being kind of upgraded remix
Then you probably heard of Jimmy Z
But I'm not going to tell you who plays
Lick guitar, bass, slide, B3 organ and Roads of piano
But you know who he is basically
Think about it
I'm telling you who it is at the end
I know you know him
This is the house for the love
But I'm so bad right now
Yeah, I'm going to cross the wind
And I'm on the moon
You've been sweet on the moon
I'm going to end it more
I'll tell you know the visitation
No time to worry
There's the blame no one can see
Yeah, I never think you'd think
Yeah, but there's a deal
Yeah, I'm going to cross the wind
No one there the whole
The rain we chose to go
Water's turning away
We've stopped by a lot of memory
They got me and they're with us
We're going down the semblance
And all that I don't know
She says all the love that was in me
Tell me if I'm a stone
I can't have a place to live
I can't have a place to go
And I'm going to cross the wind
No one there
Yeah, I never think you'd think
Yeah, but there's a deal
No one can see
No one there the whole
The rain we chose to go
This is all gone
Bye-bye
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. No, no anymore, no people no μα o'ypen, no para
Đây.
It's so cool.
So man, you can't hide it
I think I actually have heard the song, but indeed it was like 17 years ago when it was
first of the quarter.
I don't believe ever released either, so that would be cool to have it on the network.
The project's titled, Savala Bloom, Jimmy Z, studio tapes from 1995, transferred into
Logic Pro at the Bloom Residence, Ron Bloom indeed, partner in CEO of Potio, played
lead guitar based, slide, V3 organ, Willow's Appiano, Jimmy Z, they're on Harp and Vocals
and of course the fabulous Blue Zets on Back and Vocals and Studio Legend, David Raven
on Drums, hopefully to be released soon for all podcasters to play.
Bloom, it's your own dog food!
I had him, Mike the B here, thanks for the shoutout for in-working hammer on DSC599.
I just loved the fight flight cast, it sounded like a model flight to me, you do a great job
with that radio, particularly with those continental accents coming through.
I'm sure the flight scores will be used in the podcast in their training.
I found it demanding enough to keep up with all the info I had to get in gift to the
AT controllers around South East England, given that Heathrow, Gattwick and Farm were split
the airspace into funnels, vertically and horizontally, no spot is outside intense radio
control.
I just have to say, well done, fold up.
Adam, it's got her hands, it's on to the DSC on Tuesday, May 20, 2021, you're on your flight
night, have to say that I'm interested in knowing how to fly as to the London Aircraft
and I'm wondering if you have any tips for somebody who is interested in doing so, how much
time and money it's going to take to get that license, so if you can help me up, that'd be
great.
If you don't want to play this comment on the air, you can email me, it's Jack.
Hey, Adam, it's Chris over at PlainMan.com and the PlainMan is podcasts and like I promised,
I've got another five second flight lesson for the week for you.
All right, so here's the deal, you're trying to call your traffic control, but nobody's
responding and you try again and again and again and they're still not responding.
You know what you do?
You get off the couch, you get down the airport, you get in the air plane, you go fly
and man, it's just been way too long.
All right, another one for the week, we'll see you next time.
Dude, I love that, the five second flying lesson or flight lesson, that's great.
You should do a podcast of all of that.
And of course, continue to send them on over to, to this particular part.
I'm about one more mashup on.
I'm gonna have to stop singing this one since I heard it.
I'm not gonna push you, this is the last part.
There's no squeeze, but there's motion, I got it.
I'm gonna break the pictures.
You're gonna break well, it's still in my room.
I'm gonna pop that.
I miss you too much, but I got mine.
I'm gonna break, quit playing the UK, and you can't shine.
Oh, then it's just a week, I'm gonna try again and again and again and again and again.
There's never too much noise, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna break, quit playing the UK, and you can't shine, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no this is a sentence, i think to touch something I may believe somewhere, so it won't be, so it won't be, so, who,'ll be! so, hope it won't be, so it won't be! and I think that I
It's so hard it's going at it
It's making it even the heart
I'll fight it
I'm dirty dirty
I'm the saddest
I'm losing you
You're too much
Come on, it's black and I
I'm not gonna let you
Come on, it's black and I'm not gonna let you
Come on, it's black and I
I'm not gonna let you
Come on, it's black and I'm not gonna let you
It's black and I'm not gonna let you
Yeah, you know where it came from, the National Town.com, don't prove it, it's fitting, it's
fitting.
That's what you get with you, we cross the guys with cheese with 50 cent.
I don't like most of those 50 cent matchups with this one really did it for you.
Yeah.
On Germany, host of tips on the top floor and a proud member of the Potio family, and
I hear you talk a lot about Darmstadt recently, so it sounds very interesting to me and
I'm really looking forward to all the news that you're going to bring home around that.
I'm also an active potcaster in Germany for the German market, so we might want to talk
about a few things here.
I've also just released my show number 200 of tips on the top floor, if you want to see
the trucker Tom as an alien, Don and Drew Dancing, CC Japanese singing, and of course
the Jeff Smith, who wrote the theme song for the show, then yeah, going over to tips
from the top floor.com, lots of photography tips in that show as well, and by the way, I'm
not even going to go into what Darmstadt actually translates to.
Yeah, I know what it does with you, but I know, oh, all the hooter, and of course I'm going
to come and hang out with you.
You know that.
I just needed to get, to get things started in intestine town, because I think that's what
it means, right?
Darm is intestine, and stuff is sitting, so intestine city, intestine town, here's
going from California.
Her name is Curious, this is Goodbye.
You're mine, so I curse that door on your way out, hang out through it tonight.
When you said, look in the fight, teaching me for forever, when you said, look in the fight,
you know you remember me forever, you said, you don't tear my heart, but look at me now,
I am really dying here, all I want is to disappear, don't make me feel like I'm
going to get wasted in my time, just get me to lie, when you said, look in the fight,
teaching me for forever, when you said, look in the fight, when you remember me forever, no matter what
I want to be scared, no matter what you feel like, I want to be a angel, now I'm going to be
alone, remember my broken dreams, say, look in the morning, just get me to lie, just get me to lie,
when you said, look in the fight, teaching me for forever, when you said, look in the fight, when you remember me forever, no matter what you feel like,
anymore, no matter what you feel like, you know you remember me forever, no matter what you feel like,
Hey Adam, this is Dawn Miscelli, your special, special secret girlfriend over here at the
Dawn and Drew Show.
And I heard you talking about Tylenol PM and how their sponsor of the show, and I just
wanted to let you know how much I love Tylenol PM.
I've suffered with insomnia for years since I was actually really little, and doctors have
prescribed all sorts of stuff, and most of it actually hasn't worked.
It hasn't helped me get to sleep.
But all in all, Tylenol PM always has helped me fall asleep, and the next day I'm not
Dragon Major asked.
So I just wanted to let you know how I felt about it, and I just wanted to also tell you I miss
you.
Bye.
Ah, Dawn, that's so sweet of you, girl.
By the way, you do know that Tylenol PM of course works great, but I've got something
that could really put you to sleep, baby.
The band was formed in 1975 in New Orleans, Louisiana, previous members, saw my friends.
This power trio still, till this day, has all three original members.
The first album went gold and became the fastest selling debut album in the history of
Atlantic records.
During the next couple of years, they played open-source for Erils Smith, Journey, Zezee
Top, Leverboy, T-Trick, Saming Hagar, and R-E-L-Speed Lagen.
The group has produced five albums, and five videos with combined sales of almost 2 million.
They have a brand new DVD out, right now.
Brent Bradley, a pod show radio sits down with a lead vocalist and guitarist for the rock
band Zebra.
He'd be surprised, but you find out, check it out at potshowradio.com, beginning on Monday,
June 4th.
From Jerusalem to Japan, from Australia to Oslo, all over the world, at the very same
time, someone will be running with you.
In Spittling the street, Lincoln, England, in Knoxville, Tennessee.
And Scotland joined a global community of runners and participate in this free non-commercial
worldwide event that celebrates the joy of running with the challenge of a road race.
Share your local experience with a global audience of friends and fellow runners in the
Fitbitations Worldwide Half-Marathon and kick the coach 5k road race.
It's the Fitbitations Worldwide Half-Marathon.
To learn more, go to worldwidehalf.com.
Think global, run, local.
I wanted to remind you all that you've probably heard the suckless campaign is kicked off
now across the network.
If you're listening to Daily Source Code right now, please, I really would like you to
particularly if you are a listener who does not have a podcast that really appreciated
if you went over, signed up and filled out the enormous length of questions in our surf.
We tried to make some of them entertaining, but at the end of the day it's just really
difficult to make basic demographic questions easy.
I guess that's why we're giving the opportunity to get free stuff for going through
some of these painful exercises, but you actually really do help us suck less.
Now, just to put it all into context, we understand, I'd say 99% of the complaints about
the site.
We understand about many of these little issues that thousands of people have emailed us
about, but if you really go through the structure of all of these questions, you give us a lot
more information about even how we can make programming better.
And this information is also going to all podcasts, who are participating on the network.
So it's not just for podcasts, it's for your favorite podcast.
Please go to suckless.podshow.com.
All right, yeah, it's time for something a little different.
You know, sometimes I'm so far away from your dolly.
I'm not safe, he like me to why I read and it's time for you.
That's what I want you to do while I'm going to go.
Tell me.
You want to take my love with you.
Everywhere you go, I want to take my love baby.
Everywhere you go, don't take my love baby.
Everywhere you go, in a street and a cross, when you're home, all alone.
You want to take my love with you, everywhere you go.
When I'm gone, so far away, in your heart, I want to stay.
So babe, keep your mind on me and will I love it.
And it's me who I don't have tension, can't turn around.
But you know how I'll always be around.
You're just gonna take my love with you, everywhere you go.
Come on baby, take my love with you.
Everywhere you go, don't take my love with you.
Everywhere you go, everywhere you just stay.
Everywhere you go, in a street and a cross, when you're home, all alone.
You've got to take my love with you, everywhere you go.
You've got to take my love with you, everywhere you go, in a street and a cross, when you're home.
You know you're just not to my love with you
Everywhere you go
Wow, you want to take my love baby
Oh baby, take my love with you
Everywhere you go
You know you need to stop and take my love baby
In the street
And I'm proud
You know when you're home
When you're all alone
All the highways
All the pathways
You know it sounds like you went back to
I don't know was it's 60s
Maybe even earlier than that
But no nothing like that
A street-y paper boy read
And the true loves
From Massachusetts and the United States
Actually from Boston
And it's on the podcast music network
Am I just fooling myself and take my love with you
Two tracks that you definitely need to check out
And what we need to check out now
What's playin' on
Ados first
Tonight
This of course is the complete plot-lock segment of
The Daily Source code
Particularly when it's a maximum music football pride
We gear up my first generation iPod
Probably gonna have my six or seventh gen iPod
When it comes in the iPhone
Even if it has only 45 minutes of battery life
I'll be interested in it together
It's just the kind of the thick one
It didn't have all that space on it
But it's just the one that I did develop
The actual iPod or application on
So there's a lot of shit on this
From years and years of finding stuff
On Napster
Back in it was illegal stuff
That I've bought through iTunes
And actually Napster Rhapsody
And I have a special Friday playlists
Which I had collected over the years
And I'm gonna just...
Hold on a second, we put it on
Random here
Because you...
You know, you've got a...
When I hear it, hold on a second
Okay, maybe this will work
Yeah, there it goes
Ah!
Oh, I know what this one is
Remember these vibes?
Was it Clark Daxler?
This was huge
Even in Russia
All right
From the first gen iPod
Shattered dreams
So much for your promises
They know that they'll let me go
Cut up in web of lights
But it was just too late to know
I thought it was you
Through a step on the sky
And now you're giving me
Nothing but shadow dreams
And shadow dreams
Feel like I've got a way
Don't wait
From there's a fever
You said you'd die for me
I'll look up to reality
I'm found a future not so bad
I dreamt the impossible
But maybe things could work out
Right
I thought it was you
Through a step on the sky
And now you're giving me
Give me nothing but shadow dreams
Shattered dreams
Feel like I've got a way
Don't wait
From there's a fever
You'll give me nothing but shadow dreams
And shadow dreams
Feel like I've got a way
Don't wait
From there's a fever
You said you'd die for me
I thought it was you
Through a step on the sky
And now you're giving me
Give me nothing but shadow dreams
I thought it was you
Through a step on the sky
And now you're giving me
Give me nothing but shadow dreams
Feel like I've got a way
Don't wait
From there's a fever
You're giving me nothing but shadow dreams
Feel like I've got a way
Don't wait
From there's a fever
And it was in 1988
So I went to Russia
And this is way before the wall came down
With a Moscow music piece festival
And it was basically
And I was behind the iron curtain
So the western music band
It was all underground
The kids knew about Aussie
They knew about the scorpions
And stuff like that
Because Germany
Relatively close proximity
But an Aussie of course
But there was no radio playing
The stuff people had cassettes
And I remember going into a restaurant
That I think kind of half restaurant bar
Type thing very small
Actually one of the nicest restaurants in Moscow at the time
Because we were with some officials
I can't recall who
It was a long time ago
And it was just
There was a band in the corner
And they were playing
Singing kind of
It sounded like traditional Russian stuff
And then all of a sudden they started
Into shattered dreams
And the girl had clearly
She had no printed lyrics
So it was kind of phonetic
So the lyrics were all off
But her heart was in the right place
It was really a fantastic experience
Oh, so I can see what we got going here
What day is it today?
It's Friday
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
Food on Friday
Adam Spine of Thunderfome
Yeah
Oh well
I'll tell you
As you know
I've had Germany on my mind for the past week
And having grown up in Amsterdam
If you know a little bit of history
The Netherlands
See the Nazis in the Second World War
Basically
You know
Drove right through the Netherlands
Who capitulated within two or three days
And they bombed
The shit out of the country
Rotterdam especially
And we are growing up in the post World War Two era
In the Netherlands
There was always kind of an animosity towards the Germans
And of course we're really talking about 20, 25 years ago
Maybe even longer
I can kind of feel this
And it just wasn't a good vibe
Now it's still been a relatively short time
Only you know one human lifetime
Since the Second World War ended
60, 60, some odd years
But there is of course a whole new generation
That has grown up
And having been in Germany for the past couple days
And really having had an opportunity to speak with many different citizens
And of course they're all European citizens
But just Germans
It's completely different
I have to say
All the people I met
And of course most of these were business discussions
Curdious
Nice
You know
Funny
Just really
Awesome
And I have to say the level of English that the Germans speak
Is really really high
And it's kind of surprising
Because they don't subtitle
Television programs
Well like movies and TV series
They really do overdubs
So there is no way to read along
And hear the words
And kind of learn like countries surrounding Germany do
So I don't know where they get it
I don't know if it's
I don't know
It's just good
It's work and I like it a lot
And so it really kind of
Kick me in the ass once again
You have these preconceived notions about people and nations
And they're based on perhaps old information
Like in my case where it's been many, many, many years ago
And I've got to tell you
I'm very excited about our movement of Germany
And of course now we get to decide
We're going to have our headquarters
Now I tell you where it's not going to be
It could be Hamburg
It could be Cologne
Cologne
It could be Munich
It could be
Well
What's your suggestion?
Let me know
Alright everybody
In the United States
Have a great memorial day
We kind of everybody in the United Kingdom
Have a great bank holiday
I'm so glad your banks give us so many holidays
And of course I will be doing a show on Monday
No idea where I'm going to be next week
Could be Germany
Could be San Francisco
Could be New York
Could be in your backyard
DataSourceco.com
Adam or podshow.com
Have a good day
Take care
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight