Hey, I don't know who the fuck this is, but quit fucking impersonating Adam Curry.
Cock-sucker.
Hello there, Mr. Bard. This is Scrutch in the Cloud. Normally at this time each week I
should have been a little inspirational message to Mr. Adam, but he doesn't seem to be answering
his email at the moment. So I guess I'll just have to send this to you. Whenever life trials
and tribulations have you down, and everything at the San Francisco office looks like an unbelievable
clusterfuck, just do what Mr. Scrutch does. Smoking others, blip. Call up Cataly Lewis
and jog dirty. You can turn their darkest day into happy smiley one just you watch. This
is scrunching the clone. It's signing off. You're listening to the Daily Source Code
with Mark Yoshimoto Namcoff.
This is the Daily Source Code 5-8 for a company from Adam's house here in Guilford, somewhere
deep in the UK. Got a real big show for you today. Got a big announcement I'm going
to make, and a special interview with somebody, well, who's a friend of the show? Well,
I have a friend maybe pushing it, but let's kick it all off from their album, Major
Lodge Victory. This is the gin blossoms, but learn in the hard way. Here on DSC.
It's just no matter what they say. That's how through this desert, travesty, not west.
Stop for the yes and copy. Because we're as blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed.
We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed. We're blessed. We're blessed.
We're blessed.