Dromatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise-cancelling headphones and
work, home or travel, shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones.
Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good.
I'd like to think of a sign to this journey.
I'm just taking this out of the curry.
Yeah, man.
Delta.
Scarrot.
Charlie.
Six, nine, or seven.
You know, Christmas Eve, this is the government.
We roll out American Heartbreak without a doubt.
This has got to be the best Christmas song ever.
Do you remember that in down the Christmas tree?
Don't remember anything for waiting for my phone to ring.
Wake up that I'm freezing.
Drinking doesn't kill my thing.
Children spinning at night window must be Christmas time again.
The stars will melt at you.
No more chance for me.
My wish came never came.
Every is the same.
I'm just like, I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna be like myself with my.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be by myself with my.
Live my life again.
Space another year.
You can't be a fool to battle.
I might be dead by Christmas anyway.
Christmas party.
You look the other way.
I wish I would never have gone.
See another Christmas day.
The stars will melt at you.
No more chance for me.
I wish came never came.
Every is the same.
I'm just like, I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna be by myself with my.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be by myself with my.
Live my life again.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be the world.
No more Christmas day.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be by myself with my.
Live my life again.
I'm gonna be by myself with my.
See another Christmas party.
You look the other way.
I wish I would never have gone.
See another Christmas day.
The stars will melt at you.
No more chance for me.
I wish came never came.
Every is the same.
I'm just like, I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be by myself with my.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be by myself with my.
Christmas again.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be the world.
I'm gonna be the world.
I don't think I'll be alone.
I'll be alone.
I'll be with my girls.
It's not gonna be too busy now.
The Christmas season really kicks off.
Once you've heard American Heartbreak.
Greatest Christmas song of all time on the Charlie.
American Heartbreak of Parts.
Featuring.
I'm not sure it's very own.
Son of Love.
Michael Butler on this.
Everybody how you doing?
Daily source code.
Six, nine, or seven.
Coming to you from the curry condo once again.
In Northern California.
It is Thursday for y'all.
It's Wednesday night for me.
Wow, it's later than I thought.
It's 11, 30.
I'm feeling much better.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All systems are go.
Stuff starting to function is normal again.
And a really good day.
I spent a lot of time looking at V3.
This is the new version of, of Potcha.
I'm not gonna say the new version of the site because it's,
it's a new version of Potcha, really.
Damn, there's some cool stuff.
I'm like, this, I couldn't even start to tell you what it is.
But it's something you'll want to use.
It's not, it's not the site.
Does that make any sense?
Chris McIntyre is gonna do a screencast for the,
I think for the Potcha producers.
So then they can start saying how much they love it,
but they won't be able to explain it either.
Oh boy, I was just thinking actually doing that song.
I was like, wow, you know, it's a real bummer
that neither Patricia or Christina.
I don't think they ever listened to the show.
I know she would like the, the Butler song.
I know she likes American Heartbreak.
I know that, I know she likes Michael.
And Martina.
Do you hear a hum somewhere?
I'm hearing something.
Hold on.
Oh my god, that should be better.
Yeah, much better.
And I'm just thinking about, you know,
I, I tell so much about what's going on and what I'm thinking
on the show.
And I wonder, do I tell them?
Do I forget to tell them stuff that I'm thinking sometimes
because I think I've already told them or told someone.
And I guess I've told you guys.
Anyway, some of the things you gotta think about.
You know, for the past,
I gotta say eight or nine months.
I've been receiving emails about the show called The Plugcast.
And I get asked to do interviews a lot.
I pretty much decline every single one.
And usually mainstream interviews.
I don't even answer anymore.
I'm just not interested.
And mainly I don't do them because I know that my schedule
is going to get messed up.
I'm going to have to postpone to lay.
I hate that.
I really hate it.
So I'd rather just say no, sorry.
I can't because I'm literally just too busy.
I am busy.
Look at it.
It's 11.30 in doing my show.
And it's not like I've been hanging out.
But I, I, when, so I think it's,
I forget the guy's name.
Anyway, the plugcast.
He, he had his idea of,
I don't know if it's the format for the show or whatever.
Whatever the thought behind it was,
you know, it's like why don't I get a whole bunch of people
to ask Adam to come on the show
and have other podcasters ask him.
You know, podcasters who I presume have appeared on the plugcast.
And you know, and the plug, I don't want to plug anything.
First of all, I have nothing to plug.
And I really have nothing to say.
And I really don't have the time.
You know, or I'm sure I'll schedule the time.
And then, you know, oh, sorry.
Different time zone.
Different continent.
Yeah, sorry.
Not going to work out.
It sucks.
I, I hate that out of everything.
That's why I usually say no.
I'm getting pretty close to saying yes to the plugcast.
After Zack sent in his version of an invitation
for me to go on the show.
Yeah, I'm super excited about it.
You know, it's interesting about him.
Nothing.
What?
Well, you tell me he's an asshole for me.
No, from what he needs to.
Like, he gives a shit.
Well, I love a lot of people.
Actually, because that's what my job entails is making sure
people care what he has to say.
I'm interviewing him.
Wait, wait a minute.
Sounds like he's a she who needs to interview me.
Well, if I'd known that.
It's just me.
Maybe I just don't give a shit.
I don't think you're an asshole.
I'm Korean.
I do give a shit.
Show some holiday spirit, Adam.
Through a shameless plugcast interview.
It's a doll that keeps dropping like that.
I probably will have to.
If you want to stay with it and stay your cool guy,
you should go.
You're so right, though.
Yeah, do something with the young guys.
Yeah.
And that will keep you young.
An example of some questions in my experience.
Do your hobbies are drinking, smoking weed,
and all types of ill shit.
I like it very much.
Just kidding, Adam.
I'll be rain for your call.
We still does that.
And now you want to give me the freak out.
Who is the plugcast?
Is it Zach?
Is it who sent this?
Or is it who's the girl?
And who's the guy who wants to tell me I'm an asshole?
I don't know.
I'm confused.
So many mixed singles.
Now I don't know what to do.
Ah, please help me make this terribly tough decision.
Hey, this came in a couple days ago.
It kind of got stuck in a pile of doo-doo in Gmail.
But my sister checks in from from the hills of Florence.
Italy.
And as you know, she's a Nokia fiend like myself.
She, uh, she too has the E61 eye.
And, uh, she really uses this thing.
She uses the VoIP, uh, I think the Gizmo client.
No, wait a minute.
She uses, um, eeeeee.
Why am I forgetting?
Uh, I don't know.
She uses one of those VoIP clients that kind of integrates with the, with the phone book.
And, and when we're on vacation on, uh, uh, fire island.
Is it fire island?
Can you remember?
August.
We were in, uh, an island somewhere in New York.
I think it was fire island.
Um, I saw her use it consistently on the Wi-Fi in the house that we'd rented.
Okay.
So you're going to love this story.
Hi, Adam.
Sister calling in from Florence, Italy.
Um, I just finished listening to your Fuber Friday.
And actually was very, very fortunate that I was able to do so on my E61 eye.
Um, this is all, I mean, theme with, uh, your listener who was asking about the, uh,
what was it the N95 or the iPhone.
And he wanted to have more information.
Well, I've got to tell him and, and, and everybody, you want an okay.
If you're any, if you're anything like me, you want an okay.
And I just had another experience that just confirmed that, um, last night, I was
listening to, uh, your, uh, your, uh, your Wednesday episode.
And, uh, some listener called in and I was just, uh,
I wanted to pump up the volume a bit because I couldn't hear so well.
Uh, because I don't wait the, uh, the headphones.
Well, because, uh, I didn't forgot to mention I was in the tub.
And so you can feel where this is going.
Hold on a second.
I just got a visual.
I really didn't need to have realo.
So I picked up the phone and it slipped and it went to the tub.
And I also found out why the bathtub is worse than the toilet.
Because if you have a bowl bath, like I do, you can't find it better.
Oh, let me tell you.
It wasn't easy for me to find my iPhone when it slipped into the toilet,
pre-flush either.
Okay.
So, you know, and, and, and there was also obstruction going on.
Find the phone.
Anyway, so I lost a few extra precious seconds there with my Nokia in the water.
But, uh, I finally found it.
I did the usual blow drying thing, opened it up.
You know, all that's good stuff that you can't do with an iPhone.
Take the battery out.
I'm the radiator in the morning and I work like a charm.
So I just wanted to share this wonderful experience and, uh, Nokia.
That's it.
Okay.
Have a nice day.
Bye.
I don't know.
Wait, yo.
Yo.
Well, I feel really bad, but I'm, of course, extremely happy that it came back to life.
Uh, your connection didn't sound all about hot though.
Were you called?
Were you actually calling on the E61?
Because it sounded a little bit muddled.
It sounded like there was some bubbles still left in there.
Oh, man, that's such a horrible feeling when that happens.
Oh, that sucks so bad.
But it is true.
You know, you, you open that sucker up.
You rip the battery out.
You start drying it.
It'll just come back to life like magic.
And I really do love it.
They candy man, dude.
You should be hookin' my sister up.
Listen, that commercial.
Well, hey, hey.
By the way, she did not end with the obligatory.
I love you.
Yeah, that's a little bit disappointing.
Hey, Adam.
This is Zach from Vegas and fuck you, Adam Curry.com.
I'm listening to episode 695 right now.
And there's a guy Eric from Portland who sent in a message saying that he was tired of everybody
saying fuck you, Adam Curry at the end of their message.
And that he wants everybody to say, I love you, Adam Curry.
And you agreed?
Well, I got to tell you something.
Yeah.
I agree with him too.
I'm getting tired of saying fuck you, Adam.
I didn't like it to begin with.
It, that maybe that's why I was angry.
Because everybody kept saying fuck you.
And I knew deep down inside that I really did love you, Adam.
You're the first man crushed I've ever had.
I just, I don't know what I would do without you.
Oh, baby.
And all those times that you've been driven out of me that I missed the daily source code.
I'd take it out on everybody else.
Oh, no.
Small animals.
For everyone.
My parents, my girlfriend.
Everybody and anything I could possibly think of.
So Adam, I didn't mean to hurt you.
It's okay, man.
I really do love you, Adam.
I know, I love you.
I really do.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
I'm in my car.
Calm down.
Oh, I'm down.
Okay.
I got to get us together.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I'm getting rid of fuck you, Adam, peri.com.
Oh.
And I'm going to start the, I love you, Adam, peri.
Good.
I really love you, Adam.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, God.
I can't see.
Okay.
All right, Adam.
I love you.
I love you so much.
If you ever get divorced from Patricia, I will,
I will, I'll move to England.
You'll be my best.
I'll marry you.
We'll have lots of gay happiness.
Love you.
Okay.
I love you, Adam.
I love you, too.
Bye.
Hey, very good job.
The Academy Award winner.
No doubt about it.
I gotta tell you.
I feel a lot better now that we've changed it all around.
And you guys seem to be having fun with it.
And it really has changed the comments once again.
You know, I do this just to see the results and, you know,
Vulcan mind trickery.
And it's amazing.
Uh, once I think we've now taken the quality of the comments,
yet up one more level.
You can just hit the, the old Gmail box here.
Let me see it.
We've got, uh,
This was a nice one.
Uh, from Susie Tyler.
Carmen Tyler's mom.
And she has some suggestions on how I can stay in sync with two different
time zones by setting two different clocks.
Yeah, I don't really have a problem with that.
It's other people who have a problem with keeping track of my time zone.
Maybe I should have, uh,
and maybe I should, that should be my status message on my I am, you know,
I am in the San Francisco time zone.
Maybe some of you are,
I've been in the San Francisco time zone.
And, um,
And uh, Susie ends up here.
You don't have to end up having your TV on,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, don't you just love having someone trying to mother you,
is what she says to me.
It could be worse.
I could be mother and lawing you.
Hmm.
I don't think that's worse.
As you know, that would mean I would be tasting the sweet nectar of your
lovely daughter.
Uh, uh, take that visual.
visual. Um, let me see. Man, what did you guys send me? Is anything good? I'm sorry for
I, you know, I do this and then I realize that I'm actually not saying anything. Oh,
here's something about I've been looking for Iranians to get on the show. This is a good one.
Billy Waters. Adam, uh, I know some Iranians who fled Iran and now live in my country.
Iranians are gregarious, jolly, normal, noisy, pushy, nosy, just like everyone else everywhere
in the world. I was knocked flat by their openness and they have, uh, and they have some lunatics,
though, who mix religion with politics running the country. If you want, I can get you the number of
one who I'm sure would be willing to talk to you. I also know a guy who recently cycled the
bike from Ireland to China through Iran and it's only worry was being fed to death. He might be
wanting to talk to. Let me know if you want to hook up. Yeah, um, can you get me a female Iranian,
please? About a 5.10. Yeah, man, absolutely. Uh, I'd love to. That's what I asked for. I'd love
to speak to someone who's from, I'd love to speak to actually someone who's in Iran. They can make
phone calls, can't they? I mean, they've got, they have GSM technology. Can they call, can they call
the United States? Or can they call certainly they can call the United Kingdom? I mean,
I can't imagine that that country is completely isolated. I know they have internet. I know
they have bloggers. I know this. Gosh, so it's this one girl I met in Khan and, and I've forgotten
her name. I can't, um, I gotta find out who she was. She was the personal secretary of some
advertising agency Bigwig and she was from Iran and we were talking for like an hour and, uh,
she was telling me all this stuff about how young people are, you know, how metropolitan it is and
how they, how they, how they're into, I mean, she gave me some, uh, some blogs to, uh, I, I, I have
the piece of paper with a blog to look at or I had it. I don't have it anymore. I don't, I don't
remember her name. Uh, it's driving me crazy, but I know she could make a hook up. Shit, she would have been
great. Let's just try and find that. Hey, this is, uh, you know, going on to the, uh, the
Eisenhower quote that got a lot of response, uh, from the other day about the military industrial
complex, uh, Dave from New York said that you should check this quote out. I looked for an audio
version of it. Couldn't find it. I probably looked about 15, 20 minutes. So, and there was nothing,
uh, no video either, but I'll just read it to you. This is from 1954, uh, President Dwight D. Eisenhower
should any political party attempt to abolish social security, unemployment, uh, unemployment
insurance, shit. Let me start again because I want to sound presidential. Should any political
party attempt to abolish social security, unemployment insurance and eliminate labor laws and farm
programs, you would not hear of that party again in our political history. There is a tiny
splinter group, of course, that believes you can do these things. Among them are a few Texas oil
millionaires and an occasional politician or businessman from other areas. Their number is negligible
and they are stupid. How about their apples? This guy Dwight, you know, there must be a book about
Dwight Eisenhower. I don't think I've ever read a book about him. I know apparently extremely
little about the man, but I'm in very impressed. He's like the Nostradamus of America. And he's
been predicting shit that is coming true in my lifetime. We cannot remain ignorant to this.
We cannot. I asked for a little more in depth explanation of Ron Paul stance on property rights
that has a few people, not quite up in arms, but disappointed or confused. And we've got a response.
Adam, Andy here from Portland, we're going to respond to your question about the proper
rights issue. If you guys are on ball, there's campaign and saying he's a strict whatever
interpretation. Constitution. Constitution of the Constitution. And the problem I have with it is simply
that it's an over-stimplification. If that can be possible. I know that the Constitution is
mainly focused on property rights. Yeah, I think that Dwight Eisenhower also said, keep it simple
stupid. That was him, wasn't it? I know that the Constitution is mainly focused on property rights.
It's a very short document. It's very short. Yes. And I think that easy to remember.
Society, we have going on here. There's a bit more context than that. And I feel like the
government, the federal government and the state government's roles in our lives is to support us
and protect us. Do protect us? To look out for us, to support us is not quite the right
phraseology. And help us out. We pay them. They should do what we want. And anyway,
it's a more complicated issue. I think they're just a strict property rights interpretation to
me have there. And that's about to get. Thanks for including me in your conversation.
I really enjoy your show. So, all right. Okay. So, that actually didn't tell me anything.
I don't understand the issue. I maybe I got the wrong, maybe I got the wrong comment. Am I just an
idiot? Oh, I'm on a second. Well, please don't answer that. Okay.
No, crap. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what's gone wrong. I heard a couple other people
try and call in and explain it. I think it has to do with the government taking your land.
You have to understand at this point in time, you do not own the land that your house stands on.
No where except, hmmm. Was I going to say Texas again? I think it's Texas.
I'll have to go back and look at the constitution lessons that I posted on curie.com. I don't know
a couple months ago. You'll learn all about it there. Your car is not yours. It belongs to the
government. Okay. You do not hold the title to your car. You have a certificate of title.
You do not own the land that your house stands on. The government owns it. That's why they tax
you on it for using it. That in itself is unconstitutional. Anya.
This is a beautiful comment that came in. Hey Adam, touch here. Just got done listening to DSE
six nine six and just a few comments with the pizza hut and Burger King being on the military
Yeah, so this is part of my my thoughts about the military industrial complex and how
our tax dollars for the war against terror are being fed into mainly corporate America.
And that's where all this money is going. It's not just to put our boys and girls into the
sand to throw hot lead back and forth with an unknown enemy. Now it's to pump up revenues of these
companies by giving them business. And so yeah, Burger King Pizza Hut right there in Bosnia and Iraq
feeding our troops. I was in the army for 12 years and okay first of all. Thank you for your service.
And I don't mean that like those bullshit politicians when they say it on sea span. I really
fucking mean it. A lot of the fuel for you know you've been in the field two weeks and Burger King
and Pizza Hut. That's a fucking taste at home. Okay, yeah, you know, but if it was a look, if it was
apple pie, dude, that's shit'll kill you. That's more dangerous than terror itself. So I understand.
I really do understand. But you know, sure, you know, there has to be a limit to this.
Maybe only one or the other. It doesn't have to be both, you know. That's that's my point.
War is ugly. And a war zone is ugly. And it just goes beyond the imagination as to what's
being put into this war. You know, so much money is being spent on so many things.
Ah, it's too late in the week for me to get into this. All right, I'm sorry. Oh, food.
And well, oh, yeah, there's a song I think you should play on the DSC by a band called Valorant,
or Valorant, whichever way you pronounce it. It's spelled V-A-L-E-R-I-A-M and it's children of the
menicide deals with what you're talking about about corporations taking over our world, our mind,
everything. And just a suggestion on the Ron Paul thing. Every site I go to, whether if you see
N-N-N-N-B-C-A-B-C-Fox, Google, Yahoo, I search for Ron Paul. Now, just think if you had all 100,000 people
always searching for that, it would go to the top of the search end, maybe get a little publicity.
Anyway, that's just my two cents. And, uh, oh yeah, fuck, no, of, whatever. Yeah.
All right, man. Thanks for the search engine optimization tip. That helps.
Sounds pretty good. I haven't actually listened to it, but I'll just take your recommendation
because you have done your service, my friend. Valorant, I guess. Children of the men's side.
The fun stuff, generation. We fertilized up the junk food and farming pollution.
The sealer's green, he's as red as a lot. All right, look at the game. Yeah.
The magazine's up all the trees we've never read. We cry in the night of our minds.
We're all the children of our lives. We give all the thrill. We're all the children of the night.
We respect them down on courage, limousines. We can't escape our fate.
We are the children of the men's side.
We're the children of the men's side.
We're the children of the women's side.
Yeah, okay, so let's not say we don't learn anything here on the Chuck.
Menticide, the undermining or destruction of a person's mind or will, especially by systematic
means, such as mental and physical torture, extensive interrogation, suggestion, training
and narcotics or brainwashing.
Menticide.
I like it.
By the way, that sounds like an episode of the Daily Source Code, doesn't it?
Menticide.
Good word.
I'm going to be using that one a lot.
Welcome to the Menticide.
Hmm.
Yeah, sounds good.
Nice.
Let me see another beautiful email.
Peter Grace, Adam, your show's six nine or five was one of the finest shows I've heard
you do.
Man, thank you so much.
I gotta tell you, when someone says that to me, that means a lot.
A comment, though, on boycotting or striking out against the military industrial complex,
probably more accurately called the military industrial financial managed healthcare complex.
Welcome to the Menticide.
Most of us are wage slaves.
I have a family, two mortgages, no hope for my future, but hope for my kids.
I'll encourage my kids to make a difference, but becoming homeless doesn't work towards
that.
I hope to make a difference by investing and voting.
I'm voting Ron Paul and I encourage others to do it, too.
I've put a lawn sign for Ron Paul on my lawn in addition to donating to his campaign.
Be well.
Peter, first of all, thank you again for the kind words.
Second of all, here's my philosophy.
You're never in trouble if you're out of money.
You're only in trouble if you're out of ideas, because this is the country of ideas.
I understand, I understand, you know, your situation is fucked up, food barred for sure.
But I do have some ideas.
In fact, I have a really, really good idea how we can get ourselves, how we can break
free from the Menticide.
Oh God, I love this word.
I'll only play this one other comment, which plays right into this, and then I'll give
you my idea, which came to me late this afternoon at the office, while I was a perusing
a suggestion to look at something on the web.
Listen to this first.
Adam Gary, Chris Keller, I'm a town band of Ania.
I have a little story for you, so it'll metaphor or whatever you want to call it.
There's a bank robbery.
The robber said, all right, everybody put their hands up.
One of the host you said, let's bum muslim, he can't get us all.
You're the one to why no one does anything, or there's a reason no one does anything.
So, right, he can't get you all, he's got limited bullets, he's got limited time,
he's got limited motion.
But he's going to shoot, so he's going to get some of you.
And there's no way to tell who it is, he's going to get, so no one moves, because no one
wants to be one of the ones that get it.
That's why you're a suggestion of striking just can't work.
It's not going to work.
I mean, you're relatively self-sufficient, you've probably gotten up money and savings
to survive, even with a meagre visits to the rest of your life without work.
Most of us don't.
Most of us are a one or two months away from total poverty, from total, you know, bankruptcy
and debt and not being able to pay our bills.
We can't just strike.
That means losing our income, losing our income means losing our lives like that.
So, how do you do it?
Well, the only way to do it, the only way to make it work is if everybody does it simultaneously
all once, all together.
If you need to do that, no matter what everybody, I mean, the whole country, I mean,
another country to demand a decision.
I think even 10% of the United States population will be enough to have dramatic effects
on Washington.
I mean, if 30 million people stood up and said, no, what are they going to do?
Ignore them?
If 30 million people, you don't ignore 30 million people.
But how do you organize?
How do you motivate and how you orchestrate the actions of 30 million people?
That's the problem.
That's where they have us by the balls.
Because the power of dollars, even if it took away all of our freedoms, the power of
dollars, 255 million people versus how many military.
I mean, short of nookiness is nothing they can do to stop us.
But all they have to do is cause us to stop ourselves.
So think about that.
It's not about standing up and saying, no, it's about how to get enough people to stand
up and say, no, simultaneously, in the unison, that's the problem.
How do you organize that many people?
Just don't think about, fuck you, Adam Gary.
OK, I'll let you slide for that one.
OK, so I'm listening to this at the office.
And then the female comes in from a raw, uh,
crotatual thing.
Adam, love the show.
This short video is great.
I think we would end up generates an interest with your listeners, uh,
which he found by a Boeing Boeing, and I will put that link in the show notes.
But you're going to be able to remember this one because it's a website that you can find
at storyofstuff.com.
And it is literally, um, the story of stuff.
Well, I'm like, one of my jacks is host.
Come on, bitch.
OK.
So let me, uh, since, um, since this is audio, I'm going to,
I'm going to play a piece from this for you.
It's kind of, it's like a widescreen kind of format.
There's a woman who, of course, I forgot in her name.
And that actually is quite important.
But she's kind of a superimposed over, uh, one, two, three,
over five, five drawings in the background.
And so it's five chapters of the story of stuff.
And it's, uh, it's not really that short.
It's quite long, actually.
Uh, but the, the five stories, the five chapters are extraction, production,
distribution, consumption, and disposal.
And then, of course, she has an alternative way.
And this is really about how we're raping the earth,
to manufacture, shit, create toxins, the toxins,
go into all the products that we make, um,
the products are designed to, to not last long, or it's a throwaway
products. You know, we have a throwaway culture.
And then, of course, this stuff, uh, only a small percentage,
is actually recycled, you know, all of this, uh, you know,
we're killing the earth. That's what this is.
You want, you understand that when you see it,
you'll say, I understand the story, but you should actually sit through it and watch it,
because, um, it's a good story.
It's good to be reminded and, uh, particularly, um, when she talks about
government and big business.
And the cartoons are kind of funny and very illustrative.
I'm sure my daughter's going to watch.
I hope so. I'll, uh, if I recommend it to her, she'll never watch it.
I'll try and get her one of her friends to recommend it to her, um,
but there's a piece in the middle that, and it just, it like hit me,
like, whoa, I have the solution to how we can actually create a positive,
a positive show of force to demonstrate against the, let's just call the
industrial complex, because it's not just military, big part of it, by the way.
But we can actually, we have, we've had the control that our fingertips for years,
and we haven't even understood that we have the power.
And to enforce this power, actually, enriches our lives,
literally, and riches our lives.
If you take it in one literal sense, there's a couple of them.
So I just want to play this one part called consumption.
And I think you can drop into the middle of the story.
So right now, you see, there's this, uh, we've gone from, uh,
extraction of raw materials from the earth, of course, in their world countries.
Into production, we create toxins, we blow toxins into the air, everyone's toxic, we're all going to die.
Then it goes over to distribution, you know, Walmart, Apple, Microsoft, uh, yeah,
hardware, um,
came out, no, Walmart, um, you know, the Sears, uh, radio shack, whatever, big distribution, consumer goods.
Thank you.
Then it goes into trash, I take, you know, trash out, and then how we get rid of trash, and
and how basically, you know, we're sucking the earth dry, okay.
But then there's this one little golden arrow, which is the consumption part.
Please pay attention to this. Just listen, sit back.
You'll, you'll hit the part that I really, I can't fast forward. This thing otherwise, it probably would have
cuted up. I know I'm getting to it. I know I would have cuted up a different
different spot, but it'll be worth a couple of minutes to listen to this chapter from storyofstuff.com.
That brings us to the golden arrow of consumption.
This is the heart of the system, the engine that drives it.
It is so important that protecting this arrow has become the top priority for both of these
guys. That's why after 9-11, when our country was in shock and President Bush could have suggested
any number of appropriate things to grieve, to pray, to hope. No, he said to shop, to shop.
We have become a nation of consumers. Our primary identity has become that of being consumers,
not mothers, teachers, farmers, but consumers. The primary way that our value is measured
and demonstrated is by how much we contribute to this arrow, how much we consume, and do we,
we shop, and shop, and shop, keep the materials flowing, and flow they do. Guess what percentage
of total materials flow through this system is still in product or use six months after
their date of sale in North America. 50 percent? 20? No. 1 percent. 1. In other words, 99 percent
of the stuff we harvest mine, processed transport, 99 percent of the stuff we run through this
system is trashed within six months. Now, how can we run a planet with that level of materials
throughput? It wasn't always like this. The average US person now consumes twice as much as they
did 50 years ago. Ask your grandma. In her day stewardship and resourcefulness and thrift were
valued. So how did this happen? Well, it didn't just happen. It was designed. Shortly after World
War II, these guys were figuring out how to ramp up the economy, retailing analyst Victor Lebow
articulated the solution that's become the norm for the whole system. He said, are enormously
productive economy demands that we make consumption our way of life, that we convert the buying
and use of goods into rituals, that we seek our spiritual satisfaction, our ego satisfaction in
consumption, many of things consumed, burned up, replaced and discarded at an ever accelerating rate.
President Eisenhower's Council of Economic Advisors Chairman said that the American economy's
ultimate purpose is to produce more consumer goods. More consumer goods are ultimate purpose,
not provide health care, education, or safe transportation, or sustainability, or justice,
consumer goods. How did they get us to jump on board this program so enthusiastically? Well,
two of their most effective strategies are planned obsolescence and perceived obsolescence.
Planed obsolescence is another word for designed for the dumb. It means they actually make
stuff to be useless as quickly as possible, so we'll chuck it and buy a new one. It's obvious
with things like plastic bags and coffee cups, but now it's even big stuff. Mob, DVDs, cameras,
barbecues, even everything, even computers. Have you noticed that when you buy a computer now,
the technology is changing so fast that in just a couple of years, it's actually an impediment
to communication? I was curious about this, so I opened up a big desktop computer to see what was
inside. And I found out that the piece that changes each year is just a tiny little piece in the
corner, but you can't just change it at one piece because each new version is a different shape,
so you've got to chuck the whole thing and buy a new one. So I was reading industrial design
journals from the 1950s when planned obsolescence was really catching on. These designers are so open
about it. They actually discuss how fast can they make stuff break that still leaves the consumer
having enough faith in the product to go out and buy another one. It was so intentional, but stuff
can not break fast enough to keep this arrow afloat. So there's also perceived obsolescence.
Now perceived obsolescence is to throw away stuff that is still perfectly useful. How do they do
that? Well, they change the way the stuff looks. So if you bought your stuff a couple of years ago,
everyone can tell that you haven't contributed to this arrow recently. And since the way we
demonstrate our value is contributing to this arrow, it can be embarrassing. Like I've had the
same fat white computer monitor on my desk for five years, my coworker just got a new computer.
She has a flat shiny sleek monitor. The matches are computer, matches are phone, even a
pen stand. She looks like she's driving in spaceship central and I kind of like going
about a washing machine on my desk. Fashion is another prime example of this. Have you ever wondered
why women shoot heels go from fat one year to skin is the next to fat to skinny? It's not because
there's some debate about which heel structure is the most healthy for women's feet. It's because
wearing fat heels in a skinny heel year shows everybody that you haven't contributed to that
arrow as recently. So you're not as valuable as that person in skinny heels next to you or more
likely in some ad. It's to keep us buying new shoes. Advertisements and media in general plays a big
role in this. Each of us in the US is targeted with over 3,000 advertisements a day. We see more
advertisements in one year than people 50 years ago saw in a lifetime. And if you think about it,
what's the point of an ad except to make us unhappy with what we have? So 3,000 times today,
we're told our hair is wrong. Our skin is wrong. Our clothes are wrong. Our furniture is
wrong. Our car is wrong. We are wrong, but it can all be made right if we just go shopping. Media also
helps by hiding all of this and all of this. So the only part of the material's economy we see
is the shopping. The extraction, production and disposal all happens outside of our field of vision.
So in the US, we have more stuff than ever before, but polisho that our national happiness is
actually declining. Our national happiness peaked in the 1950s. The same time that this consumption
maniac exploded. Interesting coincidence. I think I know why. We have more stuff but we have less
time for the things that really make us happy. Friends, family, leisure time. We're working harder
than ever. Some analysts say we have less leisure time than any time since feudal society.
And do you know what the two main activities are that we do with the scant leisure time we have?
Watch TV and shop. In the US, we spend three to four times as many hours shopping as our
counterparts in Europe do. So we're in this ridiculous situation where we go to work maybe
two jobs even when we come home and we're exhausted. So we plopped in on our new couch and watch TV.
And the commercials tell us you suck. So we got to go to them all the bisoning to feel better.
And then you got to go to work more to pay for the stuff you just bought. You come home and
you're more tired. You sit down and you watch more TV. And it tells you go to them all again.
And we're on this crazy work, watch, spend treadmill. And we could just stop now you see that's the
paint that's the piece. We spent all this stuff. Shut up. Thank you. That's the piece I really
want to get to hear. Wow. What an eye opener perceived obsolescence. That is indeed a fantastic
model. It's never been mine, but it's the business model of fashion. As an example,
it's the business model of cars of consumer goods without a doubt perceived obsolescence. Fantastic.
So the easiest way is to slow down the consumer spending. I don't know. We don't have to stop it.
But the good news is when you slow down consumer spending when you and I start spending less.
We actually have more money. What a concept. What a great protest this could be. Stop the
menicide. Stop shopping. Now obviously double edged sword here because I'm a part of this machine
or we're starting up or we're kind of in the mid cycle of a of a new version of this.
And you know, I'm a commercial MF. I got no problem with making money with advertising.
But perhaps we can look at what we're buying first and foremost. Reusables, green, etc, etc.
But really just slow it down. Particularly this perceived obsolescence. I think that's a big deal.
I really do. I, you know, when when someone is trying to sell you something, maybe this is
the best plan of attack when someone is trying to sell you something because last year's model is
uncool. And that's the product you should not be buying. Then you're buying into the whole
work really hard. Have TV tell you you suck because you don't have the latest and the greatest.
Go shopping, go work harder to go make some money for that is a deadly deadly circle of
cycle that we're in. I can see I can see my own daughter in this cycle easily easily.
And even though she gets minimal input from television because she really doesn't watch that much TV.
Well, I'm sure banner ads and shit, you know, magazine, whatever fashion fashion is doing it.
Maybe we should start a new fashion line. I have the wrong bag. Just put it just a bag, a hand bag that says
wrong bag. You know how women will look at it. She's got the wrong bag.
Can you believe it? She's got the wrong bag. Look at those heels. Wrong heels. Just make it like the red products,
you know? Instead of saying red or instead of saying Gucci, just wrong. That's even better.
That's, uh, I've got a new brand, the wrong brand. I've got the wrong bag. I've got the wrong car.
I've got the wrong shirt. Excellent. Hey, Chris Mac, let's start making those up. Let's
start making up some t-shirts trademark. I'm calling it right now. We're going for the wrong brand.
What a great idea. Stop the menicide by wrong. Stop the menicide. I say bye wrong.
Oh, I should wrap this up.
I'm good. Chris and River Town. I can to call you and leave comments in real time. I'll actually
pause your podcast and call up and leave a comment. What I just heard,
course, that was about 30 seconds before we change from buck you haven't carried. I love you haven't
carried. So I got another one for eight updates. I fucking love you. I'm carry.
That's a great one. All right, uh, one more song, uh, not pod safe, but uh,
very appropriate for the time of year. Happy Hanukkah, everybody.
Good old young Haka, it's time for Hanukkah. So much fun, Haka, to celebrate Hanukkah.
Oh, my God.
Hanukkah is the best of all of us.
Instead of one day have a presence. We get eight.
Where do you feel like the only kid in town without a Christmas tree?
Here's our new list of people who are Jewish.
Swallow slide you and play.
When no narrator drinks to manage heaven's wine.
Then spins the drain home with a raffle and a kelvin climb.
Get your shoes and receives loads of Hanukkah toys.
The girls from Baruchasov and all three Beastie boys.
Letting grab it is have Jewish.
Court in love is have to. Put them together. What a fucking badass show.
We got Harvey Kaitel and flashed answer to the bill.
It has been played from Baywatch's Jewish and yes, her boobs are real.
So let our nanny Haka, a shot of Hanukkah, two time Oscar winner dusting Hanukkah,
shall ever let's run a gun.
Still not a Jew.
The guess who is the guy who does the voice for Scooby-Doo.
Rob Dylan was born a Jew. Then he wasn't but now he's back.
Mary Tyler Moore's husband is Jewish.
Costware pretty good in the sack.
Yes, you got barbets fitted on the PGA tour.
No, I'm not talking about Tiger Woods. I'm talking about Mr. Happy Hillmore.
So many Jews are in the show.
It's not roasting. It isn't Jewish, but my mother thinks he is.
Still there will be a monocone. It's half the sale of freedom Haka.
It's not your house, Jannaka. But she is sighted in Hanukkah.
So reach our home, don't fight Haka. Get drunk and deal with Haka.
That's a new updated version of the Hanukkah song. I don't know how old it is.
I was familiar with the first one. It's like a new list of Jews, fantastic. Happy Hanukkah,
the Hanukkah song. Nice to hear some actual vinyl crackling there.
Haven't heard that in a long time.
Okay, so I think we've got a whole new fashion statement. We've got a whole new A to protest.
We could roll this out globally. Stop the men aside.
By wrong. I just love it. I can see you the wrong brand everywhere.
And good old products made in the USA, by the way. And recyclable reusable products. By wrong.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to do a food bar Friday for you tomorrow because I'm
actually on the plain home. Thank goodness Friday afternoon. We've got early morning Friday
meetings. I won't be back in the condo until late Thursday night when I'd normally do the show.
I got a pack because I got to take my bag with me to the meeting. So I just don't know if I'm
going to have time because you know, a food bar takes a little prep with songs and all that stuff.
So I'll make it up to you if I don't just remember. Man, there's so many things to
remember. You've got to live your life with passion. You've got to enjoy your freedom.
And we've got to stop the men aside. Vote for Ron Paul and shop wrong.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Make a statement with Saudi stereo ear buds.
Sleek metal housings that reduce vibration delivering killer sound from a tiny package.
Buy yours at Sony.com slash headphones. Sony earbuds with style meets sound.