This podcast is brought to you by Paancho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
In a world where women wear comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you get your entertainment.
This is the pod show network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
Got to share Charlie 674.
Not say for $60 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm shining in the street.
I'm trusting you in the street.
And if you watch their plays, good music like Adam and The Doctor.
And yeah, you're super lucky to come in.
And hey, fuck you.
I know you said you feel like it.
I'm trusting you in the street.
I know you feel like it.
I know you feel like.
There you go. What you got to do is a half. I'm waiting for it. Just tell me what's the play.
SuperLoxist Tokyo. Of course on the Pod State Music Network.
I'll link to that in the show notes at DailySourceCode.com.
That's the show you're listening to right now.
Episode 674. Everybody, how you doing?
Boy, I love this new trip we're on about F-Uing me at the end of every single comment.
Everything you send in, you know why? Because it's a social experiment I've been doing.
And it works so well. I've discovered that if you encourage people to give that burst of energy at the end of a comment,
they fuck you, which of course is a perfectly acceptable term, perfectly acceptable language on this show.
And after nine o'clock on the BBC as well. It's perfectly acceptable, but it gives you such a buildup.
You can just, ah, you can feel it in the comments. There's so succinct. It's really working.
And then one day eventually we'll be able to take off the F-U and we'll be great at providing feedback to each other.
After of course, I learned how to do it in German.
Hello, Adam. I just listened to 672 and I want to bring some personal advertisement for you.
Yeah, nice. In Germany, we say, thick day.
I have thick day. That's FOXTRA in the Yachali Kilo.
Okay, thick. Delta in the Yachali Hotel.
Hey, say, yeah, me, thick, thick.
Hey, hey, hey. Everybody now. I hope that helps for you.
And I might come in Andy for your negotiations for the poster.
Oh, yeah, that'll help.
So whatever you're going to do, I want to keep this caution because this building is a strong representation of your emotions.
And should not be used in a humorous way or to fire backwards, definitely.
That's it for today.
And, um, and folder.
And, y'all.
Oh, they're thick meat.
All right.
I can just see me using that over in Germany. That'd be pretty funny.
The noise you hear in the background is the heater.
I've got to cranked up, uh, you know, just to put a little blast of hot air into the attic.
It's even though the sun is shining, it's one of those beautiful autumn days where we've got blue skies again.
Oh, so nice.
Yeah, England gets such a bad rap for its weather, but it really has been just spectacular.
The leaves are turning color and it's a nice, crisp, cool atmosphere outside.
It's a little bit behind today.
I'm going to, uh, into the city.
I'm staying overnight in the city, uh, because I got a couple of early meetings Thursday.
Um, had another meeting at, uh, at Unilever yesterday.
I told you, which I have to say, uh, went very well, man.
If we could, if we could reel these guys in, oh, they could do so much for our network.
And we could do so much for them.
Uh, of course, as Patricia says, you're just staying overnight in London so that you can sleep with your girlfriend.
Adam, it's Mike UC from the UC radio pod show.
Yeah, speaking of girlfriends.
And it was great to meet you out in Ontario, California at the, uh, PB and Jay, whatever the fuck they're calling that thing now.
You got to tell you, you're not as tall as Nemcoff makes you out to me.
But I guess when you're only five foot four, everybody's tall.
So that explains his perspective on things.
The, uh, reason I'm calling is there was a guy named Parkie that called it on show 672.
Uh, he's talking about gun control and all that and you blew it.
But you said that the boom town rats on was about a shooting that took place in the UK.
Uh-huh.
It was actually about a shooting that took place at the Cleveland Elementary School in San Diego in 1979.
When they arrested the chicken, I think her name was Brenda Squires or Spencer or something like that.
They arrested her.
After why she didn't, she said, I don't like Mondays.
And a little fun fact used to live right down the street from that school.
Hey, listen, uh, the one last thing.
There it comes.
Fuck you.
Yes.
No way.
Wait.
Fuck you.
Nice.
Hang on.
You feel so motivated.
That's what I get up for in the morning.
Yeah, I blew it on that one, didn't I?
A couple of people emailed in about that.
That was clearly a mistake.
But I think the point, at least it was a well-made, that no one is immune from death by gun.
Ah, they're flying today.
You know, jealous of you guys.
There's been a couple of comments about the second amendment of the United States Constitution, which, of course,
is kind of this trip I've been on since I found out about presidential Republican candidate,
Dr. Ron Paul.
I don't think I've ever voted Republican that I can recall.
I may have.
I don't know.
I guess I have to think about it.
But it's certainly not the party I turn to.
It's being the party of Bush.
But this guy, who, of course, is being labeled as, uh,
you by the mainstream media as a cook, internet phenomenon, et cetera.
The cook who has been delivering, uh,
children to the world all his life who's, uh,
been in Congress for, uh,
10 terms or something crazy like that.
He is, of course, uh, he's labeled, uh,
in Washington as Dr. No, because he always says no to everything.
Uh, mainly things that he believes are illegal according to the Constitution.
So let's just examine this.
And I don't really want to dwell on it too much.
Although I certainly will be talking to, uh,
to Dr. Ron about it when he calls into the show.
Where's that further on that, by the way?
Just read the email.
Uh, so I got an email back from Don.
Remember, I played his voice mail.
Uh, Adam gave your contact to info to Jesse Benton,
our communications director, Oops, hand off.
We are very interested in Jesse assures me that he will be contacting you tomorrow.
Thanks so much for your support, Don.
Okay. All right.
So still hopeful.
Uh, if that campaign is really together, uh,
then I think they'll get in touch with me.
I've reached out.
I did what I was asked to do.
So, um, here's a, is a pretty decent comment on, uh,
on what the second amendment means.
Uh, and again, this is the rule book that was written for the United States.
Only 220, some years ago to it in 25 years ago.
Um, and it was, you know,
we have founding fathers.
Uh, it's, it's very traceable.
This was the rule book that was written.
Uh, these, uh, you know, the, the Bill of Rights,
the amendments, the kind, the, uh,
uh, the Constitution, uh,
very much set in stone,
but not always, um,
interpreted the way it was intended.
Of course, everything's open for interpretation.
Check this out.
Adam Curry still wants to even San Francisco.
I said a little bit of light on this gun thing.
It's going on.
It's good to talk about, um,
the accounting fathers had a debate.
They were not letters to each other during the time
that they were creating constitution.
And so, and we have those letters.
You can go and actually see what the context was.
Oh, that's nice.
Make sure you send me a link of the letters.
I'd love to read through those.
Yes.
I'm sure we do have the context around this decision.
That's great.
Very great.
For instance, about the, uh, the second amendment.
And what these guys were talking about at the time was
if you're having a debate between the idea of having you standing on me,
like we do today, um, or not.
You know, why would you not have a standing on me?
Do you fear explicitly that in the past standing on me
had been used against the citizenry of the countries
that they were supposed to be protecting?
So the little eerie doesn't it?
Like, you know, we're kind of close to that.
But the guys who, who were against the standing on me,
what?
The compromise was, okay, here's how we're going to have an army
because we don't have to defend.
What are we going to do?
Well, we're going to let everybody have guns.
And if we get invaded, it's kind of awkward to say.
Okay.
Well, there's your army.
It's every able-bodied man with a gun.
Oops.
I had the mic close there for saying, yeah, which I think is,
I agree with that assessment.
And of course, that changed.
And it would be interesting to know how a standing army
was put into place.
And if that, she, I guess if that, the question is,
is that was that constitutional at the time,
fascinating stuff this, fascinating.
I'd love to read those letters.
There's your army.
It's the militia.
That's what they call it.
And that's why it says, in the amendment itself,
that a well-on militia is necessary for the protection of the United States.
Now, I'm not trying to see that's a caveat.
The assessment will longer true.
You don't have the right to be a gun.
Well, actually, I think that it's specifically states for enemies
from outside or within.
And of course, if you have the government controlling the army,
and even worse, if your vice president is certainly very closely linked
to the war machine, that would be the companies that receive the money
to create weaponry.
You know, that's a very, very dangerous conflict of interest situation.
Don't you agree?
And look at the guys who've been called, look at Donald Trump's felt.
You know, look at the guys who've been calling the shots with,
with arm militia.
Or, I guess, would say, with our standing army.
Just might not have been such a great way to go.
Tough, tough stuff this.
Okay, let's go.
But it's important that I think to understand what these guys were thinking.
And it wasn't just, you know, we didn't say anything about going hunting.
I'm sure these guys hunted, and I'm sure they have no problem with anybody else hunting.
That wasn't what they were talking about.
They were talking about, should we or should we not have a standing army?
Context is changed.
It makes the whole issue a lot more complicated.
I don't think they saw this one coming.
But this, I realize this doesn't change anything with that.
It keeps to the base.
But I think it's important to understand the context.
Fuck you.
Fuck you in the hearts you rode in on.
Fuck you, Adam Curry.
No.
Yo.
All right.
Yeah, you know, I think there are, so yeah, thank you very much for the comment.
And I would love to read the context of that and understand how we made the transition from
an armed militia, basically every able, body person having a gun to protect from outside and within,
to a standing army.
I'd love to see where that transition was made purely from historical interest.
I think there is some confusion, though.
And I guess what the best thing for me to do is post a link to the constitution of the United States,
which is really important document.
The documents are always important.
So important, in fact, that both the Netherlands and France voted against the European Union constitution,
because they did not agree with what was in it.
Probably very, very visionary menopped be the right word.
But, you know, I think they were smart.
They read the document.
And by the way, the European constitution for the European Union is quite a document.
It's not quite as simple as the Bill of Rights and the amendments and the U.S. constitution.
It's a real tone you have to get through.
So people take this shit very seriously because it is the foundation of law.
And so when I get this email from Ed, Ed Shubban says,
Adam, I agree that Ron Paul seems like a candidate because he has several popular positions.
I agree with many of those libertarian positions, and they do sound good.
But think about these positions, no department of education, welfare, health care for children.
These are services.
The government can and should deliver.
They improve our country and make it better.
Probably wasn't when the constitution was written.
I remember you describing a while ago how the NHS and Britain provided several benefits
to children such as parade, paid prescriptions.
Right.
So the point that I believe Dr. Ron is making on this is that this should be handled at a state level.
State level, not, and that's really a lot of the message.
But the state governments are extremely important and should be providing for their immediate community.
Makes a lot of sense.
It really does.
But that the federal government should stay out of people's lives.
And that is essentially how the constitution was written.
So there are many, many ways that we can provide health care for those that don't have it.
And still stay within the boundaries of the original rules.
And of course, it's got to be a huge transition period.
And Dr. Ron's point.
I just got a call on Dr. Ron.
I can't call him Dr. Paul.
His point is that if we close all of these foreign bases that we have pulled the troops out of other
countries, we will have hundreds of billions of dollars to do this with to make this transition
possible and really set some goals for us to getting back to the basics of the foundation
of the country.
And the idea that I can choose as to how I want to live my life is good.
No Department of Education.
Again, what is the benefit of the Department of Education?
What are they really doing?
Do you agree with everything?
Do you have kids?
Have you ever had kids in public school in the States?
I have.
I got some to say about that.
I understand he opposes the current military actions, but I think he would also have opposed
US support of World War II.
No, this is what your misunderstanding.
He's not against going to war.
He, quite clearly states, we are illegally at war.
If you want to go to war, you have to declare war.
Congress has the right to declare war.
And then you point out your enemy and you go kick his ass and you come back.
And there's got to be a lot of good reasons in that process.
So this war is on an undefined enemy, namely terror.
Well, that could be just the terror you witnessed on a rollercoaster.
So there's no clearly defined enemy.
Believe me, no one is saying it's the war on radical Islamists.
No, it's the war against terror because that's an undefined enemy.
This can go on forever.
You can be terrorized all the time.
That part is working quite well, actually.
So we have that.
And then the fact that there was no congressional declaration of war.
So the president basically assumed all of these powers.
Patriot act, go and read it.
And he declared war on terror.
And we all followed its illegal and an unconstitutional war.
I believe we actually declared war through government, through Congress, for World War II.
If not, then please correctly.
But I would be quite surprised if it didn't work in the proper manner.
So that's really what it is.
I think it would be important just to read through.
It's a very short document, this constitution.
It really is.
And that's where his stance comes from.
And it's a real American thing.
And I've just gone back and re-read it a couple times over the past week or so.
And like, yeah, yeah, you know, if the country were actually run like this,
it would be really freaking awesome.
And we do away with a lot of the shit that we're in right now.
All right, back to some bubblegum for your brain.
Hi guys, it's Matt from Game's Weasel here on this week's show.
We're reviewing Ratatouille on the week.
Also the legend of Zelda, Phantom Outglass for the DS.
We've got a development diary of Assassin's Creed.
And you can win over £100 of goodies, courtesy of me.
All that against Weasel.beteepotshow.com.
Show Matt Coddle.
Thank you very much.
Hey, some fantastic news.
I think by the time you hear this show,
it will be official news.
So doing it now, kind of breaking the NDA,
but I think I can live with the danger of it.
Nokia is announcing a brand new internet tablet today.
The N800 and 10.
And so they're doing it at this swanky party in San Francisco.
So I guess what is it?
9 a.m. San Francisco Time is the one.
So if you hear this show before 9 a.m. San Francisco Time,
you didn't hear it, okay?
Obviously, it's the next generation of internet tablet
beyond the N800.
I think it'll be available sometime in November.
This thing looks awesome.
The main change is that now has a slide out keyboard.
This was actually rumored.
I think I saw a picture on and gadget or one of those geeky blogs.
And I think it actually was the correct image of the new device.
The Nokia is doing some other interesting things.
Another story.
They may even be announcing that today that they're coming out
with a tactile touch screen for a new device.
So when you touch the screen,
it actually gives you some form of tactile i.e. feedback.
You can feel on your finger.
So you know that you're hitting the keys properly.
I personally really like a physical keyboard myself.
But I'm pretty excited about that.
And of course, I'm already begging the candy man to hook me up.
I'll happily buy it.
But if I can get it through him faster, that's all the better.
Adam, any moose and orange bell telephone.
I want to say thank you for everything you've done so far.
We're talking about Ron Paul and the other Republican candidates.
I'm actually registered as a libertarian.
So I can't vote in this primary.
But right now, I'm looking at the Charlie 672.
And I'm just leaning from year to year.
Just listening to you talk about Ron Paul and how you believe in him.
And you know what?
It's firmly to just research.
It sounds from what I've heard on your show that I'm actually one of those forms.
So you're already changing minds and sparring interest.
Wait for him?
Yeah.
I'll talk to you.
You're fucking big character.
Adam Curry.
Love you.
I mean it.
Ah yes.
Yeah.
And look, this isn't a awakening for me.
People who are writing in sending emails, sending voice mail saying,
you've changed.
What's going on?
I feel pretty alive actually.
I feel pretty vibrant.
Finally, there's someone I can stand behind and say, you know,
it's not about these individual issues.
It's going back.
The guy stands for something.
Let freedom ring.
He stands for the Constitution of the United States.
And look at all of the debates.
Not a single candidate can re-but this guy's argument.
You know, he just takes over the stage.
It's a 70 to 72 year old guy.
You know, that's if there's anything wrong with Ron Paul is like,
you know, another old guy in the White House.
You know,
although I know, you know,
Bill Shattner's also 71 or 72.
So you know, you can be pretty vibrant 70 year old.
But it's, you know, he's not out there running on,
on little issues or big issues on issues individually.
He's out there on a platform.
And the platform is one of the most powerful ones ever written.
The United States was built upon this platform.
And all he's saying is, let's return to the basic routes here.
Because we got a little bit out of control.
She'd like this happens all the time that happens in all kinds of
organizations and companies.
And, you know, of course, countries.
And I think it's time for a reboot.
And I think that's the message that is coming through.
And it's coming through to young people.
Young people online.
You can vote when you're 18.
My daughter is in, you know, in shit.
My daughter will be able to vote in the upcoming elections.
Can you believe that?
She does no shit about anything.
Yes, she's in her teenage moronic stage.
But now, you know, so I think what's happening is her peers are catching on.
They're reading about this thing called the constitution.
You know, they're reading about, you know,
they're just reading some different messages.
It's catching on, you know.
So we could be very surprised by what happens if we get young people out there
and voting.
They certainly seem very motivated online.
Of course, it's a big step from behind that your Facebook account to the,
to the polling booth.
I have it not everybody thinks he's going to make it.
Hey, I'm curious.
Nick Jackson from the Bay Area.
I just wanted to call in with a little bit of stuff about the
Ron Paul.
I got to talk about.
I think there are a couple of issues with Ron Paul becoming president,
not the guy himself, but him ever becoming president.
I just, it sucks.
But I honestly, I know I'm some skeptical man,
but I don't think it can happen.
And there's a few reasons why.
Because when you look on the internet, he's actually,
I've heard from a few sources that he,
that he is one of the most talked about and read about,
discuss subject in the blogosphere this whole year,
which is pretty amazing.
So I mean, it shows the popularity of the sky.
But then when you look at polls and stuff,
the guy and he's tramming behind, he's often all the way
in last place amongst the Republican.
And let me just say something about polls.
Who cares?
Polls are samples taken by commercial companies.
The outcomes are always manipulated.
In some polls, he's actually done quite well
and the polls have been hidden.
The polls are just as accurate as,
I don't know, as television ratings, I guess.
And by the way, how accurate is our voting system?
Now, I think it's more about the ideas.
If we can all start thinking more like this,
you know, Ron Paul doesn't have to become president,
but just thinking about the constitution
and calling our Congress on these issues,
time and time and time again,
which of course is the real way to change anything.
You know, it is a democratic republic.
The whole point is, I use your congressmen
or congresswoman to make change.
I think we're perfectly capable of that.
We're just starting to flex these muscles online.
And people are just starting to wake up
to this very clear message,
which is, I think, just a great platform.
Let me see.
Add one more about another website you want to check out.
This is more about the financial side of the story
about the federal reserve and IRS and income taxes,
which is all interesting by itself.
But to me, more important is war and killing people
and stopping that insanity.
Hey, Adam, this is Tracy and San Diego.
I'm a new caller following the Ron Paul news,
like a shark after blood.
Anyways, I listened to a couple of your podcasts
and they're great.
I hope you're able to handle the massive traffic
for Ron Paul, who are getting into power.
Anyways, since you and your dudes are pretty savvy
and after the US constitution,
I'd like to recommend you look into goldmoney.com.
It's a perfect bridge between our fiat monetary system
and a gold-based monetary system,
and actually hold a lot of gold right there in London.
Anyway, I don't curse, so go curate yourself.
Go ahead, laugh at that.
Alright, let's backslash on all this stuff right now.
Let's get back to, let me think.
What can we talk about?
Oh, of course I know.
If you have nothing left to talk about,
there's always pussy.
Cats, a chorus line, laymates,
and now a new light shines on Broadway.
Look at me.
Think of me naked.
The Seattle Gazette Review calls it the feels warm
and also good musical of the year.
The body may be failing.
But pussy's still on my mind.
You can feel the heat before the curtain's part,
says the Okanogan Free Quest.
Oh, I love you don't it truth.
If you're a douche, this shows for you,
Barney Finkel, the Evanston Day.
I miss your pussy.
It's sad for truth.
I miss your pussy,
but I can't say I miss you.
Nominated for a Tony Award in the category of loose game musical.
I pussy, oh yeah.
White pussy black pussy red pussy yellow pussy
Maybe there's even some kind of green pussy.
Cosific coast hell way presents.
Pussy the musical and audio book.
Only a pussy the musical.potcho.com.
Everybody comes from there.
Yeah, well there you go.
It is, I guess pod shows answer to high school musical too.
I'm so proud of the work we do.
That's right, saving the world.
One crack at a time.
Nothing like a little bit of monk to wake you up
with it makes the world go round.
There's something great about this old world.
Oh yeah.
The whole earth is full of every type of girl.
Short and tall, large and small.
Quiet and loud, nervous and proud.
Everywhere he goes, made it here.
One thing is awfully clear.
Big pussy little pussy hair,
pussy sweaty pussy loose pussy tight pussy oh yeah.
White pussy black pussy red pussy yellow pussy
Maybe there's even some kind of green pussy.
I could go on the days about that little pubic mound.
Cos the world's made up of all kinds of pussy.
Cos he sure makes the world go round.
Yeah.
In every city and every town.
Oh yeah.
There's something I want to show you.
When you are around.
You don't know if you're in slow and just stop instead.
All the way in.
From now you down here.
I got an interior.
It's all more than clear.
Big pussy little pussy hair,
pussy sweaty pussy loose pussy tight pussy oh yeah.
White pussy black pussy red pussy yellow pussy
Maybe there's even some kind of green pussy.
I could go on the days about that little pubic mound.
Cos the world's made up of all kinds of pussy.
Same pussy.
Show makes the world go round.
Yeah.
There is France, Bangladesh, India.
New York, Lisbon and Berlin.
London, Melbourne, Mexico City.
Yeah.
Let's go to Tokyo and try to get out of here.
My heart is overwhelmed with the joy that I have found.
Cos the world's made up of all kinds of pussy.
I say make the world go round.
From pussy the musical.
You can find it at pussythemusical.potcho.com.
Big pussy little pussy hair,
pussy sweaty pussy loose pussy tight pussy oh yeah.
I got to tell you.
I find it highly appropriate.
This topic because it feels to me a bit like we've all become big pussy's.
We sit around on the internet and we bitch and we mone and we complain and we get into groups and we bitch and we mone and complain some more.
And it's time to do something.
Let's get to work.
Let's stick our hands out.
Let's do something.
I'm going to do it.
I'm off the London.
Do something.
I think.
Suzanne Vega is definitely doing it.
She's caught onto the podcast music vibe.
She is just released a track on the podcast music network.
A link of course in the show.
It's a daily source code.com.
If it's right in with a theme today.
It is the pornography's dream.
The lovely Suzanne Vega.
She's a pornographer's dream.
He said, I knew what he meant.
But it made me imagine what kind of a dream he would have.
That hadn't been spent.
What he still dream of a fire.
The flash up on high what he saw.
So much of.
Wouldn't he dream of the thing that he never could quite.
Get the touch of that of his hands over his head.
Out of his reach.
Under his real life.
He didn't know me.
Covered and sick.
Dreaming of what he might be.
He made his hands over his head.
Out of his reach.
Under his real life.
He made his hands over his head.
Dreaming of what he saw.
Pretty page, he's still the rage with her voice.
And lover.
She turns to tease the camera and pleas-o-scat.
We let her lose to love
Watch your shoulder for soul
We let pleasure
If what she reveals and what she can see as is the key
To our pleasure and our lives
We're our help
Out of our reach
Under Chris real life
Dreaming about what we need
Out of our reach
Over our hands
Under Chris real life
Dreaming about what we need
Suzanne Vega
Poor Niagara First Dream
Munching on a bit of bacon here
I lovely wife just came upstairs
Had bacon and eggs for me on perfectly toasted English muffins
A little to realize that I just ate a huge breakfast before doing the show
Ah, that's so horrible
I'm munching on a piece of bacon
Gah pork needs him
All right
I had this whole train of thought
That is not completely gone
That doesn't matter
Okay, no show tomorrow
Definitely on for football Friday
Can't wait to talk to you guys
Maybe we'll have Ron Paul on
We'll see what happens
Hey, enjoy your freedom, William
Another poncho podcast
Stick it in your ear