Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Adam coming to you from still the old curry cottage.
We've got another best of Charlie lined up ready to roll for you.
It is best of Charlie number three, a little house update where you can hear there's
lots of stuff going on, dogs barking in the background, pick up the key to the new place
yesterday.
I immediately lit the fireplace, start and warm everything up, it's all very exciting.
I'm standing amidst lots of boxes here.
As I start to pack up the studio known as the second bedroom, the last thing they're
going to come actually reminds me a bit of a Jackson Brown song to load out.
The last thing they're going to come and get is the podcast console, so I'll be able
to continuously provide updates and bring you the best of Charlie's throughout this
ordeal.
Yeah, remember what's the Jackson Brown lyric, just be sure you got it, I'll get to go before
you come from IPNO.
That's kind of the way I feel.
In between everything, I've also been reading a fantastic book by friend of mine, Rudy
Sarzo.
I was currently in DO, but you may remember him from, well, as days with the white snake
in the late 80s and the early 80s, of course, with Ozzy Osborn, I also played in a quiet
riot.
And it's really, it's filled in a whole bunch of gaps for me about history that I witnessed,
not all of it because Rudy's a little bit older than I am, but I don't know if I'll
be telling you more about the book in the next couple of days or more about the move either
way.
We've got another fantastic best of Charlie sent in by Sunder Huxberg.
Sunder is, I presume he's from the Netherlands, let me just double check.
He's email address.
Yeah, he's, at least he's using a Dutch email address.
It's nice about this, he said, at about a really good time making this, it's a good
start from me in 2007, it's this year.
I'm going to focus with my company on producing podcasts for others.
Thanks for the opportunity.
Now, he, he says his customers well, fantastic.
Here's an example of what Sunder can do in today's best of Charlie's episode three during
the big move of 2007.
Enjoy everyone.
Oh, by the way, today's show brought to you by, I can't get away from it.
Tom, the yard, the brand new movie, which opens up in, was it just eight days from now?
Go to stompthepodcast.com, Tony Costas will tell you all about the movie.
I know you're going to enjoy it.
It's from the same people who had us promote the little man movie, which of course was
a totally senseless movie, but God, did you love it?
Was it the number one movie?
I think we're going to do it again.
Okay, here it is.
The video scene number three for the big move of 2007.
Enjoy everybody.
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
How's tomorrow down there in Australia?
Unless you forget what the daily source code is all about, please feast your ears on
this movie style promo.
You know, world, work corporate monstrosities control the airways.
A new media has a risen one man leads the internet rebellion and that will change the
world forever.
Potual production presents Adam Curry as the pod father in the daily source code.
Gotta go listen to that show.
There's just no two ways about it.
The guy with the heavy voice told me to do it.
I cut the class.
I skip school.
I hold that to sleep out in the parking lot of coke and nuts where they had the tickets on.
Now we're too obstructed.
You are saw the show that changed my life but I get nothing to say.
Yes, I'll take off your ticket.
Miss Montelica.
You are two years off when ride the lightning came out.
You felt no pain with birds and died but you cried when they canceled.
Baby, what this?
You mess around the club.
Let's take off your tickets.
Miss AC DC.
You don't even know how hell's bells from a hate brain.
You got the sugar's urban stuff.
It's so cool.
With loads of bells just like we saw lunch and take off your ticket.
They got your ticket.
Miss Montelica.
Miss Montellica.
I will do this.
Oh, not all women have a G spot.
All women have a G spot.
Not all women have discovered their G spot.
Right.
And they might be on a different, in a different spot.
Yeah.
Just email adamactxo.com or point it out to you.
Be happy to send you graphics and instructional Power Points.
Miss Montelica.
On this something you have to admit.
But you know you like it a bit
Adam's God, a great big house
Adam's God, a pretty life
Adam's God, a daughter who cares
Adam's God, a pretty good life
But you know, that he's kind of a moe
There's something gay about Adam
There's something you have to admit
But you know you like it a bit
Adam used to have really big hair
Adam used to have funny bowloat ties
Adam used to have assholes like the chaps
Adam used to have
Bowdo's a curler in him trying on bikinis
And some of our house in far island
There was just a rumor
But you know
That you like him so
There's something gay about Adam
I think it's it
There's something you have to admit
There's something gay about Adam
But you know you like it a bit
Does he swallow his bit
How?
Something like shit
Yeah
Thank you Mark Yosimoto
Isn't that great that we've built a company where I can actually pay people to do that stuff
I didn't ask for it, you know, people just sit around all day and say what could I do for the boss
You know, let me write a song about being a bit gay
Uh, huh, nice
That awesome
I think it's a hit, it's kind of the mellow yellow
And isn't it true?
What?
Hahaha
Uh I'm just in touch with fighting
I'm just in touch with fighting
Bring your back
And you are ready
Never to want your ways always the best way when you're with the world
I used to come to this place in sensation
Things for me falling from the world
And was I'm in your wish to come and let me
Grab as I want to find me
Find your thought, I'm shining your head
And I can only see you, deep, deep, deep
Lost in the fire of the world
Then you go round your eyes with me all black
Find your thought, I'm shining your head
Come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come
, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come
Bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up
that, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it down, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring the stuff, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, brings it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up
Oh yeah, when Adam gets back to San Francisco, I'm gonna buy some stock and Chris go.
There's big Christmas grin and holiday chuck goes ill tear up your owing with his greased up knuckles from Thanksgiving.
Red to the new year, he's got one hand right up your rear and while you're celebrating holiday masses, he's ramming his fist right in the air asses it's.
Adam Curry's, Mary Mary Fistmus. Oh yeah.
When he gets started, it's hard to make him stop. He'll treat you like Sherry Lewis treated lamb chop because he's bringing joy to all the girls and boys with a rubber ball gag and the bag of sex toys.
On his belt, you'll see some mistletoe and he's got his hand inside your Cheerio and maybe while you let him deck your halls he'll give you a reach around and tickle your balls it's.
Oh yeah. Adam Curry's, Mary Mary Fistmus.
Insert cowbell here, he's making a fist and greasing it twice and when he's all done, you'll probably need ice. He knows if you've been folding, he knows if you might scrunch and if you're really lucky he'll give you a donkey punch.
It's a real sing along. Mary Mary Fistmus. Mary Mary Fistmus.
Happy Fistmus everybody.
Wow. Yeah, I did feel that one. Well, that one in my ass. You could actually do that with two people that exercise just to make it a little bit more challenging.
I've got to go ahead and visualize what I look like doing that and you'll know exactly what I'm talking about.
But the funniest thing was yesterday, your dad had emptied out the entire refrigerator and was resetting the shelves and your mom freaked out.
I mean, I should have, I should have videotaped it. It was so, so fun.
It was absolutely hysterical. Once this starts with each other and one of my mom gets mad.
No, then it's all over. That is quite, you know. I know. I'm not like that.
If I had gone ahead and cleaned out the refrigerator and changed the shelving without your approval, I think.
What do you do? What's you doing? No, you would have said, what the fuck did you just say?
What's the matter, Karen? I have a terrible sore throat. Do you have any throat lozenges?
Well, I have my balls. My balls? What's that?
It's a throat lozen shape like a lollipop. Nothing will sue the ear throat faster than my balls.
Wow. They sound great. Do they last a long time? Absolutely.
In fact, you can leave my balls in your mouth for hours at a time and that smooth, soothing feeling never goes away.
Wow. I can't wait to try them.
Here you go. Now tell me, don't my balls feel great on the back of your throat?
Hmm. My balls throat lozenges. The next time your throat hurts, lick or suck on my balls.
Now a new limited teabag flavor.
I knew that my day was going to be funky yesterday. It started off with a phone call.
So, you know, what's kind of like, I just thought it was a joke. She sent me a picture by the way.
Okay. I don't know who this is but stop fucking calling. Is Alan Moll.
So.
Oh, my, man. I'm getting so much trouble.
And he sounds like 7 feet tall. I'm gonna beat me to the bottom.
I think I'm gonna hang back on the tour now.
Oh, my, man. He's such a cool stuff.
I will give you a bigger advice.
Oh, wow. Thank you.
I mean, I'm not angry.
I'm just done in the world where we're in.
Fuck.
I question everything.
Everything is wrong by definition.
Answer me in repetition.
You don't know anything.
It pauses me in hindsight.
Frammonition.
My style heart is fiction.
I bitter harmony.
I know that it sounds better than before.
I guess I'm just expected more.
The bigger ball we've won.
Now stillness is all it's done.
We're making plans a real time.
But we're on the burning cover.
When I close my eyes.
You always disappear.
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry.
Where's my finish line?
It's never been down here.
And I've been waiting for a blacklist of rain.
But the world will wait for me.
So I thought when I was feeling upset.
But I was so many young and still bad.
There is happening.
Others will be plans.
I know what I was.
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry.
Where's my finish line?
It's never been down here.
And I've been waiting for a blacklist of rain.
When I close my eyes.
You always disappear.
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry.
Where's my finish line?
It's never been down here.
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry.
Where's my finish line?
It's never been down here.
It's not like me to shave and say I'm sorry.
Where's my finish line?
It's never been down here.
The last zero.
We got it out, fucked up.
Beyond All Repair.
I think I'm going to hang back on this one.
Yeah got in yesterday.
After an uneventful flight.
Virgin Vs 19, C12k If you look and blown me up.
That's the one.
Men live live live.
You inquire- Descreation.
But not me.
My desperation's loud.
And so it is, I'm taking your rejection like a man, a man who's freaking out, I admit, I have my flaws,
I get drunken with the bed, but look beyond that, and I'm sure that you would love me.
I'm a gentle man by far, but if you break my heart, I'll shoot your puppy.
My love is real, so is this pistol in my hand, and it's really loaded.
You love your dog, but I wonder, would you love him more than me when his heads exploded?
I am not the violent kind, I will even swat that fly, but all this love stuff really makes my head claw.
I'm a Christian man in power, but if you break my heart, he's a dead dog.
Whoa, funny day, what can I say about the way you make me laugh when you told that dog is sick me.
You clever girl, you call the cops while I was wiping off the drops of blood for where he bit me.
What's it been, three weeks since I've been in, and today they're going to release me.
The doctor said all the voices in my head are in my head, and she that was easy.
And I know now I was wrong, and you won't see me no more, because I'm sedated with an order to restrain me.
Who but if some night by chance, in some cosmic circumstance, we should cross paths while your dog is sniffing round,
finds me hiding behind your couch, minding my own business, and you scream so loud you startle him, and he begins to attack me, so I fire three or four morning shots above his head,
but I hate you instead, no one can blame me.
George Worsbach. Oh man, wouldn't it be cool if in like, you know, I don't know.
Fifty years were all dead, and people still play that song, wouldn't that be fucking cool? They could certainly happen.
Hold on, can't sign off without that.
Tina Mark, everybody.
Get this piece of the show, and more great ones like it, on the BT Pot Show Media Network,
powered by Pot Show and Limelight Network.
Control your part in the show at btpotshow.com.
Thanks for watching.