Are you tired of that yet?
Me too.
This is Matt DiTilo of Matt's Today in History, and on this day in 2007, I helped
pod show suck a little less by putting together a shorter blur of asking you, a podcast
producer and listener, to visit suckless.podshow.com, and sign up to participate in some
pod show surveys that will make a difference.
Once the last time a media company asks for your opinion, never?
Well then, let's make some history together.
Visit suckless.podshow.com, and get involved.
In a world where women wear comfortable shoes, and technology has changed the way you get
your entertainment.
This is the pod show network.
No big media.
No excuses.
No BS.
Y'all to share a Charlie 636.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying.
Make it all the money.
Where does it get?
We'll let the past deal.
All right, put on a show.
I'll see you come in the layover.
Driven down, jump.
Come home in the evening.
Watch your ear on the phone.
Watch your mouth.
We need a good time.
Time is wild.
Come on, jump, jump to the ground.
Give it up.
Take a trip out of the world.
Give it up, give it up as a girl
Let it out, take a trip down the road
Let it out, you better let it stop to me
You can't take it down, you can't take it with you
Let it out, let it out
Let it out, take it, don't touch it
You're trying to escape from it
What you got to do when you need a little time and tell us right now that I'm just up to the rhythm
You got to give it up, give it up as a girl
And yeah, take a trip round through
And yeah, oh man, Hollywood, take care of you being all my life
Can't really hide not on the pots and music networks since April 3rd
She's from Ontario
I love this, I love her
She's awesome
Completely pot safe and ask kicking
Give it up
I'm just read from the bio here
With a voice that is as sultry as it is powerful, Hollywood's captivates with their passion
Softer strong
As a former lead singer of Toronto, Hollywood delivers with an experience that only comes from years of doing it right
Bang on, eh?
Excellent, you can find a link to that at atasourcecode.com
It's right off the pot safe music now
Work everybody, how you doing it is episode number 636 of the daily source code
Ooh, it just went silent
Just as I started
They've been cleaning the carpets today here at the curry manner and swanky serene
West side of G-town
That was been damn noisy
So I waited a little bit and waited an hour and a half like I just got to start
I got to do the show I got so much to do
I'm not feeling too hot
It feels like I have a little bit of maybe a kind of flu
A body type flu, it got some aches and pains going on
Of course, I'm also an old guy
So that could be part of it
And again, I kind of alluded to it on Monday
That it was going to be a really really tough week
Not just this week but next week as well
So you're probably going to get four Charlie's out of means
Instead of the usual five
Or is it really the usual four of these days?
I can't help it
The rest of
Sucking less just gets in the way every single time
It was good though, yesterday
I took the train to the UK crash pad
In swanky shore ditch
Because there was a huge pile up on the M25
And parts of it were closed for hours
So it was actually much faster
Just to get into the city by train
It had tons of meetings
And then we were doing our management off-site
Which means we're physically removing ourselves
At least from the San Francisco office
I was in the London office
And we've got video conferencing
And word doc sharing
And that's good, it really is
And what I should really turn that fan off
It's kind of annoying
Or I should
There you go, I should just leave it on
So you can hear it better
Yeah, we've got all the elements
We've just got to align everything and arrange everything
Today I will be reviewing
I hope I'll be reviewing a cheddar
Before it's released
Now that may happen tonight
It may still take another day
Or maybe two
I don't want to push any of the technology
And there's lots of things to be evaluated
Because it is, of course, something that's going to go live
Even though it's kind of like a little beta test
For us folks to people listening to the Charlie
Essentially to kind of mess around with
And there's no explanation of how it works
It'll just kind of show up
Yeah plenty of explanations on my web
Bloggerdcurry.com
But
So hopefully we'll be able to be using
The new channel editor, codename cheddar
Very, very soon
Let me see
When I got back last night
Which was around
Hold on, let me just turn off this fan for a second
Don't move
Hey, I saw you move
Actually, it wasn't the fan
It is indeed the carpet sucking device
As downstairs
I saw the, I guess it was
The first episode of the Beckhams
Coming to America show
Which is David Beckham in
Posh Spice, Victoria Adams
Dash Beckham
It's their reality show
Now I heard that
I guess they changed something
Somehow they moved upscale with the production
19 entertainment is doing
Those are the same folks who do
Like pop idol and really really good editors
And I recognize some of the names
Because I'm trying to look at that stuff
When the credits flow by
I gotta tell you I like the show a lot
Obviously a lot of what they're doing in the show
Is being done specifically
Well, because it's great for the show
I recognize that
But I like Victoria
I've never met her in person
And from the public persona that
The perception you get
She's stuck up and
Difficult and cranky
But she's funny man
In fact, I have to say she reminds me
Quite a bit of the lady Patricia herself
So that has a lot to do with it
But not bad, not bad at all
I guess that's a weekly show
That's coming back
Something to email that just blew me away
I think
We have an internal project
Which has codename big number
You can only imagine
With all the shows that we're serving up
And all of the different page views
There's lots and lots and lots and lots
Of data being transferred
And so this is a statistic
Since January 2006
I hope I'm getting this right
It appears that we've served over 1 billion megabytes
So
Wait a minute
That's a petabyte I think it is
Or 1,000 terabytes
That's an amazing amount of something
And part of it came from this lovely young lady
Hey Adam, it's Andy
Gosh, I've been so busy the past week
Getting a final mix of the love spirals together
To master our new album this weekend
That I was just now getting caught up with
Daily Source code and saw that you played me last Saturday
I feel so bad I missed it
I just thought I'd mention that that's actually
The D minor remix
He's a local hip-hop artist from Los Angeles
And we met her to show
He said he wanted to do a remix
I really don't know what was it
And thanks so much for playing it
I also was thinking of you last night
Because
I don't want to know
Don't you don't even have to say
Just the fact that you were thinking of me last night
Isn't enough
Let me just
Wallow in the splendor of that for a second
Okay
Let's see what you were thinking
Am I heard that Podshow had signed the Let's get
Notty Podcast
Which is so cool
Um, called into the show a couple times and Eric's been after me to come on as a guest hostess.
So we were actually talking about hooking that up for this week.
So you'll definitely want to stay tuned for that.
Should be fun.
And um, yeah, anyways, it's just great to be in touch with you.
Thanks for the promo love and I'll be talking to you again real soon.
Sanjubi and Anjubi.com.
Yo, yeah, baby.
Okay, Angie.
Uh, promo love for you anytime, my girlfriend.
If you, uh, hopefully, if the upload upload, if the upload went well, uh, you'll see, uh,
well, what do you call these things?
Look at the album art for a second.
Uh, hold on.
Oh, no, of course I lost that email.
I wanted to tell you exactly what it's called and who sent that to me.
Uh, crap, crap, crap.
Ah, can't find it.
Um,
shoot.
Well, look at the album art.
It's, uh, it's not an anagram.
It's a, uh, uh, hold on a second.
I really want to find this for you because it's, it's well worth it.
Don't move.
Yeah, here it is.
Oh, and be gram.
That's what it is.
From Fritz Junker.
Uh, he, it, this is amazing.
These, these, and be grams, they're, they read the same,
writes it up and upside down.
So he sent one with Adam Curry.
That's the one I put in today's feed.
So if, you know, if you turn your iPod upside down,
it's, it still says Adam Curry.
It's really, it's a mind freak is what it is.
He sent another one with D.S.C.
And, uh, and Trinity, I sent one for Trinity.
He said, this is perfect for, you know, just in case Trinity ever should be upside down.
And it ditched for some reason like that.
Fantastic.
Got some stuff to talk about Trinity as well, by the way.
First, uh, uh, email from Chris Lighten.
Adam thought I'd, uh, thought you might like to know after hearing red by Sammy Hagar.
I immediately went to the iTunes store and bought the track.
Not only did I buy the track, but I chose to buy it in the iTunes plus format.
As you know, I'm rather young.
So this music to the soundtrack of your life is completely new music for mine.
Thanks for the music education.
Keep up your fantastic work.
Well, I'd like to take credit for that.
But of course, that is all thanks to the, uh,
organization for the preservation to the soundtrack of our life.
So, uh, use of that in conjunction with the mission from Sammy Hagar in advance,
because he's a friend of the show, uh, you know,
we're, it's a kind of like a fair use thing.
I think.
Did I explain that right?
And of course, we played that red as a part of the red pill blue pill matrix,
unjacking that, uh, I'm thinking about how to work on it, how to, how to,
how to get more people to take the red pill.
This is your last chance.
After this, there's no turning back.
You take the blue pill.
The story ends.
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want.
You take the red pill.
You stay in Wonderland.
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Remember, all I'm offering is the truth.
Nothing.
Hmm.
Yeah, that debate rages on here in the UK.
I'm hearing documentary filmmakers talking about decisions that are,
that are made in the edit rooms.
There is such a brew ha ha ha going on here,
particularly with all these, uh, you know, for pay phone numbers and, uh,
and text message services that are advertised on television.
And everyone is now just jumping out, you know, it's kind of like
it's just amnesty periods.
So everyone can say, oh, you know, well, we messed up too.
And, you know, and I guess we kind of cheated people out of money.
And, uh, yeah, it's just going to have a much deeper impact than anyone realizes.
There is so much money being made, uh, not just by the television producers and the television
broadcasters, but also, uh, by the, uh, the telephony providers, uh, providers of text messaging services.
So I predict you're going to, you're going to hear a lot more about that, uh,
uh, from the financial world as well, because it's really becoming a problem.
These guys have had a free ride for probably five to six years.
And, uh, and now the public is just not going to take it anymore.
Because guess what, they've been lying.
They've been completely bullshitting you on so many different fronts.
But it's nothing new.
I posted it the other day, the XNTV experiment, please take it.
You know, it only take an hour or two out of your day.
Uh, some of the tests you don't even actually have to do.
You know, you can imagine what the results will be.
But doing it will, will blow your socks off.
And considering we, we watch about, you know, 18 hours of television a week.
I, I think you can probably take the time to, to check it out.
So, Mel's very cool, uh, podfinder US being resurrected.
This is the show that we started, uh, when iTunes launched with podcast and capability,
it's, uh, to be found at podfinder.podshow.com.
And, uh, every week, I'll be looking at, uh, different podcasts, pod shows,
independent audio and video radio and television across the globe, uh, for you to enjoy.
Uh, we even have an enhanced version that'll be up as well.
So, uh, you can, uh, click to subscribe in iTunes.
And, uh, and then I'm doing this, of course, uh, with the, uh, with the production guys,
uh, PWB and Brian, and they're having a lot of fun putting it together.
They're themed. So it's, uh, it's, you know, it's like it's like a proper show.
We've actually organized it into something that makes sense.
And, um, well, you know, I, uh, I made an offer to, uh, the fine folks at a year at the
wheel.com, who were planning on driving around the United States, um, four years, starting
in November. And, uh, and we're going to hit, uh, all the big, uh, events and hot spots.
So, like the White House and, uh, and the, uh, Republican convention, I think the Democratic
National Convention as well. And, uh, they're making a statement. Uh, you know, not quite sure
what the statement is, but it doesn't matter because it's all about freedom. It's all about
independence. And I've added to that, can we also put in some independence from big oil
by providing Trinity for this trip around the United States? And I'm very happy to report that
I have received an answer. Hey, Adam, I wanted to thank you from my cold, cold heart.
Uh, I wanted to really thank you for that offer. Uh, I wish you would have, his, his cold heart.
This is a guy modeled after me, uh, done the sooner, but we're trying to hook up a whole new, uh,
Amy. I'm so excited. It's Shane and Amy and we're really excited to do the, uh,
biodiesel road trip. That will be so cool. Yeah, Shane and Amy from a year at the wheel.com.
And I'm so excited, you know, to make someone like me speechless is hard to do. Um, but I really,
uh, as silly as maybe we sound accepting your challenge for the biodiesel scene as the only
pictures I've seen have been broken down on the side of the road. Um, as long as I don't have to
wear clown makeup on with the car, I, you know, I thought you sounded a bit like Keith from Keith
in the girl, but I know you don't have to wear the, uh, the clown makeup down, man. I think so at least,
you know, I, I can't wait to work things out with you, but do you, uh, this is great. That sounds
so cool. We were talking about how we wanted it to be a green trip. So this is really exciting.
Well, let me just say it's not going to be completely green because there's all kinds of
viewpoints about carbon footprint, uh, regardless of what type of, uh, what type of fuel you're
using, but it certainly is a trip about independence. Uh, that I completely give you. People told
us, we'll smell like a chicken nugget. Yeah, but there's nothing wrong with that. Spread your chicken
wings and smell like a nugget. That true. I can't imagine someone with such a great appearance,
like you're savvy, seem like a very, what does that call the, uh, bass suit? No, we'll not
do you're not a student, but what does that Amy, uh, when you keep yourself tidy?
Feet best 10 years. Yeah, you look like a very fast tedious gentleman.
Wait, when it first tedious, let's see, dictionary dot com. How do you spell for
tedious? Let me see. Um, uh, would it be fast, did deas? Let's try this.
Okay. No, it would be FA fast tedious, FA STID IOUS. Let's see if that's correct.
Uh, excessively particular critical demanding hard to please requiring or characterized by
excessive care or delicate, the delicacy pay, okay. You mean like a, uh, a prissy, a prissy boy who
likes shit to be right. Uh-huh. Why can't imagine you go around town smelling like a chicken nugget,
but maybe I'm wrong. I do too. You know, who I don't know. I love it. I think that this is very cool,
though, and you know, I'm going to send you some clips of a radio show we ran last night,
where I talk about possibly getting your face tattooed on my back. If you really make everything happen,
yeah, I, I thought because I have such a hairy back, I could actually do your hair just as
on my back, so I'm like, you're really good. I could, right? Uh, Shane, do no need, man. No need
whatsoever to get into that kind of detail. Okay. So Adam, I mean, I'm really stoked about this.
You're, you're insane. And this is what I like. It's going to be awesome. And you know what,
why pod show.com rule so much is because of that, that pod safe music network. That's where
you show your hearts into the shit. Yeah. It's not just not that you're not a greedy bastard,
you know, for money, but you got it right. I'm totally a greedy bastard. And I don't know if
you're a greedy bastard, but I'm just saying that is really shows your heart is into the shit.
And we promise we'll park the Trinity right in front of the White House and take pictures,
though. Oh, yes. Right. Oh, love one in front of the White House. You wait. That Trinity photos
you're going to be more than broken on photos on podshow.com. Well, we get done with
the Trinity. Trinity at the Grand Canyon. That's right. Yeah. The St. Louis Arts. I love it.
I love it. Trinity at a Metallica concert. Hey, there's, who's the good, no, not me.
Metallica is dead to me. Oh, no. Who's that guy? Roger Waters. We're going to the Roger Roger
Waters. City of Trinity playing a guitar. Can you see it? No, I love it. I love it. All right,
forget the celebrities. Chicken fighting going on in the back of Trinity, you know.
Chicken fighting. Yeah. All right. How about some maybe oil restilling? Yeah. That's my address.
See, this is why this is a good chance. My wife is cool. Oh, she's awesome, dude.
We'll see you soon, Adam. A year at thewheel.com. Shane, Shane, Amy, guys. You guys are fantastic.
That's it. Yeah, that's over. Awesome. So we've got a moody coming in. He's probably
leaving on a flight this morning from San Francisco to come to the UK. He's a big moochachah
ahead of production. So we're going to do a kickoff call this weekend. Now, there's still some
things I want to incorporate. Because obviously, I want the free Trinity group to get into the mix
here. Now, these guys already have a route planned and they sent me a map. It looks awesome. They
literally are driving, you know, a big huge ass circle around the United States. And they were
planning on starting in Chicago. So that I think is going to change. Actually, let me play a little
bit. They had some, there's like some local radio show they called into. It was pretty funny.
I think this is the clip on the show. Shane, both of you, what's going on, brother? Yeah,
you know, Ed just said, we're sort of setting the map out our trip to go across country and stuff.
Yeah. Now, Bob was telling me about this and sent me, uh, and then I got your bolt in from
your Myspace. You're doing something with the Adam Curry there. The guy, he's like the, they call
him the father of podcasting. Godfather. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. That's what they call it.
Yeah, I know him from the old days of what had been his ball. So it's a double. Yeah, but that's
awesome. But but anyone who doesn't know Shane's a, is a good friend of the show. Very good
pal of the show. And uh, I wait a minute. They're using fun to the show as well. And he's doing
he's in the midst of starting something that's pretty fascinating. It's called, uh, not anyway.
Uh, I should probably find if that's a podcast feed, I'll put it into the into the channel.
Also, I want to figure out a way to involve Doug Pilgrim since it really was his idea
to do a cross country trip with his son. And I don't want to, you know, I don't want to harsh him
out of this. So we've got to figure out a way to include Doug and his son. Um, I'm very excited
about this. Very, very excited. Now, uh, so we're going to do this with without sponsors. I am going
to have to do something with the paint job for Trinity. We got to put some, you know, logos and stickers
and some shit and get her ready and ramped up. And we have a little bit of time because they want
to kick it off in November. Uh, so that actually works out very well for me. And, uh, it gives us
a, you know, a definite date to work towards. And we can do a lot of stuff, um, a lot of prep along
the way. So we have some time. So I'm very, very excited. Thank you guys for accepting. Can't wait
to talk to you over the weekend and we'll get everything kicked off. Uh, let me see.
I wanted to do more things before I leave you for today. Oh, Jersey Todd sent me, uh, I got to put
this link in the show notes about, uh, sound exchange and, uh, and the new fees for, uh, for internet
radio for streaming playlists. Very interesting. Um, the, uh, and this is, uh, one of these lawyer, uh,
websites, which of course I really, you know, appreciate the fact that he sent this to me, uh,
where lawyers discuss thing. And I like, I don't know if it's a, it's, it's a new site. Oh,
I probably looks like more like a weblog. Uh, what does it called? The Rit, the Rit.
Fine. Oh, it's a find law. Legal news and commentary. And so their take on all of this is that,
you know, as you probably heard by now, um, sound exchange, who was supposed to collect all these,
you know, millions of dollars starting Monday, uh, has extended like for a six-day period, uh,
the negotiations and conversations with, uh, the webcasters, uh, to try and figure out, you know,
these fees and, uh, and, you know, caps on the fees and essentially what they're going to be paying.
And what they distill it down to is that this is really a bad signal. They're saying that sound
exchange just really has no way to actually enforce this, uh, these fees. You know, they only have,
like, you know, 30 people on staff and they have no way of, of tracking everybody down. So you should
read that. It's, uh, it's pretty interesting. Um, but at the end of the day, they say, look, if even
if sound exchange can't figure this out, somebody will because it's money in the bank,
so all this is probably predicated by the fact that sound exchange just haven't,
doesn't really have the infrastructure, uh, to go and, uh, and collect these fees. So thank you,
Jersey Todd. Of course, we'll be hearing from him on, uh, on Friday as the official musicologist
of the Charlie. Also shout out to the guys over at the one more thing podcast. They, uh,
they asked me, you should go and check it out. It's at MacOSX.nl. They asked me to, uh,
to put together a little, uh, voice over for one of their special shows. I'm not going to,
I'm not going to blow it for you. It's a, it's a video show. So, uh, another thing I could put a link
to in the show. And I was definitely take a look at that. Uh, they're, they're having some fun
over there in, in the Netherlands. And then finally, uh, Martin, uh, thought guy dot com says Adam, uh,
you know, uh, on those European threat levels you talked about Monday. Uh, did you somehow miss these?
Now, remember, this is, uh, the threat levels that other countries have the United States, of course,
is currently, uh, stuck at orange. And they could be elevated to red at any time in Switzerland.
The terrorist threat level is being maintained on, there is no threat as long as the trains run on time.
God. Meanwhile, across the Atlantic, the threat level has also been changed recently.
Having long since passed through the baseline levels of, why does everybody hate us and surround
uh, everyone with everything to charge in shooting wildly at everything, including your own side.
And that was belittedly raised to now we're here. How do we get out?
Uh, this is going to be a bit far, man. This has raised considerable worldwide concern as the only
two higher US threat levels are invades somewhere else. So it looks like we know what we're doing.
And trigger a nuclear holocaust and hope for the best. And the Japanese threat level finally remains
at it would have all been so much better if you'd let us win the war, which is the only level
they apparently have.
Haha, alright. Check this out, it's phased.
Okay, nice and accurate, like a first fire farm, as my words are sharp as steel of the
Dakotana. I never knew a girl called so much plus in drama. This duo taking back her country
like the Dalai Lama. You're not some Maya rival of the king in the air. We'll fit in now
words like a fully loaded barrel. A construct with lyrics like Swatima Parallel,
bringing latest headlines. So call me Will Parallel and then girls do his call.
Jennings or diseases when I grip this mic. My general thesis, spit miracles like the incredible
Jesus women who didn't like the way with regrettable the sweetness. I never said back,
and watched my life more and have six spending money on how to praise gold. I plan my
cards right, always making nice words because women now are gazing, nothing but ice cold.
It's your boy phased next back. Yeah, it again. It's complicated shit. It's gone down
way too quick. When me and you is pretty tight at one point in time, but your girl
Mr. Dub was at some sort of crime. I don't take a person though. You've made the wrong choice.
So he stopped being tight and we stopped being boys. While he leaned me hanging, I thought it
was your boy, boys. You and her were done. Now we're back to be a boy. So he's still kids
though, and I'm always be your boy. So he's just back and forth. No doubt there was
vodka. Said it rums now, all the bullshit's done. Done. Asked how we yard out,
probes is none. No evidence wasn't there. We're real sorry, but we all make mistakes.
Fucking pissed off and was slow. Though I would be honest and tell the fucking truth,
it's a beef and a bad, it wasn't beef. I don't know, man. It's kind of pot safe, I guess.
All the zi's featuring expected space from pot safe music. Now we're rinks in the show notes
of DailySourceCode.com. Very interesting fade out there as well. I look at the calendar. I'll be
good for a show tomorrow and of course the food bar Friday because I've got stuff in the city
but only in the afternoon. So it's going to be able to get through this. And let me make a
prediction right now. I'm really into weather. I'm really, really into it. We've been having
some, you know, this La Nina, La Nina weather has been messing us up and actually Australia has
been having some issues with weather. You know, it was raining and hailing about an hour ago and
now it's a beautiful blue skies. Prediction and please hold me to this next week is going to be
you, T. Full in the United Kingdom. You can bank on it. Adam at podshow.com DailySourceCode.com
talk to you guys tomorrow. Bye. Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery, podshow and
live weight.