With the International Popularity of the Daily Source Code, we would like to welcome all
our English speaking friends to the DSC 602.
And of course to our Roman friends, welcome to the DSC DC I.I.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Now who decides to walk?
Who decides to pace?
And their language less?
How?
Did we ever know?
For all we ever knew?
It's just like with your house.
Before we fall in the oven, we are in the oven.
We're on the endless corner.
On the oven and find you.
Who belongs to me.
Once marked by such a big city.
But now you're fondless.
How did I use to sleep for all I ever saw?
It was just a marvellous.
Before we fall in the oven, we are in the oven.
We're on the endless corner.
On the oven and find you.
Before we fall in the oven, we are in the oven.
On the endless corner.
On the oven and find you.
All I've got is only for me,
I've been calling for the greatest corner of my life
To grow one of the weeks of the past
To let a night in this crime turned over
But I've tied a time to grow one of the weeks of the past
But I don't know if it's time to turn over
The end of the time
They hail from Australia now available on the Podsaf Music Network
But getting a lot of pod play recently
So I thought, what the heck?
Give it a spin!
Plastic, Palace, Alice
Gotta say, one of the better names, Empire Falls
Let's see their bio here on the PMN
Hail from Melbourne, Australia, since 2005, the six-piece
Led by brooding songsmith Rob McDowell has been in
Chanting audiences across the country
And as this year, it's debut LP entitled The Great Depression
What is this noise?
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
Welcome to Daily Source Code episode number 602
Coming to you from Gilford, it is the middle of the week
Got a exciting fun dinner plan for the evening with Super Agent Keith Bishop
Is something still on?
I can hear something
Sounds like a pair of headsets is open somewhere
I'm sorry to bore you with this
I hate it
Okay
The lady is going with me, the lady Patricia
And it's great because Super Agent Keith is going to be working with us
What is going on here today?
Hello, hello
Shit, you know, sometimes as someone comes in the middle of the night
And just does stuff
Twiddles my knobs
Okay, so Super Agent Keith
That's the dinner tonight
And you know, I'm having a great time doing some of the pre-production
This Afghanistan trip
In fact, I'm now at the stage where I'm thinking
You know what?
Maybe I could do a double whammy and ship Trinity
Over to the desert as well
We could have all
Our own transportation
And how obscene is that
Having a
Petroleum
A non-petroleum based automobile
Writing on top of the world's biggest oil fields
Must think about it
So we've got conversations with
Broadcasters for TV special
That's always fun
I still haven't spoken to all the logistics people about
What kind of connectivity they'll have
I mean at that point and this will be
What is it week 39?
Typical military shit week 39
I have to delve into my calendar
Couldn't you just say like September the land of the third week of September
That would be a lot easier
By then I think the plus will be up and running
I know we've talked about that before
If you don't know what that is
Ask some other listener
So we might be able to go live
And I think that will be very exciting
Particularly from the Condahar camp
Which I believe has international presence
So you know working on it
Petrishes is she's off the hook man
She's organizing all I mean what an extra have again
And they're doing some
Big important
Maritime slash military thing
On what is it June
I think it's June six or no
I don't know
I need to I need help here
I don't need an assistant
To now track both of our calendars
Make sure that we're in the same hemispere
Let alone I guess
Well we're both in the same hemispere
But certainly not in the same time zone
Oh my goodness
There's definitely something different here
Well fuck it
Anyway
I witnessed the pod save music network
From the artist angle for the first time
Of course I've only played stuff
When I play something I reported
Patricia is now receiving reports on number of spin
She's getting from the pod save music network
Members who use the network
Of course not all necessarily from pod show
And you know I played like ten different intros and outros for her
And she was you know actually I should play this is this was so funny
Let me just see if I can find it for a second
There was a show and I can't let me see if I have it on my desktop
I can't quite remember
Oh my goodness
Is it intro that I call it that maybe
Shit
All of a sudden it all becomes difficult
Where did I put this thing home on maybe
It's like there's too many places to put stuff that I put it in
In my documents
Oh wait a minute here it is
It'll be no shit
That's not either
Oh man
Well I think I might have to give up
Okay
Anyway there was one guy who played it on his show
And he said that the whole song reminded him of the sound of a p51
So we've mixed in this a p51 flying overhead
And then started this song
But it was it's going to be one of those days isn't it?
Oh fuck that's the that's the producer
Fuck I got to call him back later
Sorry it's our time can't have anyone interrupting
Unless they're an official subante of course
So Patricia is on the pod music countdown top ten
And of course she cut a
You know a cut a promo for the show
And she got something back in the mail
Which I'll play for you now which is just so cool
And just to see the sheer delight
You know she doesn't care about the sales
By the way the song is available on iTunes
Worldwide now
So it doesn't care about selling anything necessarily
Just recognition just people playing the song saying hey I really like the song
Like Chris daily
Hey Adam Chris daily here from the PMC top ten
And I just wanted to say congratulations to the lady Patricia
Her song the 2007 medley remix debuted all the way up at number three
In the pod music countdown this week
Very very impressive
And hey all you podcasters out there if you want to see Patricia do something Adam has never done
And reach number one at the pod music countdown
Get out there spin her song this week
And of course remember go to the pod save music network and report your play
And then go to pod music countdown.com
Make sure that you are subscribed to the show
So that when she does it number one
You'll be first to hear about it
Patricia I know it's been a little while since you've had a number one hit
And hey I think you can do it with this one
And you know what I think this one's going to be more than all the others
Because this is new media
This is the choice of a new generation
Again congratulations on number three and we're looking forward to number one this week
Well obviously she was beening from ear to ear
I found the I found the file
I found Adam Curry
It's like from Finland from Poland
It was of the coolest sounds in the evening
So check it out
Anyway, I'll tell you what got me in the mood to hear the p51
I'm listening to listening to the daily source code without a curry
See the network fucking works
It's like referral based
Patricia pay and the star sisters
And he's got like a radio scanner on in the background
Is geek like me?
Like flyboy geek and
Let me tell you something
I like all kinds of music
And I listen to you got you got to hear the
Everything from blah blah blah blah
I mean I love our us AVs
P51s again before
Yeah
Listen to this
And then the song
And I'll be back in a couple of minutes
Don't go away
I hope you like the show
Yeah play it
Brother?
Yeah a little bit more laid back this week
Play it listen to the show last week
Play it
Relax
This is it
And I'm going to see how I sound at the end of the show
And if I like it
I'm releasing it
This is actually
I wasn't all the way
So
Here we go
Patricia pay and the star sisters
And here comes
Sit back relax
Enjoy the ride
Here comes
Oh
I said
Oh no
Yeah
Oh this fantastic
So
But that was really
Interesting to hear that
But the hear is outro
That's what really put a smile on her face
Patricia pay and the star sisters
Medley remix 2007
Oh my god
I love that song
Here you hear that
When's the last time you heard that on the radio
Oh my god
I love that song
Now you haven't heard that
That's always nice to just kind of be reminded of how cool this is that we're doing
Except for the damped feedback
I'll see
Low on phone calls
Let me remind you guys with some numbers if you're in the UK
We've got a special plus four four number for you
Get a pen and write it
4 4
2 0 7
6 8 1
3 7 5 3
Plus 4 4
2 0 7
6 8 1
3 7 5 3
Oh Adam rich man was go here
Long time listener
Sullivan caller
Just want to leave a couple comments on five
9 6 5 9 8
And congratulations on 600
I know I'm behind a little bit on my listening
5 9 6
And that's all the flight across the channel
If you didn't leave a puddle in your seat then you're lying
Because that's not like one
Collatious solos like coming back across the channel
You described it excellently
I had a similar situation on one of my student
Long solos where I had a fly low below the clouds
I dare say
Stubborning because it's a bad thing
But you know you're flying that low
You have to think about twice the things
Popping up out of the ground and catching your plane
Yeah isn't always nasty that way
When if you go through the clouds and you're flying above the clouds
And then you want to go back down you can't find a hole
In the clouds to dive down through
You know what are you going to do?
You can call for a follow on radar service
In some cases but
Essentially if you're visual flying rules you're going to go through those clouds
And guess what?
Whenever you break through the clouds at the bottom
There's always a polar a mast there
It's like Murphy's law
So that was great stuff
And on five nights
Before you continued
I've been so bummed out
I've been waiting for a good day this week
Today again is not an excellent day for a
Man just it's not a good day
Besides the fact that we have to leave for the city on time
So I'm hoping maybe tomorrow
And I'm going to take you guys along for the rocks
I think they'll be fun
I know the acoustics always work very well
When you hear the inside of the cockpit of the plane
Vibrating through your speakers
And at 99
Work was a 99 terms for boobs
I was on a plane today flying
To New York International Airport
And I'm sitting in my seat just
Confolicing and laughter and just cracking up
And I can't laugh out loud
Because the guy next to me already thinks I'm a spaz
And so here I am just crying
Into the world I've never laughed so much in my life
So great stuff
Congratulations again
Keep up the great work
I'm a folder tailwinds
Take care bye
Oh my friend tailwinds to you
I now I'm beaming from ear to ear
And I think a lot of people had that same experience with the
Now what am I hearing?
Huh?
The gardeners
The 99 words for boobs
That comes from the pod save music network
Actually from an outfit called the Fump
It's Rob Balder
Possible Oscar
Raymond and Scum
The Great Luke's Key
Tom Smith, Sudden Death, Carla Obrick
Warm quartet
And some of the crazy friends
They are the Fump
The funny music project
And they're redefining comedy music twice a week
In fact I did it four times this week
And I've been following these guys and find the stuff they're doing
And I thought that maybe this one would tickle your fancy as well
So if you are particularly if you're a geek
If you're nerd and proud of it
And you're on the bus on the train
Or in public
Don't be prepared
You mind start to giggle
I got a hundred thousand comics
Carefully collected
And all the action figures for them
Carefully selected
The posters and promotions
Holy superhero movie
My ring don't rank third or rent
Ash saying
I got each permutation of the express
My anime collection is the finest in the nation
If you wonder why I worked so hard to get
Geekread well
I can't remember either
I'll let this crap go on dead
In the third
Geekly Shade
Is it kinda cold now
Who's in the streak of a year
Is it a beat in the skin now
So show free full of fear
Or else don't think I'm a tool
In the third Geekly Shade
George Lucas had Darth Vader in his High Fighter
To Stray Plus
Spielberg had indie heat
He draws and richer drapes
Talking sick and finement gates
And wasniac and jobs
The world is robust
Can't you do send on the clinic
Blobs
I act in the skills or talent
And I don't know where to start
A reality it's having
Without the seven part
But I think your that could be successful
Like those other nerds
As long as I've got all the toys
And shout out all the words
In the third
Geekly Shade
I get it when you're DVD
Now I will say
Two rooms in my ear
And was undead of the rest
Baby to me now
Watch my cash if somebody
My credit score is three now
And the third Geekly Shade
I got girls and D&D
Every volume and addition
I got a billion magic cards
I'm still not a magician
Costumes props and makeup
Run every sign by show
Where I'm made
I actually thought
That buying all this stuff
Might get me laid
Oh
I hear a couple of them
And so I walk around the internet
Search of any plunder
And where it's going to lead me
You don't really have to wander
My finances are ruined
So I live on beats and porridge
My house is in enclosure
And my toys are all in storage
The eBay people hate me
And they will not do my bidding
And I won't go and sell the stuff
Come on now
Are you kidding?
But don't misunderstand
I haven't found my inner geek
I can't afford a long-drematin
All my clothes week
And third Geekly Shade
I want to be so cool now
It's not shit it's just weird
I've been outside since you're now
And then I'm techy those I need
Form a sleep and start to throw them out
And serve if you share
I just wanted to say
You're right
The barbedo gets cold
I don't use you
Yes, I appreciate this
Or would you rather I came upstairs
Insert Geekly Shade here
Fund from the Fump
You can find a link to that on the show notes
A daily source code
dot com and of course
Potcha dot com slash music
You can search for it there
And find another cool cool music
You can hear for free
Okay, copyright crap on the on the radar once again
Attorney General Alberto Gonzalez is pressing the US Congress to enact a sweeping intellectual property bill
That would increase criminal penalties for copyright infringement including
Attempt to commit piracy
Oh boy, this is a good one
So if you even attempt to even if you think about it, I guess
Then the under the what is it the inter
Almost second
It's a good article the intellectual property protection act of 2007
Whenever something has protection in it
I always feel pretty pretty frightened
Let's see anyone using counterfeit products who recklessly cause or attempt to cause death can be imprisoned for life
So if you have an application that was running on a hacked copy of windows and someone dies because of it
You could go to jail for life
Computers can be seized more readily
Okay, here's the intended copyright crimes
Certain copyright crimes currently require someone to commit the distribution including the electronic means
During an any 180 day period of at least ten copies valued more than two and a half thousand the IPPA would insert a new prohibition
Actions that were intended of consist of distribution intended to consist of distribution
So I guess if you have it on something on your hard drive and you have that connected to to the net
And I don't think this is good
I have not looked into the whole thing. It's a whole bunch of more legal crap as a brain longest and surgersy taught our savons in the legal profession that already predicted this is you know this is going to be
The future is all it can be all kinds of big big moves and big lawsuits and trying to get jurisprudence and it's still pretty much an open play field playing field
Now it's celebration, of course, of such a such crap
You know that I've been thinking about bringing back mashups
I think we got to celebrate a little harder core, you know, I just don't see how well I'll let our friend young pull that explain it
Hey Adam young pull it here, it's been a while
I missed your last show in DSC 601 you played the boss safe sack
Well, to be honest, that got me thinking the sec part thinking
What if I do a hit test with
Literally less than half a second of sound
Will it fall within the regulations?
I don't know man, we can certainly try it. I mean half a second doesn't seem like much
But you started about everything you talked about the memories the soundtrack of your lives
Yeah, and if I don't play the answers, but you still know the answers
Okay, you could talk about it first
Will you show you what I mean?
I'm not a lawyer. This is number one
Oh, here we go
Okay, y'all
It's amazing how even that short snippet lets me know it's Bruce Springsteen dancing in the dark less than half a second this is number two
Okay, also another easy one
Our fellow countryman here paid burns dead or alive with spitting me around and the final one number three
Oh
You know the echo sounded like a short day track, so I'll just guess they sweetest have it three songs all from the 80s from 84 and 2 from 85
And I do have answers so if you want to get into trouble
Let this play on and if you don't please
Sometimes you just gotta say what the fuck stop it right now and we'll talk again hopefully
But if you don't mind getting into trouble, this is answer number one
Oh, I'm finding the big house
Funding out before Bruce Springsteen, this is dancing in the dark
Not too much
Still not copy this song
I
Downloading protected music is killing big record companies
Answer number one
Oh, Springsteen from 1984
Dancing in the dark and this is number two
Got the 1985
Dead or alive you spin me right
Watch out
Answer number two from 1985 dead or alive
And this is answer number three
The sweetest ever
Another one for the kid as the memory does not fail him despite the split
Three great songs from the 80s this was Sharday in the Swedish taboo three answers
Less than a minute of music each and three intros less than half a second
I am very curious to know what you have played from this hit test in your show
So I hope you liked it and until next time
In full young bullet that come
The art of over production I love it young thank you so much my friend
Yeah, for us first of all of course I played it all because I'm not a pussy however
I figured it out because there is a provision in the fair use articles of copyright
That allow
Very use of material if it's for education
And I think that I've proven that the only reason I want to play old songs
I don't want to play the new Beyonce
Okay, is to educate so you can hear stuff
You know that's as you said on this the soundtrack to our lives
You know you can't just throw this stuff away
And if if we don't propagate it then no one will ever hear it and the music will die
So it's all added bonus
I think someone who hears less than less than a minute of a song
And less than half a second of an intro which is quite challenging my friend
I like that
I think they'll be enticed if they like the song to go learn more
And find out about it that you'll go to iTunes or any other service
So
Ah, young
Yeah, I'm thinking we ought to crank that sucker up again
Hey Adam, it's Sam here from London
I rang in the other day about my friend's spreading Nokia mobile phone
Thanks for passing on the details onto Nokia and everything
I got an email from Mark Squares at Nokia
He's there and he's the guy that monitors the airway
He's there any signs of
Bad Nokia shit going on
Yeah, he got me an email
And I, which I thought it on to my friend
And they, she found it yesterday afternoon
And they had a bit of a chat about what it was
He said exactly the same thing
It's got to be an aftermarket battery
That's caused a problem on the battery's accident
And being pissed and that would be one of the only two things that would happen
You said the acre don't you think of one other incident
Where it actually turned out the guy at the battery and upside down
And then it used a nice to leave it back out and pissed the battery
And then it did, it, it, it, it actually did lead him
And, uh, and caused a fire
Now, yeah, this is, this is some interesting information
First of all, I didn't know that Nokia has a guy
Who monitors the airwaves, that's kind of cool
Sitting around listening to stuff
I wonder if he works for the Bush administration
So that's good, so he's monitoring
And we got a connection, very interesting
That a pierced battery could actually explode
Now, I don't know how much effort it takes to pierce a battery
Although, obviously, Jimmying out a battery
That's been inserted upside down
Or wrong way around, wrong end up or whatever
Yeah, I can see what that might not be good
And I've already heard this comment
So listen very carefully to what he says next
Nothing like this has ever happened with this sign
And I know that because I've had the case apart myself
And borrowed the battery from that sign
My own sign in the past
Ah, hmm
I would not just pass this by lightly
So you actually use the battery
Is it possible that someone swapped it out for an imitation battery
Or mine have pierced it in some horrific manner
That's set it up to explode
I think this is interesting disclosure my friend
So I know that it's a original battery
It definitely is that
Hmm, okay
Original battery
Hmm
Still, it was removed from the case
And it wasn't your hands and in your phone
For an unstated amount of time
Not being pierced and it's never been damaged
Did you examine it upon returning?
It's just a original gear
And he was saying, well, the box choir, the guy from Nokia
He said, oh well, perhaps the phone's been intercepted by somebody
He embolled
He's just kind of covering up
It's slimy
I'm going to say your advice
I'm going to try and send the phone to engage it
Or give me some guys like that
And see how we get on there
So I just thought I'd keep you up to speed
I'll speak to you soon
Cheers
Alright, well obviously I'm just joking around with you
Taking the battery
But I will say I think you've done the right thing here
I disagree
I don't think it's slimy at all
I mean these guys stand by their product
If they truly believe that it could only have happened in under certain conditions
Then I think that they're being truthful about it
And when you do send it to engage it
Please profess that with the story that Nokia is not trying to hide everything
They are doing everything to
I believe they're doing everything within their power
To figure out what happened
And I would be surprised if you were disappointed by that experience
I don't know
But I do think it's a good idea for everyone to know
That there is at least one exploding Nokia phone
That is under investigation
But please be careful
You know it's like
I don't know if you've been following this girl who is abducted
From her parents vacation home in Portugal
Melanie
This shit is on the news for over a week now
Every single morning, noon and night
And while I appreciate how horrible
It's a really horrific it is
You know this stuff always
Sprouts off bad shit
One of them being
The news were saying yesterday
They have a suspect
They can't arrest them yet
Or they can't hold them
Or they all had a different story
And it's the guy next door
Who happens to be a Brit
I don't know anything about the guy
But I do know how stories get out that you're a suspect
Or you're suspected of something
And how the press just fucking runs with it
While another 50 people died in Iraq
Yesterday
You know there's a significant other things to be tuned into
I was watching
This was another amazing thing on television last night
Geez, I didn't even know I didn't even know
I always suspect these things
But Bob Geldoff
Sir Bob Geldoff and Bono
We're in Germany
To basically complain and say hey look
We had this live eight
It was at Glennie Goals
We had the Glennie Goals summit
Took place
And all of these countries
Promise debt reduction
To develop to the developing world
Developing nations
And so far
The UK has lived up to their promise
I'm sorry I forgot one other country
But the big violators or the largest violator
Of all was Germany
And they really just haven't
Done their job they haven't
You know
Installed the debt relief
And what I thought was really really good
On Bono and Geldoff's part
Is they were saying look
There's a huge credibility issue here
We have a credibility issue
If Germany isn't pay up
That's it
We can't go before any other
World stage and try and raise money
For any other cause
And Germany looks like shit
That's all right
Podgeau's moving into Germany soon
So we'll kick that country into shape
Looking forward to it
And Bono said
If there were 10 million children
We're going to die in the UK this year
Then you would not be able to
To burn that off of the front pages
He said but reality is 10 million children
Will die this year
Do two starvation
And he says there should be no difference
Between where child lives a child is a child
Shit man
I just you know
Where little screwed up still with our priorities
And it's only because what's being offered
So let's not forget to use podcast
And to expose other thoughts
Other forms of
All their life forms for that matter
All right
Oh, this is another one had a lot of part of play
That caught my eye the Alice project
I'm having a great day
And you know
I'm in
Sun on my shoulder
And smile on my face
Nothing
Can't bother me
I'm thinking about you
Sweet
Ember
Skipping down the street
Where
Can't kind of bother me
Deep in my head
No one can take it
Feel it over
And I'm feeling okay
And I'm having a great
Having a great
Having a great day
I'm walking on water
And I'm feeling good
And you know
I know how low no weight
Just on it won't happen
Oh great day
So much to share
Feel it so high
About you
I think I have some some to share
Skipping down the street
Where some kind of bother me
Deep in my head
No one can take this
Feel it over
And I'm feeling okay
Because I'm having a great
Having a great
Having a great day
Walking on water
I'm still feeling good
And you know
I know how low no weight
Just on it won't happen
Oh great day
Yeah
Oh
Oh my baby
All right, so Lady Patricia's got a smile in her face.
I've got a smile in my face and this song should have put a smile on your face.
Well, clearly my work is done for today.
DailySourceCode.com for all the show notes, Adam at podshow.com.
I will talk to you tomorrow who knows it might be from over the North Sea.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.