In a world where women wear comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you get
your entertainment.
This is the pod show network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
The share Charlie's six-to-niner was $16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
People is the dormitory, but there's a beautiful crowd.
I don't know where to go, but today, when I pass the audition routine, I want to go to the world.
Life is like this, we know that it's going to arrive when you miss it.
You have to realize it, no?
I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go.
I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go.
I don't know where to go.
I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go.
I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go, but I don't know where to go.
I don't know where to go, but I don't know exactly where to go, but I think so.
Whatever you want
You're so fucking special
I wish I was special
But I'm okay
Nothing like a nice mash up to warm you up on a chilly day in the UK
Of course, and of course you just don't hear this shit and up on the ring
What's the last time you heard a French rap?
Maybe you gave up listening to the radio
He jazzy, brum mashed it up for us
Radiohead's creep
And Oxmo Puccino's rap
Oxmo Puccino
He's a Frenchman
I guess he's a cap's brother
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's a daily source code episode number six hundred and twenty nine coming to you from
Yet again, another overcast thunder clouded, filled, thunder cloud filled
Um
Suburb of Surrey, let's just call it that
Better known as Guilford G-Towner on the west side in the curry manner
Boy oh boy
The week is going by really really quick for a number of reasons one of course
And that may be for most Americans
And we had to forth the July celebration so that does kind of give you a nice little break
I think a lot of companies may actually have today off
They might even have the rest of the week off
I know what Potcho I think today is a holiday though
There's a couple of meetings and people are coming in and stuff is happening in Friday
We always have a food bar
Food bar Friday, which basically means everything's food bar
So let's break out the beer, let's break out the pizza and let's hang out and complain
And bitch and moan and laugh and smile and cry and get hammered
And this is a tradition that Ron and I have carried forth in all of our companies
At think new ideas are previous company we called it think drink
Same thing Friday and it would be actually five o'clock in San Francisco
We do it at four o'clock for some reason what people do start earlier
And it's nice but we're going to have a special one this Friday because
Well, we've been in meetings and in conference and congress I should say
With each other with the company with all disciplines departments
It's a part of us starting to suck less
And so we have we're ready to present to the entire company
So everyone is on the same ticket
And I'm very excited about it
Some of the things that we're thinking of you've already heard me talk about
Or you've probably seen some of the stuff
Yeah, it's I think that the things are going to happen pretty quickly now
Because we've got everything all stuff is in place
Now we are in the process of connecting all the dots
So things actually work in departments communicate for the right reasons
And it's tough man building a company I got to tell you more about that later
By the way, are we talking about another company in the podcasting space?
Of course I'd like to refer to it as independently produced media
Yesterday was the fourth of July show and I knew that the and it was funny because I had a whole bunch of
Collins and stuff scheduled
Stuff I was going to just run almost like a regular show
And then I really got into it and I got into a feeling proud to be an American
And proud to be a world citizen if you will
And I knew that that was bound to set off some people
Interestingly enough, it's set off one of my my good friends, good friend of the show
I should say James
Who calls in regularly, you recall James recently got his computer bag
And his iPod and the cell phone jack and so everything was gone
And he was bummed out so we hadn't heard from him a while
And then he tuned into yesterday's show and
He wasn't too happy about it
Adam, dear Adam, it's James, I'm left in message for a long time
I'll be very busy boy anyway, I felt compelled to renew this morning
Is 6, 20 years
It would make a lot of enemies over this one
Fuck yeah, I wasn't early sick
I'm there again, you be who who
Yeah, I just made me feel completely crazy and horrible
And also, yeah, you're right, you're a mixture of people
So you can even own the country, you don't need it
Okay, so I'm just gonna stop it there
James is obviously, his point is already clear
That he was nauseated by the Americanism, my expelled yesterday on this program
And so here come the arguments and there's a reason for this
And of course, James, you know, I respect you, I love you, your friend of the show
So, you know, don't take it personally, we're having a
We're just having a conversation in my typical format where you can't interrupt me
Because I've got the pause button, I love that system, by the way
Okay, so what do they teach you in school, James, let me ask you that first
These are the types of blanket statements we got to get rid of
Let's stop with the, you jumped the country, you stole the country
First of all, who's you, it was you
It was you guys, it was people from mother England, it was British people
They jumped the country, they jumped and by the way, again, what do you learn in school here?
This has been the modest operandi for the United Kingdom, for Britain, for a long, long time
There's a reason why many countries in this world, including India, including the West Indies
Speak the Queen's English and quite well and actually love your queen
There's a reason because
Because you're columnist, you've gone out and jumped everyone's fucking country, including the United States
But what happened was, you know, something changed
Different views were able to bubble up, but not being suppressed by the
The status quo of how things were running in England
Okay, and so it became a culture, it became an adventurous culture
People who went to America often didn't make it, they died, and they were Brits, Brits, I tell you
You guys, uh, maybe, um, and you know, I, I, I studied this, I'm a student of
Well, I'm a student of
And now we're from our spine here
It's the Yanks, versus the Brits
We'll drive each other crazy, but everybody knows that it's a parent to see
Let's just like you and me, it's the Yanks and the Brits
Yeah, the Yanks versus the Brits
Mind the gap, yes, please do, okay, so
I believe, no, let me, let me step back one, one little step here
There is a tremendous envy in the United Kingdom
In my world, which is the world of media, that's what I pay attention to the most
It does not go for politics, as an example, but for media
To be successful in the United States
Interestingly enough, there is an incredible hunger
In the American media market, to be successful in the United Kingdom
Now it's for two different reasons, and this is just the way I see it, the way I'm going to call it
In the UK, your success is limited
You can probably, you know, if you're Terry Wogan, then you can do 8 million pounds a year
16 million dollars a year in salary
I think he's probably at the top of the game everywhere
That is pale in comparison to what you can do with the successful media
Property, career, company, whatever you want to call it in the United States
Mainly due to size, it's very simple
There's 350 million people living in America, or closer to 300 million
So that's just simple law of big numbers
Conversely, you see all American media people
Really wanting the legitimization, the credibility of making it in the United Kingdom
Where the Queen's English is spoken
That's it, we are two countries, two cultures separated by a common language
Here's an example, look, Americans are natural born
I know you thought killers, but I was going to say marketing people
It's a part of the whole adventure, spirit
Brits went over to the new land, the new country, it's a very big risk, big adventure
Maybe there's some envy of those who did of the ancestors who went over
It wasn't a long ago after all
When you do something like that, what do you do?
You send messages back home saying, dude, we're doing great, it's awesome here
From sea to shining, shining sea, the beautiful plains, Oklahoma
Where the wind goes, rustling through all that stuff
It's marketing, of course, and I'm going to say it sucks
Yeah, we lost the 80% of the people on the trip
So that became the culture of the United States
And the whole idea is, and this is the nucleus
If you want to work hard and you want to bust your ass, you too can be just as successful as
Pick anyone, X, Y or anyone here, and there's lots of them, because there's lots of them
In general
So, marketing is what we're good at
And of course, like all marketing, it comes across
Brash and loud and often in sincere, you know, and we have to get better
We must get better, because look at our top marketing guy, the CEO of our huge organization
Known as the United States, the president, socks, he sucks it, been marketing
He makes everyone feel like shit, like there's no one in control
I like this Gordon Brown guy in the UK, by the way
I've been watching him, I've been watching how he speaks and how he addresses the nation
And what he's done in these first few, in this first week essentially, this guy is a good PR guy
I think he's also a really good politician, which he'll make it extremely interesting
So anyway, an example, and actually I should play the rest of your comment, because I can give a better example
Here we go
Because it isn't meant to be anybody, you know, yeah
I'm rumbling, look right now
No, no, I was a horrible episode, but I think it's a good fight
I feel so bad that you feel that way, look
Of course, team America, the whole movie is irony, but it is the way the Americans are
And we're not ashamed of it, that's the point
That is our version of what you call irony
Okay, we're not idiots
We may be shallow, I'll be the first to admit
Because we've got a layer of marketing around our skin, sure
But of course, we understand that team America and yeah, we invented Taco Bell and Band-Aids
Of course, it's irony dude, but at the same time, we invented fucking Band-Aids
We invented Taco Bell, these are not wonderful things for society
I think it is an envy, it's interesting because you pick Band-Aids
They're not called Band-Aids in the United Kingdom, they're called Plasters
Alright, so for years, you refuse to use the Plasters, you know, you refuse to use Band-Aids for Plasters
And you know, as successful as your plaster companies, I don't know
The Band-Aid Corporation is probably Johnson & Johnson or something like that, they're probably doing okay
The only time you use the word Band-Aid was for the Tribute Band-Aid
And it was a mega smash, there you go
Anyway, it believed me from where I sit and from what I see and from what I've witnessed
We love each other's countries, we really do love each other's company
We're envious of things the other has or can do
It's just a fact, but look, we are from the same family, we are from the same wood
It's just we have some major cultural differences
And that's okay, it's okay
But I must say that I've noticed a lot of US bashing going on
And it's not really bashing, it's more like, you know, it's your laughing at us
Because, you know, they're, they're these shallow yanks
Well, yes, but that's okay
Because, you know, we see you in a different light as well, but to be nauseated by it
Nah, I don't think so, that's not necessary
I'm proud that you guys can be proud that you're British, I have a sense of what that means
I'll never fully understand it, but I do appreciate it
In fact, I'm a little bit envious of it in my own way
And all I ask is that you understand the same for us
And, and know that you're welcome, just as I'm welcome here
Which, of course, thanks, Commissioner Blogger is more due to the European Union I agree, obviously
And you're welcome over in the US, let's have some fun together
He's not the whole point
I think we're going to do exactly that, aren't we?
On this Saturday, the 7th of July, the life, the life, earth concert
Should be interesting, again, we're working together
So, the world, I can't believe I'm getting myself into this
I'm going to paint myself new corner, but
It's all about marketing, it's all about what you see in the media
That's why blogging is interesting, how it's uncovering things in mainstream media
And how it's creating things that aren't true as well
It's just a lot, we have to learn, we've got to reinstate our filters, we've got to work on it
Oh, the humanity
Anyway, so I'm sorry, I gave you a shitty D.S.C.
I'll try better
The yanks versus the bits
Mind the gap
Now here's something that's getting a lot of pod play and the pod safe music network
A lot of pod tasks, a lot of independently produced radio shows play in this one
I can kind of understand why Tom Smith says it all and I don't care
Everyone is lining up to get the latest toy
With every fancy buzzword, the reviewers can deploy
It's a wireless browser, music player and a phone
Well, listen up, you apple junkies, because I've got my own
It's called I Don't Care
Amazing Gadgetree, I Don't Care
The latest in on me, it tells me if what's cool or hot
Actually matters, usually not
I don't care, the new technology I don't care
This modern sophistry, all it does has been done before
But now it's clumsy or an costs more
Every permutation, every variance in you
It's so the cost of the nation
As if it was bold and new
Slim responsive elegance, such 16 is sad grace
It's like a high price to hear
With a logo on her face
I don't care
Because I don't need to own I don't care
Another telephonic between all this noise and height
I'll come it's not as clear as Skype
I don't care
I haven't got the time I don't care
To shift the paradigm, I only want to play a song
Good thing that my thumbs are strong
So many times we've seen this sort of marketing before
You can buy a brand new lifestyle at your favorite store
Give up your apartment, your sedan, and both your jobs
To gently stroke the touch screen
And fiddle with the knobs
It may make stuff more fun to do
But keeping track is hard
Did you just win at Sudoku or max out your credit card
It's guaranteed to change your life
It really is the bomb
Like windows meet the segue
ESP and catch dot com
I don't care
Your life is more compact
With a two-year contract of Steve
I've got a perfect plan
To feed your short attention span
I don't care
And so I'm old who I don't care
Those are the things to do
And if the future is passed me by
I won't complain because I don't know why
They have new crap to buy and I don't care
I am
There you go
That's part of America's culture
We come up with the iPhone and then of course we come up with the I don't care
So yeah
So apparently one is on its way to me
Via FedEx will see if it makes it through customs
That'll be interesting to see
I have been making a bit of a study
Of course I've been thinking about it
In the recent
Twitter episode where they all had their iPhones
And they were talking about cataluess
Was on that one as well
She had some activation problems
I'm evaluating because I'm very happy with my Nokia E61I
Does everything for me
Listening to these reviews
I haven't really seen anyone right about this yet
I had expected
Technically it wouldn't have been such a problem
I would have expected for you to be able to synchronize
Through Wi-Fi
Maybe you can but I don't read that anywhere
It seems pretty much like you got a plug it in
Which of course also charges the device
Or at least it should charge the device
And then everything syncs up with your iTunes
Which means you really have to have the computer
That you sync it up with
Along for the ride if you really want it to be
Most effective
Because I'm not a big music guide
How fucked up does that sound
But I just don't listen to music on my iPod
I can't stand it because I know exactly the order in which it's coming in
And I like serendipity so I want my shows
I want to be able to get my audio and video shows
And of course I can subscribe to those iTunes
However, if I'm on the road
I can't just check and see if so and so put out the latest show
Or if I can't just listen to the New York Times front page
If it has finally been posted to get in later in later these days
I love listening to CNN radio reports
So I won't be able to get that unless I continually synchronize the machine
So I'm sure that they did this because they didn't want
Because I guess you can access the network
The network in two ways one is through your cellular data connection
Your edge connection the other one is of course through Wi-Fi
And then your direct connects with three ways
And I guess I think when you're pretty easy to restrict synchronizing
I think about it your address book your calendar
I can synchronize my calendar on the fly through my edge network
Whenever I want I don't have to necessarily
Physically hook up to a computer
Maybe I'm wrong, maybe I'm just totally missing it here
Maybe it is possible but I haven't read anyone about it
So either it's possible and everyone's just loving it and doing it
And forgot to write about it or no one's thinking about it either way
Please let me know
To rock this mother out
This is Zach from Las Bandakis
And be sure to enter the shameless plug cast on July 9
For my interview with the one
The only searchersy type
I'm like the force and comfort podcasting
I never expected this to get to where it is
There's no reason to ever walk into a sandwich ever again
I go into like a Barnes & Noble when I get depressed
Probably the secret service agent in my door soon
Well there goes my access
They're actually communicating very well together because they're taking shifts
To stay awake
Be sure to check it out at shamelessplotf.com
Have been met
Are you having the plans or endeavors in the near future?
Sleep
Yeah, I've been following the plug cast
Interesting, I like that
And it always sends a couple promos through
And guys got something good going on there, appreciate that
Oh, I discovered something pretty cool, well actually very uncool
I had already kind of suspected that I was having some trouble with the voicemail service
That sends me the files when you leave a voicemail on the numbers
Which are always listed at DailySourceCode.com
And you should have in yourself phone for when you just can't stand what I'm saying
And want to call in and bitch at me
That's why we tell you to enter the plus
Because it really helps you no matter where you are it will work
And yesterday or the day before
The Firf, Chris McIntyre from Pod Show HQ
He said he said I called I phoned in my first report for the developer stuff that we're doing
So be on a lookout for it and I keep waiting and waiting and yesterday I show I
I just didn't get any voicemails and I'm like crap man
I can't believe you sure what number did you call so he told me what number he called
So I go into it's J2.com is what I use
So I go into the J2 control panel and message center and loan behold for some reason
Certain messages it may be related to length
It just doesn't forward to the email
So who knows what freaking gems I may have been missing it really upsets me
And of course it totally makes sense that nylon has been calling things in
He's pretty long-winded
So that stuff probably just wasn't getting through to my mailbox
So I'm really bummed about it
I have a new process now so in the morning I go and I download all the most recent comments
neatly organized. There is a way for me to do that and I can go through them and check them
This really sucks
Anyway, the good news is I found the first little blur
At the office
But I'm bummed just saying hello
But I'm bummed to the game from HQ
But I'm bummed and pod shot
Hey Adam what's up this is the graphic calling and pod show HQ
Now here you're talking about a lot about this developer network working on the pod show
You don't have to spend the time in a little bit and you need to know our first update
First off, one of the APIs we have in place already that people may or may not know about is our author and the API
This allows people to upload shows along with all the related information that Kyle biscuits and keywords
To the pod show website, well that actually being on the pod show website
We have four or five applications that are using it already including
Not only cast blaster but good blaster, FDL and Ubercaster as well
So just letting people out there know that this author and API is available
Make sure to check it out on developer.pot show.com
Secondly, we are working on the channel's API
See some screenshots in your feed
On Terry.com, talking about some stuff
So I just want to touch on a little bit
A lot of exciting stuff there
Considering that channel and collecting is one of the most powerful features on the pod show website
It might make sense to be about this feature next to allow people
You know, it's a create and share playlist
In samples of information
And different audio files that are collected on pod show and from around the web
Finally, I don't want to go too deep into this one
And I'll just mention if I had an Uber nerds
But there is a spiked up there called Twitter, Twitter.com
And we may be working on something to release some cool features for that
So if you're not going to get to deep into it
People who want to stay up to date with what's going on with the development
We're going to always visit developer.pot show.com
Subscribe to the blog and keep up to date
As always, people get email as well
And info.com with questions or if they need help
Check it and I'll talk to you later
All right, the first blur of everybody
Thank you very much Chris McIntyre, excellent dude
Yeah, that's all part of what we're going to be talking about company wide tomorrow
You know what?
I'm not going to tell you about it today
Because I want to make sure that everyone in the company
Here's it from the walls of the company first
But I am very excited, it makes total sense
We can execute well, we can execute quickly
We fix so many fucking problems
Particularly with our website
Remember, remember remember the fifth of November
Gunpowder trees and a plot
I remember that we built this thing upside down
Not purposely, but that's what we've basically figured out
We've built the fucker upside down
Court City PD, the number one online police drama series
Is now available, subscribe now and get the entire first season on your iPod
And get ready for an action pack season 2
Coming July 2007
Court City dot podshow dot com
This summer when you buy coke
You get music
You can win an iPod or freak songs on iTunes
So maybe you guys have been sending in the tombs that you've been getting
Look, here's how it works
I need to, in order for these campaigns to work
And for us to show the power of independent media
I need to show some real
Where they call it, customer engagement
So you would help me out personally
And you would help many other
And this is only for UK audience, everyone outside of the UK
Just plug yours
You would help me tremendously
If you have actually been motivated
To look under the cap of your bottle of coke
And get the number and redeem it
And you actually bought a track off of iTunes with it
If you could call me and let me know that would be very helpful
Because that would actually tell the advertisers that the shit is working
Otherwise, I have to tell them shit ain't working
It's that simple
And of course, the first thing we can send them is this that I just recorded right now
Yes, just going back briefly to the Fourth of July show
There was one other call that came in that I feel I do have to play
Hi Adam, this is Dave and Philadelphia
The cradle of liberty on independent stay
I'm calling because you made a comment about
How the brits are kind of steering around Asians
I don't know whether we're doing that in the US but I'll tell you after September 11
There were plenty of circumstances
Plenty of incidents where people were getting beat up
Because of the color of their skin
People who were wearing turps
Particularly were getting called terrorists
Drivers particularly had a really tough time of it
And we've got to look at ourselves
To really try hard to get people as people
Maybe I found idealistic but I sure hope that if we all just took this back
And really thought about each other sort of as individual
We would do a whole lot better as a country as a society as a world
Too much to ask probably but there's my thought for independence there
Right on man, absolutely so first of all of course I stand corrected
I was not in the United States after 9-11
And I'm sure that there was some of that going on
As I think I said yesterday I have personally not witnessed it
So I think it's excited pretty quickly
And maybe that same thing will happen in the UK
Although it's only been one year since the 7th of July 7th 7
When over 50 people lost their lives in London
Interesting by the way how the live earth concert is being held on 7th 7th
That's kind of funky
But again I think typically British you know we're just going to keep
Play on ahead we'll do something new something fresh
So I agree with what you're saying
And I think that what we're doing here in these independent productions
At least I feel like it's happening in the dialogue
We're having is we got to focus on two things
Keep talking start doing
You know I'm a big fan of just doing stuff
Yes sometimes I do stuff and this of course is part of the risk
You know you you step on someone's toes or go over the boundary
And I'm always quick to apologize and retract if I've done something incorrect
But we have to start doing things
And I believe the best way to do it is to engage other people in the same concept
Keep talking and start doing
So when I hear people speak like this
I my immediate version of start doing something is to engage them in talking about excuse me
I really have to disagree
I'm not just going to follow along and say oh yes or be quiet and not say anything
It doesn't have to be a huge argument
But you know there are things you know you can start up a conversation
And maybe even if you feel that way even if you do want to agree
Still talk about it you may come up with something interesting
All I know is I'm a traveled man
I've been around the world I've been to many many places
I've met many many many people including Iraq
I've I've been there at the height of the war
And it's just fucking people they got iPods and cell phones
Okay, most of the world has that what you see on television
It's not representative of the way it is
Okay, so if you do anything this year get a ticket and go to as close as you can get to Iraq
Just go look at the country surrounding it. I'm telling you it is not the way it's portrayed on television and the newspapers
And we have this you know this is a this is the downside of our great marketing prowess
You know it can be used for evil
That's what's happening and it's not even on purpose
Most of the people reading the news reading the news off of the teleprompter have never been to these countries either
They can probably just point to it on a map
So Americans we certainly have work to do everybody has work to do gosh damn I'm on the soap box today
I don't know if that's a good thing
All right, so I found some other interesting stuff in the voice mail box
Hey, yeah, my name is Davis
And I listen to the DSC
But since the reason why I'm calling is and I am at the cushion the cushion of run this malls and we never hear run this malls on your podcast
Then you mall so I thought I would say cover from run just malls
My name is David's malls David's malls
Yes, thank you my okay
Well, I do miss Roger Smalls. That's for sure and David if you truly are as cousin of course
Me familiar to familiar Mikasa to Kasa, you know, you're you're part of a one of the biggest friends of the show
Who indeed I had been a bit preoccupied and and only now stopping to think
Where is our friend Roger
Yeah, wouldn't it be great if all of a sudden you heard hello at them
Yeah, you don't know what you got till it's gone ain't that a bitch
Oh, I don't it's will for my six just for the side but not on it's indeed a dick
Now that I know how to get his voicemails he might call in there's a couple of me you guys are going while I wild on nylon's ass
Madam, this is Darren from Melbourne Australia, message about the nylon
Jesus this guy is just pony ass first of all every time he spouts his opinion he speaks at a different effect
And he's representing some large percentage of your audience and I can assure you that it's purely your opinion nylon
You know, you don't represent the whole audience. There's plenty of us who enjoy all aspects of what's going on
And just just kind of down a bit you know I say this is my opinion and I'm like that
Okay, yeah, well, that's okay. You know, I don't really mind how he communicates as long as he has a contrarian view
That's the most fun obviously so from New York to the UK we now head over to Vancouver
Add on it's a sale calling from Vansford and I'm also known as beautiful Vancouver British Columbia
Just finished listening to the Charlie 627 and you know the nylon's finally pushed me over the edge
I'm actually in marketing. I actually do understand how that whole game works and I certainly understand what it is you're trying to do with the network
And nylon just doesn't get this I mean he doesn't understand that what we're dealing with here is not a conventional
You know type of business where you can go out survey customers get fantastic ideas and drive yourself over up the million
Or the couple million of listeners that he wants to have but we're dealing with here is what's classically known as a disruptive technology
And I don't like some like a lecturer like the nylon is but he might be better off
If he sat down one day spend some of his value of time and read Clayton Christians and book called Innovators dilemma a classic text and technology based marketing
But it tells you that you know you have to kind of watch out what you're doing you have to be on the leading as you have to try risky new things
And frankly that's what your channels are all about I have to be honest. I do agree with him that a couple times when you first started describing the channels
It did sound very much like a technology push it didn't sound like something that necessarily
Added value to the user added some sound of like it added almost some complexities
But you know what I did I'm listening to you and you said hey try one of these things out
So I actually went down today and put trucker Tom's HD video channel up on my iTunes
Got a town loading to my Apple TV have been watching it and it's great. I get it. I understand
And you know the easiest way to figure this out is to try it if you like it great if you don't like it time something else
So anyway, I hate to go on a rant to match the my ones, but keep up the good work
Really appreciate what you do it on the show and look forward to seeing more innovation out of the Charlie sealated. Bye.
Man, thank you so much. Oh, that makes me feel good. Okay. Well, a couple things here. So first of all
I'll talk about channels at the very end. I do want to talk. I just want to go back to what you said about marketing
Because it is you know marketing is hard and you're right a company like ours
We have to and by the way, I have read the innovators dilemma. I mean, I've read all these books
Oh my goodness. In fact, one of the guys on our board
Radi Kamasar wrote the riddle in the monk is another one that you you may have come across a simplistic concept, but hit home
Then there's the you know crossing the chasm. I've read all these books
I'm always interested in it. I love reading you know about people who have been moderately successful
And write and tell me how to be very successful
But yes, you do have to take risks and and and sometimes you just fuck shit up, you know
The big mistake, you know, the on the internet no one knows your dog. Well, on the internet no one knows really
How your company runs, how big it is, what does big mean, you know, what is lots of money, what is
You know, there's all these questions that people, you know, they look at pod show. They may quite as to Google for all
I know, I don't know. This sometimes things we do and choices we make and sometimes mistakes we make we are certainly
Treated like we were Google making a mistake within a certain you know within a certain segment
Better known as the community whatever that means I think I'm starting to think the community now means content producers and creators
And I'm actually very happy with that there's a controversy brewing right now around pod tech pod tech is a
A podcast a technology podcast network led by John Furrier
And so they have a couple of interesting and famous
People on the network so their talent includes Robert Scobel and Jason Calacanis although I think he has his deal was to put a couple of kids through school
I wonder if they've actually done that I wouldn't mind an update on it because they did use that we're abused that deal for
You know, for some nonprofit goals so an update would be nice Jason
So here's what happened apparently I think pod tech organized the vloggies
Not a horrible name
And the vloggies like an award show for vloggers and vloggers is a little bit different than the stuff that we do vloggers is in my mind is much more
I'm sitting in front of the camera I'm telling you a personal story a segment in time
But it's really one person to camera that's kind of my idea of a vlog because it it already says to me this is a video blog
So I'm cool with that
So they sponsored the or they organized I think even maybe the vloggies and they I know they put a lot of effort into it
Just reading through a lot of the posts what happened was on some marketing material or some kind of material a picture was used by pod tech
Without permission of the author and the author then so the owner and was taken off a flicker page which of course
You know flicker and I've been there and you know I I actually went to court over someone taking a picture off a flicker and
And using it for commercial goals which was a gossip magazine and boy did they use I mean just Google that or maybe I'll put a link in the show notes
You can see what that was about but actually went to court and proved that the magazine was in the wrong
I didn't get any compensation for the use of the pictures but the court basically said hey it was clearly licensed creative comments attribution
Non-commercial you broke the rules
That was bad you can't do it again because then you'll be penalized
So that was a huge win and I believe in that and I think I was right and I think it is right and that's the way it should be
But now what what we're seeing happen
So pod tech use this picture the owner said hey you use my picture
I actually this is what I do for a living or even if I did it for hobby doesn't make any difference
I think you should pay me I think $3,000 is about right and so they went back and forth on money
And you know then this thing started to spiral
So you know people are blogging about it and now pod tech is is the evil bastard who don't give a shit about people's rights
Their ownership of content and clearly don't care about content creators and they're being equated now to you know to other companies
And it's it's just so interesting to me so first of all pod tech they're they're no better or worse than we are
There are small companies. I'm sure they're fucked up and they fucked this up
So they need to apologize work it out with a guy and move on and stop fucking blogging about it
You know it's a mistake I could see it's a mistake and I really want to take their side on this
So it doesn't spin out a control because you know I pod show knows what it's like to be on the receiving end of that type of controversy
And a number of people are very skilled and used to it
So this is going to be different for this company and it's going to be interesting to watch
But my recommendation is you know look we're really fucking sorry
I think it apology was already made
We're really fucking sorry we'll work this out work it out with the guy and move on because you messed up. It's that simple
But what's so interesting to me is that here again
You see a huge controversy brewing and people yelling and shouting and calling people names
Well meanwhile there are other companies out there who are really stealing your content
And if you don't think you do business one of them then you're nuts
Okay, if you just want to post your cell phone video up somewhere and shooting a bottle rocket out of your ass
Great fantastic if you actually want to make a business out of it
Okay, you know then you're going to probably want to work with companies like pod show like pod tech
There are others you're probably going to want to do that. These are media companies and they're not perfect
We're building an industry while building companies at the same time. It's very hard
So let's you know we all look like idiots
Okay, let's just get it fixed move on and and I'm looking at scobl and furrier you guys should just do that because it doesn't do anyone any good
Yeah, cranky 45 minutes. I wonder if you're still even listening to me at this point
Okay, so I will I'm going to finalize with something about the channel something about our big meeting on Friday
The company wide meeting and changes you'll be seeing to pod show across the board
But first one more comment about the channels and this is from a technology perspective the person who sent who called this in
Is an engineer and a technologist so I'm hoping that you don't get bored by it
But you may actually be very excited when you hear his analogy
Hey, and this is a Chris Thompson in Philadelphia a humble listener calling into a use of feedback on the
Mods or channels now when you say channel I hear a feed because that's what it is you know the end pump on the output
So it comes to me in iTunes or whatever as a feed
So I'm going to you know I use some different ways I use feeds
I'm subscribed to this blog called gizmodo is a gadget blog
And they have a bunch of junk in there about cell phones and windows vista that just I don't care to read
And so I use Yahoo pipes to filter it out
Yeah, who price this pretty cool service where you can mix and mash up different RSS feeds and make your own
Output and I subscribe to that in Google reader and I get all that I want without the stuff that I don't
And in Google reader whenever I'm viewing whatever I'm viewing a an article that I want to share
There's a button down there that you know click on it and it is
Hello, I'm just going to stop you for one second. I'll show you one that a little bit
Okay, so the filtering fantastic. I love it
So this is exactly what we want to do with channels a couple different ways to filter one will be the order in which things come in
So you'll be able that is in my mind a type of filter so you can determine what the output's going to be what is going to poop out of that thing first
You'll be able to determine that the second thing is the depth how many items do you I'll just talk in in geek speak how many items do you want to receive from from this feed
So you'll be able to set that depth of one will be default actually
I think that's what we're well, that's what we're working with right now. You should be able to go to infinity I think
But zero will also be possible so you could suppress the output from from a show into a channel
What would be fucking awesome and there's two parts to it one is a filter where you can say okay keywords and show notes
If the pot if those pop up or tags then then don't pass the episode through that would totally work
Something also very interesting is the result of a search that could also be in a collection an item or a container I should say within a channel
So anytime a show comes through and and of course, you know, we're obviously thinking of indexing the content of the show as well
There's a lot of companies that do that extremely well and we're in touch with the number of them and we're definitely plowing ahead with that
So you can get some more, you know, great search essentially but the results of that search would also result in episodes
Which you could again filter saying okay if it's if it's if it matches the result but it has Microsoft in it
And I don't want it then you know filter that one out so you could really create a basically a chain or indeed a pipe if you will of the output
Love the idea definitely going to be implemented the hard part of course is how do you make that simple for people to understand
Then how do you build the right user interface around it but love that idea
I'm viewing a an article that I want to share there's a button down there that you know click on and it is
It's a share button and it goes into its own feed and that feed is a
Subscribe to buy my girlfriend's out and she uses blog lines and she's described with that so when I share something
It'll show up in her feed reader. That's a whole wonderful, you know, so basically something and come from Gizmoto
Go to Gapu pipes and at my Google reader get a shared and come out on her blog line at the end
Oh man, I love it you're thinking my thoughts
Okay, so so this is beautiful this of course already works with pod show and if you go to my channels and yes, there's a link or all over the place now
You'll see there's a channel called Pat's podcasts and these are shows that I put together for Patricia and the way it works
It's a channel that I put together for Patricia the way it works is her iTunes because she has no idea
Okay, she's a no idea. I don't want to have works. She, you know, she just wants to be able to see the shit that she likes that she's found so far
So I am actually managing that experience for her since I'm always looking at video. I'm always finding stuff and audio as well
She loves the Frank truth as an example in fact
There's a special show that is only for her that an a special feed
The brine knows put together so when when something comes through on that I drop it into her feed
The other shows coming automatically Marie Claire. There's a fashion show and when there's a single episode
I really wanted to see I put that through and so all she has to do is just whenever she's in the mood she just checks iTunes
And she'll see the stuff that I put into her channel and it went straight to her iTunes. It's like magic
So what we'll listen to the last minute of your comment here, but of course what we're really seeing is we've got all this stuff working
We can and by the way, so you send certain stories to Val to your girlfriend
Fantastic. So what if you set put that into the channel right?
But then I put the output of that channel which she normally reads on our blog lines
What if I put that into into one of my channels?
So now all of a sudden when you put something through not only does it go into Val's blog lines
It could actually bubble up into my channel which I may in turn put into Patricia's channel
Do you see the connection? Do you see the plumbing taking place? Do you see how that kind of distribution can be massive?
Because you can subscribe to channel so anyone can subscribe to the channel
And if you don't like one particular show that's in the channel then just suppress the output or maybe filter it out
That is exactly the vision. That's a very very big part of where we're going
So that's the interesting
No, I tend to use the individual seeds to subscribe to different podcasts
So I have individual seeds for dawn and through and and then cops master feed with all the stuff that he does in it
Because I like to see all the individual shows in iTunes
I don't like how a whole channel just have one big listing full of stuff
That can be useful sometimes
As it is I have one channel which contains your show
And also an awesome audio book that I know Mike Bartlett is starting in electricity
You can search for Mike Bartlett or electricity
It's a new audio pod novel he's on chapter 3
It's pretty awesome to talk that up
So that's the sum of the ways that I use feeds in my general media consumption
And hopefully that helped out. I'm going to go finish up the stuff listed right now
So keep up the good work. Peace
Oh man, do I appreciate that
So here's what I envision happening
You would have found so you've you have created a channel
And this channel you use for yourself, but it's also public
So it's very thinkable that if you're finding great audio books
Mark Yoshimoto Nemkoff might subscribe to your channel
Because he's collecting great audio books
And that would be the Mark great audio book channel
So why wouldn't I subscribe to that channel and put it in one of my own channels
So whenever you post a great new book that you found audio book
It'll automatically flow through to Mark
Which will automatically flow through to me and anyone else who subscribed to my channel
It'll flow through to them
Mm-hmm
You start seeing how powerful it can be
So creating the interface for that is I just want to say
What I've shown in these cheddar updates is not the interface
This is this is sandbox stuff
We're just trying to admit right now
I just want something that works so I can create the output
Which I think will solve part of your problem
There in Philadelphia
Yeah, if you sit right now the output of the channel is you get a whole mess of shit
And there's no order to it
There's no format is what I'd call it
Because you're getting all the episodes
You know until some certain amount of time or certain number of episodes
Which I think is quite set quite large
So that is exactly what you don't want
You want your channels to be clean
And you want them to be easy, navigable
You want to be able to follow the tree
So where did the show actually come from?
Ah, it came from Mark's channel
And oh, I see that Mark doesn't have it in his channel
It's actually from your channel
And then I could traverse your channel
And maybe find other stuff
It's really what we need
Okay, and this is the final thing I'm going to say about it
Remember I said that pod show built its site upside down
We need a better media browser
And I would love if you have any examples
For you to send me links
I'd love to see what kind of media browsers you're thinking of
Because when I say media browser it's essentially a player
Show me a player that is really thinking the way media things
Okay, how can we integrate what I just talked about
Into windows media player
I don't think you can
How do you integrate that into iTunes
So the tools we really have
I don't think we're powerful enough to produce a new downloadable player
You know, that's huge, huge amount of work
But we may be able to create a similar experience online
Through a website, through a combination of
Very, very powerful technologies
Okay
Holy, cranky!
It's been the while since I've done over 55 minutes
We'll probably just get very close to an hour
And you know what I think we have a bona fide hit on our hands
This is our Jones
His second release to the pod safe music network
It's getting tons of pod play
And I gotta say I like it
Revolution of the heart
For people around the world
I don't feel an easy man
About the future
Time to end the war
Against humanity
It's time to build the peace
We're all essential
We took a little revolution
And demolition of the world
It's been the while since I've done over 55 minutes
We'll probably just get very close to an hour
So what you can be
Over and over
It's been the while since I've done over 55 minutes
We'll probably just get very close to an hour
And you know what I think we have a bona fide hit on
But people around the world
I don't feel any easy man
About the future
The world fills the universe
Without exception
From a spec of dust
To forget it seems right that doubt too
The hearts of you and me
We're talking about a revolution
The world fills the universe
Without exception
From a spec of dust
To forget it seems right that doubt too
The hearts of you and me
We're talking about a revolution
To forget it seems right that doubt too
The world fills the universe
As something about a man, song just for words
And I love the fact that it has an ending in that nice
Lots of stuff to do is going to be another late late night for two reasons
One I have a date with my daughter, we're going out and I'm very excited about it
We're going to the Justin Timberlake concert at the Millennium Dome
Or the O2 venue, formerly known as the Millennium Dome
In London never been there before
So I have to say very excited
And these tickets came to me from RB
That's right because that's what we call them in the upper class program
We call them Richard Branson
These guys know how to suck up
Damn I love that
So thanks to Pauline and Morag who are
I got like personal people who I book my travel through man
This is awesome
That'll be fun
And I was actually surprised
When they offered the tickets I said let me just check
I had to check first to see
Well really if Christina would be interested at all
Because Justin Timberlake
She's in a lot harder stuff typically
But she was really excited
She's like oh, we're dressing my going to wear
It's great, I'm going on a date with my daughter
It's going to be a lot of fun
And tomorrow of course we'll have massive food barners
It's going to be a great day for myself personally
Because of the stuff we're doing with our company
And of course for you guys I hope as well
If only just because it's the weekend
And you've been working like a dog all week long
DailySourceco.com is where we can find all the show notes
Links to all the crap we talked about today
And of course Semini Mail to Adam at podshow.com
Talk tomorrow everybody bye
The best in the brightest
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight