Hey Peter, can I ask you a question?
Yes, do you?
Who would you say our calls important?
After 20 minutes of being on hold, I'd have to say now.
Please continue to hold.
Your call is important to us.
Yeah, it's very correct.
It's very important.
Then we'll hold music.
Uniflight communications.
Our bus is going.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Delta Sierra Charlie, five three four.
To this, we can't keep headed home.
I can't take this anymore.
Out of all this, I just need you to go.
I can't seem to have really let you go.
You're not moving on.
Don't take the older arms again and back.
You're like a king on you.
Don't take the older arms on my knees.
I'm still holding on
Memories are around
Keep me standing here
I can't move on
It's easy
Tell me everything on you
Are you wanting
What's for me to tell the truth
None of them
You don't think all around
Take it away
Feels like I'm dead
You don't think all around
How long I need
I'm still holding on
There got a good sense
You really don't feel inside of you
I'm still holding on
I just need you to go
I can't seem to
I'm real
You don't think all around
Take it away
Feels like I'm dead
You don't think all around
How long I need
I'm still holding on
You don't think all around
Yeah
I'm a sucker for the big power cords
Man let me tell you
Point to reason from the pod said music network
PMN
Don't say it's over
I'm still holding on
Get ready
John
Jesus
Lutin
Just as we're all debaraging
the final bits of an interview Patricia was doing for some medical program in in the Netherlands,
which is about coping with illnesses. And so, you know, kind of conked out last night,
but not after watching the finale, the grand finale of Celebrity Big Brother for 2007, the winner
was the the Bollywood actress, Shilpa Shetty. And of course, quite interesting because, you know,
they were all they were saying, they kept repeating it yesterday, by the way, in the show,
about this international incident, the racism occurring in the Celebrity Big Brother house.
Well, first of all, let me just play this piece of feedback for you.
I don't choose Newcastle, UK England, the world. And, yeah, I'm just putting my little two pennies
in the dead, or Jade Goody, for what a shame. Short of, you know, from you, I'd with a press
over the other side of the water, with your daughter. If you get yourself in this Celebrity,
you're pretty much, in that circumstance, you're pretty much asking for what you get. Jade Goody isn't
racist, she's thick, and there's a big difference. She's not intelligent enough to cope with Celebrity.
There might not be a lot of people over there who are celebrities who are mega-intelligence,
but she's just never been right for it. She's been pushed from, from pillar to poster, you know,
from these, they're trying to be words of an officer, you know. She's been pushed around to
these agencies, you know, and Max Clifford, I think, looked after her, and was a big publicist.
She's just not right for it. But one thing I did want to say is this puts out a very big message.
A lot of said she's not racist, she's just thick. She is a bully, and I imagine I've been a
bully when she was at school, and it just put out a very good message to kids around the world,
is that when people face up a police, generally speaking, the will, the will crumble,
bullies are just cowards, and that's what Jade Goody's proved, that when she's been confronted
by the rest of the, you know, of the same worlds, to say, well, Adam and I, you can't go on like that
what people, it's not fair, and it's not right. She turns into a cumble in that in Christ. So,
you know, that's, anyway, that's where I wanted to say, I was bullied at school as well,
and police are just a bunch of nasty little cowards, simply. See you later.
All right, James. So, yeah, no, you know, I agree with James, which, of course, is why I played
as audio comment. I didn't see any racist behavior, and we have to be very careful what kind of
language we deem as racism. And by the way, is language actually the definition of racism?
It's certainly not nice, the things that were said, let me, let me look that up for you while we're
doing that. I was going to go to my, it's one of the sites that I've gone to for my entire life,
almost, or as long as it's been available, dictionary.com, I love it. Let's just look up racism,
because I, I think it doesn't read the, that true definition, what should we do, race,
racism or racist? I wonder. Let's see what racism. Oh, I misspelled it. Here we go. Well,
I'm not stupid, but I forgot the A kind of necessary when you're spelling racism. Let's see now,
a belief or doctrine that inherent differences among the various human races determine cultural
or individual achievement, usually involving the idea that one's own racist superior and has the
right to rule others. See, that's what I understood racism to be as well. Although, let's see,
the second definition of policy system of government, etc. based on or fostering such a doctrine,
discrimination, hatred or intolerance of another race or races,
maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe. But, you know, it just sounded like what was happening is people were
using, I were using a different line, different accents or or different appearances to hurt them
in a, in a conversation, but racism, I think, really is something else. So I agree with your James
about this, about J. Goody, not being a racist, but she is, it's thick. That's a good one, thick.
For her, that is particularly applicable, I think. So, you know, hopefully, I love this stuff.
I can't wait for them to do more of this because the more reality get, we get the more pornographic
it is. Anyways, I'll show up a shitty one. And of course, you've got to wonder if this
controversy hadn't been there, would she want or not? It doesn't really matter. But when she
came out and I wish, we don't have the sky HD box yet or any of the sky box is the guy comes
tomorrow, if he can find the place, right? So I don't have a recording of it, but she said something.
She just, the words came out so beautifully, or she said, look, I didn't feel any racism. I don't
think J. Goody is a racist. We're all, as human beings, we're all valuable. She had a lot of
really good one-liner zinger nuggets in there. And she said, I'm very proud that the people of Britain
have chosen me as the winner. And I don't think that Jade reflects bad on the United Kingdom.
I mean, and she, I don't think she had any outside contact with it. They're in the big brother house.
So she really didn't even know how big this had become and certainly in the press in the UK.
And she was very, very eloquent. Maybe I can find it, you know, that's typical something on
YouTube that might be available. I'll see if I can find that for you. It was just a beautiful quote
the way she said it. Okay, big show today. Lots of feedback. Thank you very much for calling
into the, into the voicemail lines, which means most of what we're going to be talking about
today comes from that. Except for one thing I've been holding on to because I knew that this
were required some piece and quiet and some sitting downtime. Now that I'm back at the, back
at the cottage, I'm using the homemade bill desk. So I'm doing the show sitting down very different.
You know, I like to stand up when I do it, but Amy Mac has got me sitting today. What are we
doing, baby? Come on in. Amy, I'm back. Hey, baby, how you doing? Tell me how much you missed me.
I missed you so much. Oh, I missed you, too. Okay, what do we get started? I did want to send my condolences
for Trinity. Well, I can't say I'm surprised, but nonetheless, it's always hard to say goodbye.
Not completely dead yet, you know. And what's up with this evening recording thing? I don't
know if the mood calls for exercise. Yeah, that's why I'm going to anyway. Okay. All right,
what are we doing? You're going to need a chair for this week exercise. Right, I'm sitting.
A chair with no arms and a flat seat is fat. Okay, no arms. You're going to lay down in your stomach
over the seat of the chair. Holy crap. Now you're going to balance on the chair. Yes. You can put
your hands before or grab the legs of the chair. Yeah, my hands, he's reached easily. You're going to
raise and lower your legs. Okay. It's not a huge movement, but you should be lifting the legs just
higher than the hips and squeezing that butt. Like this. And then lower them keeping it controlled
and then raise and squeeze again. Oh, Amy, you're going to do 12. Ready, go. Okay, one, keep your head
in neutral position. Three, four, you should only be moving about a foot up and down. Do you do that
five? Don't let your back arch. Keep breathing. Good job. I'm going to get back up. All right,
look back to your evening on the odds. If you get a chance, check out my new video show. There's
a hot topic and move the week. I even teach how to prepare a pomegranate. Take a look at fitlife.podshow.com.
Well, it's good to be back and I have a lot of new exercising moves for you. Okay.
So until next time. Thanks, Amy. I didn't know that she had a video show, fitlife.podshow.com.
Let me just go take a look for a second. Yeah, I felt that in the gluteous maximus region for sure.
Fitlife. What you said, fitlife.podshow.com? Oh, so the DSL is hooked up. Hey, how often does that
happen? When the company tells you, well, you know, first you have 15 days of disconnection,
then you have to call up and they'll take another five to ten working days to get reconnected.
Patricia said they called and said, you're connected, Mrs. Curry. And, you know, I came back. I plugged
in the router. I plugged in the airport and cabawi. I've got the bandwidth. Loving it here,
fit for life. Nice, Amy. Let me just see what she looks like in the video.
By the way, I'm such a dick. I was before celebrity big brother came on. I was watching some
DVDs with the kids, the kids being Christina and Andy. He's almost like a son to me now.
What the hell? One, two. Did you hear that? Sorry to crackle up. And, of course, I missed the return
of top gear on the BBC, Richard Hammond, they showed his accident. And that's another thing
when I have to go. I guess go look at YouTube, see if it can find it there or maybe there's something
on London BBC. I can find a repeat. But, oh, man, can't believe I missed that. Such a dork.
All right, Amy, I'm waiting for your show to come in. It doesn't seem, doesn't seem to be happening.
Okay. Well, we'll leave that for what it is for right now. If it starts to happen, I'll let you know.
I don't, it's James again. Hey, James. No, the message. And, not, not the sound like I've been
plagiaristic that I would. And, because I have just heard this suggestion, I did actually,
after I came up with Adam's hunting aboard. I did sort of think, what about, say, I think.
Welcome to, he says, Eric, what if, rather, do you see, you know, something like that? I don't know.
I did actually think of it, so he's not like the way back. I don't know. That sounds like I'm really
copying this. And I'm really, honestly, I'm not suppose. But they go. Just like Adam's attic.
Yeah, you know, that kind of works. And it is kind of something I got to figure out now because
now that we have the DSL. Now, I'm going to configure all of the wireless access. And it has to
have a name. You know, that's the most important place to identify is on the name of your wireless
access point. You know, it's, so currently I haven't set the curry cottage. Let me see,
I got a couple of emails here about that. Who's this from? Jessica, I have a few naming suggestions
for your family's new domicile. How about curry manner? It's a bit more upscale than cottage.
Not quite as grand as castle. If you have your heart set on a little duration, you could try
pod show polotto. I think it would be Patricia's polotto before it would be the pod show
polotto. I do have some experience in the naming field. I guess I came up with a name for my parents
cottage. Blake's Lake estate estate is also nice, isn't it? Curry manner, though, that does have a nice
ring. It doesn't have the alliteration stuff. I like so much Jessica Anderson from Gainesville, Florida.
But I think that, you know, that's kind of sticking for me. Now, what do we have here? Jersey Todd,
okay, he says the game ends right now. I've heard all the suggestions. Here's mine. The curry
quarry, the place where rock lives. He's been even written like little liners and stuff,
podcasting from the curry quarry where we dig the raw rock from the ground and get it to you,
fresh. Hey Todd, man, don't quit the day job, baby. I had him park you checking in again with a
with a suggestion for the name of the new curry place and gulfed about the curry colony. I figured
that would be nice because of the American connection and it all wants to be there. So it's quite
a few people making a colony. How about the curry colony? Take a bus. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know.
You know, it sounds okay, but then you look at it and you see the word colon jumping out at you.
It just doesn't quite work from me. So let me know. You know how to reach me, no?
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven, last one, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
You know, I often wonder which number people in the UK called. Do you call the plus one number? Or do you
call this number?
Okay, we're going to talk about Trinity in just a couple minutes. This is something that
came in though that was a bit disturbing to hear. Hey, this is Chris and Hager's town.
I was calling the ask you about songs no longer allowed on podcast. Podcasts,
safe songs on the podcast. Music network because I'm going through the songs to add them to my
podcast and one that I played before, I went to go play again and now it says, it's ghosted out.
It says, not allow for podcasts. So why are they even on the podcast? Music network.
Anyway, how do you start? You know, I'm a Latino talk to you later, five.
Yeah, so I appreciate you telling me that. I have not seen this myself, so it was interesting,
yet very unhelpful at the same time. Like, what was this maybe? Is that my, what is that?
Is that my, my headset or is that something else? I don't know if you can hear that. My left,
time to left channel cut out for a second there. Anyway, what song was it? Could you please
give me a little more information? It wouldn't make any sense to have a song up there. There's
not available for play on podcasting on podcasts or for other people who have signed the license.
It is, of course, entirely possible that the artist took his song off, his or her or whatever,
whomever song it is, they, you know, they can take it off whenever they want that doesn't mean by the
way that you have to get rid of any work that you've used the song in because that remains
in perpetuity if you read the license, you'll see that. But tell me which one it is. And we're
looking to it because that does not sound, uh, doesn't, doesn't, doesn't sound, uh, shit, it doesn't sound
like this. It's time once again. She's gonna go. She's gonna blow.
Everybody know that this is gonna be the better way. All right, everybody.
The Trinity, Trinity, the quintessential luxury, Trinity, Trinity, let the bio diesel set you bring,
Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity. She free Trinity, she save the world, win valuable prizes.
Yep, Trinity is going on a road trip. And let me tell you, uh, we had her towed out of the
Podshow HQ parking lot last week, and taken to the garage, where she was repaired. Guess what?
We saw the work order for this thing. I don't know what kind of garage Rosie took Trinity to,
but it said like, Kano start. Okay, Kano start. They replaced the battery, which was nothing
wrong with the battery. I think it, I had a brand new battery. Dickheads. So 200 bucks for a new
battery, and then they cleaned out all the fuel lines and everything. Rosie picked the car up,
and she tried to bring her back to the office and the same thing happened again. It caulked out.
So Trinity's back in the shop. We're gonna get her running. And the deal that I've made with Rosie
is as soon as she's up and running, Rosie's gonna drive it in from, uh, into work every single day.
She's gonna use it to keep her running, because we gotta keep it all the parts moving. You know, we can't
kick off this whole thing, and then all of a sudden have no Trinity, you know, have her not running. So
I'm gearing up on my end. I'm getting ready to, getting ready to put her on the road.
Hello? It all started when Jersey Todd told me about this podcast called Blarman. This girl had
broken up with her boyfriend. So I received this email from a girl named Nicole from a podcast called
Missing Something. And she just broken up with her boyfriend, too. And I was so touched by Dana's
story that I sent her an email. And we haven't stopped talking since. So I emailed her back,
feeling thankful that there was somebody else in the universe who was sort of feeling what I was.
If laughter's the best medicine this girl's been my doctor for the past few months.
And if it wasn't for Nicole, I would have gone insane months ago. But we can't be kept apart.
And so Dana's already coming to New York in May. And I've been trying to plot and plan a
scheme to take a road trip up to St. John's to see her. So pictures and chatting and long emails are
great. But I want more. I want Nicole to come and visit me in St. John's Newfoundland.
And let me, let me just interject you for a second. So here's two girls who found each other
apparently through the pod show podcast network. And who are communicating quite a lot, they
have in common that they have no men. And they love each other. I'm going to show her a good time.
I want to be there for her driver's test or for her first road trip in a car. And I would love
for it to be Trinity. I'd love for it to be biodiesel. I'd love to experience biodiesel so I can
get behind it. And I just love the idea of this big town girl coming to visit me, this small town
girl out here on this rock in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean. For years I've been working on
transitioning my life to be more toward the cause of sustainable and renewable energy.
And yeah, I'm all for the environment, but I just really want to meet Nicole. And so you've got
two pod show podcasters united by this strange medium as it is. So I'm just going to interject
real quickly. If you're listening to this on serious stars 102 go to dailysourceco.com and download
the rest because YouTube could participate in the free Trinity coast to coast run. Save the world
valuable prizes. And yet about a thousand miles apart, what better away to bridge that gap than
Trinity. So now you have to bruised and battered and slate your heart broken, but brand new and positive
podcasters trying to find a way to meet each other. Brute bruised and battered? Oh man,
how do you girl sound like fun? It seems to me that a Trinity is the absolute perfect way.
And maybe we'll even tell you how a part of our therapy has been sending each other naked pictures.
So, oh. Oh man. Did I hear that right? Let me just roll it back a little bit.
Fricked way. And maybe we'll even tell you how a part of our therapy has been sending each other naked
pictures. Yeah, so Adam, you and podcasting have allowed Nicole and me to connect. And Adam,
you and your ideas of sending naked pictures. Well, that's made us feel better about
ourselves. But now maybe you and Trinity can actually bring me in the call together
in real life. Can I take pictures of that? Please? Okay girls. Hey, this sounds great.
You know, we're trying to figure out how to get Trinity from West Coast to East
Coast and perhaps from the West Coast over to Europe. And I think it would be great
for Trinity to take a little diversion up north. Certainly if naked pictures are involved.
Hello Adam. My name is Yuna. I'm a 20 year old architect to just return from a couple
of years living in Georgia's London. So I kind of know where you are. And I just have a
comment about Trinity's story. I was wondering why on earth do you always have to turn
everything into something commercial? I know your business guy and it's a very good
visit. But I'm also very aware of that the way you do business is that you try to push
people to do something very new. Push. But the Trinity thing, the guy was just having
a father's son's story and you just tried to make it so commercial. Do it great. Just give
you the break. Thanks. Well, you know, I don't know what you're calling from. You sound
Dutch actually. But you know, turning this into something commercial, that's not a fair
characterization of what I'm trying to do. You know, if President Bush had been smart and
had waged the war for the independence of oil instead of a war in Iraq or a war against
terrorism, if he just said, you know what, we're going to be independent from oil from other
countries. You know, it would have been a whole different and by the way, if you mess with the oil
we have now, we'll kick your ass. Excuse me, since I was splinter. It would have been a whole
different situation we're in right now. And I truly believe that this biodiesel thing is catching
on. You know, I talked to people a lot about it. They they talked to me about it. And as far as I
can tell, people find it very interesting. Look, it may not be the cheapest solution. But just
about everyone says, Hey, man, I'd rather give some guys in Berkeley who have a garage filled with
bio with biodiesel. I'd rather give them two and a half bucks per gallon to fill up my car than
I would to be oil companies. And it makes a lot of sense. And, you know, it's a very American thing.
So to make a lot of noise for this and to draw attention to this has nothing to do with, uh,
with commercialism. And by the way, you know, the, the Doug Pilgrim's offer to drive Trinity back
over a week was fantastic. It sparked off a lot of ideas, but I'd like to get more attention for it.
I want you as a today to write about it. You know, about this eggnog colored Mercedes 300 turbo
diesel five cylinder station wagon from 1984 cruising on biodiesel surrounded by all these other
biodiesel vehicles trucking across the United States of America. I want people to know about that.
And the fact that not only can we do this, that there is independence of foreign oil and that people
are, you know, little initiatives are sprouting up left and right. You know, let's get Willie Nelson
involved with his biodiesel. We'll stop at a couple of his stations, even though they're mixed biodiesel.
It's a damn good start. You know, draw some attention to it. And at the same time, you know,
draw some attention to what we're doing that independent media can make a difference.
Hi, um, uh, blah, blah, blah. Big brother reality TV shows, blah, blah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm looking
to, uh, yeah, see something something something yesterday. Um, talking about Trinity and you're
bladding on and I lost concentration. You're saying something about driving it around with a
some voter phone, but it was not here boxed by the, something like that. Yeah, great. I'd be cool.
Still I'm still my other dudes with this time, I've got my vote. Um, but I've got a quick question.
I think biodiesel, um, can you only run biodiesel through it? Can you put a regular diesel through it?
Because that would clear out the pipes. And if you're driving only a hundred miles before
swapping over, can you get some town to town in the state? I exactly. So first of all, the
answer to your question is yes, any conventional diesel engine you have. Certainly in any modern
vehicle, you can put biodiesel right in it. No conversion necessary. Don't need to change anything.
Trinity's case because it's an older car in 1984. I think anything around that period or early
has to have different hosing and different tubing installed. And maybe that's part of the problem,
by the way, because the viscosity of vegetable oil is very different from the petroleum based diesel oil.
And it starts to break down the hoses and stuff. And so that crap is very, it's a very good chance.
That's what's happening, by the way. That's what's getting into the fuel line.
Interestingly enough, you cannot buy a diesel powered automobile in the state of California.
Anyway, the answer there is yes.
100 miles, the town's town where you would actually get to a place where they sold biodiesel.
So that's what we're going to find out.
Really, a logistics question. It's just the question really about my, you know, just show my ignorance
of the states. And that's one of the reasons why I want to go and drive across the state.
I suppose I should drive across Europe first, but, um,
it's not as warm in places. Anyway, the other thing is to sort of bridge versus the bridge question.
All right, so first of all, yeah, that, that will be the thing that we're looking to figure out
is can you do it? Can you drive 100 miles or do we need to make it 50? Or do we need to make it
300 miles? Whatever it is. I think that we have, there's a pretty good chance if we
mapped it out that you could probably drive 100 miles a day and you could go from town to town
and you would never have to get any conventional diesel oil.
I'm, I have a feeling that's actually possible. There's certainly cool to find out and to bring
attention to it if it is so. And if not, then we have some work to do. Trinity can keep on
trucking until it's done. I mean, I'm in arguments with someone who says that the word
X isn't the word. As in, uh, I had some potatoes. Um, but he says it knows H, I ate some potatoes.
Why I said to date, I don't know. Anyway, if anyone could tell me, it's spelled A, T, E,
so it's spelled A, but I've always understood that you can use the word at, uh, in, in place of
A, because it sounds nicer and it may well be a pre-all post-to-tenth something, you know,
put, put, put, put, put it there, present or pastend. I'm not sure. I'm not an, I'm not an, an English
graduate, but some, I like this message. Have your good, Charles from London, say goodbye.
Thanks, Charles. If you call up drunk again, man. Uh, what am I saying? I think it's eight.
You know, for a country that prides itself on, uh, on originating the language. And I must say,
for a country that has such extensive vocabulary use of the English language,
you guys got a lot of weird slang going on. I've heard that at, at that. No, I think it's eight.
I don't think there's any, any other way to pronounce it. But of course, language is allowed to
change and morph. Nothing wrong with that. Uh, something else I was hearing on Big Brother yesterday,
the use of the word sat. It was really interesting. Uh, uh, I'd have to go look at it again.
If it comes up again, I'll come back to you on it because, yeah, there is some weird uses of, uh,
of the English language. Okay. So for Trinity, back to free Trinity, we want to get her on the road.
We need to get things scheduled. And of course, help come it from the Lord.
Hi Adam. It's Neil Faulk and you today. Uh, just calling to say, um,
wouldn't mind having a chat with you when you're back. You're back here. We're done in the free
Trinity project. Uh, with a view to possibly helping to project manage, making it happen.
So if you're in Turkey, I think you've got my details, but it's not, um, Neil Dixon knows how to
get hold of me. Um, yeah, we're done with, uh, would appreciate your opportunity to talk about it. So,
uh, hope you have a safe flight home. Uh, take care. Talk to you later. All right, Neil, fantastic.
I appreciate it very much. Yes, I will get in touch with you because we need to get this thing rolling.
We need to get Trinity on the road for the coast to coast tour.
time today.
I'll figure out, I'll watch you go. Let me never be buying a home. If this is going to be
the better way.
Trinity, Trinity, the quintessential luxury, Trinity, Trinity, left the bio diesel, set your
brain, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, she free Trinity, she saved the world,
When valuable prizes, all right.
Let's see, we get this thing wrapped up pretty soon,
you know, like this week, so we can get started.
I'm tired of just talking about it.
Oh, one thing I wanted to remind you about,
we've talked about this show on,
on Potio Plus Bolivian Rhapsody.
So the first episode or actually the Bolivian episode
is now up, it's like a 30 minute documentary,
and it includes Mike Del Farrow,
who is this fantastic musician,
a music musician, musician, musician, musician, musician.
And if you like combination of music styles,
particularly from worlds you've never heard before,
I mean, this is not like a sting thing,
you know, where it's like plates in the lips
and really complicated, you know,
this is like intricate jazz and folk,
and you've got to check it out,
but it's also about the kids and education in Bolivia,
and it's a fantastic project.
You want to find out more about it.
Go to BolivianRhapsody.potio.com.
I'll put a link on the show,
no, it's a daily source code.com
because it's a bitch to spell Bolivian Rhapsody
with an H in there.
So I think the Himean Rhapsody
except it's Bolivian, Bolivian.
And I think you really enjoy it.
I gotta get that thing in rotation,
get it on the home page.
And we have time for, let me see if we have time
for wanting it, what do we add now?
Oh yeah, let me just open up one more conversation here.
I think I've handedly said,
maybe Thursday or Friday,
that isn't an amazing how medical companies
are so incredibly targeted with their ad buys,
and I know exactly when everyone has these particular types
of fevers and colds and viruses,
and they have the product and the solution right there for you.
I'm not trying to insinuate anything,
but there are apparently some viruses going around
to the United States.
Hey Adam, this is Jeff from Northern Michigan.
Just let's then see your DSB533,
and you are wondering about
sicknesses that we're going through.
It's been kind of country-wise,
but not so widespread that it's necessarily
an epidemic.
Still, as several viruses go around,
one is more like a severe cold sort of flu,
and then there's another one, a normal virus.
Sometimes people hear about the normal virus,
it makes people stick on the ship,
or it's big call for stomach flu.
There's been a version of that running around here as well.
Here in North Michigan, my wife and daughter were talented
for about a week or so.
That's probably about a month ago,
and it's been, you know, as anything goes with our,
it's my world with trains and trains and automobiles.
I think it all over the place.
Anyways, just thought I'd share that with you.
Former, clear.
Of course, you're a folder, man.
That's why you didn't get the severe flu.
Now, I'm pretty much convinced that folders are less sick.
Yep.
And so, okay, so we've got some distinct viruses.
You just wonder how they get into the air.
Yeah, where do they come from?
They just, all of a sudden, they pop up?
You know, or they couldn't be that they were fabricated
or could they?
Hmm.
On the way back in the, in the upper class lounge,
Virgin Atlantic at the San Francisco International,
I bumped into Jan and John from Magnetoon.
I had a nice little chat with them,
and man, they're really positive about stuff going on.
And they live, I guess they have a place in San Francisco
and a place in London.
And so we, we just talked a little bit about Podsac music
and I'm pretty sure I'm not sure all of what they've got.
I'm Magnetoon, but I know I've played some tracks.
And, you know, they talked about uploading the catalog
to the Podsac music network.
So, it's very cool.
And it was just, it was nice to see people
have exactly the same vision.
I'll just from a, from a different vantage point.
Because as you know, Pod show is about,
let's get the artist everything they can.
All we want is a capability for producers
of independent media podcasters to be able to, you know,
fill up their shows with great music.
And there's a little bit more to it.
What I call the social reward, which works both ways.
It's great when an artist hears their song played.
Cause, you know, it's like someone saying
to the 1000 of their friends or in the case of this show,
several 1000 of your friends saying,
hey, I really like this stuff.
It's cool.
And it makes you feel really good.
And it makes me feel good besides playing
in all this fantastic music is, well,
when you hear back from the artist.
I have them, this is Melanie Lewis,
calling in from London a very cold London
where we have snow and everything this week.
But I just wanted to say thank you for warming me right up
by playing my track revelation on your show.
It was great to hear it.
And it was really good to know that it got you up
on your feet and moving.
It's a shame we can't see that.
I've got to be away.
Maybe technology will move on, but until then,
I have another track on the podcast
and music network called Satisfymey.
And it might not make you dance,
but I'll be very interested to hear
what it does inspire you to do.
So let me know, because I'll be listening out.
Loving you show, can you put the good work, Mr.
And thanks again.
Okay.
I love it how you save Mr. Well, Melanie.
Maybe we should hook up at the shortage office
one of these days.
Come on, who's honored or something like that.
I'll tell you what this song motivated me to do.
You're satisfied, Melanie.
Let me sing into the sea.
But every little bit of you.
Watch me get care about the rain.
So I'll win you in a good way.
Down home.
Yes, it's true.
I'm in danger by you.
You're making it so intense.
Don't tease it if you're eager to please.
You have my full consent.
Yeah, it's funny.
Just say it's funny.
Yes, that is funny, babe.
Just see your immerse for me.
Underneath I've ever heard of you.
You miss women and resty.
Nothing here could ever be too much.
I've been the crowd to you been circling around.
We should know on your ending.
Right now, you got me on the ground.
Make that funnel disappear.
Just say it's funny.
Just say it's funny, babe.
Where do I go now?
My life's on my reason.
Oh, man, I know it's bad.
You gotta be so open good.
Just say it's funny, babe.
Gotta please all make it a dream, babe.
Yeah, I don't want to show me you cause that it's funny.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah there yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah,
Where have you been all my life?
Are you kidding all of these?
I love it.
Fantastic.
Melon, you know, it's satisfying me from the Pod Save Music Network.
Wow.
You know, it's cool.
I found something out the other day.
If you go to podshed.com slash music.
Or if you go to Melony Lewis from from daily source code.com, I'll put the link in
the description.
I'm going to take you to her artist page on the Pod Show Plus.
And you get the artist.
You click on get it to the little master control icon.
You can put that into your collection and then you can play back all of her songs in
a row.
It's almost like an album.
You know, you see, get your album art and then you get all those tracks.
You haven't actually downloaded them.
You can't actually put it onto an iPod or a portable device.
But you can listen to it whenever you want.
And it's cool.
So a little get it there on Melony.
All right.
Everybody.
So we're back.
It's feeling good.
I got a lot of work to do here.
Got a lot of crap to clean up.
Got a lot of boxes to unload.
My part of the house is the last part to be completely moved in.
And I'll start on that today.
Lots of stuff to do with the sky guys coming tomorrow.
I got to take jagging to the shop.
I was at the dentist this morning.
Oh, by the way.
I set my appointment now August the entire month of August.
I'm going in from my airframe overhaul.
And I'm going to have a whole bunch of crap down to my mouth.
And hopefully I'll be able to make it to my death with the teeth that I then have.
Yeah.
It's the midlife airframe overhaul.
All right.
Adam and pod show dot com daily source code dot com.
Take care everybody.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best of the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limelight.