16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
Fantastic.
It's a battle curry.
Yo, it's the Daily Swasco 542.
It's worthy of a wild thing.
Kiki de sil obstinatlic.
Yeah, head, maybe a mess.
It's just my turn because no one's home.
I'm just sitting here running, now we're getting Friday long.
I'm not getting through, I believe it's true
I believe it is, I'm in no way
I need to be left alone
To see you here, while I'm in my misery
I see you here, nothing in my life can bring me here
I say here, I'm further, can you help me?
Hey, hey, hey, oh those crazy things I said
When he threw my head
As I like him and I still want him to spend
It's no use I swear I'm not getting up
No one, no one can get me out of this deeper world
I need to be left alone
To see you here, while I'm in my misery
I see here, nothing in my life can bring me here
I say here, I'm further, can you help me?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Oh how's it going to be?
I'm here, I'm further, can you help me?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I need to be left alone
To sit here
While I'm in my misery
I said he'd have to learn
To sit here
While I'm in my misery
I said he'd have to learn
To sit here
Nothing in my life can bring me cheer
I said he'd have to
Brother can you help me
Interesting room noise there on the vocals
P.M. Brother can you help me
Just join the Ponce of Music Network
They're from New York influences
Well, it should be no surprise
Led Zeppelin, no doubt, blondie heart
Like it a lot
And even though there's no picture of the lead singer
On the Ponce of Music Network
There's one on their own website
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Thursday
It is the 8th of February 2007
In the affluent suburb of Surrey
Known as G-town on the west side
Today would have been an aside
Today would have been an historic
Day in my personal history
As I was supposed to meet up with comic
I had in shortage London
The aliens or maybe somebody from the future
Wanted to disturb our meeting
So my airplane has been returned in the air
I repeat in the air
Because all London airports were closed due to the snow
And because in the continental airplanes from USA and Asia
I'm very sorry
Here is Captain speaking
And I have to learn what we have to coordinate
And we have to go back to London again
To reveal the echo
The last information we got to come
Hold on
Must let the airport travel on a little tip
Close the boat
To London clock local time
And stand for 10 o'clock local time
To get big
But minor clock local time
The question is if they can accept us
For the flight back to London
Due to the idiot boats
Over the ocean from USA
All the earth got the metal flight
So we are
After a while we had the situation
Other ground, please let us
I'll give us some time for that
We will get the information back
Thank you
As I've turned my man
I'd like you to leave the aircraft
No buses waiting on the left hand side
For the information we get from our aircraft
We will be advocate for you
But we all airports
Area of London are closed
So for the information we get there
Thank you
So you can see Adam
That I couldn't do absolutely anything
I am very sorry
You
Shaha
Come Mr. Blogger
It's okay man
We have a saying in Holland
But the infot seat for your need
And that means
I don't want to try and translate that
It'll be okay
We'll work it out
So obviously due to snow on the ground
Yeah, we got a couple inches here as well
Not enough to deter the lady Patricia
From taking the roads throughout to have her nails done
As was the entire plan
In fact now
The sun is kind of breaking through here and there
And I think the worst of it may be over
Which of course is important
Because you know I have a trip scheduled for tomorrow
To to the Netherlands
Now of course that may have to be postponed until Saturday
If it does then you know CSB could come back tomorrow
But you know it's like so much is up in the air
I think we're just waiting till after three GSM
Which is the conference that comixer blogger is going to
Not just CSB but
This is like the mobile phone conference I guess
So you'll have to listen to
What is it?
Mobile phone
Oh crap
What the hell is the name of that show that he does
Anyway go to comixer blogger.com
Comixer blog.com
As a link at curry.com
See you can find it
CSB I'm truly sorry my friend
I was really looking forward to it
Everyone at the office was all excited
And all set and
Bummer
But there's always a silver lining somewhere in the clouds
Yes
It's like me back
It's time
Once again
She must be
Yes
Adam
It's Amy man
Hey Amy back
She's back
Are you ready to ask her side
Yeah we get the other mic up and running here
Okay
Today we're doing one like it's flat
I want you to start standing tall
Shoulders back
And squeeze the abs and butt
Okay
Now like your right leg and stick it out
Straight in front of you
Now squat with your left leg
Go as far as you can and then come back up
You should really feel it in the legs and butt
And your abs should be keeping you from tipping over
Now switch legs and stick out the left leg
Okay
And then squat with your right leg
Good
Seven more on each side
You want to make sure that the ground of leg doesn't let the knee come over the toes
Six
Oh that's nice
You should have the weight in your heel
You almost want to sit back a little bit to counterbalance
Okay I got it
I got it
Oh yeah
Breathe
I always forget to do that
Keep it slow and control
Yeah
Slow
Okay
Nice
Oh
Oh man
Great job
Have you been practicing all your ascercising moves?
Yes, yes, I have
I think we should start an ascercising campaign
Our mission is to rid the world of saggy bottoms
What do you think?
Well anyway, you know we're to find me
And until next time
I think we should go on a mission here, Amy Mack
To rid the world of saggy asses
And of course, ridding the world of saggy asses
Starts at home
We're all alone by the way
There was no school today
Oh Christina had her play last night
Oh man this was so cool
This is extra
Outside of the regular curriculum
The her drama teacher
Had written this play
Which was a very very complicated play
With multiple scenes, multiple times
Crazy
I should have brought the program up
I should have read it to you
Because it was like a bet that he made with a friend of his
That he could write a play
That included all five genres
And the ending had to be at the beginning
I mean, it's one of these right?
Oh man
Three hours
Three and a half if you count the half hour intermission
No wonder the kids been home late every single night
From practicing this piece
It's an incredible long
But it was good
Oh, we were a bunch of proud parents
It was so nice
As a couple of Christina's friends came
Came down from up a little bit of North Alton
To come and watch the play
Of course, Indiana was there
So it was a good time
No why am I mentioning that
Oh yeah, because that's why
Even though Christina has to do the play tonight
There was no school because of the snow
And as you know, the lady Patricia is
Is out to doing her nails
Yes, I got a call from a listener
Who had stopped listening due to a very busy personal schedule
Stop listening to podcasts in general, I believe
But he did specifically mention this program
The Cha Cha, the Charlie, the Daily Source Code
Delta shared Charlie
And he asked for a recap of what had happened
Since he stopped listening
Which, of course, I said is quite a challenge
But Keith is here
And it seems from library
I've written a show yesterday
Got call in English
I want to know everything that happened
I'm show for like the past four years or something
Like he's called in customer service
Asking for like always counter information
Just going to sit on the ball on all day
Or paying away
And so this message is for the guy
You called in, let's have a message
I got the load out
So Adam went back to California
Then he went to London
Then he went to California
Then he went to France
Then he saw your underpants
And then back
All right, okay
And then he went in and then
Like a month ago
He bought everybody
And I bought that
Listening to the show
Stuff for you
Because you are listening to a loser
And then he went
A body house
Okay
And then he was going to go to
Yo and then the government
And London said can't do it
So he went and bought
Another house
And then now he owns like four of them
And then
Got married again
Now he's got like six wives
And then
He went
Along
Loosen the train
Thought you're going on tangent
Okay
And then and now I saw his car
Because he wants to buy a bigger airplane
And an airport
So
More stories
Better not
Don't ship any more like a
Like you did
Because now you got in just in time
He's given
Everybody gets free music
Because of Apple
And copyright
And Beatles
So
And that's it
And if you've been listening
You even know
Got on keys from library
And that's all
So
Keep from library
That's it
Ow
Shh
Thank you so much man
Absolutely
Down to a tea
I think that's just about everything that happened
Particularly the free iPods of everybody
Yeah
You know I've been talking about this Nokia
And 800 internet tablet
And it's kind of a dual experiment
And it's working out quite well actually
You know the experiment was
Can I live with just the tablet for
You know places where I would
Not necessarily want to carry a laptop
And I was very
What should we say?
Skeptic about using the on screen keyboard
And I've learned to use it
Now this has been going on at the same time
Of course that I've been sitting down
To do a number one
Yeah, this is all part of our posh people
Potty pigs
And of course not being a potty pig
Also starts at home
So to appease the lady Patricia
I'm doing my appeasement
While sitting down
Which of course goes very nicely
Hand in hand I might add
With the just having the internet tablet there with you
So I know that there are a couple of developers
From the Memo project who are now listening to the show
You guys are doing awesome work by the way
I'm I really haven't had time to dive into the community
I'm not a programmer
But I do I can parse
And understand what's going on
In a developer based community
And
G potter which is a python variant
Python being a programming language
A python variant of the original iPodter
That I wrote and of course
That many people picked up on
Is now ported to the web to the internet tablet
So I had some problems actually
Installing because you have to install python first
And it should be a one click operation
But there's this application manager
That had that make sure that all your libraries
And you're basically like like if you're on Windows
Your DLLs and all that crap that you don't want to know about
That it's all up to date
And I was having some problems with that
Craig helped me out by the way
Thanks buddy, really appreciate it
So it was just kind of through trial and error
I had to uncheck some repository
Excuse me, full jurors
Gourmet coffee blends
With some wonderful splendour
So I had to change some of these repositories
And turn them off and then make for
You know one update I guess I got out of sync somehow
It's probably what happened so anyway
I'm got it all installed and fired up G-potter
Which I was very excited about
And it works it absolutely works
But I was a little disappointed
Because the main feature
The main feature of iPodter
As originally spec
Was that it runs seamlessly in the background
Once you've configured it it runs in the background
And it's just downloading stuff
You know whenever it's available
So particularly with the internet tablet
Which already knows
How to connect to wireless networks when they're available
And activate stuff
You know what we're missing here is like an hourly scan
So really the interface which is not bad at all
If you're right now it's a manual download
Essentially you subscribe to a podcast
I subscribe to my podshow plus channels
Which is nice because
You know I was thinking we could do a couple of really groovy things with this
Well let me just finish the thought here
So you know basically you're adding in
Feeds manually
And then you select the feeds and you say download
And then you can watch the progress download
And then once it's downloaded it can play
But the whole beauty of this is it should just be running in the background
And when you go and check your subscriptions or your channels
I think channels will be much easier because
You know no small devices really meant for managing subscriptions
You know then it's just there if it's not there then it's not there
It may be downloading but it's not there it's not there
So we need some kind of I guess in the in the Unix world
We'd say we need a cron script to run
Preferably configurable not everyone wants it running
An hour some people want it running at half an hour intervals
Or maybe once a day
So you know I'd really love to to work on this particular version of iPot
Here's the suggestion I have by the way
We have a an API
Available
Um for unantined foil headers
An API stands for application program interface
I think
Essentially is how other programs can talk to the podshow
Plus platform so based upon a login
username and password
Um the system can spit back all the channels that you've created
So I have an on the go channel. I have a news channel. I have a talk channel. I have a tech channel
These are all very basic channels that I filled up with shows that you you add to a channel by by getting them
It's a little button called get it next to each show on on podshow.com
And you can add it to a channel right there from the show itself
It doesn't have to be on the podshow network. It can be an external show
Just anything that is within the database
Which is pretty big
So what if we modify g-potter just a little bit so you supplied your
Um
Your podshow plus credentials and then it immediately spits back channels
Now these channels you manage through the website
Obviously because it's just not convenient to be cutting and pasting URLs into little boxes
So you'd manage that all at podshow plus and then um
You know then you get a kind of what it has now you just see here your channels and here's what's been downloaded from the channels
Now you can find the API
And developer.podshow.com
And if you have any questions, please let me know because
Essentially I'm just trying to get something working that I'd really like myself
Yes, we continue our quest to find if
Push people are potty pigs and Jochen Lily says add a mine of coins
DSC 540 had me in tears listening to you speaking German about good bathroom manners. You're right
The concept of sitting down to pee is a pretty strange concept to some men as you can see at this illustration. He has an interesting flicker link there
We're to put in the show notes, but if it's explained well a man can get used to it after a while I got used to it too
Especially because it's my turn to clean the bathroom including the toilet every second week
Jochen, is this what your wife makes you do?
Ah, man those German women or something else, huh?
If you're just tuning into the daily source code you're wondering what this is about
We're trying to find out if people who are posh are larger potty pigs than others
And what we're finding out is that well
Pretty much everybody seems to be a nasty potty pig
Hey Adam, it's polo flarity here from oflarity.dk and I just wanted to send you a quick message
To let you know how things are here in Denmark we regard to posh people being potty pigs
Now when I first came here the Denmark a couple of years ago
I used to work in bars and the one particular bar that I worked in because I was the new guy
I always got stuck with cleaning both the gents and the female toilets after you know a busy Saturday night
And I must say while the male toilet the gents toilet was absolutely terrible
I mean you know, pee everywhere, shite on the bowl, the whole night
Shite not on the bowl on floor
It was nothing and I mean nothing in comparison to the female toilets
They were some of the most disgusting things I've ever seen
And I've got a new theory about this
First of all the running theory is that people are pigs in public bathrooms
Because they know that at some point during the day or at least before the next business day
Someone is going to be tasked with cleaning that
I'm just going to make an assumption here
That women possibly could be even larger potty pigs because they actually clean other people's shit at home
If they are family women
I would have to sit now not trying to be sexist or anything
But it's more than likely that more women clean crap out of toilets than men in western society at least
As far as I know
Perhaps they're so fed up with doing that
That they're like I can't wait to make a mess in this bathroom because some other suck grass to clean it up
Now
Listening to
DSC
I can't remember her name but I heard woman talking from California
And she was talking about sanitary pills
She was talking about women poverty
You know it
I'm going to stop this comment
First of all it's really long
I appreciate the calling from Denmark
But it gets pretty gross
You even grossed me out dude
I have some some some other outlets
Burning question which I've been interacting for quite a while
I haven't tried to play the traditional or any other
Any other demo of Jeff Smith and he leaves you a long one
And I want to hide it
And I want to how does it work
Does Jeff create a big loop for you as you just keep playing playing playing
Just by the end of your comments or your topic
And for some of you it's too like
The end of six
So do you know what I mean?
It's like well it's the first half of the intro to Trinity
They have a long time
Exactly just a music
And they have like yeah
How does it fit?
It's three parts of the jingle
How does it work?
Can you elaborate on that?
Because I'm preparing my new podcast thing
Or a menu card
I just thought
Hey let's do exactly the same as yours
Buy a car and give it a website
So it's calledmyfuse70.com
Which is my new 24th
But where is the Volvo G70?
Which is coming up that was the one with the origami roof
Y'all
So if you work for five years to get a car
Get a website
Never mind
I didn't go get it
But I should
Bye
I do
This is like asking David Copperfield to tell you how he makes the elephant disappear
Or the statue of Liberty
I mean you know
You're basically saying how do I do it that I time it so perfectly
Every single time and put it in all the comments
Well it's a quite a process
The Jeff and I go through to make these things exactly the right length
And if you believe that, well my friend
Hey Siri said I'd listeners
We'll talk to you tomorrow for Fubar Friday
Bye bye
Let me see what I should do here
You know I
Oh here's here
Let me talk about this
The couple of things I wanted
I'll move some stuff towards tomorrow
I found an awesome show at PodShow Plus
You have to check out
It's Girls Gone Weed
It's a ggdub.podshow.com
That's Gulf Gulf Delta Uniform Bravo
Ggdub.podshow.com
They've got some awesome videos
Basically it's cute girls smoking weed
In pipes and bongs
And welcome to the network ladies
I'm totally loving it
And there's something I wanted to try out with y'all
And I only wanted to do it with the listeners to the podcast
Not the series satellite radio listeners
This is some software company in the UK pitched me on this
And they essentially pitched me to see if we would want to integrate it into podshow
Plus
A lot would have to happen
But it's pretty interesting
It's a very basic functionality
In essence you get a phone number
Where people can send a text message to
And the software on the back end will count votes
Yeah, exactly
Kind of like our own little mini american idol
Only I don't want to use it that way
What I wanted to do is I wanted to ask
Those of you listening if you have a mobile phone
A mobile
If you wouldn't mind texting
Whether you're a scruncher
Or a folder
So that we have a real running tally
And it doesn't matter when you text this in
If you do it now or if you do it tomorrow
Because the software will just keep tracking
Those that particular campaign I guess you call it
Now because it's a demo system
There's only one phone number
So you have to add AC as a pretext
So let me explain
So you get ready to compose a new message
And SMS message to text message
And you send and of course the number will be on the show notes
But you sent you want to send it to plus four four
Seven eight one four
Three three eight
Five nine
Zero
And then in the message you want to start off with AC
As an alpha Charlie
Space
And then put in folder or scruncher
Depending on your preference
So text
AC space
And then folder or scruncher
To plus four four
Now the plus of course is for your external access
It will work in every country
So do plus four four
Seven eight one four
Three three eight five nine zero
And I will be posting
A graph
Yes, I will
A graph of folders versus scrunchers
That listen to the daily source code
Hey Adam, this is Alan Briss and Gospel
Just finished my daily commute
Listening to DSC 541
I'm very interested to hear what you're saying about Apple and DRM
And couple of funny things happened
After I finished listening to DSC
Finished halfway through my journey
Alan Rigby by the Beatles came onto my right bottom
And followed by that
I killed you playing on your show before
They're still in wait
And she played a song called
Bound
And I couldn't help but think
She's singing about DRM
So have a listen
See what you think
Seems very spooky to me
But maybe she's actually talking about
Blocks, I don't know
And anyway, that's to Apple
And this whole thing about the packaging
I certainly thought swatches
You know, you write about every week
New style, new colours
It's got to be happening
I think you're writing it's a very exciting time
Next
Yeah, I don't know
Nextive months is going to be
A very interesting time for the music industry
So keep it up
Love the free currency
And all of that
If you need anybody to write across Switzerland
Drop me a line
Somewhere
And yeah, hold it
Okay
Yep, make sure you
Thank you
Make sure you text it in
And of course, we need people to drive
Across all continents and countries
Please sign up to the
Trinity Google Group at groups.google.com
Slash Group slash free Trinity
Hey Adam, it's Derek from Sydney
I've kind of piled up all my comments together
Just like Charles the Drunk Londoner
Oh, come on now
You can never compare yourself
The Charles the Drunk Londoner
He is completely unique
I accept I'm not drunk
I'm just so tired it feels like my face is going to fall off
And you're like not from London
You're pronouncing things
I work with a palm pomegranate girl
I got to explain pomegranate
That's what
That's what down and that's what they call the people from the UK
Pum
Prisoner pomegranate
Prisoner of Mother England
In other words, you have not yet escaped
Like me, I'm a pomegranate
Even though I'm a young pomegranate
I'm a young pomegranate
The candy store I work at
And I was asking her how she says I ate it
And she said I ate it
I said yeah
She said I ate it
I ate it
Oh wow
If I didn't know what we were talking about
I would be totally confused
So she ate it
And I guess that's just
They're dialect
They just have reminded me of
A little Britain
Anyway
I remember you said herb
That's a funny man
That's the wacky woman from the asylum
Who smears shit on everything
Yeah
It sounded just like it
That just struck a chord in my brain
Where
In Australia we say herb
Well, that's great
We don't only say you hate it all
Like if you hear someone doing that on a game show
Like we love fortune
It just sounds very
I don't know
Not good
And
Well my mum's American
So I know a bit of the American language
And I'm just always known it's be herb in America
Like just drop the age
Kind of
Signage or whatever
So yeah
I also tried to get some folgers
Free coffee, gourmet selection
Being from the website
And that's US residents only
Ah bummer
Yeah bummer
I got excited
But then I got disappointed
Anyway
And Trinity
Well she has to come to Australia
Because we're
We're trying to be
Environmentally friendly
And stuff like that
And podcasting is sort of taking off
It's becoming independent
And all that kind of thing
And well mainly
We have to get our going across the harbor bridge
It's
The bridge is 75th
But they, I think that would be a great
But they present for this
The harbor bridge
You know, Trinity
Well that's for me
All our
Shaking later when
I have a face that actually works
Take it
I'm a folder
Sorry
Sorry for the pilot error there
You know, Trinity
I was going to say Trinity
Doesn't have a very good record
When it comes to bridges
So we may want to reconsider that
Please sign up at the Google Group
For free Trinity
DailySourceCode.com
As we can find all the links in the show notes
That was down yesterday
Or it wasn't down
DailySourceCode.com
And other custom domain names
All of a sudden we're pointing to
The Podger.com homepage
I don't know how long it was like that
But I got a couple messages
And sent it through
Engineering through our critical list
And it was fixed within
Within no time
Literally
But I'm still trying to figure out
If it affected more people
If you notice it
It's fixed now
That's for sure
What's this thing I saw about
Ask an engine
Do you watch the Ask an Injip podcast?
I love it
And I think everyone loves the Ask an Injip podcast
Apparently
He's built up his audience
Online
At his Myspace page
Or at least a significant audience
And he wrote this
This was a couple days ago
I think it was end of last week
That he hosts all of his video
At REVER
And that
Anything any link to REVER
In fact, even the words
REVER
If you type it into a blog post
Or if you put it into your profile
On my space it gets deleted
That's fucked up
You know that's like
That's like
DRM
You know that's like
The media version of DRM
That's so completely wrong
It just doesn't make any sense to me
You know
I haven't really proved over and over and over again
That letting people link all over the place
Is really what works
It's just surprising to me
Anyway
No surprise
I was going to play this one for you
Because we've got to give you another updates
As Trinity is ready to
ROWL
Driving across the USA
Open to make a good time today
I feel like I've been watching you
Letting everybody know
That this is going to be the better way
You can't help but sing along at this point
Trinity
The quintessential luxury
Let the bio diesel set you free
I
We've got drivers who are offering their services from coast to coast
Some of them are celebrities
Hey, I'm em, it's Callie
I love what you're doing with free Trinity
So I just wanted to let you know
If she takes a trip through Texas or even down Route 66
I'd love to do something
I could drive or as you know, I have a diesel car
And we used bio-willy diesel
So I could follow behind and shoot some HD footage
And I don't know, whatever you need, I'm in
Just let me know
With a reason of course
No naked picture, sorry
By the way, I'm a soldier
Of course you're a soldier
No naked pictures
How disappointing
Thank you Doug Program for pointing free Trinity.com
To free Trinity.podshow.com
And he's still trying to find the perfect car for me in San Francisco
Dude, I'm just going to buy some POS that just runs
You know, if I can find a little more modern diesel
I'm happy to do that
But my days of really caring about the car that I drive
I have to say are really long gone
It's just it doesn't excite me anymore
I really know I'll get an old
Hi Adam
Yes, please bring Trinity over to Germany
Or as your friend in Abu Dhabi, put it
Trinity comes home
And while I'm at it
German fans of the Charlie
And I'm sure they are a good number
You bet there are
I'm here, I'm a podcast entity here in Munich, Germany
I live in a two-minute driving distance of a station
Where you can get exclusively vegetable oil
Here near the Technical University of Munich
And I would gladly pick up Trinity's say in Brussels
Where my wife was born
And driver over here to Munich or a pick up in Munich
And driver to Franco in Belaitalia
So let me say one more thing
Folder
Or naturally
Good to fat
Yeah, good to fat
And now you can laugh your ass yourself
Brits
Fart of the New Goodmaner point
Yep
You know, is that awesome
That everyone who's calling in from around the world
They all are aware of biodiesel
And they know where to get it
I mean, this is so much bigger than I anticipated
Barbara Palo Alto
Podcaster is working hard on the Google Greg
That was yeah, it's in bad
On the Google Group
Ah
Okay, she put a link on the main page of the Google Group
So people can join Teen Trinity
By sending an email message
Stating name location
How they want to be involved in the project
And that's you can send that to free Trinity at gmail.com
And she's been receiving a number of
That's interesting
She's calling them invitations
Which I kind of like
It's an invite for Trinity to come by your neck of the woods
So if you're really serious about it, please send off an email
To free Trinity at gmail.com
But definitely jump into the conversation over at the
The Google Group for free Trinity
One thing we do not have yet is
Well actually, we need more yanks
More people from the states
And so far, no full suggestions for music venues
So, and I like this, you know, this part of the
Of the plan very much is, you know,
To try and coordinate stops where
Podsate music artists may be performing
Or where there's some kind of, you know,
Some kind of venue where podcasters are involved
So that we can spice it up a bit
So get your asses on over to groups.google.com
Slash group slash free Trinity
You can just go to data source.com
Click on the link in the show notes
Oh, boom, boom, boom
I think it has something to do with the weather
But I'm really messing through
Trinity, Trinity
Because a central luxury
Left the biodiesel set to bring
Trinity, Trinity
Free Trinity, to save the world
This is a win valuable prizes
I'm telling you man, ever since Ever since he asked me
How, how I actually do that
How I close those loops I'm freaking out
I can't seem to do it anymore
That's why this song is so perfect for me
Or today, I'm an asshole
I know you got aspirations
Can be a new boss one day
Who put that stick up your ass anyway
Yeah, yeah
Post a phone for company cast
Restoration, we travel and you kiss the crowd
Go TV just by making a whole face
Round
This is the manager company boy
You sat with that fuck
And you're a asshole
It's kind of like you very much
That water cooler might look better
Stop right up your butt
There's already an asshole
I can't believe you're still employed
There's a stop for business
But be one that can't break
There's already an asshole
You're speaking out
Everyone's business
You stay a little hell out of mind
You know it'll come back to find you in time
Yeah
Well, I'm not just telling everyone here
And not that little thing
I know about you
I got you in the clouds
It's been blue
And the lighting is shaping the copyright
And when the CEO tells you that
You're a asshole
It's kind of like you very much
That water cooler might look better
Stop right up your butt
There's already an asshole
I can't believe you're still employed
There's a stop for business
But be one that can't break
There's already an asshole
You're an asshole
You must be
Made it to someone
It's the only way you could have got here
Underqualified
The statement of the year
A left handed rabbit package
A fancy to the job better than you
You could even prove a thing
Oh
The statement is present that I've ever met
And I just want to ring your goddamn neck
Cause you're an asshole
It's kind of like you very much
That water cooler might look better
Stop right up your butt
There's already an asshole
I can't believe you're still employed
So the company's not looking at me
But be one that can't break
You're an asshole
There's some matter for you
But hopefully no one in this room
But if you're not singing then it's true
That I'm singing this hair song about you
And you're an asshole
And I don't like you right there in touch
That water cooler might look better
Stop right up your butt
There's already an asshole
I can't believe you're still employed
So the company's probably damaged
But be one that can't break
There's already an asshole
You're an asshole
Oh yes
That's right
For today I am
You're an asshole
From the pod tape music network
From roadside attraction
They've got more gems like that
A 41 42 minutes perfect timing
Once again
I'm going to get out of here
Remember to text in your
Your preference
Scrunching or folding
And tomorrow I'll be back with the
Well it kind of depends on the weather
If I look outside right now
There's going to be no flying tomorrow
So it may be the
Football Friday edition early
Or I'll turn to believe the football
Friday edition late
One way or another
We'll talk to each other
DavidSourceco.com
Adam and podshow.com
Take care everybody
Bye bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Served up daily
By the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight