Ladies and gentlemen, I present Padshal's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Roses are ready. My sweater is beige. For your domain name needs, you should go to this page. GoDaddy.com.
Now, there are those among you who have wronged. There are those among you who have sinned.
But remember, the mark of the beast is 666, and the mark of the curry is 555. Now set forth congregation and bum rush the chart.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
This is D.A.C.55, a podcast of Adam Carey, who is not scared of nuclear rockets from Iran.
Because he is equipped with internet domain from GoDaddy and a cup of soldiers coffee.
Fuck you.
A poet says, just be yourself, always be true, say to some free.
You got to love me.
So we first met always give you real.
In a moment we'll never give you real.
I live alone. Give it up.
Because it's no one.
I live alone.
But courtesy of a TV log who suggested it to me lifted culture, we rock, damn, do we rock.
And also, thank you, comic strip blogger, you're intro to today's triple five or treble
five, as we would say, and United Kingdom, treble five Charlie, that was perfect, man.
It fit exactly right.
And it is daily source code, Delta Sierra Charlie, five, five, five, everybody, how
you're doing, coming to you from the Kori condo in Northern California.
It's, of course, just turned Thursday, it's 12, 20 a.m.
So kind of Wednesday night, I'm so tired, you cannot imagine tomorrow, I fly home, so
I arrive Friday, like mid morning, I'm really hoping, and I'm just trying to keep
in the vibe, through better living through chemistry, actually, using some caffeine and
other things to stay awake, and then, you know, I'm able to put myself to sleep very quickly.
So I'm hoping I'll be able to sleep on the entire flight home, I'm really looking forward
to it.
But it's been a, it's been a great stay, and I didn't have a, well, it was actually
today was a very good day, because everyone's kind of tired near the end of the week,
a little bit punchy, me in particular, yeah, then shit that's irritating you, or you're
thinking about, you get into conversations, he did debates, and I love that stuff.
That's a big part of the creative process of company building to me.
I had a great time.
A highlight of the day, I appeared on cranky geeks with John C. Dvorak.
Now, cranky geeks dot com is where you can find this show.
It's a very entertaining program.
I've been a fan of John Dvorak's for many years.
We worked together on an original pilot for Cnet back in the day when it was purely meant
for television.
Actually, it was going to be an interactive television channel.
That's a story for a whole another day.
I've been looking forward to seeing him again.
He was quite gracious as a host.
He invited me to go out to lunch after the show, and I made a really, really stupid
mistake.
Like a real rookie mistake, I was severely injured due to my loss of porn today, and let
me explain to you.
I've been waiting for the, what do they call it?
The navigation kit for the Nokia and 800 Internet tablet.
Now this is not even for sale in the stage yet.
And, you know, this is, in fact, the holder that comes with the kit, I believe, is a prototype
holder.
And I've been waiting for this thing because it got stuck at customs, and, you know, then
I got the developer device, we're going to have to give her a name, by the way.
The N800 who's going to spread her ports wide open for developers to come in and violate
her file system, let's think of a name for the N800 that would be pretty cool.
So, you know, I want the nav kit on there as well, otherwise it makes no sense what are
the developers working on if they can't develop with the real, the real deal, right?
All the stuff that's in there and functioning.
And so I get a box and I like, it's a box from Finland, you know, and this is before I
go to cranky geek.
So it's like quarter, twelve, and to be there, twelve, ten, it's just five blocks away,
so not that bad by car.
Drove Trinity, by the way, Rosie drove me, showfird me, uh, in Trinity up to, uh, up to the
swankies, if Davis offices, now it's pretty cool, and I'll arrive in style.
So I grabbed the box and like, at least I give me some of those box with, because, of course,
you know, the fins, man, they seem to have blow towards to open up this packaging, and
that's to postal packaging.
She gives me one of these brand new, um, titanium scissors, which I only know this because,
um, I found out exactly how effective they are.
I sliced open my, uh, my middle finger on my left hand.
I mean, like, really, like, and it, I could feel the blade just gliding through the flash
because it was such a brand new pair of scissors, and I want, uh, uh, and, you know,
blood is just like spouting out, literally, and luckily Carolina, who, uh, sits a reception
for us, doesn't mean she's actually a receptionist, uh, she immediately, you know, she's like,
oh, I love blood. Come on. Let me help you. I got plenty of it for you, baby.
Uh, so, uh, so the good news is it wasn't indeed the world kit that came in. It's
very happy about that. Um, the blood is, uh, the box is now somewhat blood stained, uh, and I
have a huge bandaid on my middle finger, which I'm happy to show anybody except that kind of
breaks them out when I stick it up, the middle finger that is. Um, yeah, I'll start with that
and cranky geeks, and, uh, well, so we do, uh, I had dinner with Ron and, uh, his lovely wife,
Marta, and I was nice for something done that in a couple of trips. So, uh, life is good.
It certainly is. Got some, uh, I think some more good news. I actually, I have an abundance of
stuff that I need to get to. There's so many different promos and things that I want to play
this stuff left over from yesterday show. Um, but of course, it being Thursday. Well, you know,
we, we shovel up all the food, the, all the food bar onto Fridays. So when it comes to Thursdays,
it's gotta be my girlfriend, the one who keeps my ass in shape nice and tight for the 42 years that I
am, her name is Amy Mack. It's time to ask her size, everybody. Hey, Amy. Hey, Adam,
Amy Mack. Hey, baby. Oh, I missed you so much, Amy. I missed you. Well, since you can best
to a fatness attack the other day, I'm going to play it for you. Oh, we're going to work it off
today. Uh, Mr. Amy, are you going to make me work it on down on the floor, so adjust whatever
you need to. Hey, hold on on the floor, like this, Mr. Amy. Good. These are called mountain climbers,
and you've probably done them before. Hmm. I've done lots of things before. Get in a push-up position.
So hands are your shoulders and you're up on your tiptoes. Oh, okay. Like this.
Now you're going to place your left foot up for your chest while keeping your hands in the same place.
Oh, please. This puts you in a deep launch. Yeah. And then switch those legs. Okay. Yeah.
I'm good at this. It's my fancy experience. Quickly. Yeah. Oh, yeah, run. The goal is to move fast and do as many
steps as you can. Ready? Oh, I'm going to do one of them. Okay. Oh, yes. I can do it.
Do you do a certain number of them? You're going to do as many in 30 seconds as possible?
I'm going. I'm going. Oh, hey, me. Keep breathing. Thank you for reminding me.
10 seconds down. 20 to go. Okay. I'm going, baby. I'm going as fast as I can. Do those
areas melt away. Oh, yes. It's melting. It's melting. Amy's melting. All right. 10 seconds. Oh.
Really keep those legs under you. Oh, Amy. It's happening to me. Great job. Now we
need to get that button top shape for the answer to my video. I mean, I'm thinking people will get tired
of staring at my butt. So we'll bring you in for I can. You better go find your speedo. We got to get this
thing go. Amy, I love you. Next time. Bye, bye, baby. Oh, I love you. I love you. You know I do. Are you
kidding me? You will, I mean, since we're talking about it, Amy's ass is amazing. It's triple A. It's
just like that. It's a triumphant. When is that exercise video show coming out anyway? Come on.
Let's get out of it already. Chris Mack. It's a working boy.
Okay. Hey, you know, James called in from London. And we've been talking about
network names and what kind of what is your network name and and open and unlocked. I'm talking
about wireless networks. Why if I open and and locked up networks and, you know, just the abundance
of wireless in our world. And you know, how I like to keep my network completely open so that anyone
can, you know, use it if they need to because hey, you know, so if I need a network, I'll use someone
else's. Of course, I can't find any more open networks here. And I'm on the 24th floor of the
condo and everything's locked up and closed up and James calls in. James regular color of the show.
And he, he, I think he has just a wonderful idea, a really, really wonderful idea that I believe
could become a culture, culture in the world of sharing your sharing your pipes,
your tubes, tying your tubes with your buddies. Listen to this.
Yeah, James sorted. Yeah, I think it's a beautiful idea. It's very simplistic. You know, there's a lot of
open source firmware and stuff that you can load onto your wireless access points,
Belkin and others and what what dealing and all that stuff. And, and lots of cool stuff,
actually, a whole systems where you can leave your access point open and then when someone connects
to it, you'll first get to come to a webpage. Very much like team mobile does it or a hotel
wireless system. And then from there, you can request access. But that requires real work and
crazy as work. You know, then I just, you know, it's geeks who are going to do that stuff. But the idea
of changing your network name to your email address is eloquent and simple and very nice. And I
think if I saw a wireless access point that had someone's email address in it, I believe I'd
probably email them and say, hey, dude, can I use your your access point once in a while? I really
think I would. It's a it's a simple yet very nice idea. Thank you James,
much appreciate. Adam, Alan, Britain, Basel here, long time listener. I was listening to the
five, five, two, Charlie today and a couple of things occurred to me. First of all, the piece of
music that was kind of classical. I think that was when you were having some interesting girls with
cellos. I was talking about another track from Adam's first gen iPod. Yeah, man, I love chicks
who play cellos, chicks and cellos. It's it's it's Alt it's porn. A lot of things are porn.
Opening that Nokia box was what that's what the porn that I was referring to. These are nice
when you open up a box with new gear inside. I have to say Apple boxes smell the nicest.
It really do. Anyway, back to the other porn. I remember correctly from a long, long time ago.
Anyway, moving on this whole thing with your first gen iPod made me wonder, I remember when you
went to pot-safe music and you were, well, terrified, it's probably stretching a little bit,
but you were pretty worried about the authorities coming and so in you for all that don't
license music you were playing. I just wondered what's changed. Why have you suddenly decided that
it's okay and that fear should now go away. I just wonder whether there's something happening in the
background who knows. If you're going to bring back some non-pot-safe music, I think you should
bring back young palettes head-test. That was one of the big parts of the DSC that I think a lot of
people would miss. Anyway, one other subject, you were talking about the guys comments about the
Trinity thing and the green connotations. Well, I kind of agree with some of what he's saying.
Your take phrase goes, save the world, win valuable prizes, saving the world could be
construed as being green. Anyway, there you go. Just my inputs, keep up the work of the DSC.
It's great listen to every morning on the way into work and of course folder.
Holder, of course. Hi, man, thanks. So that's, I played that because basically we've answered all
those questions or the topics that have been pretty much discussed. So if you're new to this show,
and you didn't know what that was about, you know anything, but they're all resolved. Okay,
it's all taken care of. Speaking of hot chicks with cellos, or stand-up bases, as it were.
Remember these girls? Busiveous bitties. This is Amanda Monaco,
guitarist for the Lasivia's Bitties and Bittie cast. In January 2005, I was diagnosed with multiple
sclerosis, an unpredictable inflammatory disease of the central nervous system.
Please join the Lasivia's Bitties and our team, Team Bittie. On Sunday, April 22nd, 2007
at New York City, South Street, Seaport for the MS Walk, New York City, 2007.
Go to bittiesmusic.com to join our team for the walk, or make a donation through Team Bittie.
Last year, we raised over $23,000 for MS research, and this year, our goal is $50,000.
Any donation, smaller large, is a big help in our fight. Last year, there were many small donations
from great people like you, and those small donations add up and they make a huge difference.
Thankfully, I've been doing well and living my life as I always have, but not everyone is as lucky as I am.
MS continues to strike people in the prime of their lives, and its effects can be devastating.
Visit bittiesmusic.com to walk with us, or to make a donation to help stop this disease and
find a cure. Thanks. See you at the walk.
Oh yeah, I love those girls.
Hey, is it wrong that if I told you that I've had sexual dreams about Amanda Monaco?
Actually, I think I've had fantasies about all of the bitties. Go to the side. You just see what I mean.
I presume CC's walk at a long this year. It's fantastic. I get 20 more than $23,000.
And what kills me is I was just listening to that promo.
MS has been in my lifetime, has been there throughout my entire lifetime.
You know, we've solved a lot of things. We've had all diseases come and go.
And we haven't figured this one out. We really should do this. This makes absolutely no sense.
So please participate, contribute, as you can. It would be much appreciated.
And I'm sure Amanda Monaco will let you two have fantasies about her.
Oh, yes, of course. I got feedback from our superstar actor here in San Francisco.
As I was so excited about Eric Bergen's performance in Jersey Boys here in San Francisco.
And he sent in a lengthy comment, but it's as always entertaining funny and informative. So let's
listen to what he has to say. Hey, Adam, it's Eric Bergen from the cast of Jersey Boys.
First off, thank you for Wednesday's show. It was so fantastic to hear you talk about the show
and such a positive way. I'm so, so glad you enjoyed it. I knew you would, but I was a little
worried when Tuesday night we didn't exactly get the response out of the audience because it was a
little bit older of an audience that we normally do. Usually it's like a rock concert at this show.
People just screaming and it was a little bit more reserved Tuesday night. So I am really glad
you enjoyed it and that you totally got the show and you absolutely understood it and that you identified
with it. It meant a lot to me and the cast was very excited to hear that you were in the audience.
I had to say in a personal note, this whole no one second. As you know, I didn't go back stage.
When it was hot chicks were they excited about me being there as well. I do think a follow-up
is warranted in this case, because that was a good look in girls in the, in the cast.
Whole thing has come full circle. It's absolutely hilarious. You know, back in 04, when I first
got into podcasting, I, you know, you would a first show I listened to. And it was really the
reason why I got into podcasting. And now two years later, you're doing almost a whole show about
me in Jersey Boys. It's absolutely unreal. So first of all, thank you so much for coming and
and really glad you enjoyed the show. The second thing is, I just wanted to make some
some clarifications to some of the things that you were saying about the show. You are absolutely
correct. There is a broader production and there is a San Francisco production. Both the exact
same show, two different casts. There is not currently a Vegas production like you had said,
but it is in the works. It should be happening soon. There should be details of coming out about
the Vegas production sometime in the coming months. The schedule for, for my cast is this,
we're playing San Francisco, the current theater until the middle of May. I'm sorry to the middle
of April. I should clarify. What's happening from mid-April to mid-May? I'm not quite sure yet.
Starting in mid-May, we are going to be playing the almonds in theater in Los Angeles. And
that's going to take us through the entire summer. After that, we're not sure what's happening.
Or should I say, we are sure what's happening. We're just not allowed to say it yet. A third
production of Jersey Boys will be opening up in Chicago this fall. You can check out all the
information about the two touring casts at jerseyboystor.com. For information on the Broadway cast,
you can check out jerseyboysBroadway.com. There also isn't announcement coming about coming out soon
about my cast of Jersey Boys. We have a upcoming big appearance that Adam, I know I've told you about,
but don't say anything. I'll let you know when you can say something and you can tell to all your
viewers because it is going to be a blast. It's very exciting for all of us. The other thing I wanted
to mention is the person playing Frankie Valley that you saw was not actually Christopher Kale Jones,
like you had said. The person you saw was Jared Specter. We have an alternate actor who plays Frankie
Valley on Tuesday nights and Wednesday, Matt Nays because the role of Frankie Valley is so hard,
we give our normal guy a couple more days off than everyone else. Damn him. But it's just because
he has to sing 27 songs back to back all in his fall setto and it's really just a bit of a role.
So we need to give our Frankie some relaxation time. So yeah, that's pretty much it. And again,
thank you so much for coming. I'm so glad you enjoyed it. You can check out more information
on me at Eric, ERICH, Bergen, B-E-R-G-E-N dot com and check out my podcast, greenroomradio dot com.
And I know Adam you told him to go fuck podcasting, but I still like it way too much.
Oh and last before you get to that, let me just say a couple things because we're about to say
goodbye to our serious satellite listeners. Dude, you should be in the Broadway production.
I think you've got what it takes. Several other members of the cast that I saw as well, I would have
to say. In addition to that, if that wasn't the normal guy, holy crap, that's your backup guy.
He was good. And I really also like the casting of this, just in general, the way you guys look.
And it was fantastic. Again, my recommendation to go see the show.
A serious satellite radio listeners, thank you for sticking with me. I'll talk to you tomorrow with
who are Friday. Let's hear the last bit here from America, because it's a personal message.
You know, I should just say, I just talked to my mother and she's also a huge fan of your show.
And she was so excited to hear, you know, she literally screamed on the phone,
which she heard you talk about, Jersey was. She's a podcaster herself in a damn good one at that.
In fact, tomorrow, she is celebrating one year of podcasting. Her podcast is called craftcast.
It's at craftcast.com. That's craftcast.com. It's for anyone who's interested in crafting,
decopaging, knitting, sewing, you name it, whatever. It's a fantastic podcast if you're domestic,
like my mother. And it's you hot. Happy birthday, mom. You know, one year of podcasting.
Okay, Adam, that's about it for me. I have to go do two shows today. Good Lord.
That was not just in. Oh, and one more thing. Oh, Eric Bogen. Yeah, scruncher. Oh, wow.
It's surprising. Uh-huh. Hmm. Okay. This changes my view a bit on the scrunchers.
Hey, Eric Mac, good luck. Good luck to you. And thanks for the invite for coffee, but
it's just no fucking way. I just, I can't swing it. I'll be back probably in about three weeks.
Going to do a New York trip and then come back. I'm also going to a North Carolina
for a, and that's on the, was it the 9th, I think, or the 10th, or the 11th, I don't know what
date is. I have a special cameo in what will be the, the next episode of Port City, P.D.
So I'm quite flattered by that. I'm looking forward to going to North Carolina.
I'll, I have no idea how much time I'm going to have while I'm there. I have no idea. I haven't seen
a script. Maybe we don't have a script. Maybe I'm just getting killed. You know, I have no idea.
But if there is time, and maybe we can, you know, I'm sure there's people in North Carolina,
we can hang out with Sandra naked pictures. Let me see. There's a couple more things here.
You know, really stuff that I wanted to, I wanted to play during the sound light window.
I'm sorry. I was disgusting. Okay. I'll save all this for tomorrow. It's kind of good. You know,
it don't send me anything unless it's food bar specific stuff. Because I've got enough
promos. Don't send anything for tomorrow. Well, it doesn't matter. It's okay. Send me whatever you want.
It's just do whatever you want. Okay. Let's, uh, let's do this. I heard I, I, I,
it's not much more left than me. Uh, sorry. It's time to, uh, hold on. I know idea what that was.
But that, of course, is my, uh, is my first gen iPod. It's time for another track from Adam's
first gen iPod. As you know, I've got this iPod. I've had it since 2004. I haven't said,
I started working on this thing that turned out to be podcasting. There's all kinds of stuff on it.
There's everything from audiobooks to production elements to podcasts to some of my favorite songs
from the 70s because on this first iPod, this is where I put all the stuff that I collected on
Napster when it was still a thriving system. So, uh, without further ado, let me grab the first
gen iPod and hit play. It's completely at random. Oh, wow. It's going to be too long to play in the
whole show. But it's, it's a, it's a George Carlin live on HBO. Wow. That's the surprise. No music at all.
Let's listen to the genius, the master. I bought this off audible.com. I remember that much.
Okay. Maybe just listen to, uh, opening piece then, okay?
Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate that. Thank you. Thank you. So,
let me ask you something. Let me ask you. How's everybody doing tonight? Hi.
Good. Well, fuck you. Just trying to make you feel at home.
Listen, I've been out here all this time, and I haven't been complaining about anything yet. So,
I think it's time to go into the complaint department. This is just a series of things that are
pissing me off. Okay. Let's just, let's just listen to this one together. Okay?
Please, that are pissing me off. Because I don't remember Thursdays. I have major psychotic fucking
hatreds, okay? And it makes the world a lot easier to sort out. First thing on my list tonight,
airport security tired of this shit. There's too much of it. There's too much security at the airport.
I'm tired of some guy with a double digit IQ and a triple digit income,
rooting around inside of my bag for no reason and never finding anything.
Haven't found anything yet. Haven't found one bomb in one bag. And don't tell me,
well, the terrorists know their bags are going to be searched, so now they're leaving their
bond at home. There are no bombs. The whole thing is fucking pointless.
It's completely without logic. There's no logic at all. They'll take away a gun but let you
keep a knife. Well, what the fuck is that? In fact, there's a whole list of lethal objects they
will allow you to take on board. Theoretically, you can take a knife, a knife, a nice pick, a hatchet,
a straight razor, a pair of scissors. Oh, this is so early. Oh, this is so early.
Knitting needles and a broken whiskey bottle. And the only thing they're going to say to you is
that bag has to fit all the way under the seat in front of you. That is kind of interesting, though.
I'll, I'm going to play a little bit more of this. And actually, I know that I've played this
on one of the early early early daily source codes. The title of the, the specialist, you're all
diseased. But clearly, this was a pre 9-11. Oh, kind of interesting, though, isn't it?
Of course, airport security still didn't work. He was right about that.
If you wouldn't take a weapon on board, relax. After you've been flying for about an hour,
they're going to bring you a knife and fork. They actually give you a fucking knife.
It's only a table knife, but you could kill a pilot with a table knife.
Might take you a couple of minutes, you know, especially if he's hefty, huh?
Yeah, but you could get the job done. You really want the killer prick.
Shit, there's a lot of things you could use to kill a guy with. You could probably beat a
guy to death with a Sunday New York Times, couldn't you? Or suppose you just had really big hands.
Couldn't you a straangle of flight attendant? Shit, you could probably straangle two of them one
with each hand. You know, if you were lucky enough to catch him in that little kitchen area,
before they give out the fucking peanuts, you know? But you can get the job done if you're really
cared enough. So why isn't they allow a man with big, powerful hands to get on board an airplane?
I'll tell you why. They know he's not a security risk because he's already answered the three
big questions. Question number one, did you pack your bags yourself?
No, carrot top pack my bags.
He and Martha Stewart and Florence Henderson came over to the house last night.
Fixed me a lovely lobster new bird gave me a full body massage with sacred oils from India
performed a four way around the world and then they packed my bags. Next question.
All right, that was a little bit from Adam's first gen iPod.
And since there was no music on that track, I'll play some for the young man.
That's a world of lamb ribs.
Hell felt like you were moving on, moving on to some new.
Feel something took out your heart. Hell is nothing you can do.
And you watch and know why I'm staying.
Oh, I'm feeling a sway. Hell yeah.
Hell my role to love you.
Hell my role to feel a little way I do.
Hell yeah how mature by a lot Saint's
No I know this is true.
So the screams got me getting into you.
Hell is nothing you can do.
And you watch and know why I'm staying.
Who I am feeling this way, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
What you want around to stay here is I'm feeling this way
Hey hey hey have you I'm wrong to love with you
I am her on for feeling her way I do
Am my roles Her role for love and you
Am her role for love and you
Am I roles for love and you
Am her role for feeling her way
I guess you're right to
Am my roles for love and you
Laugh andI- eternity
Am I wrong for loved and you
See her in the way I do
Probably
In my room to love you
In my room for feeling what I do
And she's going to love me
Nice
Okay, I'm hooked up
Officially booked
Too bad about the fade out
Great song, but why doesn't have to fade out?
End it
Okay, that'll do it for today's show
Links for the songs you heard
And other stuff in the show notes
DailySourcecode.com
Send me an email
Adam at podshow.com
And I think
By the time I get home
I'll be able to switch over the curry.com
Domain as well to
Or at least the email portion of it
To the new
Super Uber Google office
Hey, thanks for listening
Take care yourself, bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best and the brightest served up
Daily by the sharpest minds
In content delivery
Potshow and lightweight