Hi everybody. How you doing? It's Adam here at the Curry Cottage, and of course the
affluent suburb of Serino and his Guilford still on the east side of town. As we're
in the middle of the big move of 2007, and I've got another best of Charlie lined up for
you today. That's what we've been filling the feed with for this past week and we'll do
so for next week as well. Listeners, fans, other podcasts have been so incredibly kind
of putting together these shows that I call the best of Charlie. Essentially, a highlights
of previous shows that anyone who wants to put together a show like, and they're really
interesting montages. It's very, very cool to hear what people find relevant, interesting,
funny, intriguing it. By the way, you hear that in the background. It's the last time you're
going to, or one of the last times you're going to hear that. That's the garbage guys backing up
the truck again. I wonder, I don't even know what the garbage schedule is at the new place.
Anyway, things are a little bit tense around the Cottage. Patricia definitely does not,
does not like a mess. She's very organized, as I'm sure you can tell from her personality.
The thing she really doesn't like is when she's cleaning stuff up and other people make a mess
around her. That wouldn't be me that would be more the teenager that is making the mess.
Somehow, I seem to get the brunt of the fallout, though. There you go. It's the glass, man.
It's okay, though. Things are going quite smoothly. Thank you, several people who emailed
it and said that the vote of phone, wireless broadband, USB-Dongol is actually a pretty darn good
solution, and we'll probably work out just fine for me for the week or maybe two weeks that
will be without broadband in the new place. Nothing new to mention about big brother. Other than that,
I was of course completely wrong about Dark Benedict. I'm not even going to get into it now,
but I thought he was in battle-star Galactica. No, it wasn't that. It wasn't that. It wasn't
that shit. Hold on a second. I'll look it up, because you know who, of course, emailed me.
Brittany Mason. She always knows exactly what's going on. Hold on.
Here we go. Dark Benedict. He was star-buck on battle-star Galactica. Not buck Rogers. There you go.
That was Jill Gerard. Okay. Thank you, Brittany. I knew you'd set me straight, girl.
But yeah, nothing really happened of any importance. I'm very intrigued about your main
jacks, and I can't wait to find out more about this guy and what he's like other than the
two times I've met him. We're seeing very sweet, very nice, very personal, actually a little bit shy.
Of course, he's got a lot of the Michael Jackson freak juice sprayed all over him, so we'll see how
that turns out. Anyway, oh, by the way, I got my my tax disc squared away. After all that,
after all that bullshit turns out I was able to do it right online through direct.gov.uk slash
tax disc. I was done in like four minutes. Today's best of Charlie is done as produced by Chris
Daily, a host of the Pod Music Countdown, the PMC Top 10. I put together a very cool show,
despite that he was definitely under the weather. He'll tell you all about that.
So thank you with advance Chris. And of course, I do want to remind you that great deals on
domain names can be had at godaddy.com. Use checkout code dsc3 for fantastic deal.
And if you have not yet checked out, stop the podcast.com, please do it's all about the new
movie, stop the yard, which opens up on January 12th. It's going to be a major smash.
Okay, I'm pretty sure I'm going to check in over the weekend as well, even though there may not
be a best of Charlie, but I'm back to doing a lot of blogging. You might want to check out
Curry.com, which soon I hope to actually switch over to the new blogging platform at Pod Show,
which has not been entirely released, but if you check it out now, you'll see that already. We have
a pretty cool editor and some new stuff in there. And I'm already rambling on much, much, much longer
than I intended to. So enjoy. Today's best of Charlie number five, and I'll talk to you guys
over the weekend. Bye. Well, hold on a second. I suck. Okay, it was just a new setup. Here we go.
Boc number five. Enjoy everybody.
Hey, welcome back to the PMC Top 10. Wait a minute. This isn't the pod music countdown.
Daily source code. In fact, it's a best of Charlie episode hosted by yours truly the
C dog Chris daily. And if I seem to have a little bit more berry white in my voice right now,
it's because I woke up with some serious throat issues. I think and strip throat or something coming
on. But hey, I promised Adam I would get this show. So hey, I'm going to do it, man. I just took a
big swig at this bucklies cough syrup. And let me tell you that stuff is horrible. But I said I'm going
to deliver. So I'm going to. You see Adam, you see what I do for you? Now, most of you know that I host
the official countdown show of the pod safe music scene, the PMC Top 10. Each week I count down the
top 10 songs being spun by podcasters all over the planet. While my staff is busy compiling
stats from all the great music sources like the pod safe music network. I owed a magnitune,
pod safe audio.com, garage band, and many more. I get the very, very cool task of listening
to the great music podcast. You know the ones, those influential podcasters that helped determine
the success of some of these great indie artists. No list of influential music podcasters would
be complete without the podfather Adam Curry. Whether he's breaking songs to the public for the
very first time or just pumping the great stuff. He hears on other music pod guests. His DSC plays
a big part in the drama we call pod safe music. One of the artists that benefited greatly from Adam's
Pampage was Howard Jones. This is from the October 23rd, DSC. Found the Howard Jones is on the pod
tech music network. Howard Jones, of course, have been playing his records ever since I was 19.
And looking at the picture of him on the pod safe music network. He's lost a lot of hair since
then. It's like receded all the way back. But it's great. And there's a little blurb up here.
He has released one track, which he put up yesterday, released for podcasters to promote the
forthcoming UK hitmakers tour with ABC and Toya, a world tourist to follow in 2007.
When playing this track, please include tour details. And this link. Oh, hold on. podcast live.
Oh, I see. There's, um, oh, interesting. Let's see if we can open this up. What is this link?
That's kind of that's an interesting way to do that to promote something on the pod save music
network. Hold on. This link is a little messed up. Will it fit tour dates dot pdf? Cool.
Oh, we have a 404 arrow at the fuck is that? And I can't be right. Hold on.
H j two or d h dot pdf. Looks like I'm, um, shy. Let me just go look at that home page.
I'll see if there's anything there about how our Jones tour dates.
Well, there's a link to podcast live dot code.uk. But there's the link that, uh, how our Jones
put in the pod save music network is not working, um, not to look into that. Okay, so we'll find
out what the tour dates are in the meantime. I wanted to take a listen to the song because it's,
I really liked it. It's kind of like classic Howard Jones, but modernized. Oh, no 80's
got just rocking, building our own future. From the pod save music network, Howard Jones,
D.S.C. or paints 3.
So take a step in this place
God will accompany our own future
Just roll out for a day by day
We need to choose a life that stands for all of us
Putting people's heads at the top
It's the first incitemeration
Changing in the heart of just one
A lot of things will tighten things up
Don't give it up
To the face of the force
Around us we decide
Between the end and the outside
So take a step in this place
God will accompany our own future
Just roll out for a day by day
We need to choose a life that stands for all of us
Sons of God as we
Mothers and fathers, brothers and sisters and brothers
All in the middle of the way
Comes in the rest of the world
So take a step in this place
God will accompany our own future
Just roll out for a day by day
We need to choose a life that stands for all of us
Sons of God as we go
So take a step in this place
God will accompany our own future
Just roll out for a day by day
We need to choose a life
We need to choose a life that stands for all of us
Sons of God as we go
See how tall is it, rock?
Our Jones of that
It's a great way of producing the
Kind of that snare
Back
Very typical for him, sounds lovely
Building our own future, Howard Jones
You can find it on music.podshow.com
To the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
I found it, so I'll put that link into the show notes for the PDF
There was a little space that snuck in there accidentally
Howard will be performing at the Historic Avalon Theatre
Yeah, building our own future
Finished up number 10 on the recently released
Top Sons of 2006
Which can be found at www.podmusiccountdown.com
It's spent an amazing four weeks at number one
And it could have gone much longer
Had it not been for the whole Christmas season
Pushing everybody out
90% of everything is
Krud
Sturgeon's Law
The podcast dedicated to the 10% of everything
That isn't Krud
I want to make fast running zombies
Like you see in 28 days later
The gender and biguous old and wizard
That's why he runs across cab drivers
And don't have shops
I like diet so much
I buy 10,000 copies at a time
In enormous hall
With aircraft everywhere you look
www.sturgeon'slaw.com
This is a different thing
It's spontaneous, it's called wit
Wow, my throat is killing me
I really hope you're enjoying your vacation Adam
I hope it's worth it
One of the most popular songs
In the entire history of podcasting
Matthew Ebel's drive away
From DSC number 370
Back in April
I'm the idiot European
Oh
On a day like today when you've got
Sunshine breaking through the clouds
Ah, there's all the driving along
I need some top-down driving around music
There's only one song that comes to mind
That will satisfy Matthew Ebel
And drive
There's a time when nothing stood in between us
Now there's a curve in the world
So sharp it'll make you bleed
We don't talk with just punks to clap
Can't bend each other in the same old rhythm
Like maybe a little scheme
What we need
We love and you work like a dog
Every morning
The city's a pain like the loud taste
Staying on your dress
Hidden the band before you raked in
And don't cost the band to leave this town
You're on the road
Because we gotta get out of this mess
So let's drive away
Let the sunlight chase us all day
Now there's nothing going to stand in a way
Let's drive away
There's a word in the song
We're gonna took it for granted
But bumping the road, not really apart of the drive
Come on, come on, it's all right
You made me believe tonight
The verb makes you so damn good to be alive
Oh, so let's drive away
Let the sunlight chase us all day
Now there's nothing going to stand in a way
Let's drive away
Drive away
Sorry, but I've seen fast, but I gotta be going
Gotta be more than the coffee shops in the bar
Lady, lady, it's still good
Lady, baby, it's just me
Lady, you take my hand and get in the car
More and more close to this town
And wait
Let the sunlight chase us all day
Baby, that's all I got to find
I gotta say, baby, it's just me
Drive away
Let the sunlight chase us all day
Now there's nothing going to stand in a way
Okay, here we are just arriving at Ferrox Airport
Not too bad today
About 30 minutes
Just to be expected, just a little bit of traffic on the M25
It's really busy here today
There's a thriving aviation community at this airport
Alan Mann, helicopter's a station here
So there's always a ton of helicopter traffic
And there's lots of cars parked out
The weather's a lot quite as nice here as
It is near the cottage
I'll just pull up here
Now with any luck
My request to pull the plane out of the hanger
Has been granted
So let me get all my stuff
And walk over, pre flight the airplane
Find Jason and do some flying
Talk about your staying power
Drive away, finished as the number four song in 2005
And the number 12 song of 2006
No other song has even come close to that
That is off his amazing album, Bearing Coffee
I cannot recommend that album enough
Be sure to check out the most recent episode of the pod music countdown
At pod music countdown.com for this
And all the top songs of 2006
And then while you're at it, go ahead and subscribe
So that each week you can hear the top songs from the previous week
Hey, this is Jersey Todd of the Jersey Todd Show
at www.JersyTodShow.com
And right now you're listening to the top pod safe tunes
Being spun by podcasters on the PMC top 10
With my man The Seedog
Check it out
One of the things I really like to do on the PMC top 10
Is to promo great shows
It's my little way of thanking the great podcasters out there
That are making this revolution happen
Alright, well I'm going to break from format here just a little bit
And I'm going to play a song that has never been in the pod music countdown
It's a song I would never get to play
Because my shows carried on several terrestrial radio stations
So we've got those FCC rules and all that stuff
Yeah, you know those right?
Yeah, this is a song the FCC won't let me play
And hey Adam I have to thank you for letting me play with
My enormous penis
Literally in every continent
Ships it C tuned in
That's fine as long as my mother doesn't listen to that
And all the rest of the Chinese people won't understand what I'm saying
Here we go
Alright
When ever life gets you down
Keeps you wearing a frown
And the gravy trainers left you behind
And when you're all out of hope
Down at the end of your rope
And nobody's there to throw you online
If you ever get so low that you don't know which way to go
Come on and take a walk in my shoes
Never worry about a thing
Got the world on a string
Cause I've got the cure for all of my
All of his blues
I take a look at my enormous penis
And my troubles start to melt away
And the happy times are coming to stay
I gotta sing it on dance
When I glance in my pants
And I've done it like a sunshiney day
I take a look at my enormous penis
And everything is going my way
I'm bummed
I take a look at my enormous penis
And my troubles start to melt away
And I've done it like a thermal scan
And I take a look at my enormous penis
Look at my enormous peanuts, and I have it as a comment to see.
Yeah, I got great big amounts in the place where it comes,
and the feeling like a sunshiney day.
I take a look at my enormous peanuts, and everything is going my way.
We're bobbing time now, everything is going my way.
Hey, look at these cool birds.
Hey, everything is going my way.
Hey, do I want?
Hey, this is going my way.
Wow.
I guess there was the bobbing time machine.
Nice.
One of the smash hits of 2006 was the band The Shakes,
and nothing was bigger for them than Liberty Jones.
It was the number four song of the year after 15 huge weeks in the chart,
including two at number one.
And since Adam overlapped Jeff Smith's satellite repair man,
Jingle, with the intro to the song back in this July episode,
you get Uncle Jesse's theme song as well.
Consider it a bonus.
Alright, thank you very much.
Well, of course, if you're having troubles,
there's only one guy who could really come down
to help you get your porn reception back in order.
His name is Uncle Jesse.
He's the satellite repair man.
He's coming after you.
I'm satellite repair man.
What's he gonna do?
He'll fit your missing sections,
and answer questions too.
He's nothing in the universe
and he can't move for you.
I'm satellite repair man.
What?
Here it is.
I need your money.
Heavenly Liberty Jones
Works in the shop that she owns
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in
Just because she don't like to drive
Take to see a stud fine
And tease her thoughts out of sight
To the river at night
Here is a sea of something
Why don't you come for me and take me away
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
She's got a big night
And it's a name wouldn't lie
Things are only designed
Here's a sea of something
Why don't you come for me and take me away
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
And tease her thoughts out of sight
Lessons to music like swing
When there's no customers in Just because she don't like to drive
Lessons To music like swing
Lessons to music like swing
I want to thank the music podcasters for pimping this great music, and I want to thank the
listeners for leading the way in the revolution called podcasty. Be sure to subscribe to the
PMC Top 10 at podmusiccountdown.com. Until next time, I'm your temporary daily source code host
Chris Daily reminding you to keep it real.
Get this piece of the show and more great ones like it on the BT Podshow Media Network.
Powered by Podshow and Limelight Network. Control your part in the show at
BT Podshow.com.