This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
A stupid fucking mistake is ruining the whole fucking day.
It's the onion radio news. This is Doyle Redland reporting.
Local man Matt Harbert can't believe his shitty fucking luck today.
After missing the goddamn express bus, which has now ruined his entire fucking day.
Harbert says this shit hit the fan when he arrived ten minutes late.
Missing a major ass phone call that could end up costing him his goddamn fucking job.
I'm so fucked.
Gowork or Monica Weinberg, however, says Harbert just needs to relax.
It's not the fucking end of the world.
Harbert now fears that his fucked up day could spill over into the evening and on into the foreseeable future,
eventually fucking up the remainder of his sorry ass life.
Doyle Redland for the onion radio news.
Delta's year, Charlie six seven nine.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped by ass.
To the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm podcasting his bedroom curry.
I've run the mountains.
It's still the ice.
Release the fire.
It's my problem way.
Don't take me down.
I saw the shadows.
Oh, David Godz.
Whispering answers.
That's time for time.
For him but true.
I'm frozen blue.
There's not much time.
It's not the fucking end of the world.
It's not the fucking end.
We all betrayed you.
You're not the world.
There's not much time
All right, why you're properly depressed now?
Well, it's a good shit, baby.
Lilian Axe from the Pod Safety's Ignatwork and Artica Kickin' Off Episode
Number 679 of the Daily Storms Code coming to you from the Apple and Suburb of Surrey,
known as Kilford on the west side of G-town.
We're up in the attic, it's the Curry Manor.
Your Daily Source Code is on.
In the world, we're women where comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you get your entertainment.
This is the Pod Show Network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
I don't know why I did that, I just felt like playing a jingle after I set off.
Everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to your show.
It's another beautiful day in Blighty.
I've got the windows wide open.
It's almost like spring, but yet it reminds me very much of Autumn in New Jersey.
And I can almost imagine going into New York,
and it would be a little bit colder than it is, actually.
Chestnuts starting to roast.
Hey, hey.
Is it almost time yet?
We're not quite in November yet, are we?
Because that's when we got officially started playing all the Christmas songs.
You know how that works?
I'm sorry.
Holiday tunes.
Oh yeah.
So thanks to PG Kelly for the opening one times there from the Onion Radio.
That's awesome.
That's a great way to start it off today.
Roll and ride into Lilian Axe.
Because you know, I don't get a lot of, even though I'm online all day,
and I'm connected, I really don't have a lot of time to go around surfing.
This pastime that people have called Googling,
running around the internet and finding cool stuff,
and it has become a pastime.
Of course, I'm on the internet all day,
and I have a social network, which is essentially email.
That's still what it is to me.
I've just not been able to win everybody that I work with off of email.
It's just, you know, I can see where Christina doesn't need email anymore.
She has one email address that she used to send me crap to print out for her for school work.
Or I should say, or where I shouldn't say crap.
But otherwise, it's all Facebook.
I think she still does some my space.
I'm not quite sure.
I'll have to get a ratio from her.
So my social network is of course email,
and I get all kinds of stuff sent to me,
and it's really great.
But on the other hand, it's almost sometimes it's depressing.
Anyway, an update on that story that we've been following about the fake FEMA press conference.
Now, of course, for those of you who haven't followed along,
FEMA, the Federal Emergency Management Agency,
who are responsible for emergencies, such as Katrina,
while we know how that well they did on that.
They're also responsible for managing the emergency in California.
Now, I believe the whole state is in a state of emergency.
I think that's the official status.
The FEMA, of course, responsible for helping,
can you put the fires out and managing the entire crisis.
They sent, they set up a press conference,
sent out word to the press core 15 minutes before it was bound to start,
which, of course, was a complete set up.
And since they were no actual members of the press,
as far as I know, none were in the press room,
they just had some FEMA people ask the questions.
And what was it, Pat Filbin?
You just answered the questions.
So anyway, this, of course,
caused quite an outrage in an uproar.
And so he's, he didn't get fired,
but he was scheduled to become director of public affairs for
National Intelligence Director Mike McConnell.
And that apparently is not happening.
Looks like he got set back for,
you know, it's what a bloody,
with the bloody cheek of this guy.
A FEMA in general to do this.
So anyways, I go from the FEMA story.
I run into, you know, other things about this,
a company called Blackwater,
which you've probably heard about.
And I'm going to talk about that a bit today.
I'm going to try and stay off of the Ron Paul trip.
Although I got a call from Ron Paul's finance director.
Probably.
They want my check.
I told him November 5th is when I'm sending it.
Remember, remember the fifth of November gunpowder trees
and a plot.
Send your money to RonPaul208.com
and your country.
You will not have forgotten.
Yeah.
I made a rhyme on that.
I have high shelves.
I've a ceiling.
I left you very drunk.
Nice six shelves.
Oh man.
Charles, did you ever?
I wish I, maybe I saved it.
You were so hammered dude.
And it was just like this,
it was, it was funny,
but then it got unfunny because it just didn't stop.
And you were like really falling over yourself.
So I didn't play that one.
But yes, you did call Charles.
This is Charles, our drunkard London friend.
I better known as Charles, the drunkard Londoner.
My calls, messages.
So I remember being on the phone.
The morning after, the one who was I called.
So yeah, I hoped what I said wasn't rude or whatever.
But yeah, that was me being drunk Londoner.
I'm loving the dialogue you wrote me up about the US Constitution.
It makes me think a little bit more about our own situation in this country.
And how I really ought to educate myself a little bit more.
I'm a 33-year-old man who, I don't even know how many counties are in England.
I certainly couldn't name them.
When I really couldn't, which is EGAC.
So when people talk about American ignorance, then they do.
In their own ignorance.
I think they really ought to be looking at themselves as they say.
When one's like, you just pointy forwards there are three pointing back at them or four maybe.
So yeah, I don't want to end message with your latest sign off,
which I've only just tapped into because of in a way for a while.
But what I will say is do our intellectuals.
Or do we see stuff?
Let's see whether you've got any Swedish listeners and words.
It can talk to my boy.
I want it.
There you go.
Sounds like you gave me the blue version of the Elskady.
So I handed off the, actually I sent the link to the Ron Paul interview.
Daily source code 672 are a UK press agency.
And evil Alan Kingston does this part of the assignment.
And really interesting what he got back is,
you know, what he did is, actually here's, I'll just read parts of his email.
I put together a transcript of the saline quotes,
which I hope would interest the UK press.
That's not been successful in getting them to run with the story.
Which, of course, is okay.
You know, I thought it might be interesting.
It might be good for the show.
It might be good for Ron Paul.
It might be good for the Constitution in general.
It might be good for the English reading public to learn a little bit about what's going on.
The reactions as Alan has been pretty lukewarm.
The message from all the press I've been to that if and when,
Dr. Ron becomes a serious presidential candidate.
Then of course, they'll be interested in him.
But right now, they say, isn't too much interest to their UK reader since most are unaware of him.
Well, that's a chicken in the egg.
I've heard one.
And do which, of course, I say, that's interesting.
He got like a 35% rating in the, in the most recent Republican GOP presidential debate in Florida,
which was the highest of all of them.
But okay, so marginalization, I think, is what they call it.
And here's the interesting part.
A couple of newspapers made the point that he has consistently said things about the US maintaining an isolationist style worldwide,
which is not true.
You can, you can equated to an isolationist style.
But that's not the message.
I don't think he's ever said that.
To go on, pulling all the troops home and ceasing to be the world's policeman.
Yes, but why the reason why is was very interesting.
It's a very different reason though, any other candidate is using.
The press said they consequently, the consequently,
the consequently, Ron Paul said nothing new in hence newsworthy as far as they are concerned.
You losers.
Oh, well, I tried.
Here you go.
So clearly the British press, much more interested in Madeline McCain.
That's that story.
That's what's the story now that the parents of this poor child use some of their.
Madeline fund, which is donations from people to pay their mortgage.
And so, okay, so what do you, what the fuck is going on with the press over here, man?
You guys are obsessed with this fucking story.
Patricia was telling me yesterday, she said, oh, it was so horrible.
There was this, she did see some new story probably on BBC about hundreds of kids who were being kidnapped from poor countries.
And then brought back to the UK, I think, is where they were being brought to.
And being sold at easy adoptions.
And I said, what do you mean?
You're kind of like the Madonna thing.
I think she actually did the official way, but okay.
And, you know, she's like, oh, that's so horrible.
And I say, yes.
And how come that's lemon on the front page of the newspaper every day?
You know, why is it all about one white child?
Just the questions I asked myself.
So, yeah, you know what, let's get into this,
what's going to this, these videos that I've been watching that have been sent to me through email.
Right after this, this promo, which would get you off.
Hi, this is Michelle from Whisper Pearls and Michibelle's Hollywood.
When I first conceived with the golden path of love,
I imagined Shaharazad telling erotic stories to her lover,
to keep him aroused until the next time she met him.
I hope you have the same experience when you listen.
Golden path dot pot show dot com.
May it fulfill your every fantasy.
That's part of pot show press books dot pot show dot com.
This is cool, man.
We got so many great things to listen to.
I'm going to San Francisco tomorrow.
So I'm going to load up.
I got a whole bunch of audio novels that I want to take with me and listen to on the plane.
I'm going to load them into the end 800 since it has the best battery light of every any device I have.
Oh, holy moly, almost forgot to tell you the Mac.
It came back to life, of course.
I, um, I configured it.
I've installed everything.
I've got time machine, which is the automatic backup.
That's all working now.
I've restarted it a million times to make sure that the, the dreaded OS X setup assistant
doesn't come back.
I got to tell you, I am totally, totally loving it.
The speed is, uh, you know, it's, it's really, it's what I wish Red Hat was, you know, 10 years ago when we were banging around on, you know, on, on cheap hardware with with Linux installed.
And I don't know, man, I just had, it has it.
It, uh, as I've said before, it takes all the boxes.
Now, um, incorrectly, the guys in the Apple store said that the new boot camp in Leopard that you could run Windows and OS X side by side.
And I said, are you sure?
I thought you had to reboot and then, you know, you could use one of the other.
No, no, no, he was very certain that you could run both.
And I'm pretty sure that he was confused because I had access it.
I mean, I want to copy a parallels.
So, uh, I'll pick that up when I'm in San Francisco.
I'll have the guys at the office install.
We have, you know, sight licenses and all that crap.
So that'll be easy.
You can probably do it that way.
Um, but I don't even know if I'm going to use the Windows side of things.
I mean, the only reason I really use Windows.
Oh, my goodness, excuse me.
Oh, I know what I'll do.
Run Paul every time I burp.
That'll help you.
I use Casplastron Windows.
Of course, that's pretty much what I, you know, the main reason I'm using Windows.
And this, the new Mac Leopard, man, the way it finds Windows machines and, and mounts,
uh, other drives and shared folders is quite phenomenal.
What a, what a beautiful interface.
So happy with it.
So, uh, I will of course install that so that I couldn't get Casplastro up and running.
But, um, I also went out and I looked for, you know, there is some improvement in the, in the OS,
10 in the Apple Mac category of programs you can use to create podcasts.
And, uh, one really, the one that I like the most, which, uh,
uh, now it's only half of what Casplastro does is called sound bite.
And with sound bite, you can basically load up just tons and tons of buttons that you can fire off.
Very much like what Casplastro does for Windows.
Um, and, you know, there's some, you can set keys for shortcuts and there's all kinds of little,
little things that have improved.
I've seen this program before over the past couple of years, but it's really improved quite a bit.
Uh, and it really works, um, phenomenally well.
And there's lots of nice interface customization you can do.
Of course, it doesn't have the other side of what Casplastro has,
which is the recording part.
Um, and Casplastro's pretty bulletproof because it's, uh,
even if your home machine crashes up until the point where you're recording,
it has written it to a temp file.
So you can get temp.mp3 and it'll always work.
And of course, that's been a big problem with, uh, with the Mac audio hijack pro.
I know that, um, in the past, I'm not sure about now, but in the past,
if you, if it would crash, it would basically screw up your whole recording.
So I'm looking for a good recorder.
And I may even just try some experiments, see if I can get everything working
and the show running the way I wanted to with, with only Mac apps.
So I'll keep you posted on that.
I probably try that out in San Francisco.
Anyway, so the first link I got, uh,
but I wanted to talk to you about was from, uh,
Poppy Moreno.
And, uh, Poppy's, uh, and Poppy's emailed me in the past before,
and the subject of the email, please watch this.
You should have this woman on your show, and I'm like, oh, yes.
But that's because she's just hot.
She freely is.
She looks a little bit like one of my cousins back when she was hot.
And my cousin's still hot, I guess.
Kind of.
Yeah.
We're all old now.
So we get less hot.
Uh, her name is Naomi Wolfe.
And she's written a book called The End of America, which, um,
I'm hoping to pick up while I'm state side.
I was thinking of ordering a via Amazon, but I'm sure I can pick it up somewhere
by the bookstore.
And it, well, the title kind of says it all.
It's a real uplifting title.
The end of America.
But, um, essentially, this, this video is a speech of hers.
And it lasts about 45, actually 48 minutes.
It's quite long.
And in this speech, she goes through the 10 things that every
desperate or dictator or fascist has done to shut down democracy and free society
in an effort to take over that country in the world.
And she compares, of course, to Hitler, Stalin, Mussolini, these,
these are the main guys.
And she puts the Bush administration into that.
And when she goes through all of these 10 different steps that have to be taken,
which often have the exact words, such as embedded journalists.
Uh, this is something that, uh,
Gubbles, um, pioneered for the Nazis, uh,
literally the word embedded journalists.
Uh, what was another really good one?
Um, sleeper cells, which was used by Stalin.
And sleeper cells actually, when used in the context of when Stalin
invented this concept, was supposed to be, uh, us.
You know, uh, like those crazy, uh, capitalist.
And they were going to all of a sudden, you know, live amongst the Russians and,
and dressed like the Russians in one day just pop up and we take over Russia
from the inside.
Sound familiar?
But the one that really caught my eye was about black water.
And I've been hearing about black water often on it is a private security firm
that by now has over a billion dollar government contract
to provide, quote, security, uh, to,
I guess it's diplomats in Iraq.
Now, I'm not quite sure how many, how many of these rent army guys there are.
I've heard people say 30,000 have heard others say 100,000.
What was most interesting to me is that when Naomi Wolf compares black water
to, um, the Mussolini's black shirts, hitlers, brown shirts,
um, it sounds so much like TSA, like Homeland Security, uh,
a high-mont, by the way, the German version.
Sounds so much like black water.
And that apparently, and, and I've looked this up and it looks pretty true to me,
that, uh, a large number of black water rent a army guys,
rent a army guys, like green army guys, only rent a army guys.
Uh, we're, um, deployed to protect,
I think it was to protect the French corridor during Katrina.
So now we have next two police forces and, et cetera, local levels.
We've got, uh, the army, and then we have this, this like independent army.
And these guys are pretty John Wainish, if you ask me.
And the idea of having a for-profit army patrolling United States streets,
or whatever, or streets of Baghdad is,
sounds, I think it's constitutionally wrong, not sure,
but it certainly is morally fucking, it's just wrong.
And I'm not going to play you anything from Naomi Wolf's, um, speech,
although it is, uh, of course I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
You have to watch this, and she's hot too, so you like that.
She's pleasant to watch.
But I will play this, it's like five minutes, um, from video nation,
of course, link in show notes at dailysourcecode.com for this as well.
And it's, it's a short video piece, it's actually about five minutes,
so I'll just play the whole thing if you don't mind.
Um, and it's a titled Blackwater Shadow Army.
And it's, uh, if there's anything on screen that needs to be read,
I'll read it for you, but this piece pretty much speaks for itself.
Um, and I'm not quite sure what is the guy's name.
Uh, I'll read it in a second.
Let's start this off, hold on.
I'll tell you who the guy is when it comes up, I'm screen.
One of the most frightening developments in the occupation of Iraq and the so-called war on-
Okay, it's a Jeremy Scahil.
He is the author of, I guess, a book called Blackwater.
Okay, let's continue.
Er, it's actually something that most people have never heard of.
In addition to the 150,000 troops that the US has on the ground in Iraq,
the Bush administration has deployed a shadow army of some 100,000 contractors.
Of these tens of thousands are heavily armed mercenaries that roam Iraq with impunity.
Among the most powerful of the companies operating in Iraq is Blackwater,
USA, a secret of company based in the wilderness of North Carolina.
It's headed by a right wing, Christian conservative, bankroller of President Bush and his allies.
And Blackwater envisions itself as the FedEx of the National Security apparatus.
But the reality is that Blackwater has become a prime player in the war on terror,
nothing short of the Bush administration's Praetorian guard.
Blackwater, USA largely operated in the shadows of the US war machine.
Until the morning of March 31st, 2004, when four Blackwater contractors were ambushed and killed in the
SUNY City of Falugia, Iraq, their bodies were burned and dragged through the streets.
Two of them hung from a bridge over the U.S. river.
For most people in the United States, the United States, the United States, the United States,
the United States, the United States, the United States, the United States, the United States,
like through the streets, two of them hung from a bridge over the U.S. river.
For most people it was the first that they've ever heard of private military contractors operating in Iraq.
That was the Moga dehum moment to the Iraq war.
In many ways it was the day the war turned.
Unlike Somalia when the Clinton administration pulled out the Bush administration initiated a massive
revenge attack.
They laid siege to the city of Falugia killed hundreds of people, displaced tens of thousands of
others, and in the process infelame the Iraqi resistance that haunts U.S.
that haunts U.S. occupation forces to this day.
I didn't know that that was the reason for Fallujah.
This isn't pretty graphic imagery, too.
The Bush administration came to power
with a radical privatization agenda.
We see it in our schools, prisons, healthcare system,
and law enforcement in the United States.
The occupation of Iraq and the war on terror
had brought the greatest privatization
of warfare and modern history.
Blackwater USA has become one of the most powerful
private actors in the so-called war on terror.
It provides the Bush administration
with an extraordinary amount of political cover.
The deaths of blackwater contractors and other war contractors
are not included in the total death count.
Even though some 780 of them have been killed in Iraq,
their injuries don't get calculated either.
Their crimes don't get punished.
What you have is a revolving door.
Blackwater and other companies benefit the Bush administration
and in turn, the Bush administration
and its Republican allies and Congress
have shielded these military contractors
from any effective oversight, any effective accountability,
any effective legal system.
Their operations are shrouded in secrecy
and people in Congress find it almost impossible
to get information about blackwater
and other companies' operations.
And we know virtually nothing about this.
We think about 40 cents of every dollar.
This is Democrat representative of Jan Chikowski,
of the House Intelligence Committee.
So listen very carefully to what's being said here.
This guy just said, well, you know,
they aren't held accountable by law and boy,
this was done in 2006 this video.
No shit.
So those guys were just granted immunity
if you read the news.
Immunity, there were immune from killing civilians,
civilians, killing civilians,
not the part of the United States Army.
It's crazy, I tell you.
Those two private military contractors,
we think about 800 of them have been killed in Iraq,
but we don't know that.
They're not even counted.
And we think there's about 25,000
to maybe 40,000 engaged in military activities
and combat related activities.
But we don't even know how many there are,
but that's a lot, man, 25, 40,000 outrageous.
We don't know.
And we can't find out.
Hello, you can't find out.
Blackwater USA has 2300 men actively deployed
nine countries around the world.
They have an additional 20,000 contractors at the ready.
But while Blackwater has operated in Iraq and Afghanistan,
the company increasingly has its sights set
on deployments inside of the United States.
Blackwater is setting up a new facility in Illinois,
another one in California.
I was in New Orleans in the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina
and I saw Blackwater mercenary speeding up
and down the streets and unmarked cars,
heavily armed with M4 machine guns,
flat jackets, other weapons strapped to their legs.
And when I talk to the Blackwater guys on the ground
and ask them what their mission was in New Orleans,
they said they were there to confront criminals
and stop looters.
To have mercenary companies which have operated in Iraq,
Afghanistan and elsewhere in the war on terror,
essentially declaring themselves above any effective laws.
Now deploying on the streets of US cities
should be seen as an ominous threat.
Yeah, that's totally the way I see it.
Completely an ominous threat.
Definitely, yeah, 2006 by the nation corporation.
Great job on that.
You know, what are we going to do about this?
What Netanyahu Mewulf says is we need to impeach
the president and the entire administration.
Is it time for those types of discussions?
Has he actually,
has he committed treason?
What are we going to do?
We're just going to talk about it.
We're going to do something about it.
We're going to run around circles.
I'm so I really am thinking that this has to be stopped, man.
When you watch these two videos,
if you ever go to curie.com,
then you'll have seen the Naomi Whulf video.
I'd love to hear your feedback on it
because there's something quite a miss here, my friends.
Quite a miss.
Hey, Adam, Chris Lutterell, originally from Minnesota,
calling from Southern Germany, where I'm an ex-pap,
say I want to follow up on the whole zeitgeist
and follow the money.
After doing my taxes here the last couple of years,
or at least especially this year,
found out that the U.S. Congress has changed the laws
on ex-pats, they don't want to be raising tax.
As well, they've raised it on us and changed the law dynamics
for 2007 Ford, so we're actually praying incrementally
on our entire amount outside of the tax income tax credit
that we get normally living abroad.
But as I'm doing my research, we'll call in
and give you more information on that,
but just can't believe how two faces all can be.
So Ron Paul, very interesting.
I love the interview on 677.
And yeah, I think we need to heat this up going in
to 2008 because starting 2007 ex-pats around the world
are totally getting screwed with the new tax law
that was just tax, essentially double taxation.
Red pill, scruncher and proud of it,
and thought you had him carry it.
Yeah, yeah, yo.
Yo, yeah, I know it.
I have been made aware of the new ex-pats tax regulation.
And of course, for those of you who don't know,
United States citizens have to file a tax return.
Every year, regardless of where they live worldwide
and you can get credit.
So if I pay taxes in the UK or if I worked in the net
of the Netherlands and I paid to pay taxes there,
you don't get taxed again over the income in the States,
but that is apparently changing somewhat.
And can anyone actually explain it to me?
No.
All I hear is, hey, you're gonna get screwed.
So I'm not quite sure.
I'm sure that, no, actually,
one, I can be reasonably sure of is rich people.
We won't bother them that much.
It's just the way it always is.
But that doesn't mean it's right
and it doesn't mean I'm not gonna speak up about it.
I guarantee you.
Hey Adam, it's click on Monday after you know agenda show,
which by the way, I've listened to probably half of it.
Great, I like it.
It's the new show I'm doing with John DeVorek.
We'll probably do one this week, Thursday or Friday,
know agenda.podshow.com.
You only listen to half of it and you still like it?
Not.
You did an excellent job with that interview.
Just because you just laid back
and left the guy talking so fast.
So people, you had no agenda in your,
at least no parent agenda in your questions.
So that's it.
I guess he's talking about the Ron Paul interview.
Could draw whatever conclusions they want from it
because you have the tentative speak
without leading or trying to trap the tentative.
So it's extremely useful for people on both sides
to hear this guy talk his ideas through.
Excellent format.
I was wondering whether you're interested
or whether there's any chance you could get
any other candidates on either other Republican
candidates or other Democratic candidates
or other third party candidates.
Because it's something you never get in the main media
is, you know, a real chess just here
the person talked and felt out.
Yeah, yeah, of course, good point.
Although I'm pretty sure if, if I said right now,
let's get Hillary Clinton or Barack Obama
or Rudy Giuliani for that matter.
I don't care.
Any candidate, of course, I'll be honored
to speak to any one of them
and would give them the exact same courtesy
and exact same format of interview.
So if anyone wants to set that up, I'm your man.
You know that, definitely.
I'm not gonna go chasing him.
You know, I think Ron Paul was pretty amazing
within one week he was on the show.
That was pretty awesome.
Let's see if we can do the same.
Please, please send the same emails to the other candidates
and I'll ask them the exact same questions.
See what they come up with?
We could, oh, we could even put them side by side.
Now, couldn't we?
We could actually play one, one candidates answers
to the other candidates.
See what their response is, kind of like a asymmetrical debate.
I'm up for it, man, definitely.
Just set me up and hook me up.
Because somebody like Hillary Clinton would be passing
to Hillary talk herself out
because she's always positioning.
It would be great to hear her only argue with herself.
Or Barack Obama or anybody.
Just hear them talk themselves out
and see if there's anything behind what they say.
Because I have to say at least Ron Paul
has a consistent set of principle
that he applies to every question.
I mean, I agree with all the conclusions,
but still he has a consistent set
that he applies, which is excellent.
So thank you very much.
And good luck to you.
You're showing the power of your media.
And I have to know you listen that it doesn't bad.
Fuck you Adam.
Yeah, yeah, it's a start, isn't it?
That's for sure.
I'd love to do this with you guys every single day
and really produce it and do nothing else.
Just not in the cards for me yet.
Be a while longer, I'm sure.
Enjoying what I can.
Yeah, so again, the format of the interview
if you haven't heard at Daily Source Code episode
677, it's what new media I think is good at.
We don't, everyone's laughing about the long-winded intro
that I did, but I wanted this guy to know
that he can talk for as long as he wants.
He doesn't have to worry about me getting off the air
or hitting a commercial break or hitting the top of the news
at the hour for the news or any of that.
Just talk man, no worry about it.
There's a fast forward button
if you're boring people shuttles through it.
That's just that simple.
Tell you what, today being October 30th,
one more day tomorrow is, of course, Halloween.
So let's honor it from the Pod Sabies Ignatwork
and the Martians, the Pumpkin Grays.
When he happened, now he's the Pumpkin Grays.
We got this one.
I was so mad, I didn't even find so bright for the camp.
The light and the jump didn't sign cause they were not brave.
This thought didn't ring on the garden.
I think the save, I think the top of the dark, the dark.
Making it in way, I call my daily jump.
Didn't sign cause they were not brave.
As the night's roll, one of the children came in the toy
and jokes in the show, they're ready.
They dance for cheats, apples, nuts,
and sweets, and we feed it their backs with nice things.
The only one they turned around and they saw the grail
and charge the name of the bucket day.
They jumped in fright cause they were not brave.
But now, here they lie on the pumpkin grave.
When the wheels turned round,
the whip, shark came in the dead, woke up and got out there.
When they knocked the doors in the show, they ran.
Stop the doors with the shells you gave.
They turned around and they saw the grail and the children dead.
My bucket day!
They jumped in fright cause they were not brave.
Now, here they lie on the pumpkin grave.
We quave a year until after to the year and after we all end blue.
We unlocked the doors with the thing to do and we ran.
Outside, put without the blue.
We turned around and we saw the grail and the dead, the kids.
And we jumped in fright cause they were not brave.
Now, here they lie on the pumpkin grave.
They jumped in fright cause they were not brave.
And on Christmas night, we are getting out of the grave.
With our pumpkin heads and the one called day.
We'll greet through the streets and have brains to eat.
And you'll jump in fright cause you won't be brave.
And then here you lie on the pumpkin grave.
I'm the pumpkin.
The pumpkin grave.
The marshans from the pod save music never find out all about them.
At podshow.com slash music course directly at DavySourceco.com.
Alrighty.
So as I said tomorrow, no show.
If you have any suggestions for something to take along with me on the airplane.
So upon arrival, I always sleep on the plane.
So when I get in around three o'clock in the afternoon and San Francisco,
I like to go to the office and say hi to everybody.
So kind of get some juice flowing.
I don't want to sleep anyway.
But everyone's going to be dressed up in there in the Halloween costume.
So what should I be wearing?
Something I can take along with me and just maybe I...
That's too easy.
Well anyway, if you have an idea, let me know.
Okay.
Adam at podshow.com.
Adam.podshow.com is where you can find all of my channels filled with
Awesome crap to look at and listen to.
And of course, DailySourceco.com is the URL for this program.
Uh, nothing else? No.
I love my Mac.
I'll talk to you on Thursday.
Bye.
Another podshow.com guest.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the shop
Asmines in content delivery.
Podshow and Livelight.