I, everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code, best of Charlie episode number four.
I'm at him coming to you in a, well, it still is the official curry cottage, although it's
starting to get a little bit, um, discombobulated, not empty yet because the move doesn't
actually take place until next week, but we're already starting to bring boxes over stuff
is getting put into boxes and, uh, and I'm spending a lot of my time changing services, still
in the midst of trying to get, uh, broadband all set up before when we move into the new
place, which, uh, I can pretty much guarantee won't work, is not going to happen, although
the telephone did finally switch over yesterday. So, um, so that part is working. Of course,
now we have no home phone here, so I had to do the old star 21 star to forward all, um,
by the way, it's not called call forwarding in the UK. It's called call diversion. Took me
wild to find that one. Um, so, uh, you know, and we've been, uh, been over the house, uh,
a couple of times each day, um, just getting stuff ready, uh, the house is, uh, it's pretty
much exactly the way we want it, so we're real happy to move in, uh, other, uh, so for the
broadband, uh, what I've decided to do, since I'm sure there's going to be a one to two week
overlap before we actually get everything cranking, um, I've decided to get one of those
vote of phone, um, broadband via G3, USB dongles. They claim that you can get speeds of up to
1.5 megabits per second. I'm pretty sure, uh, that's just the advertised speed in my, uh, my speed
may vary due to road and weather conditions. Uh, but it doesn't really matter as long as I can, uh,
as long as I can do, you know, the normal email stuff and calendar and just be connected, uh,
and particularly for Christina and for Patricia, who also has become quite a connected gal herself,
and, uh, and then for the occasional download of, uh, of some, uh, podcasts, but it looks like
I'm going to have to be, uh, going off to Starbucks or maybe in December, Cisco to get some true
bandwidth while we wait for, um, the broadband to be, uh, to be reconnected in the new GF. Um,
so I have another best of Charlie lined up for you today, which is sponsored in part by Stomp
the Yard, which is a new movie coming out, um, on January 12th. And if you want to know more about
this movie, go to StompThePodcast.com. Tony Costas will tell you all about it, and he's doing regular
updates on this movie up until the movie is released. Uh, and of course, uh, the 12th, the 13th and
the 14th will be able to see how well it did, uh, uh, that's probably the opening weekend. If, uh,
if the little man, uh, exercise, we, uh, we took together. If that's any, um, any precedents, I'm sure this
is going to be a big hit as well. Also brought to you, a part by GoDaddy if you want a great deal
of the main name, go to GoDaddy.com, and you check out code DSC that's Delta Sierra Charlie. DSC
three, uh, for the great savings. And I just want to let you know that just as, uh, I'd pretty much
given up on, uh, on TV again here in the UK, we had some pretty good stuff over the holidays. Um, and
I do love the BBC. I love the stuff they do, but I got out a little bit lean, um, right after the
new years. And yesterday, I'm so happy this show is back on the air. It is, uh, celebrity big brother
once again in the UK. And they've got a great lineup that I'm going to be following. Uh, I'm totally
hooked on this stuff. As you know, I was there. Would big brother has a concept was born. In fact,
it was called Golden Cage back then. Um, so I've always been a fan of the show. And I love
with who they have on this year. Check this out. I'm just pulling this from the, uh, what is this?
The Daily Mirror. Uh, here are the, uh, the contestants who will be in the house for 25 days.
They're not really deal liberties anymore. Well, uh, although we start off with Donnie Turett,
you know, what I'll do is a poly Hudson, uh, writes on the celebrity page of the Daily Mirror.
I will, I'll just read her little bits next to each of the, yeah, each of the contestants.
Uh, you might be thinking, who, but trust me, he's literally a spinal tap-esque hilarious genius.
Great, great booking. No, really a great booking. Donnie Turett is the lead singer of Towers of London,
uh, Christina knew the band. Then there's Dirk Benedict, the man who's gone from 18 to Z list in
expecting 25 days of absolute hell. Here's hoping. I'd also like him to fall in love with Cleo, please.
So, you fuck that. She's horrible, what she wrote. Okay. So, Dirk Benedict, better known as
face from the 18 and, uh, Han Solo. No, not Han Solo. I'm sorry, that was Harrison Ford.
Uh, who, Dirk Benedict was in, uh, was he buck Rogers? That's what it was in. Yeah.
Then Cleo Rockus, who, um, was the girl with the nice boots always leaning forward in the, was it
the candy ever show? I think, uh, English comedian. Then there's, um, disputed and kind of
grumpy old guy, yet perverted grumpy old guy, filmed director Ken Russell, who's in the house.
Then there's Carol Malone, who is a gossip magazine reporter and boy, she's enjoying all the
celebrity. I always knew it. People who write about celebrities want to be celebrities.
Then there's Ian from steps, or better known as H from steps, who coincidentally came out
of the closet 24 hours before going into the big brother house. So, uh, let's use that
with you to take a, yeah, it's probably the token homosexual. So, obviously, it's how they're putting
this together. But a big surprise here. Leo Sayer. Uh, you know, Leo Sayer from the 70s.
What was, uh, you know, I can't dance. You know, I can't dance. Uh, you know what tomorrow,
I'll, uh, for tomorrow's best of Charlie, I'll find Leo Sayer, so I'm play a bit for you.
Then there's a lead singer of S Club 7, Joe Omera. And then there's a girlfriend of a, uh, a
well-known, uh, football player, Daniel Lloyd. And then there is an award-winning
Bollywood actress, Shilpa Shetty, who's also in the big brother house. Beautiful. Like,
I almost like an Indian princess. And her mission is to show the world that, uh, show the world
that there are a lot of misconceptions about Indian people. And finally, I love this, germane Jackson
of, uh, that's, uh, Michael's older brother who I've met a couple times. It's a really nice guy.
But what the heck is he doing in the big brother house? It's going to be, um, a very interesting
season for sure. And the gofers are back bringing you today's best of Charlie. Hope you enjoy
it's chock full of second-life stuff. So, well, at first I thought, uh, I'm really not interested in
hearing all that. But, you know, going back and listening to the enthusiasm is pretty interesting.
And thanks to the gofers, of course.
Hey, baby.
The source code listeners, this is happy again from bedtime stories. My kids love. And again,
I'm hosting a best of the Charlie while Adam moves to the new curry, shall I? Or like I said before,
whatever he wants to call it. Well, this episode, we're going to talk about something that Adam
really got into last year. Second life. And you're going to hear some of the best Adam Curry
second life moments on the daily source code. Listen up.
What is all this stuff? Ow! Watch out. Can you hear me? Can you learn how to fly?
Do I man? No guns. I'm running to the music. Right. The castle is closed.
I'm out of here.
It's crazy.
No, you're crazy. I think that's a Jeff's artistic way of saying, man, I kind of got
interested in sucked into that second life thing. You had a big fro. That was pretty cool.
But there are more people doing interesting things in second life, though.
Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip. Comics trip.
Hi, Adam Curry. Guess who I have met in person in second life yesterday?
It was Jeff Smith, who is making theme songs for Pat Castas for reasonable money.
We were chatting about making theme songs for me. And he mentioned that
his little daughter is running around the house and singing comics trip blogger,
comics trip blogger, Tim Song. Wow, that's scary, don't you think? So, speaking of second life,
Adam, matey, please meet Roger Smalls up. You both live in fucking gulfot. And he's now
sad and bitter because he has no credit card to join second life fun. So, please meet him in
R.L. known as real life and cheer him up. You. You. I've sent an email to Roger. I have
not heard back from him. I hope he's okay. It's very unlike him to be silent all this while. So,
let's just hope that he's okay. I don't think he was going on holiday. I mean, I just don't know.
I really don't know. But it's been weeks now since we've heard from him. So, I'm a bit concerned.
Maybe some problem with the draft and darts thing because he said he couldn't make that.
And that also didn't seem very Roger like. Maybe he was there after all. Maybe he'd actually
met me and thought what a dick. I don't want to send anything to him. So, but anyway,
that Roger smalls, I think he's tough at me. And we haven't heard from him for like three weeks now.
True. And he put this whole thing on his on his weblog that he can't well, he can't get on this,
he just he hates second life. Everything about it. He doesn't want to be part of it. And he
feels left out. And it's like, I don't know what to do. But he's not sending in any more stuff.
Well, there you go. You're losing friends, honey. Roger, come back. I'll do anything.
Yeah, please. Gaining of gaining friends in the air and in your second life, losing them in
RL. In real life, could you tell? Didn't I warn you about it?
Hello? Hey, Roger. Now, I'm at the go for home in second life. Yeah, yeah, it's pretty cool.
Hey, where are you been? It's been three weeks since we heard from you. Yeah, yeah.
Sincere. Yeah. Hey, Roger. My cell phone's ringing. I got to go.
Yeah, I changed my ringtone. I got to go. Yeah. I got to go. Bye.
Hey, CSP. Yeah, and be moved the bedtime story towers you can see curry castle. And now we have
a matching sun in a house. Yeah, it's pretty cool. A CSP don't forget to stop by the bedtime
stories. My kids love go for home in second life. Yeah, you can't miss this. We're right there
by where you live. Right by the tower. Remember CSP. Once you do go for, you never go for anything else.
Sorry about that. Just little go for humor. Hey, like I've shown the phone.
Check out this cool mashup. I got from the pod save music network.
Bro, am spécialating apparently.
What is that sound like you are playing this?
Yeah, of course.
So what are you doing?
Have I told you?
Yeah, I'm a party of Religion.
Don't you think?
I am kidding!
You!
Okay!
Jeff Tinon, Tinon, excuse me.
Sent me an email.
And I, you know, for a second there, I thought he might be right.
Hello Adam.
I have a theory about Rogers absence of late.
We're talking about Roger Smalls, of course.
I actually think he's got himself a girlfriend.
And that's why he hasn't been in touch.
I have so many friends who had some point in other have gone quiet after
bagging a new squeeze.
Leave it a month.
I'm sure he'll be back in touch once the novelty is worn off.
All the best from Jeff.
Oops, and say, oh, excuse me.
I know that's disgusting, but I just needed to do that.
Well, Jeff, funny enough, I think that your theory may be true,
because it has been almost exactly one month since we last heard from him.
Hi Adam, Roger.
I'm sorry for not sending you any recordings for a while,
but I was very upset.
My comic suit blogger's Biblings.
He drew me in crayon on his website.
Now, I'm not sure where he can't go like him as rats call me,
actually.
I know I'm not actually buried head for anything when it comes to looks.
But let's just talk into some girls that go out drinking and go for it.
Then he won't know how in the trashes I am.
Now, if he's decided to do the same thing that he does,
and demand a public apology from him,
because I think as long as he's got hold of his ass,
he's going to continue to be spiteful and rude people.
Which I don't think so any way to get on in life,
but it's all I've got to say for now, Adam.
I'm not saying another word and silly issues in apology.
So, by for now, Roger.
And while he's at stake,
he can apologize to Russell B.
He managed wine, steam,
and everyone else on your comments board too,
because he's a nasty piece of work.
But by the way, will you stop talking about that blessing
compete game?
I'm sure it's very working,
sat down and talked about space invaders for half an hour,
then he's losing all his audience.
Now, when the people think hard casting is key,
the reason people listen to your shows
to hear how much pressure your life is compared to theirs,
not to talk about dungeons and dragons and high schools.
So I am so angry, I should go,
I just thought someone should tell you,
goodbye.
Oh, Roger.
You say me my brother?
Okay, so I do take this seriously.
It sounds like you're angry at comic strip blogger.
And now,
I think he actually, I think he's been pretty nice.
You know, he's said that he's given me advice
to do things to help you out.
You know, send you money,
so you could get on second life.
Excuse me, I need to say
the virtual world,
second life,
where I am sometimes to be found at the curry castle.
Anyway, it's good to hear your voice.
That's for sure.
Let us know if it was a girlfriend that distracted you,
but if it was really just comic strip blogger
that made you so mad,
I think we need to,
we need to sit down and talk.
And you know what, Roger,
I would love to get you
into the second life virtual world
because I think that,
you know, you and comics are blogger.
You know, maybe you guys could meet on neutral ground,
you know, meet over at my place.
And let's talk this out.
Okay,
because I don't like that.
You're the original stalker.
I'm sorry.
It's just what I call it.
It's a term of indierment.
You're the original stalker.
And,
please Roger,
please come back.
I appreciate it.
Nice to meet you.
Come back anytime now.
Comics strip.
Controversy.
Or should I say controversy?
Between.
Comics strip blogger and Roger Smalls.
Now, we heard yesterday from Roger Smalls,
who is back.
That he was really, really upset with comics strip blogger.
And I saw on thecurry.com comments.
CSB had posted an entire apology.
And it doesn't stop there.
I don't carry.
I would like to apologize to Roger Smalls publicly.
That's true.
That I have drawn a comic strip where it was suggested
that Roger is not meeting up with you, Adam.
Carry.
Because Roger is ugly and all shy.
I apologize for that.
And I have just removed the part of this comic strip
where Roger was featured.
I'll buy it as fictional character, called Roger
Squalls.
Not as Roger Smalls.
Anyway, I was wrong.
You are one handsome hank Roger.
You are not ugly.
You are beautiful Roger.
Okay.
So, dear Roger Smalls, please accept my apology.
Sorry mate.
Peace.
Okay.
Finally, anybody who is offended by any of my comic strips
or by any of my tabloid style writings,
please contact me directly.
And I will remove related pieces that are offending you.
I will accept, however, requests only from people
depicted, not from set parties.
Originally of this, sometimes people like art
or publicity about themselves, no matter
whether it is good or bad.
According to the motto, there is no such thing as
bad publicity.
So, have a nice weekend, Adam.
Carry.
I wish you sincerely a good health to your whole family.
Show Adam.
Bye.
Yeah.
People say to me, what did you do to comic strip blogger?
You know what?
I just treated him like any other person who shows up
at the Daily Source Code front door.
And low and behold, there is a pretty nice
intelligent guy underneath all that rough exterior.
Now, unfortunately, Roger hasn't heard
this public apology because he sent me something
this morning before I did the show.
So, he may have changed his feelings about you.
There's CSB after what he just heard.
But as of this morning, he was definitely
definitely not pleased.
Let's listen.
Hey, I didn't Roger here.
I heard that one of your listeners mentioned
on last week's show that's international
masturbation months for the moment.
Now, I'm not sure how this works.
Does it mean I get to enjoy myself for this month,
but then have to wait 11 months before I get to
squirt my care again.
Can you explain?
What did you say?
Wait 11 months until what?
How for this month?
But then have to wait 11 months
before I get to squirt my care again.
Oh, Roger.
Did you actually say squirt my curd?
Can you explain this, please?
Thank you.
Oh.
You want to say put the send you some songs
in about masturbation and I found something.
Hey.
You know, I think there was a,
wasn't there a piece about comics crew?
Is this yesterday's piece?
I don't know what they had I'm doing.
Now I'm all confused.
Hold on.
Is this still the masturbation?
How about a white coat?
That's the same thing.
That's the song about wanking.
This is the one he sent me.
That's right.
If there's one person who knows about easing the lonelyness of an empty life,
you can't even remember magazine.
Then it's the comic strip blogger.
I don't think it's international masturbation
month with him now.
I think it's more like international masturbation
52 years.
Because I think that guy's been a tusso roll is like.
I'm sorry to say.
It's also like the man.
Don't agree with his policies or creed.
By for now and happy masturbating.
I noticed yesterday when looking through that,
that I had a much clearer vision of what we could do with the house
than previously.
Big eyes.
And you're going to laugh at me when I say this?
Oh, not again.
It's true.
Because we're building stuff in second life.
But isn't it the way they actually do Architex and everything work
when they build houses?
Well, yeah.
You can walk through that.
Yeah.
So this is very, very similar.
And so I'm looking down like, hmm,
we could just chop this wall in half and round it off like that.
And I find myself almost wanting to move my mouse finger to click
and you know, and to move the wall.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's what they do.
When they make a designer or something,
they do that.
You can walk through the house before it's done.
But it's really affected me.
I'm not making, I'm not making it.
I believe you.
It's really affected me.
Or maybe if we find somebody who can do that.
Exactly.
In second life.
In real life.
We can see what you can do with the house.
Yeah.
So that's what we're going to try to do.
We're thinking about and see what the, the very cool.
Yeah.
Building things with two different women at the same time.
Oh.
Yeah.
I'm building the Potio Palace with Brittany, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Brittany.
No, not Brittany.
I say that.
But that's incorrect.
Yeah.
I know a Brittany.
But just Brittany.
There's no A and.
No Brittany.
It's Brittany.
Oh.
Okay.
Brittany.
Yeah.
I know.
What is that?
A lot of time with Brittany.
No.
Yes, you do.
But it's going to be very cool when it's long as you have fun.
Oh, God.
I love you so much.
Do you know how many guys are listening to this now going like.
Like, listen.
Why don't I get me one of those?
Yeah.
It's nice to see that your husband is busy.
That's true.
Not sitting around.
So he can't.
He can't.
Or do I ever nag you in the way?
Oh, okay.
Yes.
I'm often often in the way.
By the way, there's not a day goes by that I don't get 20 emails.
At least of people looking for the castle.
So I for some reason I got delisted off of find.
I'll put it back in again.
You should be able to find it.
I'm going to move the whole place today onto right in the middle of four plots.
Which I've been able to thank you very much.
Gabrielle.
Real for letting me buy your land.
So now I have enough to really because you have all these limitations.
Of how many prims, what they call them, you can put on to a piece of land.
So if I'm covering four, then all four corners will count in a different land.
And I think you can actually combine all the land together.
So all I want is just to have more more place to put stuff down.
So we can have more fun.
What's up, baby?
I was listening.
And I thought I think you need to explain every time and over and over that you are not talking about real life.
I said second life.
Oh yeah, but do people know maybe new listeners.
Hey.
What did it?
Excuse me.
And entertainment expert.
Okay.
The hell is that?
Well, because you're talking about plots and buying plots and I think buying plots.
People who listen to the show either understand.
And what if you have new listeners?
Do you want to produce the fucking show?
No.
Okay.
Well, I appreciate it.
But that would be like me coming in and saying, I think you should do that in sea instead of
D. This is my art.
I don't care.
Okay.
I was curious.
Now I understand what you're saying, but I can't reintroduce every single topic that we discuss.
No, no.
No, come back here, please.
Yeah.
In front of the microphone where people can hear you.
Yes.
I understand what you're saying.
But first of all, people aren't stupid.
Don't underestimate my listeners.
The figure.
Does it have a name?
The whole thing.
Not only second life.
But when we talk about things, I don't go back and explain everything all the time.
I mean, some things weren't re-explanation.
But this has been on the cover of business.
We people have heard about second life.
If not, they're going to look for it.
That's how it works.
All right.
Okay.
And if you ever wanted to disturb the man behind the curtain again.
Oh, you called me too in the middle of something.
Doesn't matter, does it?
No, no.
But I'm sure.
That's why we're married for 20 years this year.
Part of, but part of it is, if I go back into explaining what it is.
No, not explaining, but saying real fast, oh, I'm going to talk about it.
Second life.
Well, they call them virtual worlds.
But there you go.
That's what I mean.
All right.
Yeah?
No?
Okay.
Bye-bye.
This is worse than the guy that Howard Stern had to deal with.
He went to go WMBC.
I guess you stopped listening to me.
I don't know what I was saying.
Oh, I see how it is.
I go away for a week.
I'm locked out of curry castle.
This is Angie.
Just in case you forgot.
Hmm.
See if you get any blow jobs from this avatar.
Angie?
This is all a virtual world stuff we're talking about, of course.
Now, actually, I tried to find you because I'd love to have you be one of our first showcases
in the palace.
And I think I've got all the technology bits figured out.
Of course, what we need is a live.
I will not say a live live performance, but a live recording of a live performance or something
like that.
And I'm just messing around with all kinds of permissions and learning myself.
And you've only been in this virtual world for two weeks.
Don't get all pissed off with me now.
Please.
And she lives.
She has a beautiful man.
I gotta tell you.
I am so beyond that for myself.
Oh, yeah.
Then why are you building castles in second life?
Well, to accommodate.
Why are you castles?
Well, why just because I like what a castle looks like.
Why not a bunker?
For exactly the way you just said a bunker.
And besides, curry bunker does not have the same cachet as curry castle.
So what I mean is everybody would like to have their own castle.
Let me just say, well, we've had a castle.
And I miss it still very much.
Yeah.
That's part of it.
Because the castle I'm building in second life is a great place for entertaining.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
You want to get into second life now?
You want to talk about that?
Although, you know, I see that it's.
Very, very interesting and it's brilliant.
And I see it as a game.
But I don't see it.
You don't see the purpose of it?
No.
I mean, people can hardly deal with the first life.
And now they escaped to, they want to escape to second life.
And then, and then probably somebody that they're not.
And then, probably be a girl a chick with big boobs and a very extremely high heels.
Have you seen me in second life?
Are you the girl with big boobs?
No.
And I've seen you.
So everybody's good.
Of course.
Somebody that they actually are not.
Well, you, you can.
Is that the fantasy?
Well, did you, well, first of all, let's just step back.
And then the girl with the big boobs and the extremely high heels.
Yes, exactly.
And all the girls in all the girls in second life who look anything like you.
I immediately have a crush on.
The only thing is they're about six feet tall.
And if you were in second life, if you were in second life, what would the, the only thing
you change about yourself is you make yourself taller.
Right.
True or not?
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, let me just step back for a second because I said this to you last night.
You said, who has, in fact, you, you did want a real Patricia.
Who has time for this?
Really?
And I said, this is.
People have hardly time for each other.
No.
Before we get into that, let me just step back.
It's replacing television time.
It's replacing all that other time that is spent on other entertainment.
I don't think that it's in addition.
You know, so we spend time on the TV.
Have we watched television together?
Well, daily source co- listeners, we sure had a bunch of adventures in second life.
This past year on the daily source code.
And Adam sure had some interesting things to say with Patricia.
But trust me, Adam, I've seen you in second life.
And you don't look that way.
Well, everybody, this is happy from bedtime stories.
My kids love.
Be sure you check us out at bedtime stories.
My kids love dot pod show dot com.
We'd love for you to come check out the podcast.
Well, this has been another Adam is moving best of the Charlie.
Stay tuned for more best of the Charlie's.
Adam, hurry back.
We miss ya.
Come on now.
Hit now.
Tuck him out.
What you see.
Hit now.
That's the best of the Charlie.
Best of the Charlie.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Get this piece of the show.
And more great ones like it on the BT pod show media network.
Howard by pod show and limelight network.
Control your part in the show.
And be the pod show dot com.