This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts on GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Blog it with your free quick blog from GoDaddy.
I don't know exactly what to say, I hope you find a way to come out of the closet.
I want you to wait a second, I didn't sound right.
I hope you find a way to escape from Mark.
Hey, you've got to believe this.
I had nothing to do with all of this.
There's no way I would turn on my own boss.
No way, believe me.
If there was some way, anyway, I could help you get out of the closet.
I would do it.
I'll keep listening.
Call me when you're ready to come out of the closet.
I love you.
Big, here's the bag.
Even if your phone's my bag.
I had a, this is your favorite purple dinosaur stopping by to tell you that I want to put my fist in your ass.
I'm going to be in the Bay Area next week, and I was hoping to binge you over a table and pump you harder than a Mexican oil.
Got it, good day!
Let's sing another song, shall we?
Adams, ass feels real tight.
I could bang him day and night.
Well, Adam Gurney, thanks for spending time with me.
Maybe next time you can come over some afternoon for cake and crumpets.
And I can tea bag you with my big purple coin purse.
Ooh, good day, good day.
That would be great.
Bye-bye.
See you later.
Oh yeah.
You're listening to the daily source code with Mark Yoshimoto Nenkov.
DSC, 5-8-3.
Day, if you get to California, we can stay in LA.
Will we question you in Venice?
Like my brother, buddy, there's a man.
It's gonna kill you on that apartment.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
It does. He's got a bleep filter on his fucking computer here on his rig.
So any time he says, you see Ray? Oh my god.
That's fucking crazy. Oh my god Paul.
Nah, actually I can't take that person.
You think his rig came preset with that?
He's after factory setting.
It could be. Oh my god. Hold on. Wow. Wait a second. You see. Oh
What if you say it in Spanish like what what happens if you say it in Spanish?
Let's see. Oh radio del
Oh shit. Oh my god. It's multi-lingual. Wow. Oh my god. I can't you what maybe I'll try to say fast. You see a really
See? That's amazing. Wow. It's amazing. You cannot say you
Show on the daily source code. Oh my god. Hold on. I need to get one of them. Exactly. Oh my god. Hold on. Wait a second.
You know what? That's just got to be a setting in here. Wait a second. What time?
It's probably a switch. Yeah. Let's see. Hold on. Check over there by the switch for the disco wall.
Yeah. Wait. Here's the voice masculinizer that he's got set. Okay. Hold on.
Uh blah blah blah. Wait. Here we go. Try this. Yes. You see rates on the
s**t altar. So let me click on that. Okay. Now if I say it, right? Good. You see rate.
Jersey turned that Jersey. Jersey turned. Oh my goodness. Thank you. Look at her Bible.
It is so huge. She looks like one of those police guys. Girlfriends.
But I want to stand those police guys anyway. They only talk to her because it looks like
Mother Teresa. Okay. I mean look at it. It's huge. It's gross. She looks so
right since. I like big bubbles and I cannot lie. You pretty
Now that when a girl walks in with a KJB and a bookmark in Proverbs, you get to stokes.
You got a naming race that you know this girl is saying. It looks like one of those
large ones. With money and space in the margins. Baby, I want to re-witch her.
Here's your Bible's got pictures. My minister tried to console me but that book you got makes me so
holy. Oh my my me. Yeah. You're second one. Coin a knee. Yeah. Will bless me. Bless me. It takes me
about John Wesley. I saw her praying while I was eating. She got breaks. She's pretty
face. She ain't going down to the bad place. I'm tired of even guys singing they like
pocket size. That's the average Christian to take a look. She got a pack much book. It's so
fellas. Yeah, fellas. Yeah. The girlfriends got the book. Oh yeah. Well read it. Read it. Read it. Read it.
Read that holy book. Baby, I'm in. I feel the ribbon mark.
Baby, I'm in. I'm in. So that was a clip from Baby God book. Which is something that we
found on Christian YouTube clone. God tube. Thank God for God too. There's a God tube.
God tube. It is. It is. It's the Christian YouTube. And first of all, Mike, I got to say,
I'm not sure I want my God from a tube. Well, I anger God if I squeeze it from the top and not the
bottom. I mean, I don't. I think it's probably not possible to squeeze it from the top of the bottom.
I force you to squeeze it from the middle. Yeah. Because I want to make sure I get every last drop
of God out of the God tube. It doesn't come with an easy applicator stick. I don't know.
I mean, is it for painful, uh, itching and swelling? I see. I don't understand. I mean, I guess,
okay, I do understand. I mean, I do. Well, YouTube is such a phenomenon, right? Yes. But there is so
much, a quote, sinful content. You have sinned on YouTube by posting those videos of you
rupturing a testicle. I mean, that's it. Yeah, I just don't see a reason to watch video on the internet
if there isn't the possibility of boobs being enrolled. I think there are a lot of boobs involved.
Yeah, that's true. It's a different type. Yeah, I mean, that's very true. Well, here, here's,
here's a perfect example of one of the boobs that you'll see here on God tube. Hi, Charlie again.
This week, we want to deal with definitions of terms. So, of course, the first thing to start out with,
if we're trying to deal with a subject scientifically, is define that word science. Science is not
science because somebody that wears a lab coat who's called himself a scientist does it,
but it's because it is sensible. Meaning you can feel it with your five senses is repeatable
and it is only in the present. If we take something in the present that we can really look at,
take a woodpecker for instance, a very interesting bird. If you try to think about how could it
woodpecker evolve, slowly change from a different kind of a bird into a woodpecker,
you kind of stuck with a few problems. First, let's just look at how possibly a woodpecker could evolve.
His bird flying along one day and he sees a bug land on a tree. And so he decides to climb in,
you see the bug climbing into the tree and he says, oh, hey, man, there's dinner. He likes that
particular kind of bug. So he runs up there, bangs his head, his beak into the tree. And of course,
drives his beak straight back into his brain. So that was a little audio clip from a video on
God Tube called argument against evolution. And the guy has like oscilloscopes on the table to make
you think he's some kind of like scientist or even educated. And you know, they don't even,
here's the thing, they don't even pan down during the whole clip to show if he even has shoes.
So I don't know. The subtitle chatting with Charlie chatting with Charlie about evolution.
I mean, here's the thing. It's like, you know, he's talking about his first, and within the first
30 seconds, right? He says that science, science, true science is really only what you can see in
the present. Okay, here's here, quote, a scientist, Charlie the scientist talking about how,
you know, I guess you can only prove what's in the present, right? So like the Charlie the scientist.
Yeah, Charlie the scientist. Charlie the Christian scientist says, you know, but if you can only prove
what's in the present, if we can only grasp and understand that, which is in the present,
then what the fuck are we supposed to make out of stories? There's supposedly happened 2,000
years ago. I mean, come on Charlie. That's a good point. I mean, you know, here's the thing.
I just look, I think it's fine that they, you know, Christians, evangelical Christians want to
find some sort of outlets to put their crazy, you know, videos, they're on the web.
There's a hierarchy idea. There's a hierarchy idea. There's a great one actually I saw on
YouTube. It's actually it was done by a church minister. It was back in the like the 80s because
it was apparently shot on video. And it was, if you're a Christian clown, how how to act when you
visit a nursing home? Are you serious? Oh, it's amazing. It's absolutely amazing. It's, and they
show these clowns and they go this nursing home and how like, you know, um, you know, away from a
far because some people are afraid of clowns and then they show these old people, you know, who are
acting like that they are going like, you know, in terror of these Christian clowns, you know,
and it's always like spreading the faith through clowning in nursing homes. I haven't been doing
that for thousands of years. But the thing is that was put up as a joke on YouTube, right?
So you've got, you've got baby got book on God tube, right? Which, you know, you see,
you see the guy who's doing, I'm going to put links to these. I, you have to. No pun intended
swear to God. I got, I'm putting links to these in the show notes. You know, the guy, the, the MC,
the pastor, whatever, youth pastor, youth minister. He's like trying to be like a rapper and he's
got this giant gold thing with his initials on it. You know, around his neck, like, like he's
trying to be like some street dude or something like that. Hey, you know, street for Jesus. Yeah,
the thing I loved about the chatting with Charlie is that he goes through that whole explanation
about the woodpecker. Yeah. And first of all, his facts are wrong. He said they can pick 400 times
a second. That's way off. But he basically proves create our evolution. He talks about,
he talks about how the beak is developed to do a specific thing and the tongue does something
specific and the saliva works together with the tongue and how it's, he's, he makes the argument
for evolution. I love it. And I've watched a couple of his other videos. He does the exact same thing.
You know, just pick an animal and he's, he has argued against the evolution of that animal
while proving it. I love, I love, I love scientists Charlie. Oh my God. That's amazing.
It is amazing. And look, I have no problem with anybody's faith. Here's the thing. What I love
is, you know, his whole big thing is he's going to disprove evolution because, you know, God forbid,
you believe in evolution or evolving or that man came from apes or that there were dinosaurs
who roam the earth 50 million years ago. You know, see, what I love is that one of the
main tenants of every single religion, right? Of course, is tolerance. You know, even true Islam
preaches tolerance. Right. But most people, most people take that as tolerance of anyone who believes
exactly what they do and nothing else. How glad you pointed that out. Yeah. I love that. I love that.
You know, and so instead of, you know, basically it's just, it should redefine and say, I'm
tolerant of me. Yes. Anybody who is not me, I just don't have time for you. Then you must die.
You must die flaming ball of of hate. So that's, I mean, in Los Angeles, right? We have a
Jewish sponsored museum of tolerance, which, which, you know, in right there in West LA, right
on Pico, which I tried to go to once, but I got into a fight in the parking lot. I make it there.
So, you know, that didn't work out so well. But, uh, what are you know, actually, to tell you the truth,
I am starting a new video sharing a social network site with my rabbi called, uh, called YouTube.
YouTube. Yeah. So right now, it's actually, it's all circumcision videos. And, and I've, I've actually
got the, uh, some clips from the Goldstein bar mitzvah, the Goldberg bar mitzvah, the Goldberg
bar mitzvah, the Goldbergstein bar mitzvah, and actually a video where Jersey Todd shows his tail.
So, yeah, and I got some, I got some stuff off the Bluper reel from the electronic press kit
released by the Jews who controlled the media. Right. So, yeah, you know, we're, we're hoping to get some more
clips there. It's going to be huge. It's going to be huge. YouTube, man. I'm telling you. Yeah.
How are you spelling that? With a G. Yeah. Okay. But, you know, I, I tell you, as, as entertaining
as YouTube is, God, tube is, is, is even more entertaining to me. Yeah, definitely. Yeah,
especially, you know, because I'm, I'm like, uh, you know, I'm going, uh, there's got to be some
good stuff on here. You know, they're not going to post like clips from any of the sitcoms or any,
any, you know, daily show clips are going to show up on God, tube. But I did find this. It's,
it's a clip. I swear George Bush left a clip on God, tube. Check this out.
Good evening. This is George W. Bush. I'd like to take this opportunity here on GodTube.com.
Let's tell you my story with regards to my personal savior and Lord, Jesus Christ. There have
been times in the past when late at night. Jesus was sneaking into my room and trying to put
himself inside of me. But I was not ready to take him in. I was young and unsure. But now,
with the war in Iraq region, I've decided that it's time to let Jesus inside of me through each
and every opening I have to offer. Now late at night when I hear Jesus enter the room,
I grip my teeth, roll over and wait for his glorious love. Quietly, I can feel the hands of
Jesus on my body as he gently, yet firmly takes me by the shoulders and slowly enters me.
Make no mistake about it. The Lord's love is not easy. In fact, it's hard, like a stone.
And it's long, like a baby's leg without any. I love to feel the Lord forcing his love,
his deep, deep love into my soul through every hole he gave me.
Quiet frankly, there are times when I find myself choking on the love of the Lord. But that's
when I hear Mama's voice in my head, tell me to breathe through my nose, loosen up my throat
and start praying. It'll be over soon. And then when the Lord has done filling my empty vessel with
his love, quiet often, I will try to return the favor by showing the Lord my love. But he will not
allow it. The Lord is such a giver, but he thrusts my face back down into the pillow and he puts his
love into me yet again. Over and over, I can feel the love of my Lord ramming through my soul,
Ian and out and in and out until the Lord's cup runeth over and I feel him pulsate with joy.
There is no truth to the song we shall overcome, as Lord has so many times told me that he cannot
overcome when it comes to my soul and salvation. So I look forward to him coming and coming again,
over and over, filling me with his love and his redemption. This is your President George W. Bush
wishing you a good night and God bless America. The commander in chief on god, how inspirational.
I know I moved. Yes, I'm quite moved, actually. About 6 inches this way. So Serious 102 listeners,
you're going to have to go to dailysourcecode.podshow.com to listen to the rest of the show
And give me a call on the PCH comment line, 1-800-875-0995, or email me, at where's Adam Curry at gmail.com, or Adam Curry's gay at gmail.com.
Your choice.
So, uh, one or two listeners trust me, you're so missing out.
You got it down low the rest of the show.
We'll catch you later.
The only big program at your command is the only big program program.
Hello, Mr. Namco. This is the prolific program.
Now that you are in charge of the DSE, I thought it might be time to address my nickname.
I'm not sure I knew how I came to be known as the prolific programer.
prolific means I'm capable of reproducing.
I'm equipped for reproducing, but that doesn't necessarily mean I am capable if you know what I mean.
I believe Adam often uses the word prolific when he actually means profound.
But then English is not Adam's primary language.
I was wondering if you could make me a new theme song as the profound programmer, which fits me much better.
Oh, and tell Adam that his thoughtful gift came the day after the autograph picture.
But I don't know which end I should use.
They both look the same.
Well, bye for now.
So, uh, Mike, I don't know, do you have a big plans for the summer?
No, nothing yet.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
Well, here, wait a second. First of all, I got to tell you.
I'm fascinated with the public's fascination with San Jaya.
Yeah, I'm not sure what that's all about. I think it's his hair.
Well, he does have, he does have very nice hair.
But it's, it's amazing to me that people are more fascinated with San Jaya than say Nicole Kidman, right?
And I mean, I think I almost understand it because here's the thing.
Someone like that, she's so beautiful, right?
The most women know that they'll never look like her.
You know, even after they lose 50 pounds and Midwest women, I'm talking to you.
So, I know what.
Yeah, I know what we're talking to you.
Yes.
And I mean, San Jaya is so average, right?
I guess that people identify with him.
And you think that's it?
You think it's the every man aspect?
I think so because he's not so talented that people say,
Wow, I, um, that, that, there's no way that could be me.
I think he's so untalented people are like, you know what?
I could be that guy.
You know this?
So we're, we're shooting for the lowest common denominator here.
Well, it is American Idol.
And I mean, okay, you know, I'm following this, right?
Because I'm a student of weird news, right?
Okay.
I, um, I found out San Jaya's parents, I swear to God, this is true.
Mm-hmm.
We're a harshness according to divorce papers that were filed by his parents.
And that's what divorcing each other, divorcing him.
Yeah.
They were divorcing each other.
And apparently the father had become a, a hard Christian, a, a, a, a, a, a minister.
Priest, whatever they do.
Shaman.
Yeah.
And don't squeeze the shaman.
And so he was living in the temple or the shed, the little tool shed, the hard Christian tool shed.
Mm-hmm.
And, you know, he was, uh, not making any money.
He declared zero when his tax return.
And I guess, you know, eventually it's some point.
That creates a problem with the family.
Sure.
You know, so that there was a whole thing and they were divorced.
And then the papers, it's mentioned a whole higher Christian.
So he's brought up like a hard Christian.
Wow.
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
So that's why I think he's so popular.
He's getting the hard Christian a vote.
Yeah.
So.
How are they calling in?
Uh, you know, I don't know.
I think what happens.
At least, I don't, I don't have phones.
And I think he has something else.
They're using their mind power.
They're high Christian of mine power.
Which happens.
Skype by mind.
You know, which they're eating special lentils that have been irradiated.
I don't know.
But I thought as Sanjay, it, I think what it is to is Sanjayia.
It's just a fun word to say.
It is a fun word.
It's true.
It sounds like a musical instrument.
You know, almost like because you got the, like banjo.
Except Sanjayia, I think, would be a wind instrument.
So like here, let's use it in the sense.
Hey, Mike.
Yeah.
Dude, I went to your recital last night and you blew a mean Sanjayia.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
See, that's, that's what I mean.
It sounds like a wind instrument.
It does.
Or you could use that same sentence and name your penis to Sanjayia.
It's the worst.
It does.
It sounds like maybe the new, the new SUV hybrid from, uh, from,
Kia.
Exactly.
It's a Kia Sanjayia.
Kia said, Jaya, 40 miles to the gallon.
So all the instruments are in India.
It's all in Hindi.
Hindi.
Oh, yeah.
The speedometer reads like, you know, right to left.
Exactly.
So.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I don't know.
So, you know, you have to pull up to the pump where it's, you know,
regular, unlettered and tendori.
So you have to pull up to the last pump.
But, uh, so here's the thing.
So I think what I'm going to do.
I'm so fascinated that this summer, right?
I want to be more like Sanjayia.
So I'm, I'm going to go to American Idol Camp.
You know, it was a fruity.
We're going to say that.
I mean, did you see this story?
I did.
On the edge.
It was actually on the today show.
It was like national TV.
Oh, my god.
So free mantle media, the company that created American Idol.
Uh, you know, this billion dollar, French, multi-billion dollar worldwide franchise
is creating a camp for American Idol Camp.
I am not making this up.
That was speechless.
Yeah.
Today.
And actually today.
Oh, my god.
As soon as we finish the show, because I got to get online.
Because today is the deadline to apply it.
I don't camp.com.
Really?
Yeah.
And, you know, if first I wasn't going to, I wasn't going to do it.
Because, you know, I'm Jewish.
I don't do camp.
But, um, you know, I, I, I'm, I'm drawn to it.
I, I think I have to do it this summer.
I think you'd be good at.
You went to Berkeley, right?
Yeah.
So it was almost like there tonight.
I don't camp.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So, uh, Mike, I'm, I'm kind of hoping you would, you would come with me.
Be my camp buddy.
Yeah.
I would go.
We can share a bunk.
Well, not.
I didn't, I don't know about that.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about what you want to say.
Look, that's, you're making it much worse.
Yeah.
How about those dodgers?
Exactly.
Yeah.
I don't camp, huh?
I don't camp.
So, um, and, you know, there's no doubt.
And this thing's going to be so popular.
I, I hope that I can actually apply.
That's not too late.
Because, you know, this country has, uh,
uh, this country has American Idol fever.
Which I believe can only be properly treated with leeches.
Uh-huh.
But, uh, heard that.
Yeah.
It's unbelievable.
So, uh, um, American Idol camp.
If you're going to go, uh, I was just noticing they have scholarships.
Oh, dude.
So, you can probably, and I'll bet you can get one.
I'll bet you'd qualify.
Do you think I could get the, uh,
Bucky Covington scholarship?
For sure.
Why not?
A full ride.
See, I'd be afraid of, you know, if somebody like,
oh, you're, you're getting the full ride at American Idol camp.
And I'd be like, does that involve Ryan C. Crest fist?
Yeah.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I'm going to have to pass on that one.
Just polish up with a strap on.
Yeah, exactly.
So, I might just, I might just actually pay in that case.
And tuition is a very affordable $2,900 for the week.
That's not bad.
Yeah.
For the week.
But there's a way to mean it.
You go to camp to learn how to win on American Idol for a week?
That's, that's it.
That's it?
That's it.
Yeah.
It's a one week fully immersive experience where they,
I guess they teach you on how to maximize your audition for American Idol.
I swear to God, This is true.
I wonder if it starts off with don't suck.
suck less more often exactly there you go there you better trademark that before American
Idol steals if it is but it's a smart and copyright some of the yeah some of the classes
they teach are apparently stage presence and how to audition how to get young girls wet and
I guess you know how to wrap your lips around Simon's tool so yeah I saw that one yeah
I don't know I'm just I'm fascinated so I was thinking I was thinking you know what while we're here
You know I'm gonna apply now I don't want to waste any time so I'm just I better click on this hold on
I don't camp calm and
You know what we better read the fact first yeah frequently asked questions so hold on okay
Who can apply to Idol Camp okay to be eligible for Idol Camp applicants must be residents of the United States of America
All right I got that going for me good no younger than 12 years old got that as of July 1 and no older than 15
Oh
Wow that's a deal breaker. Oh
Do you think if I shave my balls do you think I can I can pass
If I show them my boyishly smooth sack
I be like look I'm 14 I got the sack of a 14 year old
So that took a left turn on us. Yes. It certainly did okay. Let's read the next one
It says how do I apply applications are available online blah blah blah
Complete applications must include application form consent form 35 dollar application fee blah blah blah
Submission of applications is not guaranteed acceptance to okay
Was the tuition tuition is $2,900
includes camper registration all programs of instruction accommodations and meals t-shirt and cap
So for 2,900 bucks. You do get a t-shirt and cap. Wow. That's worth it. Wow transportation to and from the Idol Camp
Campus to Bradley International Airport
I have no idea where that is
tuition does not include optional medical insurance
Transportation from your home to Bradley International Airport and other expenses relating to attendance vital camp
Such as the cost of mandatory medical exams
Oh, so I guess if if you if you you can go ahead checking you for Climidia
Yeah, I was gonna say cold-sourves. Climidia. Yeah, I don't know markable anuses
At I yeah, I'm Tanya. Well, I better I better call my doctor
Our scholarships available. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, let's see a question number
Number seven will I be Sodomized by Ryan C. Crest
Says no due to previous work commitment to Ryan C. Crest will not be on hand to Sodomize you
However, we have confirmed that we just Philbin will be there with a very lubricated finger
Okay, okay, all set up. Yeah, I still if he says he says readjust out
Readjust out
Regis in again
Regis out Regis in out in out
Got it. Yeah, so
You're just waiting for the Regis out. You're like, please readjust out please readjust out
Hurry up
So
I don't know American idle camp. It's kind of it frightens me it frightens me a lot
I have a frightens me. Yeah, you know me all these camps we've got Jesus camp
Got American idle camp. I'm not really sure which one is worse
They both involve small children some type of fisting. I'm sure exactly
And oh the pimp camp. Well, that's right. Remember. Yeah, I think what's gonna happen is we've we've signed a deal
It's not gonna happen this summer. Well, it might happen to some we you know because it's kind of one of those things where
Where it's uh, it's gonna it might be a little fly by night, but
Watch out PCH Pimp camp
Is opening up soon and
You know and you get it you get a t-shirt and a hat with that as well you do you get t-shirt and a hat and you know
It's it's all about you know wallet making and host slapping
So and you know sitting around the campfire at night with your you know 40 ounce or in a bag and
You know cold 40 sing in you know such great
Pimp camp songs like a bitch get me my slippers
And bitch kumbaya
Right, so uh, yeah, I think PCH Pimp camp is gonna be a fucking hit did
It's cheaper than I don't can it's much cheaper because it's 2895
Yeah, and we do take a cut though
We as we do take a cut of all profits over the next three years. Yeah. Oh, I thought you mean you were gonna cut me like I'm gonna cut you
No, no, no, because that's our slogan actually at PCH
Can't I get a cut you bitch?
So uh, yeah, I'm kind of hoping I'm kind of hoping so uh we can we can get that going because uh is that it's slogan on the new shirts?
It better be so it's also all right, but um, oh fuck
Did you hear that?
Yeah, dude. Oh
Did we forget to lock the closet door oh? Oh my god
I was in there trying on on his wife's clothes
No, I think oh, I think Adam got out. Oh shit
Dude. Oh, that's sorry. We do. What do you mean what do we do? We have to fucking go chase him
Don't we have to find him. Why? Why?
Because I mean
I think we let him run around gilford for a while. You think well, I think we got I think we got to find him because I personally don't have to
I don't want to have to answer to what what is conspired here over the last few transpired
conspired or was transpired over the last year? Yeah, I had nothing to do with that. Yeah, exactly. So um
Yeah, I do we got to I mean come on. You'll take his time and how hard could it be to find
7 foot tall guy running around gilford in a gimp outfit?
Well, that's a good call. We are an angle. Yeah, we aren't gilford. That's true. It might take a little time
To find the right guy. So, okay
All right, well, I still got him. Yeah, we got our afternoon cut-out for us. Oh, wow. That's true. Okay, and then after that we get some bangers and mash
I hope that's some kind of food
Me too
Oh, man, all right hold on. Let me play this
Oh
Mark, let's go on there and dance out as soon could be sweet to show you it pardon me there
We're just getting ready for the holiday that is coming up on Friday
You know what holiday if you don't Adam knows what holiday I'm talking about
Yeah
Yeah, anyway
Yeah, I was in fact silence when I called in yesterday
Although because I podcast the revolution I have
Vustily resisted my captors and dances
No resisting is like make a choice is worse later
But anyway, I have broken free long enough to call you and hope that this call doesn't get interrupted
I believe that's true that I was talking about the legalistic versus the moral of the components to the
debate about pirating music and I mean the reason that we in the public get
views about this is because it is legalistic and moralistic in the courts of course
It is only legalistic and it's a lawyer lawyers to decide
You know what's legal what's not and I'm talking yesterday about well it's illegal because of the power of the lobbying
Organization that is the IWA
But in the public sphere
Laws aren't quite as they are is weird, but they're not quite as meaningful
So we have a debate that includes the legal and which is kind of subtle that's illegal
But we feel more we're justified in taking things if we feel as though we've been screwed for 1895
We know that artists don't make money from those CDs
We know that and we know that this quote unquote piracy has occurred because
The 1895 sticker prices on into lobbying and not into
paying the artist so we feel compelled almost to take something at the top on a major
Dan Dan where'd you go?
Silence again damn you Doug Morris stay away from Dan Patterson
Hey Mark great job filling in for AC not sure I could stand another best of curie week by the way
As for your question of where this independent music thing is going well who knows what I see are independent bands
Complaining that they are being shut out of the marketplace and now they want to stick it to the man
But then when these same bands then get an offer from the same man
They forget their past and don't want to be independent anymore
So the cycle only stops when independent bands can make as much money as the band signed to labels and the only way they will
happen
Is if we all stop trying to be like 13 year old girls and
Gossip about who likes what and if you don't like the bouncy puppy hip-hop group or you you listen to your caramel
a kitty rapy group so you must suck oh come on and grow up but you see each of us just wants to be cool
And most of the time we use music to show how cool we are and thus we succumb to the music industry
By letting them tell us who to like so we can brag about how we like bouncy puppy hip-hop group or whatever and oh
We don't like her melancholy cat rap group. Oh who cares? So I'm not sure whether the strangle hold
By the music industry execs will ever go away
For me I listen to a lot of different music even Christian music and thus created the pillar cast for people who just want to hear music with a purpose
And now the bunch of messages. Yeah, does it make me cool? No, I doubt it
But the music I played doesn't have to make me cool. So I don't care what the music industry says and I don't care what you think either
Hey Mark, keep up the great work. Thanks from John at the pillar cast hi John it's male from Megalophone
I've been listening to your tape for the 19th time. Oh, that's another call. Can I call you back when I
In a band
I
You
Hi Jack, it's L from A and I, you don't really need a band, they are in the way.
We only wanted you anyway, so don't you band, it's you are the base, you better wake us up fast,
This is not a game, we're a professional, we did, I mentioned you better, you should be out of this year.
Can't I be healthy?
Go!
Back to the communication, right?
To think that you were a cowboy, we were all kind decided to be out of New Collin's door.
Come on, so let's end the past and see this journey for my child.
I play this here, good time.
Jack, you are Jack, you are shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Are you a priority?
Name this journey for your life.
I'm going to be a star.
Jack, you are just a joke.
Do you want a hit of this?
Thank you, John, from the pillar cast for those comments.
You bring up some really good points, but I think ultimately what happens is a lot of independent music artists.
They will sign that big record deal because it allows them to quit their day jobs and become full-time musicians,
at least that's what they believe it means, though it doesn't often work out that way.
And a little song, a little ditty, I've just played.
Kevin Gilbert, from Shaming of the True Wets, basically what's I call that suit fugue, dance of the A&R man.
I thought it just kind of fit.
Wasn't really planning on playing more Gilbert, but just fit.
And let's see.
Then actually relating to that.
Slaw, our good buddy, Slaw, right since it's just wanted to tell you how much I enjoyed Monday's
DSC that you hosted, cracked up so many times, which normally listening to Adam while I'm following what's going on
in the Podger world, and I'm usually not bursting out into belly laughs.
I don't know, I usually laugh when Adam can be funny.
He could be funny.
Anyway, I was also completely surprised when he got into Kevin Gilbert, one of my favorites.
I didn't know you went to Berkeley, will you?
Yeah, whatever.
Berkeley's not so cool.
And yeah, I was fascinated about the Kevin Cheryl saga while reading the book no fool to this game,
a Cheryl Crow biography, which, yeah,
I, you know, it might be interesting.
I might check that out, Cheryl Crow biography.
Like I do an outline for me, because I have trouble with that one.
See, the only, the only part, the only chapter I'm interested in is I guess they suppose it lesbianism.
Really?
Yeah, because, you know, there was a story going around for a very long period of time that she was a lesbah.
So, yeah, so, yeah, I would be interested.
Yeah, you know, if the, in between the chapter of where she fucked over her boyfriend Kevin Gilbert,
completely fucked him over.
If there's a whole chapter about munching rug, then, you know, I'll read that.
Cheryl munching rug.
So, I'll then that it, it does me no good.
But, yeah, that's the name of the chapter.
Munching rug.
My month of rug munching.
I, hopefully it's more than a month.
Yeah, I'm hoping half the book is about rug munching.
Okay.
So, yeah, I don't know.
Maybe there's somebody out there interested in this.
You know, let me know.
If there's, you know, just paraphrase the rug munching chapter for me.
Just give me the, the cliff notes version of it.
We're sent pictures.
Yeah.
And this got this email from Bob, who sent it from a commuter train in Tokyo,
a Bob son writes in,
Hi, Mark, what a shock here I am looking forward to.
We're relaxing 40 minutes with Adam.
And I hear you.
Oh, no.
PCG has kidnapped the DSC feed.
All getting aside.
Good show.
And I'll probably survive.
So.
I'm about here.
Yeah.
And I hear you.
So, uh, thank you, Bob, son.
And, uh, you know,
definitely, uh, keep yourself safe from Godzilla attack.
They're in Tokyo.
That's price.
I love that.
Oh, man.
You know what I love?
There was a couple of comments.
People left on the DSC page.
They're like, all pissed at Adam.
Because I was hosting them.
Like, you know, you should just leave the feed empty blah blah blah.
And I was like, that's fucking great.
You know, podcasting is all about, like,
giving people choices, right?
And, and the freedom for people to do their shows the way they want.
Once again, it's a tolerance thing, right?
But, like, you know, but, but, you know,
I'm going to tell you how you should do your show.
Fuckin' that fucking douchebag.
I can't remember who it was.
It left that.
So, it's like, dude, if you don't like it,
don't fucking listen.
Exactly.
Skip ahead.
Yeah.
Adam will be back next week.
At least, you know, if he,
Maybe.
Yeah.
If he can unzip the eye holes in the gimp suit,
and doesn't run into the tams or something like that.
I wonder if he'd float.
I don't know that.
That's in the suit, I mean.
Yeah, it's kind of, the, the, the chains on it.
They're kind of heavy.
That's true.
Yeah, especially the, the ones that go from nipple to nipple.
That's a heavy chain.
So that is.
Yeah.
But he insisted.
So.
And I got this one from Paul Shepherd.
Paul writes in says,
Today is International Disadvantaged People's Day.
Please send an encouraging message to a retarded friend.
Just as I've done.
Meaning to me.
I don't care if you lick windows through farm animals.
Take the short bus or occasionally shit yourself.
You hang in there sunshine.
You're fucking special.
From Paul Shepherd.
Who, who calls himself a Guatemala file.
So dirty filthy Guatemala file.
With this, you know, little pictures of Guatemala.
So they're beating off to Guatemala.
Pictures trained it with other Guatemala files.
You know, based on.
You got to frame that.
I love that.
So.
Thank you, Paul.
Beautiful.
That may be the best email I've ever heard.
I love that.
Thank you, Paul.
Thank you.
I am special now.
Have you ever seen Doofy?
Oh, I'll tell you.
It's time for Doofy to make a return engagement.
Yeah, it is.
Time to revive Doofy.
Yeah, exactly.
But you know, you know what?
I loved.
Oh, my God.
So on on.
Hold on.
On UC radio pod show.
I said it.
It worked.
So on UC radio pod show.
You told that story about how there was a girl who works at your bank.
Pretty nice.
Pretty girl.
You said you wanted to like jack off on her face.
What was that?
No, maybe maybe that's I'm just adding that.
So no, so they would.
So you used to go into the bank and she'd be there.
And you know, and then you went in there one time.
And she had.
Veneers.
Not Veneers.
She had to wear a neck brace to keep her head up.
Exactly.
And so she said to you, she said to you, I can't even do it.
Emma Emma.
And you're your son Nick, your five-year-old son Nick.
Said.
He actually said that sounds like doofy.
Right.
Which would shock me because my first house where the fuck did he hear doofy.
They're like, oh shit.
I really am playing it too loud.
Yeah.
Apparently.
I love that.
Yeah.
It's less dangerous.
Well, what can you do?
What you're going to do, please.
All right.
So I'm, I'm thinking we better go chase Adam down before.
Yeah.
He's been out long enough.
So in the English sunshine.
No.
In this gimp suit.
In his gimp suit.
Yeah.
Did you have the ball in his mouth?
Like gag ball.
Oh, the aiming the rubber ball, not the.
Yeah.
Oh, I thought you meant your ball.
But anyway.
No.
So, all right.
Well, we better, yeah.
So we're going to go, we're going to go find Adam.
And, you know, hopefully nothing, nothing bad has happened to him or nothing worse has happened to him.
It's worse.
All right.
Everybody.
I think we're out of here.
So, uh, once again, send me an email.
Where is Adam Curry at gmail.com?
Or Adam Curry's gay at gmail.com?
Or call the comment line 1-800-875-0995.
Yeah.
So, uh, Mike, uh, great to have you.
It's good to be here.
Yeah.
But I think it's sit down with you for a while.
I know that you're, you're sightseeing tomorrow.
You're going to go see Big Ben.
Um, which I, you mean that big, you mean the clock, right?
I mean the clock.
Okay.
I thought it was some, some dudes.
Not the guy down the street.
Black leather glove.
No.
Okay.
So, uh, so yeah.
I don't, maybe we'll talk to you somewhere this week at some point.
Sure.
You can tell more they can find my show.
Uh, yeah.
You see radio punch.
I almost got away with it.
Almost.
Yeah.
And um, bite me FCC.com.
There you go.
Which is always fun to type in.
It is.
Yes.
I enjoyed it.
All right.
So, uh, we're out here.
Well, thanks.
Well, thank you.
It was fun.
It was, it was a lot of fun.
Oh, you know what?
I want to play a song.
Hey, from music.podshow.com.
This is new scoggin' with what I check out the little, like, jungle beat thing.
Going on underneath with the drum machine on that.
Very cool.
All right.
We'll catch you guys later.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
What I...
Where am I supposed to go?
Something that's fake though.
What I...
Everybody and things that you say.
Yeah.
And things that I'm perfect.
And me.
What is it looking like thing?
Yes.
Do you see something hiding of you in me?
You come from to us.
Come on.
Hold us inside building your girl in love.
Because that whole thing was not that long time ago.
What I...
Where am I supposed to go?
Something that's fake though.
What I...
Talk to the middle of the confrontation.
Walk to the center of expectation.
I love the fact that I'm beautiful to the am I.
I'm what you see as much you get with me.
Don't need your stupid managers of plastic jelly rounds, that goes.
I hope my pride high on a silver tray, yeah.
What I, what I, where am I supposed to know what I, what I,
I'm starting to think about what I, what I,
Everybody makes the same, I'm in so far away.
What I, what I, where am I supposed to know what I, what I,
I'm starting to think about what I, what I,
I'm starting to think about what I, what I, I'm starting to think about what I,
Bird for me.
Another Pancho podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
content delivery, podshow, and limite.