It's the DSC-622 and it's time to play where in the world is Adam Curry.
And it's time to get the food bar out of the closet, because it's blue bar bright.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
will bring you content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
He got a nice pick, that made his ears burn, whatever happens to you, do a blend there,
to play on me right, and a central pencil, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you are the heroes,
whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, no more heroes anymore, no more heroes anymore.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever
happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens
to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you to come up here, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens, you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you, whatever happens to you
No more heroes anymore.
No more heroes.
Sure, these days have got your email.
You've always got your rockin' long.
But 30 years ago, this was the sound of the underground,
the organization for preservation
to the soundtrack of our lives presents
the Fubar Friday maximum music spectacular
to other stranglers.
No more heroes anymore.
There's more stranglers than I could do.
Yeah, yeah.
You sure are a pretty man at him.
If I was woman, I'd have put him for you.
Oh, I got so much to talk about.
What an incredible week.
And I am neckerd.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
You made me know I'm sure
You can't completely love me so fast
Gonna give it more
You won't ever make it just a set
You made me do any job
Baby, don't watch your own
I'll say I'll kill someone
But I didn't stop it
I decided you wanted to win
Baby, I don't want nobody
That's not me
I am not gonna eyes
I am alone
Gotta hear what I see
When the heavey
It's a cruise or a live, you're the best thing I've ever seen.
Oh, you're my favorite.
Show me how.
Deep within the feelings you're dreaming of.
Little brother, say you're just fine.
Break it through and eat your baby.
I want you all the time.
Say it up to you, say it up to you, say it up to you.
I do this way.
Cause I don't wanna do it.
Baby, I don't want nobody else.
Deep within the feelings you're dreaming of.
It's a cruise or a live, you're the best thing I've ever seen.
Break it through and eat your baby.
Show me how.
Deep within the feelings you're dreaming of.
Little brother, say it up to you, say it up to you.
All right, it's just fine.
All together now.
You got to do the source code check.
10, 10, 1, 2, 1, 2, check.
Check.
10, 1, 2, 1, 2, 2, 2, 2, 3.
Lock down.
It's brand new in the Pods and Music Network.
Actually, a couple of weeks now.
It's called Babe.
I like that sound.
I like what those wacky kids have done.
You can find links to that in the show.
It's a daily source code dot com.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to DSC 622.
Coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford on the west side of
G town is where you will find the manner.
Man, it's like I've been on the road for three weeks straight now with what
like two days at home.
I'm back from Khan, everybody.
And I really apologize profusely.
Well, first of all, I apologize profusely for episode 62620.
Obviously, you all noticed something went wrong.
I was back from, what was it?
Back from San Francisco, New York and Washington, DC.
And I just couldn't get the sound right.
It's something, you know, I don't know if my ears had changed.
Maybe they were still clogged up from flying it to a tremendous altitude.
But it just didn't sound right.
So I decided to test it.
You can only really test it when you're recording it and can listen back to it.
And I just kind of forgot to reset the recording on Casplaster.
So for those of you who are surprised by 15 minutes of me going test test one two.
Check, check, test one two.
I'm sorry.
He said check, check, check.
Oh man, I'm not going to rag you.
I'm not.
I'm letting you get so much shit.
I bet you got so much shit.
But it's not me.
You just give me sound the best laugh ever.
I look like a right person on the tube.
Can you see myself laughing?
So what comes off the three?
One two.
Charles.
Oh, I love you, Miss Curry.
I love you too.
And I mean it.
All right, Charles, the drunk and London are checking in.
He heard it too.
And apparently he cracked up on the tube, which is English for a subway.
Hey, so this, this country was interesting.
Hopefully you saw episode 621.
I guess it is an official episode 621.
Where I recorded some of the flight down to Khan.
I've pretty much told you all I could about that.
The trip back, by the way, was equally spectacular.
Leaving a monthly airport.
We went straight to flight level 65 from 65 straight to flight level 105,
which is, so about 10 and a half thousand feet.
And we were above the clouds.
It was, it was the most awesome flight.
I've, well, it was the, I don't know, it was, it was up there with the, with the trip over over to Khan, I guess.
But something, some other interesting and exciting things happened, which I'll just share with you very briefly.
The, we can't climb much higher than 10,000 feet without oxygen.
If you, in fact, the rule is you can be at 12,000 feet, but for no longer than 30 minutes.
And even then you still got to kind of look at each other.
Make sure you're not turning blue.
And the clouds all of a sudden start to rise above 10 and a half thousand feet.
We went through the top layer and we figured, well, we'll, we'll see what's on the other side of it.
If it, it might go down or it might go up.
It's hard to see.
You know, when you're to only at 10,000 feet.
But of course, at that flight level, the temperatures are freezing.
You go through the cloud and you build up ice.
So through the first, first bunch of tops of the clouds there, we had some ice build up.
And we requested flight level 12, one, two, five.
No, one, one, five.
And that still wasn't high enough.
And ice was building up pretty rapidly.
So we, we have down all the way down to.
Believe it or not, below three, that was like two and a half thousand feet.
That's how far we went down before we were out of the cloud.
And then we found ourselves in a restricted area, which I knew was there.
And you can request across the restricted area.
But these were like active, gunnery areas and the French military practice bases.
Which we could traverse if we were no more than 800 feet above ground level.
Otherwise, you have the, the chance of getting it.
Like, what's it?
Where do they fly there?
Mirages?
Mirage?
Or maybe it's F-16s.
I don't know.
You could get one of those up your ass.
And the weather was pretty crappy.
But landed at Antwerp, no problem after relatively short flight.
Only three hours from Conta to Antwerp.
And refueled.
And then I set off back to, back to Farrogues by myself.
Which really seemed like no big deal at all.
And you know, I've been flying so much lately.
So flying wise, great success.
Really, really had a fantastic time.
Can't wait to explore other farlands and meet children from other countries.
But it's confessible.
Now, this is something else.
This is a 12,000 advertising industry people descend upon the south of France.
I should have said false.
To talk about advertising.
Now, there's two things that really, the number one topic was very interesting to me.
And it really has the advertising world running quite scared.
And this really has nothing to do with our business.
This is more Google's business.
So it's a banners and ad cents.
You know, really click advertising, if you will.
Which, in my opinion, has nothing to do with brand advertising, but that's another story.
So now that Google has made the acquisition of what is a double click,
and 24, seven has been acquired.
So basically, you know, Microsoft Yahoo and Google, they all have these ad networks now.
And they are selling what they're buying.
It's kind of hard to explain, but they basically can go by inventory from themselves
and determine their own prices.
It's, you know, so the, in effect, cutting out the middle man being the media buyers.
So there was a lot of talk about that quite boring from my perspective.
But I did sit on a panel with, which was organized by Sean Finigan of OMD,
which is an agency in New York.
And we've done a lot of work with OMD and with Sean personally.
So I'm happy to oblige, of course.
This is the, you know, by this is how the advertising industry works.
You know, we all suck up each to, you know, suck up to each other as much as possible.
On this panel were a couple of the people, including as he was a guy from a Google
France, and there was a guy from juice.
France, I think.
No juice. He was from, I can't remember where he was from.
He was, he was like a, you know, like a director type guy.
I'm not quite sure what he was doing.
So then I don't know if they had a lot to say, the Google guy was, man,
those guys are walking like it's like they got 10 foot dicks.
Which I guess he can do.
But I sat next to when the miller.
And she is the chief sales officer at Yahoo.
And now we had, we really got into it with the other sparks were flying.
It was fun.
You know, she was talking about all this great information.
They had about about their users.
And I said, well, why don't you keep calling your audience users?
It doesn't sound very friendly unless you're a drug dealer.
And then I said, well, look at the end of the day, you're selling like banners.
You know, when is the last time someone called up an advertiser and said,
oh, man, thank you so much.
I clicked on that banner and it felt so incredibly good.
What a great experience.
Can't wait to click on another banner.
You know, and what I was trying to point out was that the advertising that we do
in our shows is a lot more fun.
At least I think so.
Anyway, so I'm sitting there.
I'm there with 12,000 advertising industry geeks.
It was all by myself.
No backup from HQ.
And you know, so I had to attend dinners.
And which I want to talk about later this one particular dinner and the conversation
I had with a couple folks, including Linda.
And what else was there?
Well, there's the infamous gutter bar.
So you have to go drink at the gutter bar, which is called the gutter bar,
because it's so many people go there.
It spills out into the streets and essentially the gutter.
So you can imagine that it was lonely.
It was just me in 12,000 geeks.
And the Wi-Fi was crappy.
And it was hot during the day, which one hand was nice.
But you know, it wasn't like I walk around in shorts.
Not that that's a very good look on me anyway.
And then all of a sudden, through the crappy Wi-Fi,
I see a shimmering twinkling light.
And it's a love message from soccer girl.
Hey Adam, this is soccer girl.
I wanted to thank you for being so nice about me and my show on your show.
I'm so totally excited that you showed my boobs to Hollywood.
It's so awesome. I'm totally psyched.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I didn't show your boobs to Hollywood.
In fact, they were, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I would keep those to myself.
No, I just said screw lonely girl 15.
This is the real deal.
Now, if they had watched the whole video all the way through,
of course, you know, all the way to the end,
you're two short stories.
And they would have seen, they would have seen the,
the, the mounds of the light.
So I don't know if they did that after we left the room.
But it was really just to accentuate.
They just looked at you after the burger came off.
And they went, wow.
I said indeed, that is soccer girl.
Except the only thing is that they're getting kind of
egotistical about it.
And, you know, it's like I'm so happy for them.
But they're totally rubbing it in.
I mean, you know, it's like hand out the be balls.
Let's get some throw yo celebrate, whatever.
But making me get hookers to snort cocaine off you.
She's kind of like,
it's kind of like, uh, drink them through.
I mean, don't you think I want to snort cocaine off of you?
Just makes me feel really bad.
Now I'm too upset to even continue this.
Thank you.
I hope you're happy.
Fuckin' boobs.
I'm sorry, Adam.
This isn't working.
I better try song.
Yo, Charlie.
Um, yeah, I think this one's for you.
You got a blaster ray on the brain.
It's a taste.
Won't get jay with me.
Teach I may seem a name.
Stratacaster cats are passing plants.
That you're adorable way free.
So many ways.
You want to make me.
Mr. Pod, father.
Girls want paint cars and not just daughters.
Also soccer.
You know, I'm kidding.
What are they like?
No, yeah.
Maybe.
Don't pony's in the moon.
Let me come fight.
Bring a pickle through a party.
Holden tie.
Curry curry.
That's a spicy attack.
Don't worry, Curry.
You know, I got your back.
This is the information that you don't yet have.
The trace amounts of semen and the evidence bag.
In this brigalogy season for being alive.
I'm a 30-style boxer with my lyrics aligned.
You're a hot potato cookie.
If it really is a win, can we get up to a drink over a soccer building?
Okay.
Thanks, Adam.
Love soccer, girl.
Oh, mean it.
Oh, yeah.
So you understand that I felt much better after that.
And then, of course, I got a call from Mark Yoshimaru,
Namcoff, and it ruined the entire vibe.
And I'll talk about him on Monday.
Let's see.
Yeah.
So it was all right.
It was one day too long, basically.
But otherwise, yeah.
And I think next year, I don't know.
I think business will come out of it, actually.
It should be interesting to see.
One thing was a little hard in France.
And in the South of France, everybody is fucking smoking everywhere.
Because you can, I think.
So I got to say, come July 1st when the smoking band rolls around
into the United Kingdom, I'm all for it.
It's hard enough, as is.
But then everybody just lighten up, you know, after a nice meal with some wine,
and then a drinking port, and then a smoking away.
Hi, Adam.
This is Andy from Guy Laplaba, and the German show about something.
I just wanted to say, you know, that you're not alone.
I also stopped smoking some weeks ago, and I have to, almost the same problems
in you, do.
Just listen to the following pre-compiles snippets of our last show,
and you will know what I mean, I guess.
And then you scream at me.
You had it at the end of the year, 360 gram.
And I'll start with the second one.
I'll wrangle you as well.
I'll burn you.
...
You're saying something like this?
I'll burn you.
What can I say?
I'm burning you.
I'll burn you.
So I like to be in my Wells Auto.
Working hard to get rid of the shit of the last 50 years of smoking,
I hope this is not going to last full next month.
for the next, I don't know, year or so. Keep up the good work. Welcome to Germany.
Folder. Yeah, don't care. Well, not quite in Germany yet. We got a lot of work to do still,
but we're working very, very hard on it. Man, I thought it was 15 years. Actually, I've been
smoking 25 years. Can you believe? Can you imagine what damage I've already done to, not just
my lungs with my heart, crap. And, and I'm glad that for these past three weeks and really
glad that it's been three weeks, it's been more than three weeks, hasn't it? I'm happy, man,
because geez, Louise, I don't think I'd be able to make it through. What have we done?
I remember so well, only two and a half years ago. Hey, yeah, man, come on. We could totally do this. I know
we can create a whole new media industry. It'll be fun. And it is fun, but crap, we forgot how much
work it was. This week's hit test for the second week in a row is brought to you by Coca-Cola.
This summer, when you buy Coke, you get music. You can win an iPod or free songs on iTunes.
One girl in casting with Adam Curry. Hey, Adam, are you ready to be stumps?
Oh yeah, good. He's the one who picked it up with young pro back. Hey, Adam, this is a hit test number
75th right fourth in a row now on the daily source code. Yep. So I'm very anxious to know how things are
going to develop in the near future. So if you know more, be sure to let me know, okay? I want
short clips in the fourth three answer. So here we go. This is the number one.
Oh, please, please, please. It's a bright Adam's Tina Turner. It's only love. And that's all. How could you
and everybody knows that intro? Don't think? And number two.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, you know, the one on the sailboat.
And the final one.
But...
Again?
I'm going to say that was uh, uh, uh, was it building a bridge to my heart? Uh, godly and queen?
And again, they were pretty easy. So let's go to the answers right away. This is one.
All right, from 1985, Brian Adams and Tina Turner.
And Tony Love.
Oh, I feel you said it.
There ain't no secret to you.
Go to work.
And it's Tony Love.
Yes.
Hey, you better go now.
Oh, man.
That takes me back, y'all.
Tony Love.
It's Tony Love.
And that's all.
Adam's in turn and it's Tony Love.
And this is from 85 as well.
Durand, Durand.
You saw me standing.
Yeah, but what's the title?
I got, it's on the sailboat, right?
Thanks, Jimmy.
Don't say the proud of all of me now.
Sit, say the prayer.
Save it till the morning after.
I think I could vote points for number two.
Durand, Durand, and save a crack.
And this is answer number three.
Yeah.
And it's all wrong.
I'm losing sleep.
And look at what you say.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
From 1987, and so number three in this week's hit list.
Wakes and building a bridge through your hearts.
And listen for this week.
Hope you did well, Adam.
They're a pretty easy game.
I think I got three, three, four points.
So please let me know how things will develop and will continue in the near future.
Hope you'd like the clips I used in this hit list.
So until next time, take care.
I'm for a Drex, and I tuned links.
Check hit test.pachel.com, all right?
Okay, until next time, bye-bye.
Be back.
Hit test at gmail.com.
www.gmail.com
You are a magician, my friend.
Now what are you kind of here, Jon, refer into it.
I said that we do a four week trial,
bringing back the hit test under the
Fair use policy because of course the hit test is a production of the organization for preservation for the soundtrack of our lives.
You never hear this shit on the radio anymore.
So we might as well at least remind you of what it sounded like,
even though we can't play full tracks.
And of course, if you go to hittest.podge.com,
you can find all of the original hit test files and links to the iTunes music store where you can buy the songs that are featured.
So does it get any better than that?
I don't think so.
And yes, Jon, we will be continuing.
As you can tell, sponsors have really picked up on the whole idea of the hit test.
They love it.
Coke two weeks in a row now.
So, Jon, don't quit the day job yet.
But my friend, we've got ourselves a gig.
I was afraid, I was petrified.
Can't think he might have could never leave without you boss.
But I spent so many nights just thinking how you did the role.
And I grew strong.
And I learned how to get along.
And so you're back.
From that is based.
I just was in the vine here.
When I said look upon your face,
I should have changed my stupid luck.
Maybe you keep it by and don't but just one second.
You be back to bother me.
Go on level.
Walk out the door.
Just turn around now.
Cause you're not welcome anymore.
Where to the one who tried to hurt me with.
Good bye.
And you think I grew more and more.
The thing was late.
I didn't lie.
I don't know that.
I will survive.
Whoa, as long as I know how to love.
I don't want to see you like.
Cause I've got a moment to live.
And I've got a moment to get and I'll survive.
I'll survive.
It took all the time.
I have enough to follow up.
Get time on the pieces of the wrong.
But I spent so many nights just thinking how you did the role.
And I said I don't cry.
But now I hold my head up high and you see me.
Somebody need me.
I'm up that chain of little persons in and all with you.
When so you felt like dropping in.
I just expect me to be free.
But now I say they know my love.
And of course I'm one who's all in me.
Go on level.
Walk out the door.
Just turn around now.
Cause you're not welcome anymore.
Where to the one who tried to break me with.
Good bye.
You think I grew more and more.
The thing I laid out and now you know that.
I'm the one who's all right.
Oh, it's all because I know I'm not alone.
I feel like it's all because I'm alone.
But I've to live and I've got to live.
I've to keep and I'm so right.
I will survive.
Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
eeeeeeeoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
but I love to love.
You know I love stuff like that you know it sounds a lot like not only does it sound like
the list of his bitties or the type of cocktail pop music they would do but of course
the darling lady Patricia who by the way offered to come on the show today I say no
I know it's a full bar I wouldn't want you to get hurt come on the show Monday and
so she's she's I think she's really wants to so that's good
So I, you know, I won't have to twist her arm on Monday.
Thank you, Spuds, from the Mr. Hey, Mr. Jesse podcast, show that I listened to regularly.
Have you heard the group the papini sisters?
Well, that's what y'all just heard now with their rendition of Gloria Gainers, I will
survive.
We featured them on the June edition of Hey, Mr. Jesse, along with the Star Sisters,
as Jesse did around up of awesome female vocal groups.
Of course, the papini sisters aren't prods safe, but at least give them a listen.
And of course, they will have a link to the, you know, to the papini sisters website.
It is the papini sisters dot com, but links to that as always in the show notes at
dailystoresco.com.
Yo, well, yeah, it seems to be catching on Andrew Grummit from Engineering at HQ,
who checks in with an update.
Hey, Adam, it's Andrew Grummit here, or should I say eight to the G and I've got a dev team update
from HQ.
This update is a new enhancement to the site that we'll be pushing live today,
or depending on when your listeners are tuning in yesterday, or maybe even a while ago.
And this update contained, is Andrew, is Andrew, did this, like, on his headset,
or seems like he did it late at night somehow?
All right, let's listen to the update.
Means a new feature on the episode upload page for podcasts.
The way the page used to work was that you would select your file and enter all the information
and hit the send button and then you wait and it's some future unknown time.
The file upload would complete and you could check to see that everything went okay.
On the new page, or really it's just the same page with a new feature.
The default will be to report progress as the file uploads into the system.
This was an experimental feature.
Up until this point, you could click a link to try an experimental page.
But now we've integrated the experience into the regular upload page and made it standard.
So podcasters will be able to monitor the progress and see exactly what's happening.
And when they can expect the file upload to complete.
So we hope that it will work flawlessly.
But wait, I have Linux and I can't use flashlight.
Much testing to ensure that there are no surprises, but just in case.
Or if your browser doesn't support the.
I use the rendering technology, which is based in flash eight or later.
There's a check box at the bottom and you can just click it.
It reads click here to use the standard uploader.
And if you click that check box, the upload should work as it did before.
So we hope everyone will enjoy all the podcasters out there.
We'll enjoy this feature.
And that's that's it for now.
As you know, we're working on.
Some fairly exciting new stuff with channels.
I just sent you an email update actually about some new work we're doing there.
But we'll have to leave that as a tease for the moment.
And hopefully that piece will be coming out fairly shortly as we get it in shape.
Okay, that's all for me for now.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
So far we're, let's see, there's about 100 people at Pod Show now.
We've had three of them calling with updates.
Not bad, 3% of the company is called into the show.
I'm expecting more.
I don't know where it's going to come from, but I am expecting more.
So yeah, Andrew did send me a he and Devon are working on on the channel.
Actually, we're doing it to the three of us.
I love working with the developers this way where I can just, I haven't,
I've given them any feedback yet, but I can give them feedback on stuff that they're developing.
And it's a, it's a beautiful loop that just did to we reiterate over and over again,
and stuff just starts to happen.
So the, the channel module that you have, that if you have a Pod Show account,
the channel module now, what I have working in, in the lab.
I don't have it working, but what I'm, what I'm, when I'm allowed into the lab to play,
to play with the toys, you can collect either shows or episodes,
put them in any order you want, visual drag and drop stuff.
And it comes out the other end on the feed exactly the way you put them in there.
So it's not reordering it.
And you can say, I only want to have one episode of the show appeared any, any given time.
I'm going to be putting all kinds of examples up.
As soon as this gets pushed to the production servers, which I think will be pretty quickly.
Because, well, because it's just going so fast,
and it's really just reorganizing the things we already have.
I'm not trying to downplay the code.
These guys are writing, but we already have so much of it already in place.
So I hope we'll be able to start playing with it very soon.
I got to put a, you know, a couple other buttons there, so that, you know,
be like a play in the dashboard, put it on your iPod.
And yes, we will resurface the orange on, or the white on orange XML buttons.
And people are getting pretty excited about building channels because this stuff really does work.
Hello, Adam.
This is Clyde J. Kelly, the voice of the old-time radio shows that were broadcast on the serious satellite.
Now, we're beginning to year with Pod Show.
I just want to call you about your, just channel matching our channel mix up on the Pod Show network.
I tried this and had a remarkable results about Friday or Saturday.
I got a site on there. It's an MP IR dot podshow dot com.
It's an old-time radio site, of course.
And I had some shows along with some other channels with other providers that I use.
And I have a remarkable thing happened Sunday.
I had over within a five hour period, over 6,600 downloads on just one of my,
the Pod Feets. And all I can say is it's probably due to the podshow dot com channel mixing service.
It'd be nice when we can actually publish the entire channel feed to the world.
It's interesting to see the results there.
To start, let you know, I've been listening to the daily source code ever since the first year when I was honored to host the old-time radio shows on the serious network.
And I like your content. Keep it to good work.
I like it.
And let me thank you and your network for doing such a great job on preserving these public domain programs that are not,
you know, they're not that far from what we're doing today.
And I'm so happy that you've seen how powerful channels can be.
And it's really interesting because people who know nothing about RSS and the underlying technology,
and immediately catch on to the fact of how you can mash all this stuff together.
But people who are much more hardcore,
you know, with the underpinnings of the delivery mechanisms we use on the internet.
And like, well, you know, they sometimes don't see it.
But for the first time, have you ever sat there and thought,
I should put this out on a feed,
but it's like individual things and I've got a hand code,
something, or I've got to get a WordPress blog to, you know,
or use feed burner to be able to,
just had another great idea.
Crap.
Hold on, let me just write this down for a second.
I can't tell you what it is.
Oh, man, my brain just fired.
Oh, geez.
Oh, man. Why was I smoking?
Okay.
You can literally create a feed of anything you want,
just by dragging and dropping stuff and hitting, you know,
you don't have to hit anything.
If they hit save, it just works.
And it plays in sequence and it, that poops out as nor assess feed and
sequence and poops out as a stream in sequence.
Oh, we're going to have so much fun.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes. Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
Let me see what else I get here.
Oh, this was, this was interesting.
You know, I have a live 365.com account.
And this is a company that allows you to stream.
That's kind of weird.
Can't quite seem to get the anyway.
They allow you to to create streams.
They have like 10,000 streams.
I pay a small fee and it actually covers or used to cover some of the,
the licensing for the music if you want to put music in your feed.
And of course, now with the copyright royalty,
it was at the, the copyright royalty board imposing new and
improved fees for streaming radio internet radio,
which by the way, this is also internet radio,
and depending on how it's internet radio that you can take with you,
that you don't have to be connected to the internet to receive it.
On June 26 from 3 a.m. Pacific to midnight,
all 10,000, the live 365 streams will be redirected to a special stream.
They're calling for a day of darkness, basically.
A day of silence, they're going to silence all internet radio streams,
which is interesting.
I guess they want to bring attention to it by out raging listeners.
I don't think that's the right idea.
And by the way, please have a look at the pod safe music network,
and have a look at the pod safe music network license,
because since it's a pre-arranged agreement,
you won't have to pay any fees over it.
You'll probably have to pay your 400 bucks a year or 500 bucks per channel.
I don't think you can get out of that, which is, of course, kind of crazy.
But you won't have to pay any other fees,
because it's pre-arranged, and the artists are happy,
and the labels are happy for you to play it as pure promotion.
So, that's just a tip from the kid on a football Friday.
Your Honor, I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Your Honor, please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out, let's all give a night.
To the hardest work in the lawyer, he's Jersey Typing in.
He's Jersey Typing in.
Here on a year, what's going on by an atom?
It's Jersey Typing, the official musicologist of the Cha Cha.
Dude, every week I am just absolutely amazed about the talent and quality
that's coming up on the positive music network,
and this week is no exception, at least.
This week I've got somebody absolutely fantastic for his name.
Well, I like his name a lot.
It's Todd Carey out of Illinois.
Probably Chicago Todd, but that's not the point,
because the point is that he has just got such a great song up on the PMman.
It's called Inkot Love.
And darn it, this song is darn near inspirational.
I'm really, really into what I love the slow build.
Check this out.
It's Inkot Love by Todd Carey.
On, you're from Bar Friday, check this out.
I got friends.
Mmm, so sweet.
To sing to when I'm passing on the street.
I got my guitar.
To play when I'm down.
And my group full loud enough to rock this town.
But it all comes down.
Nothing in the end.
But you ain't got that.
But it all ends.
Nothing in the end.
But you ain't got that.
Where I know.
I want to sing.
But just another funny guitar boy in me.
And I know.
To go my time.
But still I'm really into the fact I'm right.
That all comes down.
Nothing in the end.
But you ain't got that.
But it all ends.
Nothing in the end.
But you ain't got that.
I got my vibe.
So it's all in my mind.
It's clean when it's cold.
And I got my clothes.
And tear my foot.
But I still don't have a word.
But it all comes down to nothing in the end.
But when you ain't got that.
But you ain't got that.
But it all ends.
Nothing in the end.
But you ain't got that.
But it all comes down.
Todd, once again, truly the official music colleges of the Charlie, inspiring is correct.
For Melanoi, he's got love, Todd Carrey, brand new on the plot team music network, and on the Charlie.
Oh, I knew that, boom, boom, boom, it didn't happen, it didn't come, oh my god, what are we gonna do?
Let's have a word with the Nile, let's spread the news with the smile on where the role of light.
We're in your polite, let's listen to the Nile, no food bars complete without him.
Hey Adam, it's the Nile on.
Maybe.
I've got my beard and blonde wig on, I go into high and as you suggest it.
You won't recognize me from that one.
But after yesterday's show, I guess, all I can start up by saying is D-D-D.
I-I-I-C-C-K-K-K testing, testing, anyone there testing?
But no, what I really want to call was being a self-pulcane, good versus jank expert.
I want to get credit to the brits for finally getting one over the yanks, and that's in the form of Mr. David Beckett.
Who's Sunday has many no-players last game, it's Real Madrid, and as you pay K-Papers fail to really focus on,
they're losing one nothing for the 60-plus minutes he was playing.
A substitute comes in, his substitute scores are gold, and they score three goals in the 20-plus minutes that he's not playing.
Which is to the point, which is David Beckett doesn't score goals.
He does assist, as you record, we record in the US.
You have basketball, you have a search, and baseball, you have sacrifice, flies.
He's not a pay lay, he's not going to run up and down the field scoring goals.
It's a big sham for the Galaxy of the 80-150 million.
People are going to be crowding the stadium looking for Beckett to score, and he's going to do a great kick.
It's going to bounce off some nuts head, and then go out of bounds.
It's not going to work.
It's a great thing the brits have done.
They are finally gotten back at the yanks.
So, in the world of international football soccer, I think it's the brits one, and the yanks nothing.
Of course, for the fifth, and credit to David Beckett.
And for the guy in New York, he should try the time outsidetimeout.com, which has a New York section, which is very good,
and New York Magazine.com, which has a section above all the things happening in New York.
So, I hope you flight was fine, and I'm hoping you were landing.
You won't go in landing, Charlie, two, two, two, three, three, three.
It was the same.
Anyway, let me put my mustache and wait back on.
Please do head back out.
Yeah, it was funny when I thank you, Nylon.
By the way, I have no fucking clue what you were talking about.
It's just like you almost put a downer on the food bar.
The food bar, man.
I got to get rid of the nylon first, hold on.
Oh, he's nylon.
I'll spokin' it, fake treat.
He's in London, buddies from New York.
Whoa, he's nylon.
Controversy on nylon.
He's in London, buddies from New York.
On a, when I came back, it was, so the weather was getting,
starting to get pretty crappy.
It was a little bit windy, crosswind.
I said, look, I'm going to join base leg,
because there wasn't a lot of traffic,
which means they don't have to fly a full circuit.
And I'm on long final, and Alister, who's, he's a real old-time aviation dude.
He was manning the tower.
And so he says, you know, number 277,
Delta shared land to your discretion.
And you know, I think I'm being nice and I say,
okay, clear land, long fine, also they know that I'm coming in from a long way out.
And it was like, no, land at your discretion.
Oh, crap.
Sorry, landing in my discretion.
Apparently, it's not exactly the same thing.
It must be a legal thing, I don't know.
What's going on here today?
It's Friday.
Well, I'll see if I can get this out properly.
So I had two very interesting conversations,
which were non-advertising related.
One was with the executive assistant of the Havas agency.
He was a Iranian.
And you know, it's, of course, I had to mention that,
you know, she'd been back two years ago.
She'd been back to visit family in Iran.
And she speaks Persian.
She speaks French.
She speaks English, obviously.
Very, very interesting woman.
And I said, you know, I've been to Iraq.
And we were just chatting back and forth.
And you know, we were talking about how crazy it is that, you know,
that these apparently the United States and Iran hate each other.
And I was like, yeah, man, you know, it's like,
it's like, it's a very, it does are like modern countries.
And they've got iPods and cell phones.
And she was agreeing with me, of course.
And she gave me a very amazing statistic that this about 80 million people
in Iran, of which 50% is younger than 25 years old.
And that they are all over the place with blogging.
Of course, it's all in Persian.
And you know, I said, well, he has your job clearly.
You've got to start translating some stuff and getting the word out there.
Because apparently they're really well connected,
a bunch of folks over there.
And we should be able to communicate with them.
And they also speak perfect English.
So that was kind of mulling in my head.
And then I had dinner with Sean Finnegan from OMD with,
I told you about when the chief sales officer for Yahoo.
And I forgot his name.
Top guy at the BBDO advertising agency.
And I'm hearing them talk about the democratic nomination.
You know, who's going to be the democratic nominee?
And you know, it was all this talk about Hillary.
And I think when it actually knows Hillary and then you're about Obama.
And then it was, you know, it kind of,
and I was being very quiet.
You know, the conversation moved over to, well, you know,
what it's, you know, look at what happens to you if you're president.
Like look at Bill Clinton, you know, as hard when he turned gray.
George Bush, same thing, you know, that's somewhere.
And then they get that glassy.
I'd look, which I equated to the same as, you know,
any superstar celebrity has that.
You know, it's just you get hammered at all the time.
So how he not eventually get the glassy I'd look.
And then something interesting happened is like
the conversation turned a little bit like, well,
gee, I'd hate to have that job.
And I said, you know, kind of, I just got a stop here for a second.
You know, and there was all kinds of other discussion about how the world
hates America and, like, well, first of all,
any American should be really proud to be president.
I mean, I know I'd never get elected,
but damn, I really, I'd be very proud to, you know,
to work for the American people.
It would be fantastic.
You know, and then, you know, it's like, well, yeah,
but, you know, that's your only job,
but listen and George will be Bush doesn't listen.
I said, look, dude, he doesn't make all the decisions.
We have something called, like, you know, Congress.
We got the Senate.
You know, it's almost become a joke to say, you know,
write your congressmen if you're unhappy,
but you actually have to because that's how shit gets done.
And there were some, some thought there for a second.
And then it would, you know, it quickly turned to immigration.
And well, you know, we got people coming into the country
and they're taking advantage of the system.
And, well, stop again.
What do you mean taking advantage of the system?
Yeah, illegal immigrants.
They're what fucking system?
What health care?
They're taking advantage of that schooling.
Free schooling.
And there's like, well, yeah, I can put it that way.
I guess you're right.
So no, please, I just want to make one thing very clear.
I've lived in a number of countries.
I've worked in a number of countries.
And the United States of America,
if you're willing to fucking do something,
get up off your ass and get it done,
that's the place for you.
If not, stay in France.
35 hour work week.
Take your time.
If you're sick, you can, you know,
and everything's paid for.
You can, oh, even if you have no job,
you can probably take a vacation.
If you want the socialist way,
that's fine.
And lots of people love that.
But the United States, I found myself
just becoming all patriotic.
I didn't know.
And I'm not even necessarily a Democrat
or a Republican.
But just the words came out
and the more I thought about it,
the happier I got.
And I said, yeah, you know,
I'm sorry.
I don't think the world hates America.
It's the same thing with the Iranians
and with us.
It's like, we're all the same people.
We all have the same shit.
We've all got iPods.
We know how to blog.
We're starting to talk with each other
around all this other crap that's going on,
which we do have to fix by the way.
But I think I got through to some people there.
And I don't know.
It just felt good.
So there's no real moral to the story
other than I'm really proud to be an American.
I don't think the world hates us.
And we have some shit to fix.
And we're going to fix it.
We'll do our best at least.
But crap.
No one's country is perfect.
But just, you know, I think some flying up high
had something to do with it as well.
When you look down on the earth and you just think,
all those issues that people have and all the crap
that's going on, it seems.
So petty.
So my news.
It's so small.
We're on this little fucking nut.
Yeah, we're in it together.
We really should check ourselves.
I can only contribute to television.
We've all been completely fucking hypnotized by crap that's on TV.
Of course, you know, I couldn't leave you with that.
I couldn't let that be the final thing of the week for you.
I got to roll it out with one of my favorite songs of all time,
which a copy of which was sent to me by Tom Scuding.
That, of course, is the official biographer of my media life.
Good old Tom down there in Australia.
And I guess we found on one of the tapes that he's been digitizing.
But this is one of my favorite songs of all time, and he's right.
And Cigaya was fortunate enough to meet,
and he is just as awesome as the song.
Michael Martin Murphy.
And Wildfire on a football Friday.
She comes down yellow mountain.
On a dark flat land she rides.
On a pony she named Wildfire.
When the whirlwind by her side.
On a comb of breath tonight.
Oh they say she died on winter.
When there came a killing frost.
And the pony she named Wildfire.
Busted down its door.
In a Blizzard he was lost.
She ran calling Wildfire.
By the dark of the moon I planted it.
But there came an early snow.
There's been a who'd out having by my window now.
For six nights in a row.
She's coming from me and I know.
And the wildfire will be riding wildfire.
With the riding wildfire.
On wildfire we're gonna ride her.
We're gonna leave.
So you know whether you're American British, French, German,
We're all people of the world.
We've all got iPods.
That's proof.
For people of the world.
For to sing you on Monday with a lovely lady Patricia.
He good.
Another pot show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pot show and limelight.