Hello everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code episode number 603 coming to you from the
Curry Manor located in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guilford West Side
a town of course. A little bit later today on publishing the show because I'm on a new
regime now. Oh yes, I've got a new attitude and a new regime. I went for a lot of exercise
with the Lady Patricia. Apparently she does this thing every single day, but it consists
of walking up and down numerous hills and valleys and walking for it seems like miles and
actually working up a sweat and low and behold, real exercise taking place. And I've got
a scheduled into the rest of my busy life, but I've got to do it. Why? Well, of course,
for approximately 21 years Patricia has been nagging at me to start living in a little bit
healthier life, which includes not smoking. As you know, I'm into notorious self-medicator,
which means, oh, by the way, I quit smoking last night. Anything of the tobacco related family,
but since I used to self-medicate with tobacco combined with other bits and bobs and just going
all the other bits and bobs pure. If you know what I'm talking about, I can't function. I'll just
have to live like a normal person until the end of the day when it's time for, well, you know,
when the sun goes over to the yard arm and we can relax a little bit. So two major changes. Why?
Well, besides Patricia, whispering my ear for years, another angel visited me yesterday and
and really freaked me out. So we'll talk about that on today's daily source code.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
In theory, where TV networks, movie studios and record labels, still think they can
govern what you see in here. One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses
and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants. From Pod Show, home of the world's
most dangerous new content comes the daily source code with Adam Curry.
So we'll talk about that on today's daily source code, so we'll talk about that on today's daily source code,
so we'll talk about that on today's daily source code, so we'll talk about that on today's daily source code,
so I promise that he and I in Patricia would have dinner together in his offices in Soho, so that's we went to Sketch,
which is it's a cool restaurant, the bathroom's a little weird because you have to go in these eggs, it's kind of like a more cramork capsule,
in fact it's exactly like a more for more capsule, Keith of course, the style was late and he had never met Patricia,
I have to say he was blown away by her, in fact I think for two and a half hours I had to listen to him compliment her,
and so near the end of the evening and then we had a great time and you were talking about all kinds of cool stuff,
so we're going to be doing with Potchio UK and hey Germany is happening later, we'll talk more about that, just remind me,
so he now of course, Super Agent Keith is special because he's a clairvoyant of course,
and he can speak to the afterlife, now you have to understand if you haven't been listening to this show for a while,
my wife, the lady Patricia, is a witch, a white witch of course, but she is completely in touch with all the earth elements and stuff,
it's not like it doesn't, you know, pray to week hour or whatever, but she's a witch, she has powers, I'm sure of it,
and I could tell that these two were definitely connecting on that level and Keith reads her poem and he says,
oh look, oh I can see exactly you have a pain between the second and third vertebrae and it's a couple other things,
he said, which is it was exactly spot on and he said, but you're going to live to be a hundred, no problem,
and then he said, oh let me look at your hand at him, and this is the worst thing that can happen to you,
we look at your hand and he goes, oh yeah, okay, let's you know, like like the the the card, the black card of death,
pop to the top of the deck, and I was like, no no dude, but read it, now you got to tell me and he's like,
well, you have to be careful for diabetes, for high blood pressure, and hold on a second, your grandmother's talking to me,
and he was pretty good at accurately describing it, so I have no reason to believe that he wasn't receiving
some form of signal, he says, you got to stop smoking man, by September 15th or 16th, and you have to stage
manager life otherwise you'll be fucked up and your lifeline reflects that. So you can imagine how
I was like dude, we had a great evening and you bummed me out, and so of course,
now I have like two witches on my ass, so I'm like the new things immediately and change it up and
whack it about, and sometimes I can even overdo it if I like to.
Hey Adam, how's it going? Hey Adam, how's it going? Yeah, pretty good, I've got to exercise more.
Are you ready for a fun new ass move? Oh, give me some ass moves. Today, we're doing
Cizurkicks line on the floor. Cizurkicks line. So get yourself situated and lay down on your back.
Oh my back, okay. I'm into it now, I need to. Are you ready? No, hold on, yeah.
Okay, now you're laying flat, lift your legs a couple of inches and cross the right over the left.
Then separate them and repeat with the left over the right. You're like should be doing the same
motion as you would if you were making a snowy angel. The arms go under your butt for support
and your head and shoulders lift off the ground a couple of inches. Oh, shit. You do this
continuously for 20 seconds. Okay, I'm doing it count me down baby. Really concentrate on breathing
and squeezing the ab and butt. Okay, and I'm breathing. You should be looking up at the ceiling.
Okay, oh Amy, it's an obstacle. Don't let that back arch. Oh, shit. Okay.
Almost done. Deep breath. And they're walking. And come down. Good job.
Can I get up? I'll see you in a few days and until next time.
And then you should try that one. You, you hold on me and move every mic back to its original position there.
Amy Mack, you know, she does a number of shows and there's a whole new health and fitness
channel, which is just about to be, I mean, there's so much good stuff happening. In fact,
I saw a press release today. I wonder, hold on a second. I don't get to my docs. There we go.
I'm using Google Docs, of course. Let me see if it's saved. Excuse me. This program brought to you
in part by time and all p.m. You know, that the NGB show that's sponsored by time and all p.m.
That's really doing quite well. Yeah. Okay, so I'm going to leave the bits out that I can't mention.
So name here, the popular columnist author and broadcaster has been named VP Managing Editor
of the fill and name channel at pachow.com. I guess that's all I can say right now.
But it's pretty cool. I'm excited about him starting. They've press releases get approved.
Hey, this is really nice for for our little industry here. Comscore, which is a well-respected measurement
system. And I guess they do more than just, what does Comscore do? Comscore, they track visits and
unique, but they've done some study work here on on podcasting. And let's see, Comscore
study reveals that males between the ages of 18 to 24 are more likely to download podcast via
iTunes. I'm not sure what good that is. But there's some interesting information in this report.
Or at least the summary of the report. Let's see, podcasting also popular among 35 to 54
year olds. And I love this higher income, better educated consumer segments. Hey, in other words,
we got smart motherfuckers doing this. Let's see, 18 to 24 year olds represented a substantial
share of the audience, 20 percent, and one more than twice as likely as the average internet user
to download podcast. People between the ages 35 to 54 represent about half of the podcasting
audience and are also more likely than average to download podcast. So I put a link to whatever this is,
I'm not going to show where to come from. I don't know. It's a press release. So I'll put that
up on daily source code.com so you could check it out. A lot of response. Yes, I do.
It was quite cool. We had the hit test. The young pull at the sent in yesterday. And if
email, of course, exploding. So I think we can actually pull this off as fair use under the,
which of course means it can't be sponsored and it can't really, unless it's paid for by the
government education fund. If we treated it as an educational moment where helping people understand
music and the importance of it, we can kind of get away with it as long as not playing a whole
track. You know, of course, we have the half second rule now that the young put in place. And if we
shorten, oh, gosh darn. Is that a part of the whole exercise thing? I'm supposed to just like be
bourbon. Let me see what else can we do here. Oh, show girls. Remember, they were whining a couple of weeks
ago and Franklin sent in a comment and it's kind of, you know, it's I can't quite explain it,
but I find myself like not being able to not listen to the show because sometimes, and they actually
had an explicit tag on this one. Sometimes they do take their conversations a bit far. When you
get like six or seven women sitting together. And I wonder if this is how a women really talk.
Of course, it's on Skype or something like that. So it's not a completely natural conversation.
But on the most recent episode, they talk about a lot of things. And for some reason, they started
sharing their Adam Curry moments. That's kind of listen to it. That's my little Adam's story. Thank
you. That's nicely, nicely described. That was pod chick. She did a whole thing too long time ago.
Let's get your Adam moment and how did you get into pod casting? Since we're on the topic.
Can I as well? Oh, wow. It was you, Frank. I think it was you. That's the room of girls.
Frank, you got to Adam moment. So Frank is the person who got me into pod casting. Sorry.
I'm just kidding. But um, when my Adam moment is probably when I met him, and he thought he was
really a nice guy. I just met him quickly. I didn't really get to talk to him too much, but
when the grab is gone, when the grab is fine. I don't remember any of this. I think we
met at the the first pod cast, Expo. I don't remember any ass grabbing. Is this the way the
girls remember? I think I would have remembered. Only I've limited time. I don't have time to
just sit around and talk to everybody else. Right to the good. I feel rough. I got to talk to
him, but I didn't get to grab him. Well, it scares me not everybody's allowed to. So, I mean,
to him, I think he's done what I didn't get to him. But, so maybe I need to do something to try.
I mean, I talked to him. Karen hasn't talked to him. I haven't grabbed his butt. I mean, we should call
him instead. Is that soccer girl saying that she needs to grab my butt? If with him, maybe we need
our Adam moment. We need to have our time. Now we, we haven't really talked to him.
Sad to say, but my Adam, I'm saying, we should, we should totally put together an audio thing
of all of us or however many of us to send Adam. Yeah. Yeah. We should get him on our show.
Frank, we talked him that one time, but, you know, we still haven't talked to him, so I think we
this is true. He needs to talk to the ladies. And by the way, PW Fenton is on this show.
And he's on the, you know, what's up with that? I used to go listen to it. It's a showgirls
that podshow.com. Let's listen to it. We need to do some sort of promo, something or other
for the daily source code, too. Yeah, make it sexy. Make it sexy. Let's see if Adam would come on the show.
Maybe, maybe when he's back in America, he could do it. No, you guys got to convince me if you
really want me to do that. I can't see, uh, this is Chris Ayer, confident.
I'm gonna get my money to burn. I'm gonna have a dog out of it. Yeah, it's all good.
We'll take the look and says a curse. I'm sure, we'll watch dirty. I'm treating you up here. I got a good
left up to get my way through. So I have left up and sing about the joy. But then I'm gonna bring
like a person in the old man. And I'm tired with someone. Another guy in the old, you know,
the things that I think are awful right now. I could use it, yeah. But I know I won't use it,
but now I could use a carpet on. Children these days drink red wine,
but find their glory in design and never stood perfect and integrated.
I bloody burn and a curse and fight, you take your wings so that you might as soon
learn a puppet shit up, find the meat. But ain't it greedy at home? He this buddy never
learns and takes his over time and gets a money to burn. He's a lovely dog out and looking for the
day. What do you know, this is a curse? I'm sure, we'll watch dirty. I'm treating you up here.
You got a good left up to get your spray clear. Can I get left up and sing about the joy?
But I'm gonna bring like a person in the old man. And I'm tired with someone. Another guy in the
old, you know, the things that I think are awful right now. I could use it, yeah. But now I'm
only using it right now. I could use it, yeah. Square pink, around hole, an unreleased soul,
with enough sandpaper. You're gonna think just fine. Square pink, around hole,
an unreleased soul, with enough sandpaper without cement, with enough memories,
without the regret. You gonna think just fine, you don't think just fine. I live but I've ever learned.
I take my over time and get my money to burn. I'm another dog out and looking for the day.
You're gonna think just fine. I'm sure, we'll watch dirty. I'm treating you up here.
You got a good left up to get your spray clear. You got a good left up to get your spray clear.
But now I'm gonna bring like a person in the old man. And I'm tired with someone.
Another guy in the old, you know, the things that I think are awful right now. I could
use you well. But now I'm only using it right now. I could use it, yeah.
Oh, I see it. But now I could use you.
Yeah, tell me you don't like that, huh?
It comes in.
Yeah, it's got pretty cool. It's Chris A.
One, the 2006 John Lennon Award for the songwriting.
For a songwriting in the folk category.
Home town is, uh, I was at the McLean, uh, Virginia.
I think it's from New York now. And of course, that's from the Ponce Hip music network.
Hey, you know, so I'm getting a little sweaty here. And I'm going to cut it short. Oh, by the way,
obviously, uh, no trip, uh, no flying today. Once again, just completely crap.
Hey.
All right, uh, see, you know what?
Check this out. I was just looking around for my lighter for the sign off.
Of course not.
Uh, daily source code.com for links to everything in today's show notes.
Uh, Adam at podshow.com.
Uh, help me get me through the night, please.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.