Are you tired of that yet?
Me too.
This is Matt DiTilo of Matt's Today in History, and on this day in 2007, I helped
pod show suck a little less by putting together a shorter blur of asking you, a podcast
producer and listener, to visit suckless.podshow.com, and sign up to participate in some
pod show surveys that will make a difference.
Once the last time a media company asks for your opinion, never, well then, let's make some
history together, visit suckless.podshow.com, and get involved.
So you expect a football Friday, on the DSC638?
Well, guess what?
It's not going to happen.
So Adam claims he got busy with the board meeting, but really I think he was reading Harry
Potter.
Oh well, here's your DSC638, a little less.
Well, please allow me to introduce myself, I mean, well, the taste, I've been around for a long
year.
So many amazes.
Now many amazes.
We got a crisis going on over here. I don't know if you've followed on the news by now is probably spread around the globe that
we have severe flooding throughout the United Kingdom. Mainly in the north that is now really spread to the Midlands.
England as we've called Wales and now even to parts of the southeast. Yes, even London is witnessing this.
Let me tell you Friday morning. Of course, the whole day started off food barred as it would on a Friday just by this horrible, horrible weather.
In the M25 flooded there were the M40, not that I have to travel over that but just giving an example. People were stuck for seven hours in traffic.
We have water plants closing because they've been contaminated by flooding. We have power station shutting down. It's pretty damn bad here.
It really is already insurer saying it's going to cost 2 billion pounds. That's 4 billion dollars or a week in Iraq.
It's just unbelievable what's going on. I know I predicted good weather for this week. I'm not going to revise that I will say we're not going to see such a dumping of rain like we've seen over the past two to three days really.
It was just horrible. I actually took the train in avoiding the highways.
Trains were slowed down. They couldn't go as fast because of the accumulation of water.
I think I was also something about slippery tracks. I'm not quite sure. It was difficult getting into town.
Town was heavy, heavy traffic. There was just tons to do.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, meeting after meeting. That's some fascinating people who will be starting some shows with.
If you've ever heard of the medium Gordon Smith, I had a great great meeting with him also the barefoot doctor who actually, you know,
if we're going to do a show with someone who calls himself the barefoot doctor and says he can cure you just by, you know, by using his hands.
I'm like, shit, cure me, baby. You know, remember, I don't know if a long time listeners were recall that I once fell asleep on an airplane.
American Airlines going from, let me think. I think it was maybe Los Angeles or San Francisco to Miami.
Maybe it was New York to Miami. And I fell asleep on my, on the palm of my hand and really messed up a nerve.
The result is that for the past two and a half years, you know, my left index finger is just a tiny bit numb.
And the barefoot doctor said, hold on a second. He, he jammed his finger into me into my back. That would be.
And really pushed it quite deep. And he said, look, within 48 hours, you'll notice a difference. I got to tell you, it's almost gone.
I mean, it's like two and a half years and hundreds and hundreds of pounds in physical therapy and low and behold.
Anyway, so we had a board meeting started 6 p.m. on so I didn't have time in the morning to do a show.
This is all leading up to a huge apology, obviously.
We had a board of directors meeting in San Francisco, which started at 10 a.m. 6 p.m. in London.
And that really lasted until, well, well, past 10 o'clock.
And, you know, I got home. I was so tired. It's been two, but maybe even three really, really long weeks.
It's, I was dead. And, you know, I took the advice that I should have taken last weekend. You guys said, screw it.
Don't do your show on Saturday or Sunday. Relax. I couldn't go flying or anything fun like that.
But there was something that I received on Friday from Head Sales Weasel, Chris Jacob. He brought for me an iPhone.
Yes, I have been assimilated.
And, uh, I've been playing with this device all weekend long, nonstop.
Setting up my entire environment to conform to it because, of course, there's a little bit different than working with the trustee, uh,
Nokia E61I because you're right back into the, the throws of iTunes and I really haven't used iTunes very much at all.
If at all, even on this computer. Um, so I'm back to sinking.
Over the course of, uh, the next few days, over the course of the week, I'll be telling you about my experiences. The first thing I did though, um,
you know, I knew that I did not want to have yet another AT&T account. I have a singular wireless account,
which, uh, you know, I've been moving that SIM card back and forth from every single Nokia phone that I've had.
In fact, it started out with my blackberry, which you remember how much I love that device. I really did.
And, uh, I was looking around that I found at hacktheiPhone.com. I found a procedure that enables you to, um,
insert any AT&T compatible SIM card, meaning that I could, because that's really all I want us to do.
You know, I want to test the phone out. I don't want to completely commit to it. Now, by changing my number, I'd say that's a pretty big damn commitment.
So, even though I'm an AT&T customer, you can't just put a different SIM card in immediately. It'll say, no, no good.
Uh, please put in a compatible, you know, please put in the SIM card that came with the phone.
You've got to go through the activation process. And, of course, this activation process takes place through iTunes.
So, uh, because of iTunes lives on the local computer, you know, lots of, uh, engineers and, well, you can call them hackers if you want.
Um, you know, have a way to track and see what communication is going on between the computer and the iPod, even though they really haven't been able to get into the iPod.
And so, uh, essentially, you load a program that acts like iTunes and routes around it, you know, there's some interesting steps where you, um,
have to click restore, then unplug the, uh, the iPhone from your computer quick before iTunes is able to recognize it's, uh, it's gone.
Um, and it works. If I can work, first time off. So, I inserted my, uh, my singular one, uh, SIM card and presto, my, my number and even in iTunes, it says, here's your number.
So, that was great. And, of course, I've been following along on the, uh, on the iPhone, on an iPhone mod, uh, IRC channels to see the, the progress, you know, obviously whatever one wants is to unlock the phone.
So, you could put in any SIM card from any network. I could take quite a while. It's not, it's not a trivial exercise.
And I think a lot of that information usually comes out after it's been leaked from one of the factories probably, um, that, you know, information just has a way of flowing in that regard.
Um, but for right now, I'm, I'm happy just, uh, just testing another, you know, so here's the one thing I've got to say right off the bat.
They have figured something very important out. The whole idea, and I, and I went back actually, and I, I looked at Steve Jobs's keynote where he announced the iPhone.
And he was talking about the, the internet navigation device. And yes, as an internet navigation device, I have to say it is outstanding.
And the main reason is because, um, you're not looking at what Steve Jobs calls the baby web.
When you load a web page, you can see the entire page in the browser and you can, you know, double tap to zoom in,
or you can use the pinch finger, move to zoom into where you want to be.
And it's incredibly important. It's not just a trick, you know, the Nokia.
So let me just step back for a second. So, you know, we are used to seeing web pages in context. So we understand almost instantaneously, you know, what's the layout, where's the information, what's the navigation structure, except, of course, with Pacho.com.
Working on sucking lesson that regard.
Having that knowledge then allows you to navigate through the rest of the site.
When it comes in all, you know, stuff on top and, you know, one big long strip of information, you know, what that looks like right in your cell phone,
where you get the, the side bars, the first thing you have to scroll all the way through, you know, you lose your whole context of information.
Now, in the East 61 eye the way they solve that is they have a little mini map.
And so when you really start to scroll, you then see the whole page in this kind of mini map that is off to the side.
So it does give you some context as to where you are in, in navigating throughout this page because let's face it, you're scrolling, so you're navigating.
Brilliant, brilliant the way they've solved that absolutely make so much sense.
And this screen, they, I don't know if these guys are actually making money on the iPhone because this screen is of outstanding quality, of course, a lot of it.
There's the courts, technology stuff that they already had figured out in, in OS 10, but, um, man, wow, the, the browsing experience is utterly, utterly fantastic.
Now I don't know about battery life yet, you know, I've run it down a couple times already, which is not so surprising.
I'm putting it on an extended long charge now, I ran it all the way down because, you know, batteries do develop some kind of memory.
If you recharge them halfway through and you do that too often.
Yeah, I, you know, I was very ready to hate this, extremely, and I didn't get it for free.
I paid for at least Chris paid for, I got to pay him back.
I was really prepared to not like this at all.
Now, once I've gotten around some of the ugly things, which is pretty traditional for, for Macintosh, you know, out of the box, it works great for everybody.
And if you want it to perform, you know, in a, in a way that would be consistent with a machine that is a bit more open, then you have to hack stuff around.
I think that's kind of the Mac way.
So, so far so good, I'm given it the thumbs up at the moment.
And I just saw that, that apparently they've gotten into the OS into the file system, so we're close to something.
Yeah, it wouldn't be cool if you couldn't SSH into your, into your iPhone.
Just the FTP in drops them stuff off.
Man, if we can really get in, if we can really load a shell, it's going to become a very, very important device.
One more thing I want to say about it, their integration of QuickTime is really stellar.
I've been messing around with that, because of course, I'm highly interested.
You know, QuickTime is, it's not as prevalent as flash on most computers.
But what wouldn't it be amazing if QuickTime turned out to be the mobile format?
And of course, it's not a format.
It's really, it's a, it's a container to be quite honest.
They do have formats within that, but you know, can also be H.264.
And so I have QuickTime video in it, but it just works so beautifully.
I think every MP3 link you click on it plays.
Most MP4 links definitely all MOV linked or almost all.
I mean, there's some weirdness is to what formats it will accept.
I got to get some information on that.
But it just works.
In fact, I even tried out, I watched the Steve Jobs keynote.
I went to the Apple site, went to QuickTime, went to Keynotes and events, clicked on the, on the,
was it the developers conference, I think.
And, and it played it.
It's streamed the QuickTime video right into my iPhone.
Got to tell you extremely impressed.
Adam, good afternoon.
It's you.
I am calling to prove once and for all that someone actually, we've got articles in playboy.
I got a script for years and years ago and claimed it was purely, you know, for the free speech stuff
and the first amendment promotion and all things and articles and all that stuff.
But finally, it's, you know, it's living proof because this current issue has this tremendous article about new media and stuff.
And in this nice little graphic of a big column of logos of sort of web to .0 or a new media company, the pod safety and user network logo,
right at the top of the entire column over YouTube and overall these other big, big, huge, well known names.
And the first person quoted in article is Ron Bloom.
Very nice.
So I don't know if you caught that using your ego filter or vanity filter, or if it is used and checked for news about stuff on the web.
But, uh, awesome piece.
Really terrific exposure for a pod show.
And, uh, well, of course, it would be exposure for anybody who had the articles in playboy.
But anyway, uh, how about a great great weekend and, uh, photo, uh, continuing to hear the shows.
Talk to you.
Bye bye.
Oh, Shabbat Shalom, my friend.
Yeah.
Are you and Mark Yoshimotan Mkov, the only people who pointed that out, of course, I had seen it already.
Away with those one more someone sent me a, no, that was, I think, Mkov sent me a scan of it.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
I remember being interviewed.
I was on the call too.
They didn't quote me though.
I guess I'm completely uncoordable.
But I believe it.
I believe it does work, man.
Once again, this weekend, uh, we had Dr. Cockney featured in the news of the world that humongous
newspaper here in, uh, in the UK, 9 million readers only comes out on Sunday and people say
they bite for the sports, but it's just filled with naked chicks, which is kind of the culture
here in the UK.
So it's not like a smart, well, yeah, it is smarty.
But, uh, Dr. Cockney fits in just perfectly out half to say.
And man, boom, download requests through the roof, registrations through the roof, um, you know,
people pay attention to that stuff.
They, they do read the articles.
In this case, they take the, you know, they take all the steps to actually go over to
website, you know, then go into another website and play something.
It works.
Al-Warring, right, our front, I'm going to go long today because there's been so much
response to, uh, to the trickery of television.
Of course, that's where we left off, uh, with the 637, where I went through that
interview with Michael Grayton, David Cox, uh, some great feedbacks and great examples of
things that people have witnessed themselves when it comes to, uh, media deception.
You know, nothing earthshattering, but some great, some fun things to listen to for
sure.
And, uh, so I just got so many.
I just want to rush through the, you just bang out a couple.
Also, today is the day of the cheddar, uh, if all goes according to plan and I think
it will, uh, somewhere near the end of our day in the United Kingdom will be releasing
the new channel editor functionality at podshow.com, which will enable you to determine the
output of your channel feeds, how they play.
And, and, you know, I've been playing with this iPhone already.
I have yet another, another play out in mind is to how I want stuff, uh, to be made
available.
Because that's really one of the big differences you'll see is now as an audience member,
you can go to anyone's channel and decide how you want to listen to it.
You just want to play it in the dashboard, click play channel, boom, it'll play.
You want to play it in real or Windows media or wind amp, no problem.
We've got options for those.
Want to put it on your iPod through iTunes, no problem.
Got an option for that.
Do you want to just download it? No problem.
Do you want the RSS fee?
No problem.
There's the icon.
Yep.
So let me just, this is actually left over from, from Thursday, just a couple of
quick blurbs on channels since it's coming out today.
Hey, I just want to share channels for the nylon and anyone else is still
doesn't get it.
And if I'm not right about this, you're not going to play this.
I'm just going to assume I know what I'm talking about.
And even if I don't, I don't know.
He said he doesn't need channels because your already has iTunes, which he thinks does the same thing.
But it's not just playlists.
It's smart playlists.
And iTunes, there's smart playlists.
You can set them up according to any combination of albums and artists and podcasts and banks.
You know, now that I've been using iTunes again, it is very much like smart playlists.
Oh boy, is it?
Except they're Uber, smart.
Uber, smart.
Because you put shows in and shows, there's your serendipity factor.
They pop out episodes and you never know when it's going to come.
You never know what's going to be in it.
Oh, man.
Yes, yes.
Or yeah.
And this is the last bit of functionality I'm waiting on.
You can put channels into channels.
Can you imagine how much cool stuff is going to happen to your smart playlists?
Quite a bit.
So, that's more of what channels are, but if you've done much with smart playlists,
you know, that you can base them on other smart playlists.
So, you're really sharing your iTunes playlists and sharing it.
And you're losing your getting other people smart playlists.
And then you get the channels within channels, which is, you can base your smart playlists
to other people smart playlists, which is, yes.
Yes, I guess that's a big thing.
That is.
Oh, my help.
Thanks, man.
That's absolutely right.
That's exactly how it's supposed to work.
And I must say, great explanation for someone who's never actually used it.
I'm so happy because, you know, I keep comparing this to how tough it is to explain Tvo.
And you can't really understand it until you use it.
And it's the same thing.
So, having this level of understanding without having used it, thank you.
I applaud that.
Hey, Adam.
This is Chris and Philadelphia.
Let me sum up my previous two long comment.
It's about two things, the first is the magical player for podcasts.
I think it would be some sort of program that fits on a portable device.
Like, at any hundred in the iPhone, not my palm, but that is not so good.
That, you know, it can sink.
It can download all the stuff on the go.
And let me see back.
Let me have it to a shared field.
Let me get it put in the channel.
Let me rate it.
Share it with my friends.
I like that.
Yeah, I'm down with that.
And we'll have some of that functionality in our channels.
Although I am moving away from the download synchronized part.
I can just see where we're going.
And not that we're not going to need this for a long time.
But eventually, bandwidth and connectivity will just be so prevalent.
You'll be able to, you know, stream stuff live from anywhere uninterrupted.
I'm pretty convinced of that.
Maybe five years from now, so we have some download synchronization things we need to do.
And yes, over the air.
But please, let's keep it broadband over the air.
Because it's a bad experience doing that over a mobile network.
It could also be a very expensive experience.
I want to see.
So hopefully some get on that for the iPhone for any hundred and stuff.
And second, the chatter sounds awesome.
It's exactly what the future media is.
Like everyone have their own little feeds and stuff getting passed around.
One of the problems with with iTunes and channels is that, you know, it sticks all
of shows in the one list.
Is it possible to use OKML in this format?
I know that OKML is like, you know, a listing of RSS feeds.
So I would like to really like, I nested list of RSS feeds in ID.
I'd have my basic channel.
Click on it.
It opens up two more listings, two more directories, I guess.
And there's my, you know, electricity podcast.
And there's my daily source code.
You know, that would be excellent.
That's that you're talking about change in iTunes.
You're talking about change in a lot there.
But it's just something to think about.
So keep up the good work piece.
Yeah, man, thank you.
Now, the reason I played this rather geeky comment is multiple reasons.
First of all, I want to point out that we do have an OPML important export feature.
I don't know if it's working properly at this moment.
The spec has changed.
A lot of stuff has changed.
Support probably waned a bit for it because very few people actually wanted.
But I might as well say right off the bat and right now that the entire cheddar concept,
not the editor per se and not the playout system.
The idea of OPML and RSS feeds is completely modeled after what Dave Winner built.
Of course, Dave Winner found RSS co-founder of RSS and definitely the founder of OPML.
It is if you've looked at share my OPML and reading list,
it is exactly this concept taken a bit further by being able to determine the output.
And these are the things that as a user of the OPML editor,
I was always looking for.
It's like, okay, you know,
and I just didn't know how to do it.
Otherwise, you know, the platform is certainly open enough to hack around.
But I'd like the idea of a reading list.
But I wanted more control over the output because that then makes me a publisher,
not just a collector with some, you know, standard based output of my feed.
So I want people to be able to enjoy it.
And I want to have some form of editorial control,
which doesn't mean actually writing something.
But determining what comes out of the feed,
filter certain feeds,
you know, really using it as an information router.
So I might as well give Dave props right away before,
there's some problem of who invented what.
It doesn't matter.
I just want to be able to,
I want to be able to use this for myself.
I want to be able to control what pictures,
what MP3s,
what shows, what goes onto my iPod.
And, you know, with the channel,
and if you go to Adam.podshow.com,
you'll see that I already created an iPhone channel.
Right now, there's only one show in there.
It's a twit.
And, of course, it's not, you know,
it's displaying multiple episodes.
So it hasn't been edited with cheddar yet.
But when it is, boy, I'm telling you,
I'm going to give you so much cool shit to listen to.
And you're going to be given it back.
Just do a search on your favorite word of the day
for under channels at podshow.com.
You'll see what I'm talking about.
So you think, you know, your rock history, huh?
Well, tell me this.
Who was the original vocalist for ACBC?
Wrong.
It was Dave Evans.
And Dave and his band,
the bad asses,
have a brand new CD out called Center.
Dave, his management,
and his record label,
have given podshow radio the right
to play five tracks
off this incredible CD.
And throughout the show,
we'll learn more about this badass of rock and rose.
Past and history.
Starting Monday.
Exclusively on podshowradio.com
and podshowradio.potshow.com
Jesus.
With metal.
Hey, Adam.
It's Matt from Gamesweasel.
Just so you know what's coming up on this week's show.
We've got a review of Overlord on the Xbox 360.
We're also reviewing Transformers, the game,
on the very same console.
We've got a scary preview of Silent Hill.
And of course, you can win copies of
Lost Planet Extreme Condition on the PC.
For very exciting stuff,
at gamesweasel.btpodshow.com
Yeah, Adam.
Keith from Vancouver BC.
I failed compelled to send in the comment.
Just finished listening to DSC632
and had opening track was outstanding.
I had a pretty good day today
and when I heard that track had put me into
an even better mood on the way to Ikido.
When I got home,
went straight to iTunes and bought it.
The PMMemnet gets finest.
PS.
I wanted to do I'm not here to comment,
but my wife is asleep beside me,
so I did this up on my neck.
Ciao for now.
Red pill.
Fulder.
I didn't sound the half bad actually.
That was pretty good.
I did not sound half bad at all.
I like that.
If I came out of your Mac,
dude, that's pretty, this got in a lot better.
That speech since this.
DSC632.
So that was Valley Lodge hanging on.
Yeah, fantastic track.
I love those guys.
They kind of like a Casey in the Sunshine Band
upside down in backwards.
So I'm going to launch into this whole thing
about the BBC since I got so many great comments.
People giving examples of how they were part of
mainstream media deception.
But before that, something I've got to play
you from the Pod Safe Music Network.
I believe Jersey Todd sent this into me
as something to play on the Fubar Friday.
You're going to love it because the kleptones
know the revolution.
It will be televised if you're a blue pill taker.
Ladies and gentlemen, our future.
You will choose to stay at home, brother.
For you'll be able to do everything you need
from your potato couch.
You'll be able to don your virtual helmet
and experience the revolution on 360
degree around CGI.
You may choose to view as manga
or Hannah Barbera as the hair bear bunch
because a revolution will be televised.
The revolution will be brought to you
by Apple Mac or PC World
with Nokia and Motorola providing
SMS updates.
The revolution will show pictures of
hopefuls, cueing overnight for the latest
audition.
The revolution will be sponsored by
Gown, the cocky and camel collection.
And it will storm me as you.
You will play yourself or run pit playing
you.
Or you.
Playing grind pit.
Playing you.
The revolution will be smoked.
Snorled.
Injected.
Chased on vaporized.
It will be recorded on mini-dv
and kept in the puppet.
The revolution will be digitized.
Then transferred to all available formats.
It will appear on your favorite CD
as the bonus track.
You'll be able to procure it cheap on VHS.
Or pay a little bit more for the extra footage on DVD.
Met a max will be available for the old school.
Who are more good shooting comes you
with the shelters and grips.
The revolution will shoot from the hip hip hip hip.
I used to say
I...
I used to...
The revolution will be scratched.
It will be spun back and suffered as a loop.
It will appear as the red button on your remote control.
The revolution will operate in a job share.
Or flexi time option.
It's so you can have it at your leisure.
Because the revolution will be ticked.
The revolution will be burned.
Highlight it in scent.
It will have its own awards ceremony.
With the biggest winners unable to attend.
Except for via live satellite link.
Because of their current revolutionary commitments.
The revolution will be a tick up in a storm.
Or a bottle in a message.
Or a door to a key.
The revolution will always come with fries.
Because the revolution will be televised.
The revolution will be hard, my brothers.
Because it will use via gra.
Come a gra.
Arroll tight and hardening of the arteries.
In order to fill inside.
Rumbles happy meal box.
As the free gift.
The revolution will have a new twist.
Sponsored by Levi.
With a sticker campaign written in an eligible graffiti style font.
Because the revolution will be advertised.
And paper view will have a whole new meaning, brothers.
The revolution will be available for gameboy this fall.
And Xbox and GameCube today.
The revolution will be televised.
We'll be televised.
We'll be televised brothers.
Because the revolution is alive.
Yeah.
It's common sense.
We go have Yasi Claire.
Good bye.
It's real hip hop music from the Soya.
Yeah.
Say it.
I know you're out there.
I can feel you now.
I know that you're afraid.
You're afraid of us.
You're afraid of change.
I don't know the future.
I didn't come here to tell you how this is going to end.
They came here to tell you how it's going to begin.
I'm going to hang up this phone.
And then I'm going to show these people what you don't want them to see.
I'm going to show them more.
Without you.
A world without rules and controls.
Without borders or boundaries.
A world.
But anything is possible.
Where we go from there is a choice I leave to you.
You may think it's a lot of old cockman, but that's your hangover.
You bastard.
Right.
Supercalipraginistic spirality doso.
Thank you, if you seem to have a son or a son.
If you don't say it, you'll have a success.
Supercalipraginistic spirality doso.
Remember that three years ago,
you had to return.
You spent your children.
You didn't want to tell me what's going to end.
Supercalipraginistic spirality doso.
No, of course that wasn't pod save.
No, it wasn't sending by Jersey Todd Kenneth for Burrach sent in a Gmail atom fastening shows again lately
concerning the TV deception stuff, maybe track 20 at the kleptones that I've humble
with all put that link in the show notes could be an interesting piece of music
a tie into the show.
No idea if it's really pod save, but they do offer it as a DM DRM free download, yeah.
No, I would guess that's not pod save, particularly with Michael Jackson's Ben track
on there.
No, no, don't think so, but the whole point is well taken, the revolution, if you see
the revolution televised, be very aware of my friends, you're in the blue pill revolution.
If you see something else coming through the pipes, the series of tubes, then you know
it might be a real revolution.
But first we've got a dismantle this thing known as mainstream, not that it has
to go away.
We just have to show you what it is so you can recognize it and remember inherently
television makes use of lighting and sets and zooms and cuts and fades and all kinds
of things that you will understand much better if you take the TV, the Zen TV experiment.
I'll just have to post the link once again to it.
Let's check out the phone lines.
Of course, we have a number of phone numbers for you to call in one in the United States
to New Jersey and one in London in the UK.
Hey, I'm Mr. John and Omaha, a great story on a BBC thing.
I've always been suspect, a government run communication.
Again, we're putting the media into the hands of a few.
I much rather have it in the free market where I can decide what I see is to or fact on
what somebody else.
Tell me if that or at least try and show me that that might be to or fact or fall, so
I should say.
Anyway, keep up the great work.
I would say that I'm a red pill and what you're doing with Potcho is that total free
marketization of the communication out there and getting this out of or into more people's
hands and out of the government control.
Again, that's my problem that I have with the BBC and also the FCC in the United States.
Thanks, bye.
Well, yes indeed.
I'm glad you're slipping down the red pillage there.
BBC is a little bit different though.
It's yes, government and yes, the government makes up a lot of the rules and there's
a board of governors and they're all tied into the government.
But the idea is, is philosophically really good, you know, it was like, hey, everyone
he pony up some bucks, I think it is like 136 pounds 50, so about $300 a year.
It's not insignificant, pony up some money and we'll make some great programming for you.
The problem is, of course, that it's really the problem is ratings, you know, well,
that's twofold ratings and availability of bandwidth.
Look, the BBC has, you know, three main channels, really two main channels.
BBC won BBC two.
There you go.
That for television.
Those can be seen by the entire population because it's distributed very widely, still
distributed through the air for free.
Well, sorry, not for free because of course you have to pay up if you have a television.
But there's only so much you can shove down those channels.
Yeah, they got the BBC three and four and digital channels, but you know, those audiences
are much more limited in scope.
So there's only so much you can put on.
So what do you want to put on?
Well, you want to put on the stuff that people like the most.
The only way we have to determine that is through ratings and it's the same ratings
that the commercial guys look at and, you know, the theory remains the same.
You know, you sure you may have an niche program that is great for a very small amount
of people who love it and are really happy and feel that that's worth the fee that they're
paying.
But probably it's not going to see the light of day because they have to, you know, all
this stuff has to be pushed through this very narrow piece of bandwidth, no, you know,
just two linear channels 24 hours a day.
So they have to make choices.
So it's never going to be your niche programming that you like, which is exactly why companies
like pod show exists to bring you that niche programming.
Do you know how many aviation programs I subscribe to when I listen to, there's only half
a million pilots in the United States.
It's really not that much, you know, so of course, you're not going to get tons of aviation
shows through that very narrow pipe, which is that linear, linear playout basis.
No, of course not.
And once we are able to really change advertising, show advertisers what they can do and
how much more rich the environment is instead of your 20 to 30 second in your face spot,
I think we're really going to have a lot of fun.
It may be a bit of, you know, pandemonium, but, uh, happy thought.
Hey, I understand John and Omaha, great story on that BBC thing.
I've always been suspect.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
Here's what I meant to do this one.
Hey, Adam, this is special event of the financially.
I guess that marking of a conflict was an idea of C7, you know, a great idea of how
television is deceased.
It'd be really cool.
I mean, you could such a video podcast, you know, I don't know if a person's a flop, but
whatever.
But, uh, take some clips of either stuff that you've done or stuff that, you know, you
production's your own part of and all steps through, uh, with the audience, okay, here's
where he did this.
Okay, here's where the, uh, the satellite, think, uh, you know, kind of got fun.
Here's when we did this or here's how he did this.
And really show the man behind the curtain, show the map, how the magic tricks have
done.
I think it'd be instructive, you know, for someone who's been in media as long as you
have and on the broadcast media, so I just show all the tricks and, uh, and secrets
that are out there that broadcast media uses and expose them for what they are.
Uh, they've been really, really cool in a very second, a heck of a lot of fun too.
So hopefully we'll see that, uh, from the, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the
hard show team.
The great, uh, I, I just got it.
Anyway, keep it for great work and, um, stand tuned to the DSC.
Yeah, man.
Absolutely.
And that's a great idea, Chris, and I, and I, and I will try to do that.
It's hard, though, to remember, I mean, this, it's been, my mainstream broadcast career
has been, uh, all deception, I guess, of, uh, of the public, you know, to, to, to varying
degrees, you know, not really, um, horrible.
I do remember distinctly though, I interviewed Madonna, um, in 1982 or 1983.
She was holed up at the, uh, uh, uh, what's the place that has the, the Skylight Bar, uh,
the La Mondrian when it was still, maybe it's still called La Mondrian on Sunset strip.
And this was when she, uh, the first time, no, it was the second time she was releasing
her album that had borderline on it, like a virgin.
She released that earlier in 81, um, and I'd met her very, very briefly at the Pirate
of Station at Amsterdam, that, but brief enough to do some hash under a glass.
She didn't, she didn't remember me.
That's for sure.
Um, and, uh, you know, we, uh, did the interview.
We conducted the interview on on the balcony overlooking Los Angeles.
And at one point, I can't remember, it's a long time ago.
I can't remember what I asked, but she didn't like the questions and said, this is stupid.
I'm not going to do this anymore.
And, you know, and she walked in, uh, back into the room.
She came out later to finish off, but it was like, uh, it was, she was so bitchy and so
mean.
And it was so weird that she did that.
Well, maybe that wasn't weird.
I can't remember what I asked, but something apparently offended.
But it's just through a little minor history fit, not a problem, right?
But when we put that interview on television, it was, of course, intercut with the pieces
of the video from like a virgin, and I think pieces of borderline.
And that entire piece was, you know, there were two edits.
Our director actually had made a fantastic edit where he really showed how pissy Madonna
looked.
I think for the time it was revolutionary, you know, and put that whole piece in and, and it
was, it was much more a representation of what had happened on the spot.
But management said, no, no, no, come on, man, she's a big star and people want to
love her.
And, you know, let's just make it into a happy piece.
And so, well, you know, it wasn't horrible.
I think it was wrong because it would have been so much more interesting to have seen,
you know, to have seen that side of her, particularly at that moment in her, uh, in her
career.
But it didn't happen.
I was, you know, it was changed, changed to fit whatever made sense for the ratings, I
guess.
In fact, literally, to make sense for whatever made sense for the ratings.
Hey, Adam, it's Jeff Sats, calling in from Florida, regarding your television deception
conversation.
Um, the kind of stuff you'd do with Janet Jackson is definitely standard operating procedure
for interviewing, especially when things are often done with a single camera.
Um, in the early 80s, pretty much my first job at a college, I produced a show called
Celebrity on cable television, Allison Spiel, the nightbird, was the host of this.
She was a terrific woman, a real character.
Got plenty of Allison Spiel stories for another time.
Um, excuse me.
Anyway, we would cover all the movie premieres and the press junk that's going on in New York
and we'd have access to all the stars to interview them about the movies and we'd go
to the premieres.
So we always went with a single camera and we set up the interviews with a single camera,
shoot.
So we would shoot the interview east.
We tried to get over the shoulders, shot or two of Allison talking to them from the
office chair.
And then at a later time, sometimes right then in the area to the celebrity left, but sometimes
back in our offices at a later date, we would shoot out and asking the questions and then
it would all be edited together in the finished product, we'd look like Allison was sitting
there talking to the celebrity, standard practice, probably still standard practice today.
One time Allison was sick, she couldn't show up and we were supposed to interview Robin
Williams.
So I show up to the junkets and I tell Robin Williams, I show the picture of Allison Spiel and
I say, she's going to be the hostess, but she's not here, so I'm going to interview you,
but when it airs, it's going to be awesome interviewing you.
No problem with Robin Williams, it's a terrific guy in person, great to interview.
We went through the interview.
I asked all the questions, I was very careful not to let my voice overlap with his, so the
editors wouldn't have any problem.
We went our very way, at a later date, we shot Allison asking the questions, put it
all together and when the show aired, it looked like Allison Spiel was sitting in the
area in the room with Robin Williams, doing the interview, of course she wasn't there.
Standard practice happens all the time.
Thanks again.
Yo, man, thank you for sharing.
Oh, absolutely.
I definitely still happens all the time.
In fact, that's one of the parts I love about John Stewart's daily show, the most,
is where they, I'm sure you've seen the interviews, where they're interviewing someone
about some serious topic and then there's all kinds of bogus asked questions and then
stupid answers.
And if you look really closely, so for instance, Samantha B will be on camera over the
shoulder of the person who's being interviewed.
You'll see that that person's mouth is moving, you'll see their jaw moving or the side
of their, the side of their cheek and you'll see that it isn't in sync with what they're
actually saying.
Those things are completely cut together because you're right.
They go off with one camera, do the interview and then do what we call cutaways and
noties and the noties are really important.
When you have an interview with someone, the first thing that always happens, it's cut
down to length.
You know, it's like we got, that's how the sound bite came to and came into existence.
You know, hey, look, we've got one minute, so we're going to put this in, put this in,
we're going to do a cutaway here and now the cutaway, when they do an edit, that's what
they need that, that you'll watch it now, you'll see it on the news all the time, you'll
see the interviewer doing one of these, yeah, so, you know, very interested, like head
shaking up and down, yeah, yeah, and it's a talent, the worst thing, by the way, is to
interview someone and then after they're, you have to interview, you're saying, okay,
we need some cutaways, that means they have to sit there, the camera moves to over their
shoulder and you ask the exact same fucking questions again.
So it's like, it's not, it's completely removed from a natural dialogue and in your case,
wow, you showed a picture, this is what the first thing will look like in the finished product.
You created a little, little mini feature right there.
So is it deception?
Yeah, you know, it's, it's just good to understand how it works because it's exactly what
goes on.
And again, I really have stories where all the good shit was lost because of the stupid
system, the way this is supposed to work, I interviewed Paul McCartney at MPL, McCartney
publishing limited, in the same time around, you know, it wasn't, maybe even before I
interviewed Madonna in those very early 80 days when I still working in the Netherlands.
And so MPL and London, and I spilled tea all over his MPL rug, you know, the big McCartney
logo.
And, you know, and so there we are in our hands and knees trying to, you know, mop up this
tea, ding elevator opens, Linda walks in, she's on her hands and knees, completely
beautiful, beautiful television.
We had those stupid, vis-news guys that was like, you know, because of the unions, you
couldn't bring your own camera guy, you had to use someone, it was employed locally.
And so these like, these half dead guys for vis-news and, you know, you could rent them.
And a guy had turned a camera off.
He wasn't even, he was like, just sitting there looking like, oh, well, it spilled
tea.
Oh, that good stuff, all that good stuff, all lost.
Hi, Adam, this is Raymond from the Netherlands and I was watching some live TV a couple
of years ago, from the NOS, which is of course our Dutch public service, and it was
the interview with the Newt Lover, so then the Prime Minister or the Minister of
President, and, well, anyways, at the 8 o'clock news at that night, they changed the
live interview, they changed the order of the questions, and by doing that, they also
gave the impression that is a viewpoint on the matter and was, I don't remember exactly
what it was about, but it was really surprising that, by just changing a couple of questions,
you know, the order that they could change something like that, and it was very disappointing
because at that time I was thinking, well, the NOS, you know, national public television,
that's supposed to be truthful and all that kind of stuff, but there you go, it's just
vacant, for sure, all of them.
Bye.
Yeah, all part of the blue pill world that we live in, my friend, and it doesn't just happen
in television.
Yeah, I'm a totally different, I'm calling in about the DOE, what is it, the 637, and you
were asking about media, asked to call in about media, and if you were to show anything
where we were part of a deception, well, I can't say you did that, I was on a media show,
but I was at a sporting event, and at the time, I was a sports blogger, I wrote
stories on a local sports team here in Minnesota, and I knew the ownership were well,
and they had a contest going on, and they couldn't get anybody to participate in the
contest, I guess, I don't see why they couldn't get anybody, but they asked me, if I
would grab my kid, and participated in it, and we did, and we had fun doing it, but
I don't know if it was the other participant in it, was also from the media, from a local
newspaper.
So, we've heard in the beginning about it, but just got the media involved, and of course,
I wrote about it in my blog at the time, so sports teams do the same thing, and the
new people are a lot of friends are seeing, and they're the more excited, and I'm hoping
that they're going to be part of it, not the center, but the sports teams are doing
it as well.
Sure.
I've got to let you know that one thing, so I'd have a good day.
Yeah, man.
It's all a part of entertainment.
Oh, contest.
It's the worst.
Any type of contest.
You know why?
Because they want to have people who look good on camera, or excuse me, sound good on the
air.
Oh, man.
There's not a single phone call that I haven't played back on traditional radio, where
I wouldn't have cut out at least five or six different bits.
You know, digital recording and editing in on-air studios becomes such a big deal.
Because, you know, you get a contest winner.
Oh, man, I've heard this shocky's go, you know, you just won $100, and it didn't take
it to see the Rolling Stones, and the person would go, oh, cool.
And then the disc shocker say, oh, hold on, man.
I'm recording this.
I want you to sound really excited, and I'll ask the question again, you'll just say,
you just won $100, and then take it to the Rolling Stones, and of course, the person
goes, woo, woo, woo.
It's all fake.
They weren't excited, and for the length of fuck, I already had, you know, Rolling Stones
who cares, don't know, no matter anymore.
Of course, of all the feedback I've received, not everybody agrees.
I had a minute to roll it from the Don't Compass podcast.
Just listening to your daily source code, six, three, seven, yes, today's one about the BBC,
and the way that TV has accepted the masses, and to be honest, I mean, I've worked for
the BBC for crying out loud, and so it's not as bad as you'd quite think.
I mean, this kind of thing isn't going to bring down the British Broadcasting Corporation,
I can tell you that for a kick-off.
The Director General is, as so rightly, cancelled all these things for a huge review, and, you
know, things will get put into place, the deception is no longer there, you know, it's
a really important thing that, to be able to see a doing, not just in trying to sort
this problem out, but of the content that they give, and they're reviewing over a million
hours of footage to see if there's any other incidents like this.
There's going to be the people in question of all being suspended or dismissed, and, yeah,
it's going to be interesting times, but the BBC do absolutely fantastic job, and you'll
comment about Britain, the company down, the corporation down, I feel, is a long one,
it's not, it's the trust will come back, the trust of the public will come back to the
BBC, I am convinced of that.
Oh, Adam, I just thought I'd throw my tuppins into the pond, take it easy, by now.
Oh, dude, your tuppins is more than appreciated, please, open wide, I'm going to shove a
red pill down your throat because you really need one.
Maybe I should explain what I mean by their coming down, they're going down.
Let's just understand that the nature of media has become, but I think always has been
about audience size, getting more people to tune in, stop by, pick it up, read it, surf
to download, it's about more and more people, it's always been about that.
The problem is, before we could actually, before we actually understood the beast, and of
course we understand how television works were getting pretty good out of ourselves, just
go to YouTube or look at any of the pod show video shows, you know, we understand how to
make this media, it's not all that hard, you know, it's now we have all those tools,
it's about the distribution, and this distribution, of course, has been extremely interesting
to people of power, people, and that's not just politicians, it's also people have something
to sell, you know, big consumer goods companies, and they've been able to, the whole,
the whole architecture is based upon, again, you know, the most people, it's the sureest
way to get your message out, the more people you are able to reach.
There's no real targeting going on yet, yeah, there's some, you know, of course there's
niche channels, and, you know, what's happening now with independent media is there's tons
of niche stuff around, it's my, I see my job is to enable that to continue by being able
to monetize on it, you can't do shit for free forever, just doesn't work that way,
however, there's no real malice, I do not believe in a grand master plan, there's no
master plan that says let's deceive the public, you know, people who get up in the morning
and go to work for television aren't thinking about that, but they are thinking one thing,
we've got to entertain, we've got to get the ratings, we've got to get as many people
watching or listening or reading or downloading or surfing to or page viewing, that's
just the nature of it, because that's how you make a sustainable business, of course
there's a lot of people who don't have to do this at all, and you can continue doing
independent stuff, but if you want to grow, you need money, it's just a fact, I can't help
it, I can't get around it, so the flow of media, the way it from where I see it is,
and I think probably associated press is one of the biggest problems, you have these
huge indicators of so-called news, and what distinguishes news and how it's reported and
how factual it is doesn't matter after it's first introduced, because and you can follow
this, every other single media property will quote that so-called reliable source, and then
other people will quote that source that's quoting the reliable source, it's the copy-paced
culture, because this problem is not just in television, it's not just in radio, it's in print,
it's in newspapers, we need viewers, we need people to be interested, so what are the stories,
people are interested in, well they're interested in crap, they're interested in Britney Spears,
yes we're also interested in Iraq and Afghanistan and North Korea, but if you're going to
present it in a boring way, we're just not going to watch it because we want to be spoon fed
like all the other stuff, why all of a sudden do I have to work extra hard to understand
what's going on on the news, no, that's what people wake up in the morning to do and they don't
really even realize it, they're all blue pillars, it's okay and they're just doing what they love
doing, they like creating media and having lots of people pay attention to it, that's that's the only
job, so you can't really fault anyone, however what I predict is going to happen, I think you're right
is yes the trust will come back and yes the BBC will implement all kinds of editorial controls
and all kinds of gates to make sure that you know the stuff that gets on the air or on the
website or on television or whatever that it's accurate and that it's correct and guess what,
it's going to be boring, it's going to be incredibly fucking boring, that's our chance
because I do believe because we don't have this limitation of time that we can make things
interesting to a large audience and that audience can be a long tale of many many niche audiences
and we can do it in an entertaining way, look, you know, I didn't have to stop after 30 minutes of
this podcast because I didn't have to, you didn't have to listen to it either, you could just
fast forward to the bits you wanted to or skip over pieces, there's your core difference, that's
where we win because people will migrate, they'll migrate to the things they want to hear,
the things that are interesting to them and it could be very, very niche but we're going to win
when the BBC and other mainstream media have so many regulations and so much porn on top of them
that they'll just be boring because that will also bring upon a huge financial problem because
all of these phone lines, all of these scams that were in place and make no mistake, they're scams,
oh yeah, I think I'm going to get a text back from that really cute chick, I don't get one
text back from a cute chick, I get three a week, I'm automatically subscribed, these are scams,
complete scams, just a rob people of money, you know, of course people are gullible but they're
waking up to that now, that's the whole other side of this and this is going to happen in the
United States as well and you're going to see that television, particularly television, has been
subsidizing their mere existence through these phone scams and they'll have to go back to very
boring, very simple programming. Hi Adam, this is Alex from podcastjunkie.co.uk,
loved your DSC 637, I've come up with a letter to the BBC that I've posted at my blog and it
goes something like this, do a BBC, has I've been paying you in good faith for honest television
programming to principally sum of 135.50 a year and there's obviously you've been cheating
lying to me and to millions of people, what do you say I'll skip paying you for the next year?
After all you haven't been providing me with the service I would expect, have you? You've lied
and you've cheated, you've been given a year to clean up your act, however as you've been lying
and cheating for years, I really don't think that me with holding only one year's license fee could
be considered illegal, do you? Thanks for the great show's Adam and regards to you and all your
listeners, massive red pill. Yeah, there's one thing I hadn't even thought about in the
midst of all of this, but John points it out very well. Hi Adam, he's John, long time listener,
the BBC, a public service broadcaster, paid for by the license fee, by license fee,
he read out seven instances where they confess now to break in the rules again.
They were recently signed 50,000, so the bleep teacher isn't aware they did the same thing,
presumably there's another seven now, are they going to be signed at 50,000?
In the room, $60,000, it's mine, they're like the rules, they get signed, they pay with my money!
Want to load a shit? Thanks Adam. Dude, you're so spot on, I hadn't even thought about that,
the 50,000, it's your money, it's my money, where's it going to? It's going to the government,
that is, you're so right, man, that is so incredibly wrong, the penalties have to be completely
overhauled, good point and a good, good, good point in the show to wrap it up with one last song,
which is from the pod save music network authorized by Alice Cooper himself.
She spends her life through, pleasing up her man, she feeds him dinner or anything she can,
she cries alone and night too often,
he smokes and drinks and don't come home at all, only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep,
only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep, man makes your head gray,
he's your life's mistake, when all you're really looking for is a need for break,
he lies right at you, you know you hate this game, he slaps you once and a while and you live and love,
she cries alone and night too often, he smokes and drinks and don't come home at all,
only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep,
only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep,
like eyes full of the time, don't spend the time, clean up this trash and you there,
down on your knees, again, please come watch, bleep, bleep,
watch, bleep, bleep,
only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep,
only we're being bleep, only we you're being bleep, only we're being bleep, only we're being bleep,
Only when I'm bleeding
I'm alone
And it's me to all the women in America
All the women in Afghanistan
All the women in Africa
To the women of the world
Don't let your memory ring your damn
Just keep that dick ass out of town
Stand up for yourself
And don't let your man hurt you
Just call your sister
And your sister's with me there
Only when I'm bleeding
It's got to be one of my favorite Alice Cooper tracks of all time
All time
All to you pot safe
By Wednesday
Only when I'm bleeding
Fully sanctioned by Alice Cooper
To put it on the pot safe music network
So another cool for the networking
What an awesome song
Definitely
Another piece of the puzzle
To the soundtrack of my life
That I love to share with you
Daily source go dot com
Adam at podshow.com
For your feedback
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow
Bye bye now
Stick it in your ear