Port City PD, the number one online police drama series, is now available.
The pod father had a cameo in the season 1 finale, who will be making cameo appearances
in season 2.
You?
Me?
Get in on the action.
The city dot podshow.com.
And now something really amazing, the DSC 639.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Ag esque, it's Adam Curry.
Oh, baby, I'll make it a place in my life
I'll sit around the way you want it just like my life
Sounds to be natural, I've been so crazy when I'm alone
Love, love, love, love, love
I'll take your senses, love, love, love
You're truly close to me, you're in my life
I'll sit around the way you want it just like my life
I'll sit around the way you want it
I'll sit around the way you want it just like your life
Oh yeah, if you ask me that's the way rock roll songs should be short, sweet, full of
attitude, black tie review there from Penn State, well Penn State, Pennsylvania, State
known as Penn.
Absent radio kicking off Tuesdays daily source code episode 639 from the affluent suburb
of swanky Surrey from on the west side of Vagueilford.
This is the daily source code coming to you from the Curry Manor, beautiful day today.
Uh-huh, last week I made a prediction and I was getting comments about it.
Ah, here we go.
I'm going to go and the garden isn't a DSE636, so whether it's beautiful, it's just
going to be fantastic.
Here we go.
And let me make a prediction right now, you know what I mean, it's a weather, really
tough.
If you're having some, you have this, I knew how weather, prediction and please hold
me to this next week is going to be, you, T, full in the United Kingdom, next week is going
to be, B, T, full in the United Kingdom, bank on it, oh, it's true, that becomes TSC639.
I love the rain drops, the point point, very noisy rain drops, you have there, yeah,
yeah, I should have been a little more clear, I'm expecting the weather to be great
in South East England.
I keep forgetting how big this place really is, you know, that, that friggin, many that
Christina wants up in, uh, it's a new castle, man, those guys are flooded out all the way
up there.
And let me tell you, it's a disaster.
I remember quite distinctly a number of Brits scuffing, guffing and scuffing, scuffing, that's
it's scuffing and guffing at, uh, at the Katrina disaster in the United States.
Well, excuse me, this is, I'd say, pretty damn comparable and completely unprepared.
And now, of course, the same reports are popping up here.
The government knew about the, uh, the lack of, of water management, uh, particularly the
roads and the so-called floodplains.
They knew about that three years ago here in the UK.
Gordon Browns got his work cut out for him.
And I think he's, uh, he's tackling this one head on, but man, you can just see the bags
under his eyes, you know, droop lower and lower there about to drop down over his cheekbones
because his tough, tough, tough, tough situation, really tough what's going on here.
And of course, now that, you know, the, the crisis has actually reached the outskirts
of London.
Oh, no, let's pay some attention to it, really, really unbelievable.
It's going on here.
Now, another day, I got to go to, uh, to London office.
It's going to be another busy week.
I hope to, to eat out five shows, but you know me, it could easily turn out to be
four.
I, in fact, I'm even going to stay in the city Thursday evening for an early Friday morning
meeting, but things are going so well, uh, you know, Dr. Cockney ever since we, uh,
we hooked up with news of the world is just exploding unbelievable, download
requests have quadrupled.
So we found a very good partner, I think, and this and, uh, it's just cool stuff going
on here.
I think, I think when, uh, probably, um, end of August, I'll probably go to the United
States for about six weeks in a row and try and replicate exactly the same thing we've
done here.
And amidst all of that, cheddar is coming out today.
I can smell the cheese from where I'm at already.
Uh, yesterday, I approved all of the functionality and, uh, disapproved one, the, uh, the
get channel functionality.
I'm, we're not going to release with get channel in the, uh, in the initial build.
You'll be able to, uh, to edit your channels, uh, at podshow.com, uh, you'll have tremendous
amount of control over the output of those channels.
What the output looks like and what it plays on.
And I already have more ideas of stuff I want to build into it, um, that should be
out sometime today.
Um, I post that, uh, an internal email, uh, edited, of course for the protectors of
inside the corporation.
Um, uh, I did that on curry.com.
You could see that the releases planned, uh, for tomorrow, 3 p.m., that'll be Pacific
Standard Time.
So it won't be until later tonight, but, uh, shit's coming.
Then when I say a shit, I mean, cheese.
I mean the cheddar.
Hey, they're Adam.
Hey, baby.
He may send.
Hey, Rachel Krill fan.
Just checking in.
I was hoping you'd like to play a game with me.
You like games, don't you?
Oh, I love it.
No handcuffs or feathers involved in this one.
But you seem to know an awful lot about ancient 80s music.
Of course.
Of course stuff, like HTML that pod this and pod that, but do you know your pop culture?
Yes, of course.
For a game, Adam.
Oh, good.
Like a hit test.
Now, I believe you just took Kudotter, Christina, to see Justin's in the link.
Yep.
The question is, who is he rumored to be dating, uh, Jessica, um, Alba, no, um, Jessica,
something.
So did you get that one, Adam?
No.
That my boy, J.T.
Is dating Jessica Biel.
Biel.
Question number two.
I was going to have a point.
I love the lady Patricia has competed in the global sensation dancing with the stars,
which is also a huge hit here in the United States.
Who won the most recent U.S. version of dancing with the stars?
Well, I watch this show, obviously.
Apollo, whatever the guy's name is, Apollo.
Hello.
The winner was Apollo Anton Ono.
Oh, no, Heather Mills leg did not fly off because I know you care so much, Adam.
Last question is, who is older?
Brad Pitt's daughter, Shilo, or Tom Cruise's daughter, Surrey.
I'm pretty sure the cruise has had their daughter first.
So I'm going to go with the cruise kid.
Sorry, cruise is 39 days older than Shilo.
Surrey was born April 18th, while Shilo was born May 27th.
Yeah.
So how did you do, Adam?
Well, three.
I do like to play the game.
Would you like to play some more?
If you do, I think you're going to need some brushing up on your pop culture.
Please.
So subscribe to Brittany Mason's, the pop cast with your host, David Jen, at the
popcast.potcho.com.
Ciao.
Okay, Brittany.
Finally, we got that promo to work for you.
And I didn't want to listen to it because I didn't want to, you know, I didn't want
to know the answers before I did the test.
I think I got three, well, at least two and a half.
I got the, I didn't get Jessica Biel right.
Okay.
I, if that's going to be in a regular basis, that's pretty cool.
I'll subscribe to that.
I'll put that in my iPhone channel.
Oh, people.
Oh, the iPhone.
My goodness.
This thing is has changed my life.
I have to tell you, I'm, you know, still evaluating battery life.
It finally got a full charge last night.
So today, going into the city, we'll see how well it does.
I'm taking along the charger just in case.
One thing I've found that is completely, completely full barred about this device.
There's an, an automatic spell character in the, in the, in the typing system.
Now, this typing system, I'm actually, I'm kind of getting there, you know, the placement
of the, of the virtual keys, the visual feedback you get when you hit a key, which is kind
of nice, a big, you know, the letter, it kind of explodes up real quick so you can see
that you hit the right one.
I turn off the clicks because I don't like the, even though it's a really good feedback mechanism,
I find it highly annoying, particularly when I'm in bed under the covers while Patricia's
trying to sleep.
And I'm there with the iPhone, click, click, click, click now, that's not good.
But that, you know, you can't, for some, you can't seem to turn off this, it's like
predictive text or T9 that you would find on, on the Nokia, I hate it because, because,
here, so first of all, it only does English.
So, if I'm writing a message in Dutch, then it doesn't work and it, and, you know, you
have to physically go up and say, no, do not correct it.
It's not an opt-in, it's an opt-out, which is great if you're doing speed typing in English.
But if you're doing any other language, it's really cumbersome gets in the way.
And of course, when you're doing text messaging, it is the most cumbersome of all because
text messaging really exists of, you know, shorthand, short code, like instead of
why oh you, you do you instead of T-O-O, you do numeral two.
So it's continuously correcting, even English, if I want to say, in, it'll correct it
to I'm stupid, lame, need to be able to turn it off.
If there's any hackers out there who are working on this thing, I'm sure that through
the jailbreak software, we can disable that, it's so cumbersome.
So that's really, really bad.
Google Docs, on the other hand, I found out, actually works, it's unbelievable.
I've really done a, I'd have to say, a pretty good job.
And I'll continue to, to feedback and, and let, you know, what the experiences are.
But again, so far, it's all about the interface.
And it's really, really changed the way I look at the mobile web.
In fact, nice little discussion there on yesterday's show at podshow.com.
The DeadlySourceCode.com, commentary blogger, you know, saying, hey, you know, if you're
convinced that this is the way to go, now you only have to convince the 100 million, you
know, that the 500 million other people who don't have an iPhone, I think that this
is bar setting.
I think that, now, depending on the patents, which, of course, could make this whole thing
really suck, I believe everyone has to come out with a similar type of experience, you
know, that it doesn't have to be the pinch for Zoom and all that, but, man, I, you
know, I, I, I still, I think that they're not making any money on these things.
This screen, this technology must be extremely expensive, that just no way around it.
But damn, it's worth it.
Comic strip.
Ah, he's back.
Thank goodness.
Hello, Adam.
Hello.
Very caring.
When you were interviewing Madonna, yeah, and her vagina goes crazy.
Wait a minute.
See, as B, I try to keep it a little friend for family, friendly.
He's referring to my conversation about Madonna, where they edited the whole piece to look
really good instead of bitchy as the way she was at the time of the interview.
Alright, let's plug your ears and the kids to their room.
It's comic strip blogger.
You too.
You're annoying questions.
She just left the room.
Big deal.
But when I was interviewing certain top manager from Sun Corporation, makers of Java about
mobile Java, I was interviewing him, then he grabbed my recorder brutally, stopped it, ordered
me to delete their recording, and taught me to fuck off.
And well, did I do too offend his vagina?
Well, I think you're just your entire attitude and approach is pretty damn offensive
to most people who have something to defend.
Alright, we've met, I've met comic strip blogger, and I like him, and he's my kind
of guy.
He is in your face and brash, and you, someone could call it just pure honesty, but it's
definitely not the personable approach that CEOs of large companies are used to.
And of course, they used to complete control over their messaging.
So, whatever it was, it was probably just the frightening look in your eyes that pissed
them off.
So, yes, be really wasn't the question at all, you know, oh my god, no matter what I say,
this guy is dangerous.
Danger, warning will robins.
I just asked how mobile Java compares to flesh that easily is scalable to all resolutions.
So, I'm very happy that Steve Jobs said that he doesn't like Java, and will not put
this Java shit on the iPhone, well, I don't give a fuck about your metrics talk.
When it's this about general deception, about life and so on, but please, could you also
talk about deception when it comes to marketing of various products and services?
By the way, I am blooped, take care, and loving it, yeah, you can't fool me.
Unless, of course, keeping in the matrix metaphor, you are a century, that is very possible.
You thought those centuries were the guys and the black suits were the black shades on
actually, they all look like comic strip blogger.
Deceptive marketing practices, I don't think there's so much as deceptive as, you know,
the same practices are applied, you know, sex is really used in 99.9% of all advertising,
you know, again, CSB, I'd like you to take the Zen TV experiment.
Please check it out and let me know how you fare it on that, because, you know, what basically
sells is, hey, if you drink this beer, you'll get laid, if you buy this car, you'll
get laid.
If you use this, this is it, you'll get laid, it's what it's all about, it's about not
dying, being very successful and wealthy, or getting laid, that's all that advertising
is about.
It's playing into the purest form of emotions, and by the way, you know, this is what reality
television is all about, you know, this is what drama is about.
We all understand the basic human emotions of joy, sadness, fear, and maybe there's an
escalation to terror, and it's really, in fact, the easiest is to play into terror,
by even calling it terrorist, war on terror, it's so simple.
So, you know, that's what advertising does, man, and advertising is used for everything.
You advertise when you present an idea, you know, and you may, you know, you present to
a corporation the way you did to us on your beautiful, the best presentation I've ever
seen, by the way, comic strip blogger, I've told you about that, had a great slide show
which ended with fuck you Adam Curry, it was perfect, I showed it to the board of directors,
they loved it.
I said, we're picking up some good quality business leads, you know, that very clearly,
you said, if you don't implement this plan, you know, pod show will die, and I don't
want pod show to die, anyway, I know how to play into your emotions on this show,
I do it all the time, and the easiest way for me to play into your emotions is for you
to recall the emotions that are relevant to you, to each individual, and we do that through
something called the soundtrack to our lives.
Actually it's this, and we're at number 79 right now, oh and I got some requests for this
one, I thought wild, why not, oh and, of course, there's something else I would like
to share with you, and that is this sound, can you tell what it is?
I know what that is, I've heard that one before, every dad in the world, from some sort
of tests, not a hit test, it's something else.
It worked, and it's someone that's due January 27th, awesome thing, awesome of the next
year, the sound of new life, this is still inside of my girlfriend, but I am going to be
a father again, and I'm so happy about that, so that's something I would, I wanted
to share with you.
Congratulations, y'all, awesome, all right, back to the music, the hit test, this
is intro number one, and I played this so often, a decibel radio, Odyssey, I'm going
back to my roots, yeah, number two, y'all, can you get any easier, ABC, look of love, I
recognize these, that's so easy for me, this, I'm at this projective, remember, and today's
final intro number three, these are like the best intro, of course it's yes, owner of
a lonely heart, forget the questions, I can't wait to sing along to the answers, awesome
young, and times up in this attention number one, from 1981, Odyssey, back to my roots,
is intro number one, and this is intro number two, from 1982, I'm going back to my roots,
is intro number one, and this is intro number two, from 1982, the look of love, this is ABC,
is intro number two, this is the third and final answer, from 1984, this is yes, an
owner of a lonely heart, owner of a lonely heart the owner of a lonely heart for me,
Again, they were not too difficult, so where do I hope you had them all?
Oh yeah man, of course.
The answers and iTunes links can be found at Hitest.boxio.com.
And next week I'll be back for number 80.
So until then, take care and bye-bye.
Awesome.
What the hell?
Oh, it's the hard beat.
Awesome.
Hitest, John.
And congratulations to you and your girlfriend as we say in the engineering business.
It worked.
Clearly it worked.
Of course, in the drama business, we say, who done it?
Oh, man.
I love those songs.
They were, I mean, they were what we call open doors, very easy to guess those awesome
editing job.
Beyond.
Of course, the hitest is brought to you by the organization for preservation to the soundtrack
of our lives.
Upsold.org.
They don't have a website yet, but they're for real, at least their intent is.
And as John said, hitest.boxio.com, you can find all of the answers, the clean version
of the hittest.
And of course, the links to all of these songs and iTunes.
And if I had, well, if I had 30 cents for every single song, we sold through iTunes
in that manner.
Oh, let me tell you.
Oh, let me just scan through, I've been saving stuff.
I've been starring stuff, I should say, in Google Reader.
Let me just see if there's anything that I wanted to talk to you about.
This is interesting on slash dot, email is like so dead.
Group of teenage internet business entrepreneurs confess that they really only use email
to talk to adults.
You know, I'd have to say that's true, at least that's what I'm seeing with Christina.
She seems to be living in Facebook these days.
I'm trying to gauge it.
I'm trying to see if she's on my space more than Facebook.
It seems like Facebook and, you know, I've tried to inquire, you know, why or what or what
she likes about it.
And it's kind of hard.
She can't really explain it.
It's like crack, I guess, and it has a lot to do with, you know, the quick hit fix
of instant messaging and all these things kind of tied into one, but it's, it's really
quite amazing.
Let me just check the notebook here.
Oh, this is a good one.
PG Kelly, who sends me emails on a daily basis, said, why don't you have Doug and his
son work on the prep of Trinity, have them deliver Trinity to Sean and Amy?
That would be kind of good.
San Francisco to, well, why don't we have Shane and Amy go from Chicago to Boston and pick
it up there and then start in Boston.
That's a, that's a pretty good idea.
I'm still looking for a great, a great way to, to pin for out.
Oh, this is going to be cool.
So that's starting in November.
I'm so happy we're finally figuring out the, the free Trinity project and are able to
morph that with a, a here at the wheel.
Those guys are pretty awesome.
Jason Chaser used to be an ordinary college student, but now he works for the FBI hunting
down criminals with special abilities, using a special ability of his own.
You can see the aura that surrounds every living creature.
This aura allows Jason to see what someone is going to do before they do it with a hundred
percent accuracy.
How would Jason's powers evolve?
Will he bring in these criminals dead or alive?
And how will his relationship with the lovely Catherine Wolf develop?
That is up to you.
The Aurora Hunter by Marcus Noble is the first ever audience choice podcast novel.
Subscribe at hunternovel.podshow.com for all the details on how you can help shape this
story.
You know, this whole audio novel thing is so awesome.
And we're working out a fantastic, fantastic agreement for authors who want to participate
and want to do an audio novel.
And want to be published because podshow press will actually publish you.
Marcus Ocean Martin M. Cough is spearheading that and there's going to be some awesome
books.
It's just, it's so right.
It's one of those things.
You know, you just kind of stumble on it started for us, at least it started with the Scott
Sigler and Shadow Falls and the formats been refined and we're going to make it very
much like the pod save music network where, you know, you get promotion of course by putting
your songs up and podcast playing your songs and you can sell through the pod save music
network.
It's not perfect yet, but we take none of the money, all of the revenue except for nine
cents transaction fee, which is charged by clicking by the artist goes directly to them.
It's not perfect, of course, but it's a start.
And so, too, for the sales of the books, you know, all of the revenue from the books.
And I think that's actually not bad.
I think it's like seven bucks or something.
Don't hold me to it.
But that goes directly to the authors after we've done the audio novel, which is the new
model.
It's published the audio book, the audio novel, episodically by chapter.
At the end of that release, a hardcover or paperback version book, it works.
So you know, I'm going to be up late tonight as Cheddar gets released.
I can't wait for you guys to be trying this out.
Very minimal changes for those who aren't interested except every single channel you'll
see, you'll be able to access in a different manner.
You'll be able to play out in a different manner.
Oh, my gosh, I'll even be in RSS icon.
Oh, stand back.
Chapter of Dama.
Hey, I never go to call myself, whatever.
I just have a quick reaction about the channel's thing, number one, I think it's as cool
as you do.
This is what I guess 3.0 is going to be about blending things together that it's where
it wasn't possible before you don't talk about it.
It's really cool.
You know, my problem is something that I don't think you're going to be able to solve,
but I thought I'd just, if nobody else has said this, I thought I'd throw it out.
My problem is I listen to my iPod, and you know, in terms of what I think do this, we
can mute, and this will get this through.
So I'd love to have a stream of channels that the problem is is that I want somebody to manage
my iPod for you.
So when I, you know, listen to a series of shows, I want them not to necessarily disagree
from the iPod, but to, you know, something is going to be able to manage that list.
And I don't want to have to do it manually all the time.
That is directly what I have to do.
And that's why I shy away from the channel, I deal a little bit because it just means
more things where I have to go through and go, God, do I listen to that or not?
You know what I'm saying?
A lot of manual management, and unfortunately you have no control over that iPod
or any other device.
So we need to wait to the next generation or there's going to be a paradigm shift here or something.
Man, if you could make it so that like when I'm done,
when I press play in the iPod, I get the next show that I haven't listened to yet.
And when I think it doesn't change that,
I think that's where it's going.
That's the minimum where it's going.
Of course, it's going to be more of a way to protect.
But I'm still going to check it out.
I still enjoy the idea of channels that those may be easier than I think.
Good work, man.
See it.
I think I understood what you asked.
And I think it kind of works that way.
Now, this may be only with a new generation iPod.
In this case, I have the most latest iPod, which is of course,
is the iPhone.
Let me tell you how I've set mine up.
And then you tell me if that's what you're talking about.
So in my iTunes, I'm subscribed to three channels.
Let me just bring them up right now so I can tell you what they are.
So it's the Aviation Channel, which consists of a number of aviation shows.
It's a test channel called iPhone, which only has one show in it right now.
And then really, the most important show is the on the go show, which is all the short stuff
that I want to have loaded up to take with me on the train rise and just to be around
when I have a couple minutes to listen to something.
And it's a topical stuff as well.
So I've loaded those into iTunes.
Now, when I put my, oh, I guess you have to actually put the iPod in order to bring up the settings.
So I think there's a, I think it's just a matter of settings, hold on one second.
I mean, I want you to hear the whole experience.
Okay, so I'm plugging my iPhone into the, into the dock there.
You can hear my computer immediately recognize a device.
Going, boom, boom.
Of course, it still always brings up the this wizard.
Welcome to the, to the found new hardware wizard.
This wizard helps you install software for digital still camera.
I don't know how to, it keeps popping up so I keep saying cancel.
All right, so it's now synchronizing.
And let me go to a podcast because there's a certain way can be handled.
Okay, so here are the options.
So you want to sync.
And then you can either select which, which podcast in this case three channels.
So aviation on the go and iPhone, I'll show up or all.
So for me, it's all podcasts, which is actually all channels.
And then I have options here to sync all one most recent three,
most recent five or ten all on played, all new blah, blah, blah.
So what I've done is I've selected all unplayed.
So what happens now is the pod show channel keeps loading stuff in.
It's a one way mechanism.
So it's, it's saying here's new stuff.
Here's new stuff and it's shoving it towards iTunes.
iTunes is is happily accepting that and downloading it.
But when I play something on the iPod or if I play it on iTunes and it's marked as played.
So it doesn't have a little blue ball next to it.
It then disappears from the iPod because it's set to sync all unplayed episodes.
So when you've played something, you hit next.
Oh, go to the next one.
The next time you synchronize because of course that is kind of the crunch and all of this.
The ones you've listened to will go away.
So the system does work.
I think it solves exactly what you're talking about.
Now the next big trick of course for us is to create a widget that allows you to put your channels anywhere to play them out in a smooth experience.
And even better when you find something on the web and you want to add it to your channel.
That's when I wanted to be like a dragon dragon.
I'm being on desert.
I'm just curious.
Is there any correlation between folder, scruncher, red bill and blue pill?
Something to think about.
Hmm.
Well, you think that scrunchers would have red tendencies and therefore red pill.
But I think it's folders and red pills for sure.
Scrunchers and blue pills.
Let's find out what a huge scruncher, folder, red pill or blue pill.
Or you just joke college.
This guy's ripping up the scene and jersey.
To get the love.
We were swinging like a grape for much fun.
We made it that night and got it in a fight.
Then my morning everything's alright.
I'm not much too touchy feeling stuck.
But we gotta get the love.
We all need the love.
We all need the love,
We all need love, you don't love
Haven't said from the bottom
Hang on to death, you don't love
When you find somebody, we let trust
The world, the world
We all need love, we don't love
We all need love, you don't love
We are neither, keep the love, have us sent from the world, hang on to it, keep the love, when you find somebody, we let judge the love, we are neither, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love,
keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love. keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep the love, keep
For more fun stuff right here, dailysourcecode.com, Adam at podshow.com, I'll see you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.
Don't forget the cheddar.
The best in the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.