It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Well, sorry, no good intro today, but wanted to pass along that, after you're done listening
to the DSC 535, you should go over to helpingthecause.com.
Team Bidious trying to raise $25,000 in the MS Walk in April, so as a good podcast listener
as a good podcast citizen, go over to helpingthecause.com, look for Team Biddy, and pledge
a little bit.
They can use all the help they can get in, they'll make it feel good.
And now, somewhere in the curry quarters, above the curry kitchen where the curry cat is
on the curry counter, eating curry crackers, here's that.
So, we're going to go over to the next generation radio, we're going to go over to the next generation
radio, we're going to go over to the next generation radio, we're going to go over to the next generation
radio, you know, I know I say this plenty of times, but you just don't hear enough
of it.
I'm going to go over to the next generation radio, we're going to go over to the next generation
radio, we're going to go over to the next generation radio, we're going to go over to the next
generation radio, we're going to go over to the next generation radio, we're going to go over
to the next generation radio, we're going to go over to the next generation radio, we're
going over to the next generation radio, we're going over to the next generation radio, we're
going over to the next generation radio, we're going over to the next generation radio,
we're going over to the next generation radio, we're going over to the next generation radio,
I got a couple of emails yesterday from people saying that they really hated the sound
of the setup here in the, well, we're still calling the cottage.
So I started to mess around with it, got into real trouble on the mixer, I mean, got
everything screwed up and I have no idea how it, I think I sound a little nasal, let me
see, how's everything set here, one, two, one, two, whatever.
Hi, this is Gilbert in Georgia, I was thinking about the name for a new place there, I'm sure
somebody must have suggested it, but maybe not, I don't know, why not curie kingdom, I mean,
it is a big grand, but then life is grand, anyway, just let I drop that in, enjoy
listening to the show, down here in the beach, so anyway, have a good day, see you later, bye.
All right, man, appreciate it. Okay, I think that I've decided that there are, you know,
there are a couple of names I like, I just want to get it over with already, and I think I'm
going to have to shy away from a literation, so we can't have a cook sound, although curie
kingdom is kind of nice, but if it's going to be a literation, I'd like it at least to be two seas,
I think the curie manner is sounding pretty good to me. I'm going to try it on, you're
going to do, I'm going to change the wireless access points to curie manner, see how it feels,
because it actually, it could sound good, it's like, from the curie manner, from the curie
manner on a hilltop, on the west side of G-town.
This music, on safe music live, featuring coat of funnick.
Matthew Ebel.
David McMillan.
Kevin Reeves.
Don't think I can make it on my own.
And Jeff Smith, I want it to be hell up in the sound seats, stuck in the middle of everywhere.
With special guests, C.C. Chapman from Accident Ash, on safe music live,
it all starts at 6 p.m. Tuesday that he wore a 20-bit edge hill studios at Nashville,
Tennessee.
For more information, visit accidenthash.com.
You know, that sounds like a damn good show. Gosh, I don't want now the,
I've got all kinds of ground loops in the studio. It's really weird. If I plug in the
printer, then all of a sudden I get a ground loop. If I put the, if I put the power book on top of the
TLA 55, was it 552 stereo valve processor, then I get some kind of other different like a
hard disk like ground loop sound. Ah, lots of stuff getting used. I'm going to really work on
the place today. I've got the, I've got the fireplace up here going, which is really nice. It's
a nice and toasty warm. I just got a start and unpacking some boxes. This morning, of course,
we were up bright and early in Antis, wow, it's my microphone really hot now, hot.
An anticipation of the, of the sky guy coming. Well, I'm just adjusting some stuff. I'm sorry
you have to bear with me through all this crap. Mind as well. Do it now. Okay. The sky guy was
supposed to come. I've ordered the multi rooms sky view package, which includes two regular sky
plus digital boxes, and one HD, or is they saying the UK HD? So that one, so I don't have the
HD television yet. I was planning on maybe going out this afternoon and making that purchase.
So the sky guy shows up and he's, oh, okay. Great. Let's, let's get this going here.
And he says, wait a minute, you have three boxes. Yes, three boxes. Remember, this is the same
company that, you know, the guy said he couldn't find my house. This may be the same guy.
I actually have to ask him that. He's from Leeds. He's only been in this region for three weeks.
So that sounds like it probably wasn't a nice enough guy. And he looks up at the roof and he
sending says, okay. And then he looks at where the, where the phone access point is, which, of
course, is exactly on the other side of the house. And these sky boxes have to talk back to home based,
you know, basically upload all my information to home base. So they have to talk a
communicate via a telephone. He says, you know, this is, I have six more installs today on this
is a whole day job. I said, yeah, no shit. So, you know, we call up sky home base, phone home to Murdock.
And yeah, they say, well, if, if we can wait until tomorrow, then he can spend the whole day
on doing the install here. Okay. Exasperating, I tell you, hey, lots of feedback on Trinity.
We're really, uh, we're getting somewhere. We actually have something to look at, which I'll get
to later on in this very show. Yeah, good day. Adam, it's a Scott from Sydney, Australia. It's
kind of to say how much I enjoy your podcast. It's that sort of fantastic. I've been listening to
it for a bit of a very young app. And I listen to it every day in the health desk when I'm supposed
to be doing calls. And all the guys in the health desk also enjoy your podcast and they want
to say, he got the good work and, uh, chill out, man. So, yeah, there's a lot to it and, uh,
I talk to you saying. Hi. Adam, yeah. No, thanks, dude. I appreciate it. So, you're all sitting there at
the health desk when you're supposed to be, and what kind of health desk is it? Is it for a certain
product? Are you all just sitting there just goofing off doing, you know, nothing better to do at
all. Listen to the daily source code. Oh, I gotta get my ass down to Australia. I really
really, really, really want to go. Maybe, I don't know if it'll be this year. This year or next year,
we definitely have to get down there, uh, neither Patricia or Christina have ever seen Australia.
And I know that they would really love it. It's just, yeah, we gotta get someone to look after
the animals and look after the house and all that stuff. But, um, yeah, I would love to do that.
Just revisit some of the places I've been to before. And then go to some of the other spots that
I've never been to. I've never been of north, uh, the northern part of Australia. And I bet they
would love that.
Common strip, common strip, common strip, common strip, common strip, common strip, common strip, common
strip, common strip, common strip, common strip. Now, I haven't listened to this comment that
comments were going to come through blogger sent in. Um, he's been on a rampage lately about,
uh, you know, this, this interview that I said I would do with him and he feels completely
slided that I've said I don't really want to meet him in person. So I'm thinking, I just get my schedule
together. I get my schedule together for the next week and a half. Because, you know, third week of
February, I'm back to the States again. This is my new regime. And I'm just going to tell them
when I'm going to be in London and when I'm available. Let's see what he has to say today.
Hi, Adam Curry. I think interview with you. Sorry, man. But you promised me. So yeah,
told you, I told you in a rampage about this publicly on the SC giving it to me in person.
And then you then integrated me by saying Skype only. What could be considered as racism if
only we would be of different race. Racism, shortly speaking, gives this interview to me in person
or fuck you. It will never happen. You bastard. Oh, please. So speaking of racism, Adam,
have you had about such a thing or issue as this happening particularly in UK that, you know,
there is an employer or business owner. Yeah, almost like I'm coming straight blogger. First of all,
as I said, what we're going to do is I'm going to set up a time when I'm going to be in London,
because I'm going to have to be in London anyway to do stuff at the office. And you'll just have to
come on over. Right? Because the problem is you always want to meet me in the weekend, which is just
not really feasible. I am messing around so much with all the knobs. It is, it's a knobby day. That's
for sure. Manaja, and he has a worker. And this worker is a person of color. But this worker is
lazy or is underperforming. Oh, you know what? I'm not interested. Comics are blogger. It's about
your racism thing. And I'm over that. All the newspapers here, once again, full of Shilpa Shetty winning
the celebrity big brother television show slash contest slash reality program. I think people are
enjoying it. And I predict she's going to be a huge star. I think she already got some kind of TV
gig that they offered her. Now, I think she's going to do a lot of stuff over here. The bother would
stuff. I've never really been able to get into it. Maybe I have to see it on a big screen. Maybe
someone has to explain a little bit of the backstory. And maybe I love the dancing and so the
choreography and all the wardrobe is all beautiful. It's in a photography is fantastic. But I just don't
I can't really get into the story if you don't mind. Hey, you know what? Let's, uh, let's get this thing
rolling here. It's time to talk about everybody's girlfriend. The green color of Mercedes 300 turbo
yelled just stays shining.
Oh, sing along every ride the trained need a criminal central luxury dream
watch a Triomie triumony to Les Dubaiオ- Diesel set to bring Tri familee trip
All right, so here's what's coming on the Gmail regarding Trinity.
First of all, we have a Google map of retail biodiesel locations.
It's at BrevardBioDiesel.org.
Excuse me, for that nasty Splendid comment.
Can we?
Splendid?
Since sale moment with a Splendid twist, that's what it was.
Can we get a coffee sponsor already?
I'm so sick and tired of promoting since sale for free.
Bravo, Romeo, Echo, Victor, Alpha, Romeo, Delta, biodiesel.org.
And there's a map there.
It's pretty extensive, although there are some major gaps with this, of course, as retail
locations, and it's listed by, you know, what grade of biodiesel they have.
So what I'm looking for is someone who can help me with one of these Google maps, because
now we have this part, can we take that data, can we start filling in the spots?
So we have, you know, no more than like 100 miles between each individual spot so we can
start a route.
And everybody should be able to add themselves as a, a biodiesel stop, b, a biodiesel point
of interest, c, a podcaster, and then d willing to help out anyway you can.
So if we get all those points on the map, then we can start to build up a route and
believe me, this is not going to be limited to the United States.
That's one thing, what's abundantly clear.
Here's an update from Rosie from pod show HQ Adam.
Here's the new update on Trinity.
Okay, so remember what happened was, I drove out to Concord to visit fries on the
way back, all of a sudden, she, she conked out.
I was completely right about the fuel starvation, although incorrect about the,
the lines being clogged up, here's what's going on.
The gas tank appears to be crushed at the bottom.
This prevents the gas or the biodiesel from reaching the fuel line when the tank is low.
I have to admit the tank was about a quarter full.
So if the tank's full, no problem.
The mechanic recommends overhauling the current tank and replacing the fuel send in unit,
fuel send in unit, $97.50 gas tank overhaul, $168 plus two and a half hours labor.
The whole repair adds up to another $567.79 on top of the 500.
I just spent for them to do nothing but replace my battery, which I didn't need.
On top of the transmission, which was like $2,000 to $3,000 on top of the,
well, doesn't matter.
I got a lot of money in this baby, and she's worth it.
So yes, of course, the cost has approved.
Absolutely, we got to get her on the road.
So she's running.
That's the good news.
It's no junk clogged up in the engine and was purely a gas tank initiative or issue.
Love it.
Who's this?
Scott.
From topdeadcenter.podshow.com, does Trinity have a trailer hitch?
No, I don't think so.
Because if you get a trailer, well, Trinity could pull her own biodiesel refinery.
Now, that is a damn good idea.
Because then you can get Google Earth or Google Maps, and you could get all the fast food restaurants.
This makes it a little more complex.
But if we act, you know what, okay, so here's an idea.
Why do we put a trailer hitch on the Trinity?
God, I like this a lot.
And so in addition to visiting biodiesel points throughout the country, she could also
visit biodiesel friendly.
This is great.
Biodiesel friendly restaurants, and they'll donate vegetable oil, you know, just stuff that
they got laying around got to get rid of anyway.
And, you know, and then Trinity can process her, you know, right there on the spot.
I like that a lot.
There are a couple of companies who make, who make the biodiesel kits.
They're about, what are they?
They're about $1,500 for a complete kit.
And it could indeed fit on a trailer and be pulled around behind or so.
I really like that idea.
Let's add that one to the mix.
I still don't have anyone to actually maintain this map of wonderful points.
But I think the more I read the, the more I read emails coming in and people's ideas,
the more I'm liking the whole idea of managing it through one Google map.
That just has all this information because they don't be very easy to plot out our trip.
So, if please, if you understand how to make do these map mashups,
please get in touch with the adamatpodshow.com.
Cameron Patterson sent me interesting link mini-box mini-box.com.
Company that makes cars, PCs for cars.
I don't know, I think we're, we're having, we have a call with Nokia today.
This afternoon, I'm going to see if we can get to Nokia to jump on board because it would be a
perfect application to run on, I would say on the internet tablet.
I mean, it's got a camera built in. It can communicate with a cell phone.
It can do all these things you need. It runs on Linux. So, pretty much bullet proof.
And of course, it communicates with Wi-Fi. I mean, there's a whole bunch of things we can do there.
What's this one? From Ola, Ola Christian Vale.
I think that's the way it pronounces name. He says, dude, you got a sender to the Ferro Islands.
After a tour of the UK Trinity could go on a North Atlantic tour from Scrabster, Scotland to the Ferro Islands.
Iceland, on to Norway, maybe even Denmark. I said to me a couple of pictures. Yes, I would love that.
I think we can get it around the world. Do you think it's not possible? I think this podcasting
stuff has enough people committed to promoting podcasting and to promoting something like
independence of big oil. This one from Dave from New York.
Adam, I'm totally stoked on this Trinity across the USA concept for it's free
Trinity, by the way. I just want to make sure that we keep Doug Pilgrim's original idea and
tacked free Trinity. Adam, there's nothing green about an egg nog color. Let me my pal cover her
and Astro turf. We've done it with vehicles in Europe in New York City. It looks perfect. And the
response in the street is unbelievable. Imagine how it would look on a bends. If you want to
attract attention this way, people used to leave us gifts on the car like golf balls or vegetable.
Sometimes we'd come back to where we parked to find chicks, sunbathing on the roof. Okay,
good idea. I think I think we shouldn't get our Astro turf. So we'll do that the
minute she hits New York. Hi, Adam. It's Timothy from the Twisted Risk podcast.
Not just finished listening to DSC 533. Normally I speak about riding on two wheels in such.
But there's something else I've got more than a passing interesting. And that's biodies. In fact,
it's that sweet smelling oil or more accurately Trinity that got me listening to the daily
source code in the first place. You see, I chew on an older Mercedes diesel. In fact, my 1982
300 TD aka Moby is pretty much an exact replica of your beloved Trinity. My great will of a car
was purchased with the same goal of burning biodiesel and vegetable oil. I believe I may be the
only other podcaster out there with the same car as yourself. Now, don't go think in that. I'm
some kind of freakish curie groupie. I had my car well before Trinity found a way. So it's natural
that all this talk about the free-trandy project has me pumped up with vigor. Here are my thoughts
on the free-trandy thing. One listener suggested making it an international event by shipping
Trinity to Europe when she reaches these coast. But you do realize that you don't have to go over
seas to break the border. Tell you what, get Trinity up here to Toronto and I'll ensure that she's
fed with the green grease that's good for her. We can introduce her to my movie and who knows,
maybe they could get busy and have a little smart car together, right? Now, producing a
older cyclopodcast as I do, I'm aware of a company called Star Tracks, that's star-tr-a-w-x.
That has tracking units that long distance bike riders use to keep their friends and family
at home updated automatically if they're aware about. Such units have been used extensively and
successfully in the 11 day 11,000 mile iron butt rally as well as the world rally championship
if you're more akin to four wheels. When are you considering this trip to take place anyway?
If it's around the summer solstice, the second annual podcasters across borders,
aka podgimp Canada will run from June 22 to 24th in Kingston, Ontario. That's just east of Toronto
and on the way to Boston, and the perfect pit stop for Trinity in this little picturesque and
historic town on Lake Ontario. If, however, it's too early in the year, this parade of bio-fuel vehicles,
you envision may have issues with cold vegetable oil, and that could cause some problems for some
engines. Not good. So those are my two Canadian sense on the whole idea. I hope you can make use
of some of the points I brought up and I'd love to see Trinity make her way north of the border
for a visit. Take care Adam. This is Timothy Pilgrim. See ya. All right Timothy. Yeah, absolutely.
I mean, again, we just have to get this map started out so everyone can put their,
everyone could put their, their place mark on and link to their podcast or pictures or
or maybe have a video and so we can get a good idea if we want to be involved in this.
Maybe even some folks who are listening to serious stars 102 might want to get involved.
Really easy. Go to dailysourcecode.com download the rest of the show or send me an email
Adam at podshow.com. Love to hear from you guys as well. And thanks for listening and they're gone.
Yeah, I'm getting excited about this. This is going to be really cool.
Hi Adam. It's Daisy here from podcasting. I'm just catching up with the charity after getting
a podcatcher on my Nakia phone. I got one of those Nakia in 91 music phones and you're on my
podcatcher. That means I can hear your pipes without going near my computer. I must say that's really nice
on those Nakia phones. As you say it up there in Ireland is, uh, and I have that on my E61. That's the
the podcatcher. It has a little, uh, a little application that'll download podcats. I do miss that on the
on the N800 tablet. Although I figured out some other ways to get to get my favorite podcats. You
can actually use the, uh, what is it? The play in Windows media player button on any pod show site.
It'll open up, um, either the show with all of its archives or you can open up a channel that way,
which works pretty well. But that's just pretty good. I have to agree. Also, it right there.
And you've got directories. You've got the top pod show picks. You've got, uh, all of podcats
stally, podcats pickle is on there. It's a ton of different podcats that work. So a really good place
to go find and certainly to subscribe to shows. Anyway, I'm here trying some hazelnut splendor.
When I hear dog talking to you about taking trinity across the states, I think that's a deadly
idea. And I was wondering, would dog pick up an Irish hitchhiker along the way?
His name is Doug. I know you're saying Doug, but it sounds a bit like dog. It's kind of like
a girl or a bad member. There is no one greener in the world than I was Irish, you know?
I mean, if he's driving from California to Massachusetts, he must be going through Kansas, right?
So I figured I could meet up with trinity and dog in Kansas. Then talk the lads into checking out
some wood pellet stoves in Iowa. Imagine that trinity hole, a boshal of wood pellets from my
farming cousins in Iowa. Isn't that handy that we just decided to put a trailer here, John,
or, huh? Yeah, went all through to Iowa to farm. I could snap shots from my mnuckier phone.
I'm using zontag so that I can just take a picture and then automatically tag it and send it to
flicker right after reviewing the photo. You see, this is what's going to work really well. Everybody
has their tools, their devices, they know how to get stuff up on the web, they know how to link
stuff. So I think this map will be so cool. We've done a few carcass here in Tipperary,
so it's fair to say that if I tagged along, you'll get some European perspective on the great
biodiesel adventure. And if you set this up this summer, we'll have a Nokia in 95 phone for the trip.
We've been playing around with the developer's model now and it's really, really slick.
You wouldn't believe the things that I can actually do. What else? Well,
I think Trinity should visit the Amish community in Pennsylvania dot country.
Amish have never been on a podcast, so Trinity will be recording the first Amish words,
exclusive to Pod Show listeners. Another thing, Adam.
Hold on a second, before you get to that, good idea. I mean, that's also important.
It's, that would be an interesting sight to see. I don't know if there's, if
Amish people have ever, have never been recorded. I mean, I've certainly seen documentaries.
I don't know what they think of Trinity. It's not, it's not quite playing according to their rules.
It's getting pretty close though. Maybe they could supply us with some fuel.
You're not keeping Trinity that baby poo yellow for the trip.
I am a baby.
You're a good coach at the outgreen for us.
I don't know the something about the the eggnog white eggnog yellow, baby poo yellow.
You know what? That's disgusting. Thanks for calling. I really appreciate it.
Welcome to this week in London to the podcast about my hometown. You're going to enjoy as much as I do.
I love this city and I want to share in some of the things that happen here. Tell you a little
about what's going on. Tell you what to do, what not to do. Thanks for avoiding things to enjoy.
You can find out the subscription details at London.botsho.com.
You can find the website itself at www.isweekinlandon.co.uk.
In a can email me about this week in London at gmail.com. Thanks very much.
Talk to you later.
Yeah, that's been a show that I've been listening to myself because you know London's like my town now
and it's really nice to hear what's going on. Great show. Thanks for the promo.
All right, you don't forget to close the whole Trinity segment with the official theme song.
You can't talk about Trinity without the bookmark and heard like a nice compact baby poo sandwich
between Jeff Smith's jingles on either side.
Trinity, let the bio diesel set your green, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity,
free Trinity, save the world, win valuable prizes, Trinity.
So I wanted to open a one new line of conversation. Otherwise it's all going to be about Trinity
in the name of my house, which is a little bit boring. I do understand that. This comment came
in last week while I was in San Francisco. I've been saving it because I thought it was a very
interesting question. One that I might even be able to answer myself in some ways.
But have a listen to it and I'd love to hear your take on it.
Forgive me, podfighter, if I have seen it as barely three months since I last left the voice
mail message. I'm calling you from work because I have a monumental question.
Sort of on the same lines as the folding or scrunching and we know how well that took us.
I work for a very cool put, very posh company. We have lots of very cool put, very posh, very
highly educated people. My question is this. How is it that in such a working environment?
When I come to use the bathrooms, the toilets, whatever you wish to call them, quite often,
there is toilet paper, strewn across the floor. We also have problems with broken toilet seats,
with soap dispenses that have been broken, with paper towels in the sink. We're talking about
highly educated people here and they can't do the most simple of hygiene and things.
Is it just happening in my office? Do people sort of portray this corporate front
only to go out to the privacy of the bathroom and allow it loose?
Hmm. Any help here in any place would be very much appreciated.
Isn't that interesting? And you know what? I do see that quite a lot.
And I don't know exactly what it is. The question is, are posh people pigs and if so, why?
Adam at poncho.com. And of course, oh, I should actually do the, let's see where is it here.
I haven't done this in a while. Let's give out the UK number to call in with your voicemail
comments. Would love to hear from you.
So, a while ago, I was reintroduced to a friend of mine who hadn't spoken to in years.
Rudy Sarza, who I met when he was a base player for white snake. Currently, he's playing with
the DO. And I was introduced by Ty Poe. And a lot of podcasts with no who Ty Poe is or
Prince of Pessa. I guess is how she signs their emails. She's a huge promoter of pod save music.
In particular, Sophia Ramos. And she has Rudy's email address and said, no, you know,
a little reintroduction. So, I was really nice. And Rudy has a book out called Off the Rails.
And it's about his time with Randy Rhodes, which of course was in Ozzy's band and
quite riot. And I read this book. I read to see it. It took a while to deliver. I bought it off
of Amazon. It took maybe two and a half, maybe in three weeks to get here. Because I don't know.
I don't know how Amazon works. But I guess it's not readily available on the shelf. But it was a
very good read. It filled in a lot of blanks for me about a period of rock and roll. When I just
before, I got into a television, even before MTV in the Netherlands, even during some of that time.
It just it filled in a lot of blanks. Also about Rudy stuff. I didn't know. And it's written in a
very person. It's almost, I would have to say it's a bit webloggish like he kept a diary while it was
on the road in the late 70s and in the 80s. And he may still be keeping a diary. I don't know.
But it's a great way, you know, to have notes to go back and write about your experiences,
particularly the day when Randy died, which is just mailing you read about this, it's horrible.
In fact, Rudy and other people on the tour bus are lucky to be alive because the aircraft
that Randy was in, you know, the wing, I think struck the bus first before crashed into a
into a private residence. Anyway, I mean, you'd have to read the book.
And I was very, well, first of all, I was pleasantly surprised when I heard that to quiet riot had
uploaded a few new songs from their rehab CD to the Podsake Music Network. And
Brent from PodsakeauRadio, PodsakeauRadio.com, had an interview with Kevin Dubrow of Quiet Riot.
And so I'm listening to this interview. And I was quite amazed at the following piece that I heard.
Listen to this. I'm sober. And I liked the people on playing with better.
Better than playing with the Rudy Sarasel and Randy Rhodes.
Well, no, better than playing with the Sarasel. Randy Rhodes, I adore playing with.
So what's better than playing with better than playing with Rudy and Carlos?
I don't, don't thank you, you liked playing too much with Rudy. What was the deal with Rudy?
I, you know, I really want to get into it. It's over. And the, the gift of the
situation is I'm no longer playing with him. So the fact that I don't have to play with him anymore,
it makes it so it's a good thing. It's a good for him. It's good for everybody.
Good for everybody involved. You know, so I didn't read a single bad word about anyone in this entire book.
Certainly not about band members. Only about members of the press. But, you know, that was kind of a
running theme throughout the book where Rudy's picking up reviews from the previous night's show.
And he can tell exactly when the reviewer wasn't actually there. He just kind of wrote some
shit up just to get his article in. But not a bad word. And like, listen to this Kevin to brown guy.
Dude, what's up with that? You know, first of all, you say something, I guess it's kind of disparaging.
You know, you say like, well, I'm too happy. I'm not playing with people. I want to.
And then when when you're asked to explain, you're like, oh, well, I don't have to talk about that.
Fuck you, dickhead. What's your problem? It's really unhealthy, by the way, to keep that shit
pent up after 20 years, you know? So let's, let's get it out. Get it out and the open.
This may help you. Quiet, Ryan, free.
With your dark nature, you don't know what that takes. No, no, no.
It's a marathon now. Can't you see? For a turn in your dark enemy. Here are voice that keeps on telling me.
I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm the drummer. Free from the cover. Free of the beast. Free.
I'm not on my head. Free of the dress. The moment we miss. I'm free.
You can't face a title, demons. A world cup is a rain. And no, no, no.
You suck the light fire of every room. How much can I take? I don't know.
Look a flower that merges into the touch. So beautiful, but it takes so much of the light, the light in the side of me.
I'm free. I'm free. I'm the drummer. Free from the cover. Free of the beast. Free. I'm not on my head.
Free of the dress. The moment we miss. I was free.
I'm free. Free of the drummer. Free from the cover. Free of the beast. Free. I'm not on my head. Free from the dress. The moment we miss.
Free. Free of the drummer. Free from the cover. Free of the beast. Free. I'm not on my head. Free of the dress.
The moment the moment we miss. I was free. You can fight that at the pot safe using that work.
Quiet, quiet, free. Links to all the songs and all read up links in today's show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
And to Kevin, come on, man. Don't hold no grudges. It's just unhealthy.
All right, that's it for today. 41 minutes exactly. Fantastic time. I'll work on the sound.
I apologize if I blew your dreams out a couple of times tomorrow. We'll be back once again from the
curry manner. On the west side of G-town, dailysourcecode.com,
Adam at podshow.com. Take everybody. Have a nice day. Bye.