Ladies and gentlemen, I present Padshal's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Roses are ready. My sweater is beige. For your domain name needs, you should go to this page. GoDaddy.com.
Yes, so we seem to be having a problem with Flight 576. The captain is a bit liberated. Yes, he's smashed.
Well, no, so the only backups we have for this flight are Johnson, and of course, Johnson has been sleeping, and I do believe he's a bit high right now.
And of course, Henry has not had any longer flights than London to Paris.
But I do see on the artillery that we have an atom carry who would be flying. I do understand that he is a pilot, but perhaps he could take the copilot seat and help us get off the ground.
Oh, right, so he's probably high too. There, we'll get Henry up here and we'll see if he can take Virgin Atlantic across the Atlantic.
On his virgin flight, how ironic. And the DSC 576 will go on.
Do you remember?
Way back last summer, when mainstream radio was such a fucking monomer, no ending music, nothing to funny.
Cleared channel with a fuckers, didn't bother money, but supply didn't hurt at all.
Now you can have it all. I heard it on the podcast, rocking fucking radio, you wanted it.
Got it, just downloaded a part it on the podcast. No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick it pickin' the revisions on.
Do you remember? Your first computer, that piece of shit was like a freaking rotor.
Now we've got Wi-Fi, downloading files fast, listening to everyone who's ever done on my cast.
It's his duty, now you see each and every nation. The radio is got to go inside our imagination.
May that song sing along, mash it up and mix it, breathe fucking loads of out-and-goer and fix it.
You're so loud, it heard the call. Now you can have it all.
You'll be making a real sign.
I heard it on the podcast, rocking fucking radio, you wanted it.
Got it, just downloaded a part it on the podcast. No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick it pickin' the revisions on a podcast.
I heard it on the podcast, rocking fucking radio, you wanted it. Got it, just downloaded a part it on the podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick it pickin' the revisions on.
Do you remember? Your second computer, that piece of shit was like a fucking rotor.
Pickin' up, Delta Sheriff Charlie, five, seven, six from the Curry Condor and Northern California.
I heard it on a podcast.
Oh, I love public toilets. So where's the toilet paper?
Wait a sec, there's not only the paper here.
What am I gonna do now? Oh, got it, I've got my eye, but with me, so I think DSC 5, 76 will do that.
So let's try it, it feels good.
Are you wiping your ass with your eye? I wasn't gonna make it without your DSC.
But everybody, how you doing? It is the Daily Source Code.
Completely full-barred and very, very late for me. A couple of reasons.
First, a really good reason. And by the way, really late means a 10-to-1 AM.
Of course, it is the fourth of April.
Coming up on the Lady Patricia's birthday, everybody. That's Saturday, the seventh of April.
Okay, first a good reason. I had a very awesome day tonight with Natalie Del Conti.
A known from the Hit Potcho Video Program, Textra, which you can find at textra.potcho.com.
That was nice. Oh, man. It was perfect to end a wacky day opening game for the San Francisco Giants,
who completely got clobbered by the pod rays. I think it was like a 7-0 shot out.
So the city was mad. Everyone was just out of their mind.
It was not pretty. Particularly where Potcho HQ was located, which is a right near 21st Amendment,
a very well-known bar, not far from the stadium.
Oh, boy, boy. That was a nasty mess.
Anyway, went to meet Natalie up at, I think, what's the name of the restaurant?
Treso, I think. Somewhere near her house. I forget where it is.
In a very nice neighborhood of San Francisco, then I'm in. That much I know for sure.
So I had a nice meal and then walked up and down the street there and had some frozen yogurt.
I mean, I was totally king of the dweaves. Everyone's like, I do.
It's Natalie. Look at that geek walking next to her.
So got back to the condo, not too late, actually. I don't know around 930 something like that.
And then, of course, started to do my prep for the show. I passed out.
So tired. The jet lag just hit me. I literally passed out with a laptop burning a hole on my lap.
And I don't know, wait, that was the split burning a hole in my lap.
But the laptop was on too. That was very hot.
And then I started the show and something, and I was a little confused about what the error.
And I still don't know exactly what's going on.
For those of you who I'm sure noticed that yesterday's show came through without art, without any tags.
The reason for that is when I went to save the show from cast blaster, you save the show first and then you uploaded to the PDN.
It gave me some kind of weird error that it couldn't fight.
It's first it said, picture not saved, because I put this awesome new art in that the Ben from the Ben cast sent me.
It said, picture not saved. And so you click. Oh, picture not saved because it was not found.
And then you click.
Okay, you know, basically the big ignore the big ignore button that Windows gives you.
And then it said, here's the frightening one. Access violation. Oh boy, I was violated.
Something was violated. It was deep within the guts of cast blaster.
And so it wouldn't save the file.
It would save just the file name of zero bytes in length, which of course is frightening because I just recorded a whole show 40 minutes.
Now, an undocumented feature I think of cast blasters that you can always get the whatever was recorded is written immediately to disk.
So you can find a temp dot MP3 file in your cast blaster directory with the application lives.
So that's how I was able to salvage the actual show so that I could upload it.
A couple of things this file didn't play on interestingly enough, particularly on the Nokia N800 internet tablet.
Don't know what's up with that. That was the only error message I got from people was those who were using an N800.
I don't know why it's single doubt that device for this particular problem.
So I didn't really think too much of it. I talked to Andrew Grumman on the way in and said, you know, he's what's going on, you know, why isn't it playing on that device and I explained what happened.
And as I loaded up the show, the first, of course, I do all my serious satellite radio stuff.
And I went to save that and same damn thing. Access violation.
It's so scary when I get it. It's Microsoft or terrorists, man. That's frightening language.
That's that's really scary to see that in all these hexadecimal codes.
So, of course, it took a screenshot, sent it over to cast blaster mic. Hopefully, you'll be able to decadify it.
But it seems like, you know, access error violation trying to access NTID dot D Ella.
Wait a minute. Let me tell you exactly what it is. Why am I even making it up?
Let's do a prolific programmer on you. Okay. I'm going to read out the error code.
Access violation at address 0.0067AC5 in module cast blaster dot EXE. Read of address 0.0016D0.
Now, that was one error. I know I also saw a different error about some DLL and then I don't know.
And I may have some spyware or some kind of virus in my system because the system was also freaking out.
That's stop now, luckily.
And, you know, the servicehost dot EXE that was like, slowly bring up all kinds of CPU power.
I'm very, very afraid of what's going on right now. This is not not good.
So I'm just hoping that I'll be able to replicate the same error in the same fashion and be able to save this file.
So I can still upload it to you. Sorry for those of you on a Nokia and a hundred tablet that you probably can't listen to this show.
But at least they got it out there. So I don't know. This may require a reinstall of cast blaster.
I may have to go. And I got one of the, you know, I immediately went looking for, because my own, I guess my own spyware detector stuff wasn't finding anything.
And, you know, a quick Google search and I tried, what does it spy eraser?
Those cock suckers. I hate those guys. And I'll tell you why.
Because you run the scan on your system, which takes 25 minutes.
And then it says you've got 87, 87 infected files.
All right, repair, remove, fix it for me. Oh, no, you have to buy the program by the program.
29 bucks. Let me see, before I get really angry, I'm going to go to my email.
Yep. And then you get a, oh wait, here's a cast blaster Mike just got back to me. Why do you say, what did you do?
Oh, dude. I don't know. He'll, he'll be able to use this as a bug report, hopefully.
So think you buy that software. And then you got a receipt. Thank you very much for paying.
It may take 24 hours before we can get you your download link.
Fuck, I hate that. It's 2007, boys.
Okay. So I don't want to make the show too long because I actually do have to get some sleep.
But there's so much fun stuff that you've been sending me.
Hello, Adam. This is Kevin, a long time listener from Cambridge with some audio feedback.
I'm sitting here in the airport and wanted to let you know that your show really helped me out on my travels.
The way that is is I'm used to telling people how to ring the US from the UK.
But I'm not in the habit of having to ring England from America.
But while I was on the trip, I was, I had trouble getting my phone to register the plus sign.
And I wasn't sure if I needed to work trial plus four, or plus zero zero for four, or plus zero one for four, or just zero for four, or zero zero for four.
And all this so, unfortunately, I had in my head P-dub singing in a sort of reggae sort of style plus four, two, seven, that, that, that, that, that, that.
And I just want to let, you know, that's how I managed to get through to my lovely wife while out of the country was because of having P-dub's wonderful,
wonderful theme song to your show in my head.
Speaking of being away from a loved one and staying in touch using technology, this is the first trip where I had two webcams,
kidded out so that I could talk to my bride, my lovely wife, and actually we could see each other as well as talk.
I've heard you talk about doing the same thing with the lady Patricia using your webcams and your, or the built-in ones that come with Max.
And I wanted to ask you about something about that.
Isn't it kind of weird how when you're looking at the image of them, they're actually see, they see you looking off to the side.
And when you're looking at the camera, so it looks like you're looking at them, you can actually see them.
No, no, no, no, no, no. You're doing it all wrong, okay. First of all, if you want to have a true eye to eye contact experience, there is an outfit.
I believe it's, what's the name of that guy? He's like a big green investor.
Eckard Winston, Eckard Winston is a Dutch guy. He made, I don't like a hundred million dollars with the sale of some IT services company he had.
And for years, I think I've known him for like seven years. He's been trying to sell this system and he's absolutely right about the system, but it's just way too expensive.
It's basically a camera and monitor in one.
And so instead of having your screen where you're looking, and by the way, on the eye Max, it's not too bad.
You're looking down a little bit just a tad because the camera is basically right at the top of the screen.
He has it so that it's kind of like the way a teleprompter works where it's one way glass, I guess you would say.
So the camera is behind the monitor. So you're actually going to be looking straight into this person's face.
And while you're doing that, you're looking into your camera so that you have a true experience.
And yeah, and he has this whole philosophy about how much difference it makes.
And I have to say, I've used this system and it really does make a tremendous difference.
But when you're doing this type of stuff with, with your significant other, which yes indeed, the lady P and I do.
She's got her eye Mac in the kitchen. I've got an eye Mac here in my in my kitchen as well in the condo.
And we use eye chat to communicate.
If we, when we do that, we typically don't point the cameras that are faces if you know what I mean.
Have you found this? Surely the Mac's are different.
I tried to get the camera as close to the display of my wife as possible, so that when I was looking at the picture, it looked like I was looking at her.
And that's true. But it really doesn't work very well.
So that's my first thoughts of webcam chatting.
Anyway, if you have any thoughts on this, I know you've been using this method for a while.
Thanks a lot for the show. Talk to you later and as you know, folder.
Okay.
Damn, I'm so pissed off about this. You know, much extra work it is to do this.
If you can't write straight to the to the PDN, oh, man.
Is this a windows thing? Is this going to piss me off and make me go back to a Mac? I sure hope not.
Hey, howdy. Thank you very much for letting me into your family of savants.
But could I ask for something if it's not too much of a trouble?
Could I be known as the anonymous podcaster listener?
You know, in my podcast, that's one thing.
I'd like oxymoron so much that I actually have an oxymoron of the week.
And I thought it'd be cool if I became known as a podcaster listener because after all.
Yes, shut up. Tired of you. Let's try this one.
Ladies and gentlemen, I don't want to do that. Oh, man.
Things are just not going the way. I want them to wait a minute.
Cast Blaster Mike is emailing me back. Let's see. What he says.
Oh, boy.
Now he's into the details. I can't do that where I'm talking to you guys.
Let's just move ahead. Hey, Adam, Eric's mom here. Oh, hi, Eric's mom.
So I was reading an article in the Times yesterday and I just didn't understand one thing.
And I thought I'd bring it to your attention and maybe you could help me out here.
The article begins with the sentence, aspiring pop stars can turn to American Idol.
And budding screenwriters had project green light.
So we're to fledgling public radio host, a turn.
Seems as though there's going to be an online contest to find a new national radio star.
Now, the last paragraph goes like this.
Jake Shapiro, the exchange executive director, said he hopes to receive hundreds and hundreds of submissions for the American Idol-style search.
Despite some online grumbling from podcasters, who in recent years have bypassed the radio distribution system and put their own shows on the internet.
So Adam, what exactly doesn't grumbling podcasters sound like?
Oh, hope you're having a great time in San Francisco.
Yeah, not really. I'm pissed off. Thanks for the naked picture though. I appreciated it.
Hey, and your son, Eric, I think he sang the National Anthem today at the opening day for the Giants.
First game. Whoops.
I think he did the anthem with the, with the, with the, the four lead actors of Jersey Boys.
Yeah, you know what that sounds like to me, you know, consider the source.
It's the New York Times. Doesn't get much more mainstream and established than that.
And I have heard about this. Someone sent me a link to this contest.
Oh, man. I don't know. Maybe two or three weeks ago.
And I looked at the contest page and it was, you know, it was really interesting because what, what the email said,
what, what are pointed out is that there were no rules, no terms of service.
You know, what happens if you win. What does that mean? It was like it was really flaky.
But I didn't think much of it thought, okay. Well, yeah, that's all right.
I must say, though, that, you know, this whole, you know, if, if the phrase user generated content isn't disgusting enough,
everything, everything has to be a fucking contest.
I'm so, you know, I'm glad that Cas Blasser is busted because it's getting me pissed off.
Everything to these days.
And, and advertising agencies. Oh, gosh.
Yeah, we've got this great, you know, ex-filling the ex-brand of potato chip.
Let's do a contest where people send in their own videos.
Fuck you. Stop it already. I, I'm so sick of it.
I guess that's what a, what grumbling online from podcasts or sounds like.
But I don't, I don't think I heard anyone grumble about the contest.
To me, that sounds like the New York Times reporter had an interview with this guy from Public Radio.
And, and he said, oh, yeah, it's going to be great, man. You know, fuck all those pod gasters.
They're already complaining about it because you're, they all suck. They know good. This is about quality talent.
Probably something like that.
I have not heard or read one single thing about it except for that email.
And that was definitely weeks ago.
So, it's fantastic.
And, and I encourage anyone who's on the pod show network to apply.
Please, it's a great idea.
I don't know.
I'm sorry. I'm just completely out of it. This is really freaking me out.
Hello.
Hey, Adam. Oh, this is Cacone.
Oh, Cacone. I played your song yesterday, indeed.
Thought I would stop by and say a big thank you for playing my latest track.
Get your light up on DSC 575.
I also just wanted to let you other podcasters out there, no?
And you can find, get your light up at the number one place on the web for podsafe music.
You can find the podsafe music network at music dot podshow dot com.
And hey, Adam, thanks again from Cacone.
That's what's going to say she was a folder.
Let me just go look back at the podsafe music network for a second.
Hey, how come I can't find Cacone now? What the hell was that?
Cone. I don't see what she looks like.
How was that?
Nothing is going my way today. I just might add.
Hold on. Let me go to my show notes from yesterday.
Maybe I can find it there.
Cacone. Here we go.
There's something weird going on with our search as well.
I'm not quite sure what it is.
Okay. Well, that's just going blazingly fast.
Damn.
James, save me.
Adam, James.
I've always, because I've never known you for having TV days.
I guess the liberty of all the sort of years.
You know, obviously, you know, some of your sports.
You know, one of the lads, wife, kids, house, mortgage and all.
We've got the mortgage bits.
And what's the whole end, bud?
It's like they're running out.
They get your head done.
Jesus.
Great.
Thanks. Sorry.
Can we talk to anybody there?
Thanks.
That's that.
If you're not there, don't do it.
You're all right.
Hey, come on.
Yeah.
All right, James.
Let me indulge myself once in a while.
If I want to fly my own aircraft to get my hair done in Rotterdam,
it's my prerogative.
And by the way, not a bad idea to clean up a little bit.
I finally found Cacone.
Man, she's hot.
I didn't pay attention when I did the show notes yesterday.
It wasn't looking at the picture.
But very suggestive, sexy picture here.
Okay. I'll have to go to find her site later on.
Okay. I'm just going to blow through some stuff here,
because I've got to stop before I heard someone else.
Hello, Adam.
These salt and the savants.
It's us.
He's been here.
I was just listening to Digital Planet on the BBC World Service.
And I was discussing something that's been brought up on the Charlie as well.
And that is a code of conduct for bloggers in the bloggers fee.
And then if he was that they need to be one.
Well, I'm with you, Adam, that they really is no need for a code of conduct.
I'll tell you why I believe this is the case.
First of all, the Internet is a microcosm of society.
And just as you get bad people in the real world,
you will get the online as well.
These bad people will use the Internet from the Far East Pipses.
However, when the people who left these death threats on Mrs. Sierra's blog will get caught,
it will send a few messages I believe.
I hope you all know what this is about.
This is about Kathy Sierra.
She's a consultant. She has a web blog and people are posting death threats in the comments section.
And she, you know, whole bunch of people said this is horrible.
This has to stop. And of course it's horrible.
Of course it should stop.
Yeah, excuse me, Tylenol PM.
Just in time, too, for you serious satellite radio folks.
You've got more of the pod show on serious coming up.
Right now.
So this Kathy Sierra woman.
She closed down her web blog and the blogosphere called for a code of conduct.
Which I just can't, I can't fathom how, do people not see what is happening?
What we're actually learning about human nature.
And Aussie Ben, I appreciate your comment, but I think you don't quite see it either.
This is that this kind of thing is not tolerated.
And that there is no such thing as anonymity online.
The other thing I see is who is going to enforce his code of conduct.
Is it going to be a self-inforced system?
Or will it be, I guess, a group of people who are just with this sort of job of running to blogs,
Deleting posts and what have you.
If it is a group of people, I can see a few problems with that as well.
And that is, number one is who is going to give these people a power?
Are they going to be, I guess, elected by bloggers?
Are they going to bake it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We can't have a panel.
It's just not, what is the Starfleet command?
Aussie Ben, that's not going to work that way.
You can't do it.
There's no way to police this.
You know, sometimes I think we don't realize that we really unleashed the beast with the internet.
The beast inside all of us, because, you know, of course as people and human beings were all beautiful
and inherently want love and peace for all, but there's also a lot of nasty shit inside every single one of us.
So you can't have a panel for anything.
You know, like the Supreme Court of the internet?
No.
That obviously won't work.
Sort of body or what have you?
And what happens if they come to my blog and Deleting things in my blog,
which I, I did, I won out there for the world to say it.
Right.
I just hate too many problems.
Anyways, Adam, have a good one.
Yeah.
And wait for it.
Wait for it.
Folder.
Okay.
Yeah, man.
No, no, no, no.
I mean, this happens all the time.
Whenever you have a group, a group of more than one person.
So if it's two people or if it's two, 200,000 people doesn't make any difference.
There's some post something on the internet or put something in a podcast.
I think web blogs propagate much faster, obviously, because it's text and, you know,
there's a whole infrastructure of, you know, day.com and techno-radi and, you know, all this stuff.
Google, Google alerts, you name it.
No matter what the spin is, no matter how something is said, people will read that.
And we're conditioned.
We're just conditioned as human beings of a certain age.
I think it'll, this will change over time as we evolve and understand how to deal and cope with human nature as,
as we're interconnected to one another.
I wish it was interconnected to cocooni.
Let me tell you now.
The, you know, the other people within that community, within that group, almost always without fail,
take that for the truth when someone writes something.
Usually, because they're in the same community, they have the same feelings about different subjects.
So, you know, it's really like pouring fire, pouring on, you know, gas on the fire,
if you will, more, more petrol and just fanning the flames.
And you know, and the bigger the community, the worst it gets.
And it's just something within us.
One person gets pissed off.
Another person with similar baggage sees it.
They throw their baggage right on the same conveyor belt.
And people, people who like people.
People like to do that.
I do that too.
Everyone projects their own, their own baggage on others.
And sometimes that projection can be pretty fucking nasty.
And that's just the way it is.
It's going to get a lot worse before it gets better.
And there is no court, no rules, no regulations that can stop at the beast has been unleashed.
And there's lots and lots of fantastic stuff we can do for for human nature for us as a civilization.
And unfortunately, there's lots of crap.
I mean, you know, look, why would we be any different as countries nations with our panels and groups and governments and leaders?
You know, we're killing each other's shooting hot lead in fucking deserts.
Why would it be any different?
You know, with the same people who are saying yes to that.
Or, you know, now we're saying no when we want to stop it and it's not really working very well is it.
But are we marching on 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue?
No.
Well, not yet.
Actually, there's one person who thinks that podcasting can help to do good.
And he has his own jingle.
Let's have a word with the nylon spread in the news with the smile on where the roller right.
Ringo for light.
Let's listen for the wild to the nylon.
I'm going to make sure I find the other one.
Okay.
Oh, crap. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, this is not good. I just tried to open another nylon jingle and a crap.
Oh, please.
And I got an access violation at address 060677AAC5 and modulecastblaster.exe.
Read of address 01101610.
If I click OK, that mean that may mean the end of the show.
If it continues to record, I'll continue.
So I'll just say goodbye right now.
And we'll have to save nylon until tomorrow.
Here we go. Let's see what happens.
Are you still there?
Thank God.
They worked.
They had them and they were finished by a message.
So here's what I want.
I want a mercy embassy.
I want the power of podcasting, the power of the audience.
I want them to encourage every listener to send a email to the Iranian embassy near their home town.
That's the power.
That's the power of podcasting.
So let's move the needle.
Let's move this from B to B sort of thing to a B to W business world.
Let's use the power of podcasting to do something good for the world.
And that word of apple and D are in for the near turn.
So if you want to move the needle at him, here's my challenge to you.
Get podcast, B to eat, partner work, everyone.
Send a letter to the Iranian embassy.
Free the British hostages.
Then, then, only then.
And I say podcasting in the new world in the new media, a new way has moved the needle.
And I'm glad that the access violation didn't violate you.
Yeah, okay, so you want to bum rush the embassy.
Yeah, okay.
First of all, I disagree because clearly,
the outlet the UK was over there.
And it's in dispute whether they were in their territorial waters or not.
And as I talked about yesterday, there's quite a history of Britain and Persia or Iran and the United Kingdom.
The goes back to the beginning of 1903.
And there's been a lot of aggression, a lot of manipulation.
Maybe it's just time that Tony Blair said, oh, sorry mate.
We'll get our fucking people out of there.
Didn't mean to overstep the boundary.
You know, just so you know, we're here.
Sorry, didn't mean to do that.
Just say something like that.
Just be, you know, take the high road on this, will ya?
So, everyone in podcasting.
Please send that to Tony Blair.
But really nylon, I want you to understand that I didn't get into this to save the world.
Well, I did kind of, as long as I can also win valuable prizes.
I mean, for me, podcasting is different.
You know, it's a creative outlet and it's a way for me to get naked pictures.
What's playin' on?
All right, so I'm gonna cut this just a little bit short.
Because I'm afraid that you're gonna get screwed somewhere.
Maybe I'll try a complete reinstall of cast blasts or see if that works.
Okay, being in the curry condo means, of course, I'm back reunited and it feels so good.
With my first generation iPod, which sits here in the...
Well, we had the Logitech MM50 speaker doc, which was, by the way, one of our first advertisers on the network.
So, let me plug it in here.
And, you know, I have it on shuffle, so let me just see what comes out.
Oh, let me turn this down.
Oh, yes!
Oh, what a jam.
Your size.
To rescue my eyes and shades of green.
Under dreaming spot.
To eat your book.
That's where I've been.
What did you do there?
I got hot.
Tell you why.
It's all too beautiful.
Kind.
You know, my mind gets too tall.
Don't swallow up my mind.
They won't come out.
Tell you what I do.
What do you do?
I'd like to go there now with you.
You can miss out.
I'd like to let me know.
What did you do there?
I got hot.
It's all too beautiful.
Oh man, back in the day when we had that phasing effect, which was manually produced
by running two tape simultaneously, mixing the signals through the mixing board and then
slowing down one of them just a tad.
You got that nice phasing effect.
The small faces, it's a coup-park from Adam's first gen iPod, which we celebrate with the
Jingle.
Fuck, not that one.
Okay, I can't wait to hear more about the first gen iPod later in the week here on the
Charlie from Northern California.
Hey Adam, this is Richard and today we're going to see this story today that record
companies that have a little UK commercial radio stations to allow them to play music in their
podcast.
It's almost the most radio station podcast in the UK.
It's just a presenter talking with their music which is pretty dire.
But now they're a deal to play 30 seconds of songs in their podcast.
30 seconds that's crap.
You want to hear 30 seconds?
You want to hear a whole thing.
Even if it means that you're the talker at the beginning of the end.
30 seconds?
One of the other books.
Anyway, by now.
All right, man.
What's your?
No, no, what's all that?
Okay, thank you.
Just scared me for a second there.
That is pretty interesting.
No, I did not see the news report.
I didn't hear anyone about it.
Didn't see anything.
Does it fall under a part of their part of the BBC's license?
I'd be interested to know for sure.
But indeed, 30 seconds come on.
Well, we're getting closer.
I guess if you put that together with what happened with the announcement from EMI about them,
removing digital rights management and that being sold to the iTunes store, higher quality,
all that stuff.
There are things happening.
Things are starting to adjust.
I should go back to my predictions again from the beginning of the year.
Let's see how close we've come.
I have a feeling.
I'm not far off.
All right.
Tomorrow will be much better.
I promise.
Thanks for sitting through all this crap.
And I must say, looking at Kaconie's picture, helped a lot.
Another punch hole podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
punch hole and line weight.