That's the challenge from here on out when you go on vacation, you got a lot of damage
control to do.
Sorry.
Clear prop.
Delta, Sierra Turm.
5, 86.
16 billion dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
We're in the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
At a monkey with nightmare, I'll talk to you guys for a bit more time, so that's
a bad thing.
I mean, it's just giving you a kill right into the ground, I'm tired of it, but it's
a bit disappointed.
It starts like a whirlwind, thinking that you'd go for it, making lots of time, and
you're pimped down thin, then you want to ride a song, and working on it long, and
tweak it, mix it down, and get me free, but then it comes a word from the man, he was
to slap a little steak on your plan, just be little words, don't you know it to work,
anymore?
We want it to, and like we want it to, and play it when we want it to, and bring it
up to everyone can see, and you can't lock it down, and you can never budge down, and shout
it up, and sell the music free.
I've got it in my pocket, I've even went and bought it, I did this deal, and you know
I never would, I never would, but I said don't make it look like, just another
crew, cause I'm doing what you said that I should do, so take a deep breath now my friend,
take your first step, and walk right in, to 21st century, and welcome to the way it's
gonna be.
We want it to, and like we want it to, and play it when we want it to, and bring it up
to everyone can see, and you can't lock it down, and you can never budge down, shout
it up, and sell the music free.
I can't see you, to anything, to anything, to anything else that I would want you
to, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down,
and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and
you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't
lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't
lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down,
and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't
and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down, and you can't lock it down,
and you can't lock it down, just shut it down, and set the music free.
set the musicfryin', set the music, rent, and so on.
when you hear those...
I'm shuffing music, I hope you're cooking!
And the lyrics, you know, it's got to be at Jeff Smith brand new and available
on the pot wave music, now where we're, set the music free.
Hey everybody, how you doin'?
Welcome to the Daily, source code episode number 586, coming to you just briefly,
just for one day from the Curry manor, in the affluent, subÏÎµ entrenonn district,
in the affluent suburb of serenones gulfard here in Adams attic yes the
south of the savants at your service hey back from vacation tomorrow i take off
immediately to uh San Francisco for the rest of the week i would have gone uh uh
Sunday which is actually we arrived late last night or actually early this morning
calling uh sorry i actually didn't want to hear you that was really nasty um
we arrived late last night from our uh from our eight days in the sun in ten
and reef which i never been to before very nice i have to say uh it was on a scale of
one to ten i'd say it was an eight and a half uh at times close to a nine of course uh
there were some crappy moments as well where the uh the headphone earlobe infection uh
definitely uh worsened and so i was at Tuesday or Wednesday uh i think it was
i don't remember now yeah Tuesday had the doctor come and uh i don't know if you were
following along on the uncurry dot com or the web on the web log uh i was posting
a lot of flicker pictures as well from my uh from my E61 i which uh just a fantastic device i
really enjoyed using it um not being paid to say that by the way i'm such an idiot but then
again i really like it so much um uh so uh yeah i had to order a doctor and uh you know i'm
laying there and you know my earlobe is really thick and it's starting to pound a little bit
and i've been through this before and they basically have to cut it open you know squeeze all this
crap out of it and uh i'm not got the door like okay here's the doctor you know i don't speak
any Spanish except for a year but boina that's about it and i knew how to ask for them photo but you know
and in walks a uh a young woman uh turns out uh 27 year old doctor from pole and who'd been
living there for two years uh she said she just came to the island for adventure but she really
wanted to go back to pole and we had a nice little chat and she looked at my aunt she said well
i think it's too early to cut i don't think we should do that uh you know it could cause
more problems than it could solve like what the hell does that mean and she put me on some
any biotics like really heavy shit like 875 milligrams of moxasilin or whatever and it's like
just a hum and you can feel the shit coursing throughout your veins so uh waited for 48 hours
uh it only got worse i was waking up at five in the morning my ear really really
hurting and so you know it was just the skin was all it really it was like the size of a big marble it
was disgusting uh so uh agatha's her name she came by uh uh was i think was Thursday and i said okay
look please just cut me she said yep got a cut you i said your place remind baby she said
my place but you can't ride with me because you know it she doesn't have any insurance for that or
whatever uh so i had to go over to the clinic met her there and uh she was great she was joking around
with me she's like okay uh what how big a knife do you and she spoke this really cute with
English with like a Polish kind of Spanish accent it was really weird how big the knife do you want
anyway so uh she had like some some guy off the street i think no he was an ambulance driver
hold my hair up while i'm laying face down uh she can't you can't anesthesize the the earlobe
they can only spray like some cold stuff on it so it kind of feels like uh it's numb because it's
basically freezing off uh and that she was cutting and squeezing and uh and unfortunately i didn't
i if i'd known what was gonna happen if uh if i'd actually if i was able to find Christina
would have asked her to come along and film it so unfortunately no video of the actual event
so now that's why my headphone is uh uh is producing feedback is because i have to put the
it literally is from the headphone because now i feel that the cushion on the headphone is rubbing
against the actual area the god infected so the headphone earlobe it's true it's what it's what this
whole thing is from and why i've had it now in the past uh twice at least with the exact same results
unfortunately something stuck on my throat maybe something markio shemodonem cough left
by the way i got about equal love and equal hate armna on mark filling in on the show interesting
um i didn't listen to all of them i did listen to the comic strip blogger segment which uh
it made me laugh out loud many many times but uh it wasn't uh wasn't really daily source
going material but i really appreciate mark filling in and uh pushing uh pushing the envelope so we
we know where the limits lie with with this audience at least and it was very interesting to uh
to read a lot of the feedback yeah okay so um yeah it's anyway great vacation how to great time
a little bit of a a panic last night you know our our visas our temporary visas have expired
and our permanent visas are in the in the in the works of the home office so after you know
produce all this paperwork in order to be led into the country uh you know it takes about 10
15 minutes at at customs and so we were last to get our bags and this is 130 in the morning
and uh so i see my bag and you know it's the one of the last ones and i pick it up and
it's the it's a big to me roller bag and it's got a gold card and it's got the uh the to me leather
um address you know tag and then i and i'm looking at it and it's my bag right but i say wow that's
interesting because the TSA cut my lock off how come there's a lock on my bag this is the original
lock that came with the bag and i'm like confused it Patricia put that on and then i start to see
subtle nuances uh the gold card that was uh was attached to the handle was for British airways and
not for Virgin and i'm like oh crap here it is one third in the morning we're the last ones
off the plane everyone else has their baggage someone's taken my bag obviously mistaken it very easy
to do by the way so like oh hey i got i got lucky i went over to the uh to the baggage department
the guy had actually realized it before he left the airport he had already gone through uh through
uh customs and all that stuff so he was waiting on the other side but i mean what are the chances
of two bags and the almost exactly the same configuration uh from the same flight from tender
reef so i was waving my arms like a fucking maniac i was so pissed off you know i was telling
about the E61 um i used it in many different ways uh of course line at the pool i could actually
reach a wireless access point which was really nice so i was downloading podcasts and what i did
this was an interesting little uh experiment that i tried um i used the the podcasting application
on the on the E61 i uh to download all the shows i wanted to listen to and then i access them
through the N800 with my headphones on through bluetooth there was literally streaming from the
memory card on the E61 i through the air through bluetooth into the N800 which has a nice stereo sound
that has the regular you know you know has regular headphone jack so you can just you know uh put
little ear buds in and it would it work i was just amazed the interoperability of the devices
was fantastic but uh just having this E61 i sparked off a lot of comments out of the E61 i
come out ever since it was in it's back in February i realized yesterday it just started shipping
in part to Europe and i've been reloading aid advances to hit they've got any in it you've already
got one you're so in so i can't wait to get mine at earlier if i'm really jumping at the bit
i've got a palm hand that was dying on its ass and i can't wait to count it and switch over to
Nokia stop carrying two devices anyway best of luck i'm really waiting for mine yeah man
yeah that E61 and i is something special i got to tell you um the the whole the way the whole thing
works it's it's such a it really is a big upgrade from the E61 which i had to give to Christina
because misthing lost her phone somewhere so we had to go through the whole hassle of uh you know
putting a temporary block on the account i still don't think they've they sent us a new sim card
to don't think it's been activated yet um and yeah like i've already bought her a million phones
and so i have a perfectly good phone to say he used this one she said but it's really manly say
you know tough shit don't lose your phone you know use the money you from working on weekends to go
buy a new one and also you know i'd like the uh well she had the n91 which is also a phone
that that i got from Nokia a long time ago which i liked a lot we call it the break because it's
literally indestructible it's big too but she drops her phones you know for friends cars drive
over them so we'll see how long the E61 last oh yeah love to hear from you keep those calls coming
will ya plus four four kilo seven six eight one three seven five three plus four four two oh seven
six eight one three seven five three i thought i didn't realize this thing this phone isn't
out apparently so i didn't i just thought that you know i just there was saving myself a trip to
the store and a couple hundred pounds by a good one for free but uh i guess people are really excited about
out of the gym space sixty one i i don't know where the stuff because i've gone freaking afford it
they don't get spoiled like do you do you really million i get that you know and not uh E61 i
micro SD cards go to pick stop PIC ST or P dot code or you get or see or dot you kid
i'm not endorsed by and i don't get any money off them but they've got micro SD one gate cards for like
seven quids i don't want to put some time on it again but i don't think seven quids for
my birthday you can replace your five gigs you can't believe that i can't believe it seven
pounds for one gig i think i must have paid forty pounds it like to or maybe thirty pounds for
a one gig micro SD micro dick card whatever it is i's a pretty dang good deal man but those
card you know the cheap cards will crap out once in a while okay so on vacation time to reflect
read some good books um thought about uh yeah a lot of things of course is what you do on vacation
it's been a year since we've been away and i think it's time to start changing the format a little bit
of the daily source code now i'm it's gonna be interesting because with every format change it's
all experimentation and just trying to figure stuff out and it's kind of you know just at the
almost a day before mark called comic strip blogger i was thinking you know what can i actually
was in combination with the i miss because of course i miss got uh got uh canceled i should say
fired slash canceled i don't have to rehash the story um now i was thinking idiot okay here's
what was interesting about it is even though there was a lot of uh you know like Howard Stern type
stuff um then of course uh there was then i want to take the napy headed home comment uh this is
really a program where a lot of um policy makers decision people decision makers it really interesting
people i would say would call in uh regularly to discuss uh current events and it turns out that you know
Washington really listened to don i miss i didn't know that and i'm not really an i miss listener to
be honest uh and now of course i'm like shit you know maybe i should have listened to him a little bit more
i have a it was always like maybe that's because uh he uh Stern always put him down and i say well
this guy's got to be dick it's got to be a loser show i shouldn't listen to it but now i'm kind of
bummed out because uh you probably had a really interesting show and just didn't know about it all these years
um i think and you know why can't we you know have fun and you know fart and burp and
and talk about naked pictures but also um have some really interesting people on and uh you know
i am of course the sultan of the savance and i i have a lot of uh people with a lot of knowledge
at my fingertips literally if not maybe two phone calls away i could get almost anybody i want to
really i'm convinced of it you know but we have to build it up and i'd like to talk to other people
who know something about stuff you know and not just the same old uh polished media types who
talk in beautiful soundbites and appear on all of these new shows you know we've got you guys first
of all um so i'm thinking you know i'd love to talk about uh uh financial i'd love to talk
about the world bank with the nylon right i'm sure that nylon knows a lot about the well
i'm how does the fucking world bank work what is it what does it do what you know what's up
with Paul Wolfowitz i'm not getting any of this information from mainstream media uh yeah you know
bits and pieces of it and of course i do know what the world bank does but you know i know
Patricia doesn't know Christina doesn't i don't think they care and if there was someone
interesting compelling who's already you know in the audience or friend of the show or just a savance
in general and preferably someone who has a speech impediment or hates me or you know the normal
people right let's just have human beings who who happen to know a lot of stuff talk about it
and i also thought well maybe uh there's a lot going on still with uh you know with Korea
and uh just with the uh the administration are you as the administration in general i thought
yeah maybe should call uncle Don i just want to do some phone calls uh or Skype calls or
whatever they're going to be so um i figured i'd start off uh since um uh commentary bloggers first
appearance on the daily source code in a live environment um it was not the first experience i
would have wanted him to have again i had the laugh that was into the to the the conversation
mark and uh CSB had uh figure you know why don't want to i have him be the first guy to kick off this
new format uh because i know it'll be difficult uh to uh to aid understand them probably uh b uh he
he may have his own agenda um and but you know i think he does know a lot about uh european union affairs
and there's some stuff i want to talk about in that regard and y'all so uh of course knows a lot
about uh mobile phones or at least he says he does so uh to start off uh the first of our series
of uh savon specials and i hope to be able to talk to a savon every single day uh it's gonna
take some production but again you know i'm um changing the format and morphing stuff it just takes
time it's also probably gonna run a little bit longer than usual but remember there's a fast
forward button on there for for a reason so um anyway uh comics are blogger was nice enough to uh
hang with me uh this evening so that we can talk about a couple of things in our first in the savon
series comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip that's right the very
first savon to be on the show csb how you doing my friend and finally then it's Sunday
evening and i'm going to sleep soon well before you go to sleep uh csb uh i want to uh ask you a
couple of questions because there's been a lot of uh new stories that i was following uh during
my vacation of course i had my uh my uh Nokia e61i uh in my pocket at all times and i was uh
reading news and uh and mucking around a bit and uh the big thing that a couple of big stories
first one was about uh the people who manage the and i didn't know that this was a central resource
the people who manage email that goes to blackberries uh company called rim they had a a huge
outage and um well there's a couple of things about the first of all i i think the uh the mainstream
media just kind of like glossed over it i mean for for any servers to be down for or is it uh 18 hours
or something like that i think is a really big deal particularly when it comes to uh to the blackberry
service because uh governments use it and uh lots of people i know use it and i was wondering if uh
if you had any idea you know they say it was like some cash flow problem uh you know no no no so
i have met the CEO so i have seen CEO i was participating in the session of the CEO of rim
and remit's a cake Canadian company that it's not only running the blackberry service but they
are also producing and licensing blackberry devices and software for smartphones for blackberry
okay so so you met the CEO always that were you said yes this is Balcille Balcille and he is
bald he is no hair and and very arrogant it was very arrogant and i think this uh arrogant way
of uh rim it's reflecting also how they handle the customers during this outage for example uh
they have not published and noticed but they just were quiet about the situation and at the end
they have said that okay the situation is clear now so so if you are not receiving email in your
blackberry for some day and you go to the website of blackberry there's no information about
outage so you know this is let's say such arrogant but behavior and this is caused by the fact
that uh blackberry so this corporation research in motion is is the abbreviation and they they are
simply they have simply such strong market position that they totally are arrogant through
its customers and they have some competition but it's competition is quite distributed and they
are quite focused and i think the problem was simply shitty software they have of course it was
they have updated the software to the new version and during the the change they have simply
they backup was not working and uh not professional shitty software during update okay okay so
hold on a second see us be okay so the CEO is not only is he arrogant but he's also bald on top of
all that okay he has no hair but is he responsible for this isn't there CEO or someone else who
I don't think so I don't think that there will be a putting some responsibility to anybody that
they will just say that it was shot outage and nobody will be responsible for that they as they
had very strong market position and practically specifically in this push email market they are
market leaders and okay so do you think this is a bad thing is I mean you can license their
technology I guess can't you no but they say that this is one off this is one off and they will
never every again and no problem okay but but we all know of course something like that is
bound to happen again they're they're selling what a million blackberries a month there's some
some crazy number like that it's in in total they have something like 10 million customers I'm
but it could keep you mind that apart from the blackberry devices you can install this blackberry
connects software also in your smartphone so on in this smartphone for almost except for a
will it work on a Nokia no you can't put that on a Nokia can you it should work in a Nokia I
was talking with Nokia and both in one of the trade shows and they told me that the Nokia
E61 series that they're supporting all push email standards are really so good technology on
blackberry oh okay that's pretty cool if you continue this shit properly it should work
of course remember remember the blackberry services connected with your mobile operator so why
that's curious there is so in this way you have to contact your mobile operator you cannot do it on yourself
CSB you were just such a platter association in information well I love hearing all the
stuff you know about it so incidentally because I'm going to this mobile phone trade shows and
another patients and I'm looking meeting some as close and who are you meeting?
It is managers and other stuff for example I have seen him in the session this guy from
from room in in Spain in Barcelona at the GSM and I have seen him talking that
whatever we have our devices we have blackberry connect software here it is from my
point of view this mobile operating systems but we don't care okay so personally about blackberry
I could talk about a lot but generally speaking you cannot run native software in blackberry so
you can run on Java applications so it doesn't really mean that we in comparison to smartphones
like Symbian or like Windows Mobile where you can launch any application also like very complex
gigabyte applications for navigation and stuff right so you think that it's that there's going to
be more out of just from rim this is what you predict you think and could they do?
No no I think that they now they have learned the lesson and now they will do more testing
and in future upgrades there will simply say they will be claiming that it was one off and
it will never repeat again but just philosophically CSB to have now 30 million but in a couple
years it could be double that number to have 40 50 60 million people depend on one company for
their lifeline of communications isn't that isn't there a better way of doing that?
Fuck you I don't care you don't have this thing that's in the communication
special scalable solutions and they can handle setting me on without problems okay
Alright let's move on to another question I had for you this is something that we've been talking about
on daily source code for a while about roaming charges particularly in the EU and I came across
the story in the Wall Street Journal is came out in April 13th
I don't know one thing some Esco is checking out maybe he wants you baby
Alright well so let me just read the part of this new story so
a proposal to cap roaming charges from mobile phone calls in the European Union
created an important hurdle with when a key committee of the European Parliament voted for it
I would have to bullshit so much let me tell it started okay let me just say one thing
let me bullshit a little bit more you know Patricia has a has a virgin mobile
account and they were charging her to call outside just to call back to the UK from Tenerife
one pound and 50 pens per minute just to call out and it was one pound if she received a call
okay this is crazy so this is crazy to the extent but obviously these are different countries
and the mobile operators are like vampires the stacking blood of customers but you look
the situation is such that there is new EU directives on new law that EU government is saying
Esco's bus stats mobile operators used to reduce roaming fees and I agree I think the
of the mobile operators by definition are bastards no no you are saying this to the mobile
operators and the mobile operators will increase roaming fees to such Esco's like yourself
who are coming from USA the European directed this has to be lowered then what do you mean
they're going to charge me more because they will finance this 70% reduction of the fee
by judging more people who are coming from outside of the EU okay but all right
okay so to the the EU customers won't get penalized but people who have accounts from outside
the EU will be penalized is that what you're saying yes and the apart from that keeping mind that
there are already mobile operators that are agile and offering for example if you go
there is operator three in UK you have heard about three operators yeah of course yeah
and this is a quite new one this is owned by Asian company Hachison and
sort of speaking all breeds of Asian origin are buying the three because they are
Asian also so anyway that with three if you have a three a cart and you are going to Australia
Austria Hong Kong Denmark Ireland Italy also with them and you are receiving a phone call you don't
pay anything right well this is but this is my point this is the way it should be I mean
voter phones network in the UK is gotta be the same voter phone network in Spain except
if you actually go to Spain you're still using voter phones network but you get charged all these
roaming fees so that is now going to go away effectively or it's going to be there at all but it shouldn't
be there at all it's the same network is there on network isn't it? Adam this big bastards like
what a phone team are they are too big that too arrogant to reduce it to the zero and they have no
hair probably too right if they're arrogant that they will reduce only 70% and only such small
operator like three but it it three has divisions in Australia in Austria Hong Kong Ireland
if you go to Australia with three SIM card you receive phone call and you make phone calls to British
numbers without NFC okay okay fantastic now yeah understand I understand but they don't want to do it
okay so what is the solution to the and and we haven't even talked about data I mean you pay like
a pound per megabyte downloaded when you're roaming which is another thing it just kills me the
amount of that is being paid for data traffic does this directive address that at all?
No it is only about phone calls I remember about data there are some operators that are addressing
this issue for example in case of voter phone what are phone calls special plans that when you go
Spain we do what that phone SIM card from UK then you can pay the similar of the very similar price as
in UK right okay let me let me let me let me ask you this let me ask you this just for my own
own personal benefit what is the best operator for me knowing that I spend about half my time
in the United States and I spend half my time or yeah let's say 40% in the United States 40% in the
UK and another 20% in different countries in Europe like the Netherlands what will be the most
cost effective for me not just for calls but also mainly for data because I really need the data
connection no no your situation is fact that all right hold on a second we'll be right back
with more from comic strip blogger music and making good one uplifting song and one uplifting
story in the news she told me she told me she told me she told me she told me she told me she told me
you
unfortunately okay fortunately what're they're foking ever all right
something another country is to whatever just one more thing about mobile phones CSB
be both Motorola and Nokia reported their financial numbers, the quarterly numbers, Motorola
had a huge loss, like over a hundred million dollar or euro loss, can't remember.
And Nokia, who is still profitable, made a lot less profit.
What's happening?
So I also have met this ESCO's during TGSM and the third show, and to extend their
short, the bald guy without hair, who's the he who's he?
Exender is a CR of Motorola, right, okay, he's also an arrogant guy.
And no, no, look, in the sense, look, they have big success with Motorola Razor, you know?
Yeah.
And this Motorola Razor was a success, and then instead of innovating and diversifying the portfolio
in mobile phones, they're just waiting out the news, the speed images of the Motorola Razor.
And this way, in this way, in this way, and that, you know, Motorola, that's way, you know?
Wait, wait, what are you saying?
What are you saying?
Are they good or no good?
In what sense, you're going to generalize over simplifying things?
What sense?
Well, are they making products that people want and do they know how to make them profitably?
No, the situation with Motorola is such that they first ideas are good, and they are
getting up in the next generation of products.
That can give several examples.
For example, in the case of Motorola Razor, the next Motorola Razor was thicker.
And in the case of Motorola Q Smartphone, it has wheel.
But Motorola Q, next generation, it has no wheel.
But it has HDPAs.
So there's no wheel.
Well, it has no wheel.
What is that?
Wheel.
In the score wheel.
Oh, wheel.
Okay, wheel.
Okay.
He was smart for most very popular in USA.
And even Steve Faking Jobs was showing it as the one of phones from the competition.
And it was a very good phone.
But Motorola has not released GSM HDPA version fast enough.
And when they release it, it has no screw wheel.
So that was a big mistake.
That was a big mistake.
The no screw wheel.
Yes.
And also this big mistake.
And also, you know, simply competition is rising too fast.
And I mean my career in France from LG and Samsung.
And also knock-and-boost knock-ah.
They knock-ah has new CEO.
His name is Oli Peca Calvalsau.
And he placed your Maulida who was very, very long time in the CEO of knock-ah.
No, you're not a big fan of knock-ah, right?
Yes, they are bastards.
Who do you like?
Is it only Windows mobile that you like?
I like Motorola, but no, the problem is with Motorola.
They are not consequent and not fast enough with the actions.
I got it.
How about Nokia?
Because I got to tell you CSB, this E61I.
I use this for a week.
I didn't use any other device.
And it really right down to the built-in wayfinder GPS.
You know, and it goes out and brings in the maps through the data connection.
It could find me immediately.
I installed, was it Shouzu when I could geo and code the information into my pictures.
Obviously, phone calls, no problem, the data connection, the Wi-Fi, the podcasting application.
Really, it really was a very enjoyable experience.
I think that this phone, they've got to hit with this phone.
I think it's fantastic.
Okay, I know that you have to buy a knock-ah button.
I'm, you know, they send me free shit.
Look, you know, I'll try any free shit, obviously.
Nokia has, there are two reasons why Nokia has, so actually three reasons why Nokia has such big success.
And it's number one in mobile phone industry.
It is also related to business.
And there is a number one is that they have very, there's been a lot of money on marketing.
And actually there are Eastern European countries,
but they're in with Russia, formerly Soviet Russian Republic.
But they have create image that this phones are coming actually from Japan.
So this is the first reason.
The second reason.
Okay, I don't give a shit where they're made.
It's a good phone.
The marketing for me doesn't make any difference.
I'm using the device and I'm liking it.
Doing what I want the device to do.
But the point, this is the fact that they have a very good marketing.
A lot of money spending on marketing and a very clever marketing.
It's confusing.
For example, they're putting high resolution images in the shitty resolution display
and giving you different impressions.
But okay, the second one is now, what are you talking about?
It's two megapixel cameras.
It's nothing super, but it's okay.
I mean, you're telling me that their marketing is confusing me, but it's not.
I'm using the phone and I like it.
It has nothing.
I'm already past the marketing.
Okay.
The second reason is big diversity.
The second hidden secret, big diversity.
So they are offering phones for every asshole.
They have phones.
They look like blackberry.
They look like...
My phone.
I got to tell you.
I gave Patricia the really hit pink one that kind of slides open.
I forgot which model number it is.
Yeah, it's a Nokia.
It's like it's not all the fashion magazine.
Okay, so there's a case in point about the great marketing.
But she loves the phone.
It just really works.
She understands it.
I think you got admitted just making good products.
So this is diversity.
And the third secret of sexism.
When they have that line for releasing the phone,
they release it no matter what,
even if they have to cut on features.
And in case of Motorola,
this is a point.
For example, the sexes of the Moto Latius,
smartphone was released with one year delay or six months delay.
So this is execution.
And they deliver no matter what.
Okay.
So the Nokia is not...
There are reasons why Nokia is good,
but in the phones.
But you should understand that the symbioness,
power in your phone,
is not really open operating system.
This is a cartel of Nokia,
or something like that.
Yeah, but CBSB.
I don't give a shit if there's a cartel.
I don't care if there's a cartel.
As long as they put the camera in the phone and make your work,
as long as they make the speaker phone work.
I don't mind a cartel.
I don't want to have to...
There's nothing missing from these devices
that I need someone to develop for it.
It's all kind of work, and I like it.
And speaking of Nokia, as you said,
if it has had loss,
but Nokia has still profit,
but the profit margin of Nokia is going down,
because most of the phones that are selling their cheap phones,
and Nokia would like to sell more expensive phones
like the one that you got.
And shortly speaking,
apart from mobile phones,
Nokia 25% or 30% of business of Nokia
also net mobile networks,
and Nokia is managing with Zimans
in the network series, for example.
And this could be also the reason why they don't have
such an excellent profits.
Interesting thing is that Zimans
may not just involve in Canada's enjoyment
because of some corruption or whatever,
but it doesn't disturb Nokia going forward.
Yeah, I think you're right.
They've got good products.
They have a diverse line of products.
And they understand their business.
So now, how come you hate them?
That's another reason.
Would you care to tell the Charlie listeners about that?
Because, no, I'm afraid behavior
that they should say short towards myself.
And personally, I know that they have,
you know, this is a small country, Finland.
And in this country, if you are a lawyer,
and Nokia is saying something,
you kind of have no chances to sort of Nokia, for example.
Okay.
So there's some kind of dispute that you had, which...
I'm interested in smartphone markets.
So generally, these phones of the higher end phones.
And in this market, the practices of Nokia,
with Zimian, where they're pushing this Zimian operating system.
For example, this funder of Zimian was a British company called PSEON.
And PSEON wanted to float this company on the stock market,
but Nokia said, no, because you want to keep control.
Nokia has 50% of it.
Okay.
It's pretending that this is actually open industry initiative.
Well, of course it's not.
Okay.
Let me just ask you one final question.
I really want to stop about the mobile phone industry.
The hell was I going to ask you about?
Oh, yeah.
In all this time that we've known UCSB,
I still don't really know what you do.
Could you just tell me what your vocation is?
How do you make a living?
I'm software developer.
And I was really...
I was working at Nokia in Finland 3S,
and they fired me because of blogging.
Really?
Oh, okay.
Now this is interesting.
So they fired you because of your blogging,
but you're a software developer.
So you are a prolific programmer.
And designer, yes.
Really?
Okay.
What platform?
Adam.
And the price software.
I wouldn't like to talk to my she.
I like that man.
Come on.
I really want to know more.
What do you...
What do you program for?
Symbian or do you program?
I don't know more.
But another society people want to know more.
We'll be right back with one more segment
with comic strip blogger.
Okay.
So I see that Splendon Fultures is no longer
advertiser for Pacho.
Well, I guess I'll go back to my old coffee
and...
Well, there's some about this tonal pm.
And since I've ran out of Splendon,
I guess we're supposed to use the tonal pm.
And the coffee.
So...
Well, I'll give that a shot anyway.
And let's try it out and see what it tastes like.
Okay.
Here goes.
Well.
Not quite as sweet as I thought it'd be.
A little tart.
But I got it mida.
I liked it a lot.
And...
Hey Adam.
It's Steve Warner from Fidipidations.
The weekly Pacho podcast for runners at 1.pacho.com.
With a quick follow-up that I thought you'd appreciate.
And a big thank you to a lot of the folks back in the Pacho office
who went all out to help me in my running
of the 111st Boston Marathon.
Pacho made quite an appearance in this year's Boston Marathon
and I received a lot of great encouragement on the course
as I ran this race in a brutal, noriester.
Pacho!
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, it's cold.
I'm going to eat it.
It's blown away.
Thank you.
You will.
Anyway, I just posted episode 93 of Fidipidations
where you can hear me run this 26.2 mile road race.
Check it out at run.pacho.com.
I'm already getting ready for a series of races.
I'll be running this summer with plans to run a couple of Marathons in the fall.
Thanks for all the support Adam.
I'm Steve runner and I've got to run.
Steve runner from Fidipidations podcast
who ran the Boston Marathon.
I love it that he had that T-shirt.
He had the Pacho T-shirt on and people are yelling.
Go, Pacho.
We probably could have put like cocksucker on it.
People were like, go, cocksucker.
They had no idea what they were talking about.
We've got comic strip blogger on the Skype for a portion of today's show.
Thank you.
I was going to ask you about the French elections,
but I guess it's kind of boring.
Actually, by the time people hear the show,
they live information that we don't know how the latest round went.
No, this is just the first round.
It's kind of like American idol, isn't it?
The way this works, I didn't know that the French have a very specific way of elections.
They have a...
It's almost like the Eurovision Song Contest.
They have a first round and then they have a second.
There's a third round or the second round is it?
No, the second round is the final round.
Generally speaking, in French elections,
everybody was looking at the first round
whether they would be surprised or not.
Because last time they were surprised.
Big surprise, because let's end,
which is right wing, X-ray means has won.
No.
But this time there was no surprise
and this two leading candidates,
the Sakozi and Riyal,
they have just moved to the next round.
But in Sakozi's leading now.
I like the Sakozi guy.
It looks like a nice guy.
Is he alright?
So, you know, I am myself a little bit right wing
and Riyal is a nice way.
He's left wing.
Is that what you call them?
Bigger pattern?
What did you call them?
No, it's a clear school guy.
Okay.
Nobody's left wing.
His niece, Sakozi's left wing.
Sakozi is a right wing.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Riyal is left wing.
Okay, Riyal is left wing.
And Sakozi's channel is picking
wants to prevent Turkey joining you
and Riyal is saying,
what's she wishy wishy wishy wishy.
Well, wait a minute.
Shouldn't Turkey be allowed to join the EU?
Are you against that?
Personally, I would like to give it to the vote of people.
Right.
Because Turkey is huge.
Turkey used to be the middle of Europe.
Not really.
Yeah, yeah, Turkey was like Turkey was like the, like the the other
Rome.
Wasn't it?
No.
It was constant up.
Constantinople.
Constantinople was the second Rome.
Wasn't it?
Yeah.
Is in the continent where's Constantinople?
Where the hell was that?
It's between European, Pat Turkey and the Asian,
Pat.
Okay, so it's Turkey.
It's Turkey.
Right, all right, okay, but not middle of Europe. What the fuck are you talking about?
No, I don't know. No, it was like I didn't like the middle, but the center, you know, the economic center is what I meant.
The problem is that from the point of view of old societies in Europe that are aging and decreasing in
numbers apart from UK, which is growing, the Turkey is growing rapidly. It would be situation where
Turkey would have more vote than Germany in the European Parliament, and people are scared in
France, particularly because France has a very big minority of these Muslim people, that if Turkey
will join Europe, then they will simply overrun France. But you know, it looks.
Sarkozy is against it and Real is wishy-washy about it. And the vote on the next
in two weeks on 6th May, the second round will be the final round, and then we will vote about
Turkey in Europe. Shortest speaking. Okay. So what do you think? Will it happen or not? Will Turkey be able to join the EU?
I think yes, because Germans are pushing it. Okay. All right, just I one more thing for you, CSV.
You know, I had a problem with my earlobe when I was on vacation in Tenerife, and it was something
that it's this headphone earlobe, you know, because of the rubbing of the headphone and it made my earlobe
you know, infected and grew really good. Yeah, I'm not using in here. No, no, no, no, I like the ones
that cover my ear completely. Oh, that's what I grew up using, you know, and also the headphones
are used when I'm flying. It's just the ear-taste. I've had it before and twice before they've
literally had to cut it open and all this gunk comes out and it's really disgusting and it's
painful and it's not fun. So, you know, the worst thing for this to happen, of course, is
why I'm vacation in the country. You don't speak the fricking language. And I was so happy when
the doctor knocked on my door and I opened up and it was just like really cute, young woman.
And I was like, oh, okay, this is going to be all right. And well, you alone know with Patricia.
Well, I was there alone with Patricia was in the gym at the time. No, come on, and do,
she's a doctor, right? And she was from Poland. And her name was Agata.
And Agata Zuba. Is that how you pronounce it? Zuba? I would have to see the spaling because you
are S Z U B A Zuba. It's the Shuba. Shuba. Shuba. Anyway, so she was really, really funny because I
had to go to the clinic because it had to be a sterile environment. She was joking around with me
said, oh, do you want the big knife, the little knife? And, you know, she was like, oh, I'll cut you here
and then she was, you know, drawing across my neck. And she was really funny, right? And so I gave her
my email address and I said, you know, if you're ever in London, you know, look me up and I'll take
you flying. I'll repay the favor. And she sent me an email. Check this out. She said, just a short email
to ask, it's funny because she writes just like you talk, CSB. It's great. Just a short email to ask
how are you alive and kicking? By the way, sometimes when I find something or someone unique,
I check it in the internet. Good to know on cute Mr. Van Gogh, what an ambition signed Agatha.
And then, but in her email here, I'm going to Skype this to you right now. In her email, what does
that mean? At the bottom, her signature? I just Skype this to you. Oh, this is just advertisement.
An advertisement. This is, she is using free, a service, a free email service from Poland.
Oh, crap. Oh, crap. No, it's not, I love you. Oh, like, oh, maybe she's saying really
hot. Alright. Would you do me favor? Would you just like, you just take a note. So I can write
something in Polish because you just say, uh, like something really nice, and uh, uh, and it's, you know,
it's so nice to be held by such a cute, cute girl and I hope to see your, uh, take her flying
and learn something in Polish, but I think it would be really, really cool to email her back in Polish.
I can't write it on that fast.
You got to write it to me, man.
I can't transcribe it.
I would write it to you.
Okay, whatever.
Hey, CSB.
I want to thank you so much, man, for doing this.
This is a very nice of you.
No problem.
Oh, y'all.
Y'all.
Talk to you soon.
I've been with Mike and my head from Queens.
Cause I'm about to change y'all.
We've lost my listen, y'all.
I stopped you in your eye, y'all.
With a fucking Bible.
This ain't fucking Bible.
You shoot the sign of jail.
Oh, you fucking mind, y'all.
It's a fucking cross my line, y'all.
You're so hard.
You are so weak.
You're so weak.
I know.
I don't take your life or make you die, y'all.
So what's your focus?
If I make you hate your fucking eyes, but I find no.
If you don't want to lack a lie, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, what's in my teeth?
Who's trying?
Fight, broke ain't nice, no, no, no.
When you're alive, throw a mind, go.
Look at my fucking eye.
Oh, the baby told you to act, throw.
Lock for a life, oh.
Satch one side, hold.
Right.
But no, in the same way as mine.
Oh, I'm all cut-time.
Sing the side, guys.
You're on a side.
Oh, hi.
My name's Ben Line.
I drew.
I'm sick enough to stop.
She ain't hit hard.
I got to speak bar.
Cause I'm a dog.
Stop you when you're idle.
When I ride mine.
Oh, I'm all cut-time.
Oh, I'm all, I'm all cut-time.
But I'm all cut-time.
Oh, I'm all cut-time.
Oh, I'm all out.
Oh, I'm all done.
Oh, I'm all lost.
He's on Warner Brothers records and Warner Brothers actually put this up on the PMN and I didn't
have time to set that up because well quite frankly the way I have the the mixer set up when
I call someone on Skype they can hear my voice through the microphone they don't have that
horrible echo it's basically like a phone bridge is what you call that but for some reason when
I play tracks out of the cast blaster the channel is running through even if the fader is completely
close it still plays pretty loud through the through the return line so I see as B couldn't hear
me and I couldn't set it up properly but anyway so okay so so we've done something new here
I'm going to try again tomorrow hopefully tomorrow of course I'll be in San Francisco
going to be there for for the rest of the week coming to you from the curry condo
I want to talk about web radio and the new fees that have been imposed by the copy right
what is it the copy right board or the copyright protection friction fraction
and there's only one guy I know who knows everything about that his name is Doc Serals
so I'm going to and of course he's he's a blogger as well it's I think it's a doc dot weblogs dot
com and I will see if I get a hold of him and see we can do a chat as well and let me know what you
think you know to we continue to do this was it uh and some people may have thought the CSB stuff was
a little bit long but quite honestly it's hard to shut him up maybe I could keep it somewhat
sure hey wait a minute that's what the fucking fast forward is for isn't it Adam and pod show dot com daily
source code dot com I will talk to you guys tomorrow bye bye another pod show podcast sticking in your
ear
the best of the brightest sub dot daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limeite