The song plays softly
Help Podgeo suck less
Join the suck less zone
At suckless.potgeo.com
Hey, Adam.
On the DSC 619, don't forget to tell all the Charlie Dads out their happy father's day
And hey make sure everybody takes full advantage of it.
It only comes once a year.
Make sure the kids cook your breakfast, fetch your slippers, fetch the paper,
get a job, sort of supporting themselves
So what are they're only six.
They're still sweatshops around, they can make clothes for Walmart
But hey, on the DSC 619
Happy Fubar, Father's Friday
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm justing kids that I'm Korean.
Okay, baby, I'll close my mouth and watch the time be safe.
Back to the music.
We'll fire Friday.
In the sunshine, I'm laughing in the rain.
Get it on the full shot.
Rocking in the gray.
Got no time to run my bed.
But that's not the goal.
Got a date, can't be late, but I can't get it full.
I'll get it.
Ooh, yeah.
I'm here to go.
Think I can we understand.
The horrible game, the good good things
And the things, the last day I give you the thing and the mountains
That the ocean, that the birds.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, sure it's fine
No, my, my
What a beautiful day
Yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, sure it's fine
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, sure, sure
Yeah, we've had your bank whose life is smoking, huh?
Law of girls from New York and five safe and proven it by being on the network.
Less zeppelin.
The ocean.
On a provide Friday with Max from Music and I don't know what happened then.
The phone line just opened wide up and it's unbelievable the amount of stuff that's come in.
I'm in Washington DC today.
You've caught me in transit.
We had a couple meetings here this morning.
So we took the red eye last night from San Francisco.
I'll tell you more about that later on.
And about two hours from now I get picked up.
And I'm going home.
I'm going home a whole day earlier.
I wonder, should I tell Patricia,
do you want to get rid of the boyfriend before I get the end?
Adam, this is Paul.
I was commenting on there.
I am commenting on 16th.
I just listened to, you know.
I got two comments about that.
One is the sign you've played at the end.
Mr. Gentry, sign there is.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Pause because I think about that you are now creating the soundtrack of my life.
Yes.
Because I thought back when I first started listening to your show.
And that was one of the songs that you played quite often.
And I forgot how great that song is.
And I'm going to try to track that down and make a purchase.
So thank you for that.
The other thing is the nylon.
He's excruciating sometimes.
This guy is excruciating.
But that out.
As your voice now.
Oh yeah.
Thanks a lot, buddy.
Yep.
I guess what?
He's back again today.
Another appearance from the nylon on the Charlie.
Speaking of the soundtrack to your life.
Hit test on the way.
And another massive suggestion from Dr. Hart.
Now girls want to light your fat bottom on fire.
I know we still live for this year baby.
I'm feeling your honor.
I'm so clean.
Call out that I feel like something.
So what if I said it baby.
I'm still one teller.
I hope you're as big a good one alone.
And they're on my lesson.
It's must look around which I remember failure.
Yeah.
So I love my power from now.
See the police going down.
You're fooling around with the cops.
Did I kill you near?
No one behind me.
Now I need to build this show.
You're stuck at my command and time I see that it's skit here.
And more bang on the side of your head.
Watch out your ass.
Where I spill all of the sign of the men now.
You smell what you do.
You can't make me your age.
Will you change what you initially said?
But come with me.
Good day.
But fuck on me.
Cause now we vibe in and talking and shit.
I'm not the head of your ass going.
When you walk in and shit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You take me home tonight.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
And you give it all you got back.
But I'm going to make the rockin' world go round.
You move girl, like your ass on fire.
Like your ass on fire.
Baby, I know you're probably cooking in your tablecloth.
I'm going to make the rockin' world go round.
But I'm going to make the rockin' world go round.
And feel ya goin' changevern.
But I'm going to make the rockins,
And feel ya make the rockin' world and happy.
And feel ya make the rockin' world go round.
Got nice
I'll let it all hang out, that part of girls, you make you rockin' world around
That part of girls, you make you rockin' world around
Get on your backs, ride!
I can't stop, ride!
It's court, free to step on a girl,
Mass stuff and fuss your eyes, light your ass on fire!
And this link in the show notes will take you to the matchup directly,
you can download it from free again thanks to Dr. Art
for mashuptowns.com
Oh man!
I was talking, actually.
Of course, the lady Patricia knows I'm coming home a day early, I was just messing with you.
And she's happy because that means we'll have a real father's day celebration on Sunday.
That is if my daughter remembers me.
Well, maybe when I park that pink mini in the garage, she'll remember.
So I told her, hey, excuse me, a couple of people.
We're going to meet.
That's what I said yesterday.
I can meet a couple of people in D.C.
So I'm going to take the red eye and run a fly with me and run a fly back.
And I'll just keep headed towards keep going east and come on home.
You guys will be fucking anything for that company.
I said, yep, you better believe it.
Also, we had lunch with an internet pioneer.
Legend, I should say, Ted Leones is from America online from AOL,
who run and I both know from our previous company.
And of course, Ted has done some amazing things in AOL
for I thought it was like 15 years or something like that.
And he basically almost single-handedly turned around
in parts of this town.
You know, he built a stadium in some derelict part of town.
And now that's turned into a, and it really into a cool city centre almost.
Very inspirational guy.
It's still kind of a kid from Brooklyn from Greek descent.
You know, that was great.
And so yeah, right now it's, it's five minutes to seven.
So of course, I'm late with, with Charlie,
but I know that my friends in Australia,
they love the footballer Friday.
They love to listen to it on Tuesday.
Hey Adam, this is Brian.
No, I'm sitting on my front porch with a tall glass of water.
Nice.
After a nice left or even walk.
And just wanted to get in touch to let you in.
By the way, Brian, who, who works at Potcia,
well, from his home, and he's a team with PWB,
and they do all kinds of, all kinds of stuff.
In fact, we're about to resurrect podfinder US with the team.
So stay tuned for that.
I'll just let Brian finish.
The listeners know about a new podcast that I've started.
The address is fit after 50. podshow.com.
That's, if I T-A-F-T-E-R-5-0. podshow.com.
And basically, I've let myself get in terrible shape
over the past 10, 15 years.
And put on a bunch of weight.
And I have high blood pressure.
And my lower back is miserable.
And I'm just a mess.
And a side that I've had enough of it.
So I'm going to do my best to get fit and stay that way
the rest of my life.
I haven't done anything really crazy so far.
Just been watching my diet and exercising.
And I've lost 10 pounds over the past two weeks.
So I doubt that I'll make that kind of progress from here
on out, but it's an encouraging start.
And wanted to, first of all, just document my progress
in my journey, just pull myself.
But also thought there might be something to begin
in sharing this with other people.
So again, that address is fit after 50. podshow.com.
Speedupodshow.com, I better get back to work.
See you later.
I'm Brian Fentastic.
You know, I got to tell you ever since I quit smoking at tobacco.
And of course, that also means by default that I'm not smoking
anything else during the day because you can't take it.
Can't take it in its pureness factor.
Not if I have to actually function.
And it's been kind of inspirational for people.
I've gotten a lot of support, first of all, again,
thank you so much, everyone who's who's been cheering me on.
I tell you that in Los Angeles, the whole day
and thing about smoking at all, I thought that was a pretty big win.
And so now you get stuff like this, you know, and that's cool.
But of course, Brian, I think I should make a channel.
And we're going to talk about channels again today.
I'll probably make a channel.
Or I'll certainly put your first episode in my combo feed.
I have a new combination feed, which is essentially daily source code.
So you get every new episode of this show.
And anything I talk about that I, of course,
if I remember, I'll put single episodes into the feed.
Actually, I'll talk about that in a second.
First of all, Brian, I really appreciate what you've done.
It fit over 50, great idea.
But of course, you could also just, uh,
exercise.
I've been a stand-up.
I got these props, Amy.
I'll be gay, please.
I'm supposed to do with these paper blades, Amy.
Hey, Adam.
Amy Mac.
Thank you so much for bringing this on with you,
to San Francisco.
Oh, no.
You are the sunshine in San Francisco.
No, today you're going to need a prop,
which should have been given to you by Chris, yes.
I got them two paper plates.
Yes, they are paper plates, I know.
What do I do?
We're going to start standing.
Okay, hold on.
You want one foot on each one of the plates.
I'm going to be careful.
You can leave your shoes on or go barefoot,
it's really up to you.
Let me take off my socks.
Now bend your knees.
Okay.
Lean forward a little bit.
Yeah.
We want you to feel like you're in a strong athletic stance.
Oh, okay.
You there?
Yeah, I'm there.
Now slide your right foot out toward the right.
Yep.
And then slide your left foot into it.
And again, right foot out.
Okay, I get it.
Follow with the left.
It should feel almost like a slow motion gallon.
Good.
Now the opposite.
So left foot to the left.
And slide the right foot in next to it.
Left one more.
Yeah.
It's kind of weird.
Good.
Let's do two more slides to each side.
Right.
Squeeze that button.
Oh.
Make it a wide slide.
And last time right.
And then bring it together.
Good.
Now left.
Do I breathe?
Stay facing forward.
I suppose to breathe.
Last one.
Ah.
Great job.
You're such a good sport.
Like even exercising with paper plates.
Now that's dedication.
Baby.
I'm right.
Have a good weekend.
And until next time.
Oh, thank you, Amy.
Well, this is great because, you know,
and by the way, you can get us to exercise on its own feed.
And of course, Amy has the fitness attack.
It's a huge show on the network.
And she's just cute as a button.
But.
And she's getting me props, props to play with paper plates.
Even wrote on it.
Be careful.
Kiss, kiss, from Amy.
Happy footballer for our to-at-em.
Into all your listeners.
A lot of them up.
Now we all have a song that really inspires us.
I know I have a few.
But I came across one about two weeks ago.
That really, really hit me.
Deep in the heart.
But it's not pot safe.
Oh, man.
But I know you've been known to play a pot.
Non-pot safe song from time to time.
So I'm really hoping you'll play this one.
The name of the group is called Group One Group.
The name of the song is called Love Is A Beautiful Thing.
And if the listeners like it, go to iTunes and download the video.
They don't even have the song over there.
Just the video.
So get it for $1.99 and support this band.
And Adam.
Yeah.
If you get in trouble for playing this song, I will fly out from Tampa to San Francisco.
Once every couple of months, in personally,
clean the pod show toilets to help pay off the fine.
Well, have you know that we're all folders at Pod Show?
So I gotta tell you that football is already a big spammer.
I appreciate it, buddy.
But you never know.
I could go to Big House over this one.
I feel you love could be like this.
I will pull to protect me through the hard times.
It always exists.
Me, the hardest stop breakdown.
Make a person who hates love themselves so we can love those around.
It gives everyone all the things they've done.
It's not easy, but the freedom will come.
We gotta learn why it needs to be here.
It's more than loving your life.
It's making sure you're like this loving your peers.
Now you could just catch my heart.
And we can pop from the past, let the days of the new love start because.
It's a beautiful day.
It brings together people.
A better generation.
I don't like the love.
I can feel the pain.
All the broken walls.
It's got to start with us.
And all it takes is love.
It's something you love is love.
Well, I've got to make it clear.
Love the reason we are here.
We're the object of our backship from a guy who holds us in.
And never, never, never, never know anything that we do.
Every time that we love, it's where we fight you now, yeah.
Because you are all alone.
So make you really love us.
Stop holding onto the past so we can ask him the reason.
The days of the new love last because.
It's a beautiful day.
It brings together people.
A better generation.
It's a beautiful day.
It brings together people.
It's got to start with us.
And all it takes is love.
It's something you love is love.
It's something you love.
It's something you love is love is love.
It's something you love is loved.
It's something you love is love.
All right, dude, I'll gladly go to jail over that one.
Light it up.
Love is a beautiful thing.
That is so nice.
All right, hurry on over.
DavidSourceco.com, click on the links.
We'll take you to the video and go buy that support for the band because Dan, that is really, really good.
I mentioned earlier that I started a daily source code combo channel.
This is something that right now,
most of the functionality is in Pod Show and a lot of it has been there for a while.
And now I'm working with Andrew and Devon from our engineering team.
I've got my own developers.
I don't know if I think they're working maybe exclusively on this for the next couple days.
I sure hope so.
Because there's a couple things that need adjusting in the management of the channels.
If you subscribe to these, the combo channel, I'll put it in the show notes again.
You can put that on your iPod, just through your iTunes.
And I'll put in the RSS, the plain Jane RSS link again as well.
Because these things, it's really cool.
And it gives you an opportunity to create a show, which anyone can receive.
You know, just through our player, the dashboard player, or in this case,
just to make it simple, works on lots of stuff, but in iTunes.
And it enables you to create entertainment for anyone who's subscribed to that show.
Well, you call a channel, but I'll just call it a show.
It's going to have the same properties.
So you'll be able to comment on it.
You'll be able to add it to your own collection.
If you find someone else's channel.
And you can already see that a lot of things within Pod Show are channelized.
So you can get single episodes, you can get graphics.
Indeed, if you get a song, not everything works right.
And it's still kind of burpy and crappy.
But the core functionality is working.
And people are really enjoying it.
Hello, Adam Curry.
This is Daniel Johnson Jr. from Cincinnati, Ohio.
I am calling about the Pod Show plus channel concept thing that you guys are talking about.
I really like that Pod Show plus is enabling us to get individual episodes.
I have been using the channel feature for it to subscribe to.
I'm practically all of my podcast.
I subscribe to over close to 80 feeds.
And instead of having to manage 80 individual subscriptions,
I can just put them into a couple of channels.
I have a music channel for all my music podcasts.
And then I kind of put all my video podcasts into one channel.
And then I also have one that I call use for everything else.
Yeah.
So it has been using individual doing individual episodes.
I created a channel just where I can put individual episodes of shows that I'm checking out.
Yeah.
Today I created a channel for selected episodes of one of my favorite podcasts.
And so you need to just like, I've only that podcast.
So if I wanted to recommend it to somebody.
I can say, hey, if you want to learn what's been going on with this particular show.
Just go get my channels.
Check out this speed and you can listen to all the shows and get the idea of what's going on.
This is one of the things that I've been using gigadial for.
Yeah.
I thought it put together.
And I'm sure that he has been very instrumental in helping to do some more time.
What project is doing.
And so definitely looking forward to all the different changes that are going on.
Again, Daniel Johnson, Jesus Christ.
Since that is Ohio.
They get a great day at him.
And thanks so much.
All right.
Daniel Johnson, Junior, I appreciate it, man.
Yeah, of course.
Andrew has a lot of that knowledge.
And I'm looking forward to it being applied.
Because imagine.
Oh, just imagine.
If you could determine the order of output of your channel.
Wouldn't that be nice?
If you could make that distinction and not just have to be by the most recent episode update.
By the way, we have a whole API for this.
Geeks, engineers, people listening in.
People who don't know what that is.
It's an application programming interface, I think.
It's a way for you to tie into pod shows engine.
It's essentially where all the widgets connect.
Yeah, you've seen widgets all over the place, right?
It's stuff you embed into a page.
You can put it on your my space or your Facebook or on your weblog.
Wherever you want and a complete stuff.
Yeah, we have an entire API for our channels.
So if you know how to make a widget, you can go to developer.podshow.com.
Amy's boy toy, Chris, the first we call him.
He's actually resurrecting the entire developer program.
And it's working is really now becoming a resource for developers who.
Well, it's interesting because for kind of has a.
He hasn't been to what I have.
He's actually a pretty good programmer engineer.
Enough to get himself in trouble.
Let's put it that way.
But he also understands media extremely well.
So he's the perfect guy to be working with developers on this stuff.
So, and if you make a widget, please ping me.
Let me know.
I'll put it on my site.
I'll promote the heck out of it.
You kidding me?
Hello.
Hey, Adam.
This is Jeff from Northern Michigan.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, the.
You were describing all of stuff that you're doing with the channel feed.
Yeah.
I've been doing that since I discovered it on podshow.
Some time after you guys were alive.
Really?
It's been the best feature that I think has been ever.
You guys invented on the whole site.
Because managers, you my content.
And what I listen to on a daily basis through a weekly basis is so much easier.
So, hey, keep up the good work.
Yo.
Fuller.
Thanks buddy.
Yeah.
Let me see if I can explain some of the cool features of this.
Because, you know, we generally think of feeds or what we're calling channels.
As, you know, dynamic shows that updates are already.
You know that you can make a channel out of static stuff.
Just single episodes or out of pictures if you want.
Now the pictures won't download to your iPod yet, but working on that.
Actually, that should work with photo casting, I guess.
Hmm.
You have another thing to look at.
But you'll be able to set properties on on items you put into a channel.
So you could say, hey, you know, I want daily source code in my channel.
But I don't want all the episodes in my channel.
I just want the most recent one.
And you could say, I want the most recent two for that matter.
It's not done yet.
I don't think, but you'll be able to get people.
And people, of course, have all kinds of stuff.
They have shows.
They have their own channels.
They listen to.
They have blog posts.
They have pictures.
And you'll be able to say, you know what?
From this person, I want every single new show he listens to or every blog post he puts up.
I mean, the mind boggles.
Particularly when you think that you can put channels into chat.
I, I, I, I, it is not a feature.
It is the feature.
Oh boy.
It's time for double whammy.
This summer, when you buy Coke, you get music.
You can win an iPod or free songs or nightchains.
That's right.
Today's hit test is brought to you by Coca-Cola.
Fantastic.
With Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam.
You're having ready to be stumped.
Oh, I'm ready.
I'm away.
He used it.
He doesn't pull back.
Hi, Adam.
Yon Poletti with hit test number 74.
Again, three very short clips.
I'm ready.
And three answers.
So here we go.
This is number one.
Easy.
That's not a man.
A fine, young cannibal.
She drives me crazy.
Come on.
We sing a top 40 radio station as a recurrent.
And number two.
Lucky star Madonna.
I think.
You might be my lucky star.
And the final one for this week's hit test.
Oh, it's hard.
It sounds like a...
You sound dead a bit.
Don't waste my time.
Jocelyn Brown or something like that.
And that's it.
And this is answer number one.
This was easy.
From 1988 to fine young cannibals.
She drives me crazy.
Oh, sorry.
You're trying to sing one there.
Fuck another.
Here it comes.
She drives me crazy.
Come on.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
We played that one.
We just sat on MTV.
And so number one.
The fun young cannibals.
She's a jumping video.
And this is answer number two.
Yeah.
In 1984.
Oh, yeah.
This is Madonna.
Who's your daddy?
Lucky star.
Oh, man.
We might not be star.
Because it's just only when ever you are.
Starlight.
The starlight.
Make it.
All right.
Last one.
Starlight.
Madonna's answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
Oh, our castle.
Yes.
And so number three.
And don't waste my time.
Oh, our castle.
Answer number three.
And don't waste my time.
In this edition of the hit test.
Well, that's it.
For this week.
See you next week, Adam.
Hope you did well, by the way.
Yeah.
And up ahead.
I hope you did well, by the way.
Yeah, I'm up ahead.
Two and a half stars.
By the way, the show notes and stuff is all up on the...
It tests.
They're part show.com.
Yeah.
You can also find tracks and iTunes links there.
Oh, and please dig the show.
It's cool to be Dave, right?
Okay, Adam, see you next week.
Until then, bye-bye.
With financial backing from the organization
for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives,
upsol.org.
It's registered in no website yet.
Yon Pula, thank you once again.
Hit test.podshow.com.
I, I, I, my forgotten last week,
I'll definitely put a link in this week.
Yon, fantastic job.
Why did I think Jocelyn Brown, my poor hard castle?
But that was one of the first guys
who was like a producer, producer, fantastic.
Love to hear from you.
I'm almost afraid now with all the stuff you guys
you know, dialed in in this in the past like 36 hours
that I won't get anything for next week.
One, two, one, six, two, five, six, three, five, seven.
Ganna tell you, I'm getting a little bit worried about nylon.
He's called in for the third time this week.
He's not necessarily one of your favorites.
Hey, Adam, it's Doug Pilgrim in Boston.
Listen to anybody has any kids with them right now.
Turn off your MP3 player.
It's gonna be all explicit.
Hey nylon, do a solid favor and tighten up on your loafers.
Pull the panties out of your ass and shut the fuck up.
Every time you call this show, all you do is complain and wine.
And half the time you got it wrong.
Who are your first call to this show?
All that shit that you were given, Adam,
about the fact that he's not an environmentalist.
Adam never said he was an environmentalist.
Adam was all about Trinity from the alternative energy standpoint.
Had nothing to do with the environment.
I'm the one to introduce that conversation.
You had it wrong then and you've got it wrong now.
You're whining about the fact that Adam is gonna quote,
Pimp his ride, how do you expect a project like this
to get done without any money?
Are you some kind of a goddamn socialist?
Do you want the government to step in?
Shit, like this does not get done unless a sponsor steps are quite frankly.
I don't give a crap if Adam covered that and said he's been.
So it looked like a fucking NASCAR coming down the road.
As long as the project gets done.
So do me a favor and click a cry baby crap and come up with something constructed
and serve just sitting back and feel sad and having all of your goddamn facts.
Oh, whoa, touch a crow baby.
And that whining New York accent of yours,
I swear to God, you must be a Yankees fan.
Thanks, Adam, but I couldn't take a listen to this guy anymore.
And now?
Yeah.
Pot-safe music and that whining.
Well, thank goodness.
Take it back.
Okay, I mean, Bradshaw.
Wow, them spiked words, I'd say.
Not long, but it looked out.
You said I'm gone too ill.
Three cold dry.
And it turned to the river where mudded water floored.
See, I'm tired, I've been carrying the hell below.
So I was born with the moves and bad attitude.
I went down to the river, got nothing to do with it.
Take it back.
I don't want you to fall over.
But where did you go?
Here.
Take us down to the river
Well, he really has the daddy or the ID. He or
Look cover
Take me back for a little bit of first
Take me back
Wow
Great song, great choice, Doug
And thanks for the email
We'll be talking sometime next week
It's going to be really busy next week for me
I got to tell you
Monday, Patricia and I are going to a
Gala dinner
There's a Gala
You say Gala
I say Gala
It's
The flight attendants for the
Virgin Atlantic
Have an award ceremony
And they really do this up right
And Patricia and I was like, let's just go
By the way, if it's flight attendants
It's probably as Gala
I
Yes, moving up towards the Nylon
Hi Adam, it's Kevin Crossman
The proud scruncher
You okay?
I have a comment in a question about
Recent pod show events
Okay, rock on
First comment about
Jonsky before
What ever soft lunch of just podcast
Maybe he didn't want to talk about that
On Twitter because
Whatever he's doing now
Just sucks
You know, sometimes you need to soft lunch
Something kind of see what I was going
But sometimes better to not soft lunch
Something, I don't know what he's doing
On his show
It seems like he can't even press record
On his microphone
Well, I think that's kind of the whole point
Is he really wants to get into this
He really wants to podcast
So he's got himself a copy of
Cast Blaster, which he likes very much
But, you know, it takes a little bit of work
He's got the wrong gear
He's got a USB microphone
Which of course works perfectly
But it no way does
His setup represent what he can sound like
And what he can do
So that's why you do a soft lunch
You can do this all
You know, you can make shows
Five minutes shows every single day
Imprive it and have, you know,
The pod father review
The more you could just put it out there
Warts and all, you know, that's
Isn't that kind of what we're about, dude?
And to be able to produce a show
Without standing multiple versions
Of the same showing to his feet
I don't know, it shouldn't be that hard
It wasn't for me
And I'm sure John is getting paid
Big bucks by pod show to do a good job
But he ain't doing it now
And, you know, now he's putting a call out to people
To say, what does he want to do?
You know, what the fuck is that about
Because he should be hired
To know what he wants to do
That's crazy
Oh man, come on, I talk out of my ass
All the time
And that's what you do when you're testing stuff
Stuff out
Go look at the DSC channel
The little video thing I do every day
It's totally dumb
But that's because we're testing
You know, there's a lot of stuff going on
And he's building channels
So, I just hang back and relax
Don't worry, everything's going to be alright
I am looking forward to the channel concept though
But I would like you to address the high
High-Jackish who you started around that
It seems to me that
You need traditional term of a high-Jack feed
But the gripes of people have
Is that okay?
Now I'm subscribed to this channel
And oh, the straight show is in there
And I'm subscribed to the channel
But what if the channel goes away
Now, me as a potcaster
I lose all those listeners who are subscribed to the channel
Not to my show directly
So I'd like you to address that
Sure, that's a question that people have
That being said, anybody who's pretty good at entertainment
We can't all be happy to include
Frappacat.com
Go ahead and put that in there
I'll be happy to have you do that
In any case, exactly
Bruncher
Yes, yes, yes, be quiet
That's my point exactly dude
Of course you want to have it in all kinds of channels
Because that's going to get you people listening
And you know what? I got to tell you
I've had problems with channels and feeds and podcast
And all kinds of stuff
And if it's something I'd like to listen to
Find out what's wrong with it
But really what we're doing
Personalised aggregation
That's one way of looking at it
You can use a widget
The download stuff
They could be like
RSS feeds
For blog posts
Lots of millions of people using
Stuff on the desktop to do that
And millions more using
I don't know
I use Google News
Podcast by the way
But really we enable you to customize
Your experience from these feeds
I think this is pretty unique
You're able to
Collect I mean, we have incoming feeds
Unbelievable how many feeds are
Incoming into into podshow system
But outgoing there's
A multiple of five more outgoing
Because all of these channels that are being created
And when you can start to connect those channels to each other
It's just more distribution dude
It's like a social RSS network
Hmm
It's actually something to that
And that's kind of a reager
It's got to make a better name
RSS space
I don't know what it is
But it's working and it's not hijacking
It's not the whole point
Is that you know your feed updates
Otherwise all the channels don't update
Anything that it's in
So you know hijacking is
Is it really something all together
Different
So
I don't think there's an issue to address
hijacking is when you copy the feed
And republish a feed by the same name
Only it's coming from a different source
So that is something very different
And you already pointed out dude, it's great
If you're creating a show
Because it just gets you lots more distribution
Whoa, he's an island
Outspoken, expatriate, he's in London
He's from New York
Oh
He's a island
Controvers the island
He's in London, but he's from New York
If you didn't think you had enough to bitch about the war act
Mr. Curley
Mr. Nyla
I've got palm my hands
I'm sitting here
This Sheraton Pulitzer Hotel
Oh
Overlooking the pleasing grass
And Amsterdam?
Yes
And I was thinking because I got palm on my hands
And I started playing this game called
Google Bingo with you
Which was, you know, I was counting each show
We have a couple shows
How many times do you say Google
Or reference a Google related
What?
Autoc
And then I realized
Another thing is that, you know,
Sequoia and your other VC partners
They will go to some of the initial investors
On Google
That's interesting
And then I realized
Okay, my whole rant about the war act
You've nothing something here
He's a brand name
Wait a minute
Are you saying that
Me talking about Google makes us an acquisition
That acquisition target for them
Yeah
Yeah, they need my business
Make the guy more attractive
More credibility
Yes, he does
If you force a cranky geek
With a closet geek
What do you get?
You get an acquisition target
And I had to slap myself on my head
How stupid of you?
That's funny
Highline, you've been out of New York too long
That's true
So I just want you to know Mr. Carrey
I'm going to be watching you with my Google Bingo each show
And if I get to sense you got Googly eyes out there
I don't know what I'm going to do
Because I know you wouldn't sell out for 100 million
100 million
No boy
I chose worth more than that
It's it's my baby man
Are you out of your mind?
You're in this for the long run
Yes
But it's all coming together now
I see two dots converging
You don't have the same thing
I know the SEC
But I just want you to know Mr. Carrey
I'm watching you with the Googly eyes
It's starting to come together for me
And me while I'm bipolar
Because now you got coke on there
And you got Tylenol
So I take the coke
And I'm bouncing off the wall
I take the Tylenol
And I'm falling asleep
Hey dude
Get sponsors that do the same thing
I mean I'm bipolar
You know the coke and Tylenol
They don't go together
It's why you're helpful in it again
So anyway
Anyway
I'm watching you Mr. Carrey
Are you sure you're only bipolar
My one
I know you're long
Thanks man
By the way
If you I was always told this is this a myth
And maybe it is
I when I was growing up
There was I guess it's an urban legend or something
But if you put an aspirin in a girls' coke
It would be the equivalent of Spanish fly
So maybe you're just really turned on
That's why you're calling in three times in one week
Nylon
I appreciate the thought
But now we have a little bit more work to do
Before we're let Google buy us
I'm not going to say
I got to get these channels work and man
That's going to take long enough
Hey by the way
So it's starting to work
I'm starting to get people from podshow HQ
Calling in
So we had sales, we had Greg
Of course Andrew and Devon will be calling
And I'm sure Andrew's called it on the show before
And I've got another one from from A to the B
With a suck less zone update
But Jeff Smith was so nice to of course
Turn this into an item for me
Which means we have a jingle
But I'm bum another day
At the office
But I'm bum just saying hello
But I'm bum
To the gang from HQ
And podshow
Yo, Adam and stuff
It's day to day to the B
Hey man
I'm standing outside the pod show HQ
Looking at some numbers
And it is really fascinating stuff
As I said
But let's get real here
Sorry about that
So are you a podcaster
And by the way
Obviously our panel numbers are building
So these might not be completely
You know they're going to be changing over the next summer week
Right
But
Believe it or not
45% of the people are a podcaster
Now when we started this
More like 80%
So now it's 40%
Which is pretty amazing
And then too
What type of listener or viewer are you?
Please check all that apply
Well one of the
One of the
Question is do I stick with the shows I like
And that was 75%
71% of their passionate about certain programs
60% always look for new things
And 53% casually browsing
Select
Anyway
Really cool
That's a suck less update
I may be 80 to the B
I'm so excited
You almost
Almost do
You're getting there
Yeah, no that's good
Of course we started with a very high number of podcasters
And now that's dropped down to 45%
That's cool
Which means that the listeners are now coming in
That's excellent
And you heard some of the questions there
And some of the answers
And I'm sure we'll be updating more
I really would appreciate it
If you took the survey
Go to
There's a couple of ways you can get there
Survey.podshow.com
That's the family
Friendly way to get in
The questions are remain the same
And of course
The suck less zone
Sockless.podshow.com
Adam is Chuck from Jersey
Oh my god man
You probably back in time
Listen to that
Victoria
Digital bike there
Holy
I miss the victim
I don't even know the younger
The younger of you
But I got to get the see 64
Did some basic programming myself
And I love doing that
I loved the victims
20 so much
Yeah, with that kind of wacky
To hear that computer program
Oops
Later on I was there
I Pipia
I heard that tone
All the time
Anzi text
And what was the other
The other graphics protocol
We were using we used ANZ
And we used
Was it rip? I think it was rip was another that was the graphics protocol, I think.
Oh man, you brought me back. Yeah, it's frightening.
You go from the Jersey side of things, it's a product. I loved it, man. I thought it was brilliant.
Really?
The whole thing in terms of we never got closure and everything. It was a series and it was about, you know,
Tony knocking closure with his uncle and Janice was moving on or anything about her.
And it's just, it's every day life for them and we just don't get to watch anymore.
You know, first of all, you sound a little too involved in the, in the actual show.
John DeVourke had a pretty good take on that. He said this, this show got whacked.
And it happens when you at least expect it. And when I think back on the episode,
yeah, in a way we were a participant in the show and we got whacked.
We got whacked in the restaurant. I thought that was a pretty good take on it.
And I said, I wouldn't be disappointed if Tony's crew and the New York crew had a heat style gun battle in the middle of the street.
But this just, I don't know, it just works for me.
All right. You know, you get to everybody gets to interpret who walked in the door or, you know,
what happened next or anything. I thought it was awesome.
Anyway, did they hear from you?
All right, mate. No, I thanks, dude.
Yeah, no, I got to say because if, of course, if that show had ended with a throw down between fills New York crew and, and Antony's jersey crew.
I mean, I would have been boring because we know that jersey boys would have won.
Hey, Adam, this is Robin Maude.
God bought some London.
Hello.
I love this. I'm listening to you when they show you mentioned shocker girl.
I'm going to go take a look at her and my new spam blocker says,
The site is blocked.
Yeah.
The site is trying to fix it, but also category.
It's computer set to block.
Soccer girl, Pachelor Cobb, is blocked because it's traffic categorized as...
Poor guy.
Yeah.
This is incorrect.
Please report it by the incorrect rating form.
Now, here's my, my problem, which is, I like it to be pornography.
It has to be blocked.
I have to say it isn't.
And then it won't be or what's behind it.
Anyway, I'm sure you know where she was.
Wow.
Oh, right now.
You know, the soccer girl, of course, he's a pretty famous now for bearing her breasts.
And she's beautiful.
She's just a stunningly beautiful woman.
Add to that that she's a librarian.
And it's just everything I want in a woman.
And but she, the stuff she does.
And I'm sorry that you're spam, that you're, you're, you're porn blocker, whatever it is,
that it's blocked you out.
I mean, that's, unfortunately, that's either your PC or it's your ISP or, however, that's happening.
Of course, we don't block that.
We do put an explicit tag on her.
But, you know, look, she shows her her body.
And usually in context with her show, it's not just like, I got to show my body.
And it's a beautiful body to look at.
As nothing pornographic about it.
What's going on in my mind is extremely pornographic.
But there's nothing pornographic about what she does.
What she does in her shows is often pornographic.
But not in the sense of sex, but really in the sex of, oh, my God, you know,
that you just really messed with my brain.
It's, it's really, it's an awesome, awesome show.
How many times can I promote soccer group?
You deserve a girl.
All right, I got to catch a plane.
I got to head out east to get on a beach.
Branding through fire waves to find it on the TMM.
Only you would make it, baby.
As I look down the roadside.
I love to wait that we are.
It could never go away.
It's a feeling that makes you, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All you could make me happy.
All you could make me smile.
All you could make me smile, yeah, yeah.
I only knew to make me happy
I only knew to make you smile
For a while
The other dog can chase the zippers
I only knew to make you smile
I need you now so I can feel you
I need you now so I can be
I only knew to make me happy
I only knew to make me smile
I only knew to make you smile
Fire ape, so you can make me happy
Brand new you'll find him on the pot
Safe music network
Went a little bit longer than usual today
You guys did it, you just sent an all that awesome stuff
And I am so looking forward to getting home to being with my girls
It's been a long two weeks on the road
We've been working really, really hard
Haven't been sleeping a lot
And just bust an ass
Wow, this is a Hey Fire Apes
Fire Apes
That's kind of irritating at the end there
It's Friday
Well, it's always wonderful
When I'm able to be a state side
Of course we had our week of New York with the sales weasels
And that was fun working on explaining what we do
And helping people make money
For all those wonderful work that you guys are doing
And of course San Francisco, you know, just to be able to be in the midst of it all
A lot more shit seems to get done
Sometimes in like, wow, man, I wish I was in San Francisco
It would make a lot of things easier
But I guess there's a reason for everything
And, you know, run and I are wealthy enough not to have to work anymore
And we start this company because we really, really believe in what we're doing
And just hope that you can somehow share along with me
That, you know, it's weeks like this or
When you take the red eye to catch a couple meetings
It's really what it takes if you want to do something
There are no shortcuts
It doesn't matter how much money you have, you can't build
You can purchase
That way you are striving towards
It's just not possible, you can't buy
The success that we're looking for
Which is trust me, not a financial reward
It's something much more
It's really about just all this stuff spin around
And people enjoying it and having fun and sharing stuff
And creating a new form of broadcasting
Which I believe goes way beyond the feed
It's an important part of it
But it's also what we're telling people
So much more powerful for someone to say
Hey, go check out soccer girl
Than to be recommended by an engineer or something
Anyway, I digress a little bit
If you want to achieve something, you've got to work really hard
So I want you to know that even this rich white boy
It's got to work his ass off
Get done what he wants to get done
Trick to it all
It's just fucking enjoying the ride
Yes, stick that in your thought and I'll get it for the wind
Stick those day food by Friday
And I'm spinal thought on the wind
That's it
I'm going home, can't wait to have sex as well
Dailysourcecode.com
Adam at podshow.com
I will talk to you on Monday everybody
From the car
From the manner
See you then
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Served up daily by the sharpest minds and content delivery
Podshow in limite