I can't throw this, I can't.
Hort City PD, the number one online police drama series, is now available.
Subscribe now and get the entire first season on your iPod.
And get ready for an action-packed season 2 coming July 2007.
Hort City.podshow.com.
You know, we'll be now to hear on the prairie ain't easy.
A lot of minds after cookie finishes.
Mixing us up some grubwee.
Consider how to camp fire and tell stories.
Maybe have a little camaraderie.
Then we snuggle up in Spoon and listen to the DSC, 637.
It's awful nice here, broke back mountain.
Now that I'm curious, just put this in the mood.
The lower here's levy, you can borrow one of my headphones.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
See ya from underground.
Who've done the sound?
Come set the fire, burn the old dial.
A lot of China's now.
You are never known.
All our numbers are grown.
Can't stand the thought of all that said.
And you are wasted.
You've been bought to the bones.
Sick with all you've been shown.
You've eaten time.
Two of the bowls ask you to keep far.
Two of my bowls ask you to keep far.
Thin magic can't decide.
Three bowls ask you to keep far.
We're in control, everywhere you go
Once we start to flow, you're in the know
Let the police see each other, we can't stop the bleeding
Suck away the green, break down the beach, liberate for free
Kill the radio crew
You are never known, all I know is a ground
Can stand a part of our integrity, and we share
You'll be more new than mine
Say, we love you, and we share
You'll be the fucking tank
Turn it, and we share
Black people taking a lot
Investors getting close, Bart
Black people taking over
Investors getting close
Not for you to take it all up!
Come on, baby, watch out, yeah
Yeah, come on, baby, watch out, yeah
There's just days that are perfect to roll monk out
Pod people taking over because the revolution has progressed
Yet another step, my friends, that's right
Mainstream media coming apart at the scenes in the United Kingdom
And it's going to spread worldwide
And we can start watching it as of today
Sit back and enjoy this ride
Daily source code episode number 637 coming to you
From the affluent suburb of Surrey
No one is killed for a G-town west side in the curry manner
And what a perfect day, I'm so excited to talk to you about
What's going on over here?
I have alluded about it, alluded to it for the past couple days
This fits in perfectly with the conversation about the society of the spectral goal
Because the BBC is falling apart
Not just the BBC, but all media now is under huge scrutiny here in the United Kingdom
And this is not just a ding in the armor of mainstream media
It is a huge chunk
There's a crack, we can stick our, the limit in there
And start making them bleed and I'm counting on you to help
Let me explain what's going on why I'm so excited today
First of all, yesterday a report came out from the BBC
I've been keeping up to speed on what's been going on
Is that all of these practices within television at the BBC
Which is publicly funded
Not just through some tax budget
But actually by paying every individual household that has at least
One television or radio has to pay about $300 a year
For the right to actually use that
Because we're presuming that you're going to watch BBC
The BBC is actually a trust
It's called the BBC Trust
Trust being the big word here
Because we pay this money
We trust the BBC to come up with fair
And oh boy, how weird does that sound?
And balanced programming that is not driven by commercial interests
Now of course we're not crazy
We all know particularly with government run
Mainstream media that there's a lot of politics involved
Their funding depends on how the politics are played
Report today came out that says in the run up to the invasion of Iraq
Tony Blair met with Rupert Murdoch a number of times
In three days running in three day run up to the actual invasion
Hmm, I wonder why
Okay, so this all started with this documentary about the queen
Which has not even been released yet
But the trailer was proven to be false
The queen was outraged, the palace, the royal family
Because they edited things out of sequence to kind of sex up
The queen's reaction to Annie Lieber was asking her to take off her
It wasn't even a crown her tiara for a photo shoot
And showed her storming off which was actually her walking into the photos
And now things are just bubbling up to the top
The BBC is going through a wide scale investigation
Here's just part of the report that came out yesterday
Here's some of the falsehoods, lies, trickery and cheating
That the BBC has by their own admission has taken part in
Comic Relief March 16th, 2007 BBC won
In a section of this appeal program
Viewers were invited to donate money to comic relief
That by calling in they could win prizes that belonged to a famous couple
The first two callers taken on air gave incorrect answers
The other waiting callers were lost
And a third caller was heard on air successfully answered the question
This caller wasn't fact not a viewer
But a member of the production team
TMI September 16th, 2006 on BBC 2 and on CBC is a kids program
Following a production problem with a live competition
Viewers were led to believe that a member of the audience was involved
And won a competition open to the public
In fact, the caller was a member of the production team
The program team failed to seek proper advice before running the competition
Sports relief July 15th, 2006 BBC won
Viewers were led to believe that a member of the public was involved in
And won a competition open to the public
Whereas the caller was in fact, you guessed it, a member of the production team
Children in need November 18th, 2005 BBC won Scotland
In a segment called Raven
The island in BBC Children's need appeals
Scotland broadcast in 2005 Viewers were led to believe that a phone
In competition opened to the audience had been won by a viewer
In fact due to a technical mistake calls from the public did not get through
And the name of a fictitious winner was read on the air
The Liz Kershaw Show 2005 on BBC 6 music in pre-recorded programs
Presented as if they were live
A competition was announced that appeared to feature genuine listeners
Foning into take part one of whom could win a prize on air
In fact, in recorded programs there were no competitions or prizes
And all of the callers were actually members of the production team and their friends
A new producer took over the program in December 2006
And stopped the practices as a matter of priority
Finally, white label, world service, BBC
Until April 2006 a weekly pop music preview program on the English service
On more than one occasion a fake winner was announced for the CD prize
When no winning entries had actually been received
Gee
And you think that's all you think that's it
You think that's all that's been fake
Let me tell you what happens in television
And then we're going to listen to some beautiful words from David Cox
Long time television producer here in the United Kingdom
Who was on News Night last night
I can't tell you how excited I am about this
We are going to bring these suckers down
Television is inherently a trickery medium
It was designed that way
It was magic when it first came out
I'm going to tell you just a couple of examples of how I involved in television production
Have deceived the public on purpose
Not for financial benefit or gain
Well, that depends on how you look at it
Because of course
If you tell someone that you have a satellite interview with Janet Jackson
And you promote that so that people will come and watch your show
Therefore your ratings go up
That of course can be seen this 100% deception
That I did that several times
This is exactly what happened in the 80s
When I was in the Netherlands working for a public broadcaster
The organization was Veronica Broadcasting
I did a program called Countdown
And we would receive electronic press kits
From record companies for their major artists
So when Janet Jackson came out with her album
I think that was the one that had what if you'd done from me lately on it
Huge album
Janet Jackson you could not get a bigger star
In fact we couldn't get Janet Jackson in the studio
But the electronic press kit really consisted of an interview with Janet
So questions would be asked off screen
And Janet would be answering those questions
And so what we would do is we would and this was sent out for this very purpose by the way
To take sound bites from or what we did
And I had a big part in this because I didn't concoct it
But I did completely execute it
I looked at all the answers that Janet gave
I wrote up questions which of course were similar to the questions asked
But not the exact questions
So already right there I was going over the line
I think I was not asking the exact questions she was responding to
We edited a tape about three and a half minutes of Janet's answers
And black spaces in between
And I timed my questioning to that tape
So imagine here's what happened
I would sit there and say okay we got Janet Jackson on the side
Like while I was saying that they would show a frame of that tape
So it looked like we literally put in fuzzy stuff
Like the satellite was coming in and out
Of course this was the 80s when a satellite interview was still a huge deal
We did not have the internet at the time
Or at least we weren't using it the way we used it today
And then I knew the cues I knew would ask the question
Janet's answer would come I wish I could find this tape
Or copy of it because you'll see that I probably even through in a
Funny question to which she gave a totally different response
Just to really sex up the whole interview
Complete utter deception my god
This was a music program on television
Where the artists came on and pretended to actually perform
They had their guitars with actual cords plugged in
Microphones with cords plugged in plugged in
And nothing on the other end
There was no mixing board there were lip syncing entirely
It was there was just mining to the track
That of course is complete deception
Now it's not like we don't know that anymore
But it is it's inherent to the medium
Why? Well, it's very expensive to get a great sound for a band live
Particularly if you have a 45-minute program once a week
And you have to shove 809 artists onto a stage
I mean it's a huge cost huge production
Absolutely no budget
And of course the artists and the record companies
Complicit in this whole affair because they stood up there and they faked right along
And this is just one tiny example
I can give you millions of examples of how television
Deceives the viewers all the time
Please go take the XNTV experiment
You will not be disappointed it will open your eyes
It will give you a complete red pill moment
I guarantee you
But right now we're starting to
Collectively lick the red pill
We're starting to figure out what's going on
And there's a number of reasons for it
And I think that if we all
Really focus on this
And we start the wave roll in here because the BBC
You know it's like
All right the curtain is open
The underpants are down
The bear bottom of the trust is showing
This is going on everywhere
It's going on in commercial television
You don't hear a lot of people weighing in
About this deception of viewers in the United States
I'm telling you
Network executives are pooping their pants right now
They don't want any of this
Eki stuff spilling over to them in the US
We have to do it
We have to expose them
It's part of our revolution
Now not saying that there's no deception going on
In online television and radio and podcast
Independent media
I can only speak for myself
You know I'm full of shit
You know what my mode of stars
You know what I want to do
I'm not trying to hide behind anything
And I'm not taking money from you on an annual basis
Pretending that I'm giving you fair and balanced television
Production
So this is really coming to a head
Last night on News Night a big news talk program
Here in the United Kingdom
Of course they had a lengthy interview with
The chairman of the trust
Of the BBC who was
His position of course is being questioned
Should he resign or not
And then they go into a conversation
A live on air
Luckily
Between Michael Gray
Who used to be
The keeper of the trust of the BBC
And is now the head of ITV
In the UK commercial
Commercial network of stations
Of channels
And David Cox
Long time television producer
Who pulls no punches
And says some beautiful things
So beautiful
I wanted to just play him for you today
It's about eight minutes
And total I'm going to give commentary
And I'm going to show you
What's happening
With a little bit of Mark Thompson
Talking about just the tail end of his interview
Talking about the trust of the BBC
And what he's trying to do to contain this
But trust me
These guys are trying to cover up everything
Because every single program
Everything you see
Has deception and trickery in it
Because it's part of the medium
I think the way to judge me
The way to judge
The whole leadership of the BBC
Is how we react to those mistakes
And whether if we discover weaknesses in our system
We put things in place to reduce
Or eliminate those weaknesses entirely
That's what we're going to do
And I will be judged
The BBC Trust have made it very clear today
To me today
That they will judge me
And they'll judge my colleagues
On our success
In
Taking this utterly seriously
Which I assure you we do
But then over the coming months
Everything all the steps in place to make sure
That these instances
Either never happen again
Which of course is the ideal
Or that the chances of them happening
Is reduced to absolutely a small
Is it humanly can be?
Do you accept that the
The BBC license fee is based
On trust from the British public
And tonight many people
Will be saying why should we trust the BBC
Great, great, great question
Everyone who pays the license fee
Within the sound of my voice
You should be prepared to really cause a
Shitstorm about this
I believe that in these instances
We let the public down very badly
What I would say is I hope that the public
Would also recognise
That what we've done today
And what we've done over the last few months
Is trying to be very open and honest
About this issue
Both about the fact that it exists
To explore
I think more thoroughly than in the other blockers
I'm aware of exactly how
How to extend this problem
Is how widespread it is
And also that we are totally committed
To putting this right
And in this respect
Fully winning back their confidence
Thank you very much
Okay, okay
So
Cover up
They sure they've been totally open
That was the only list that is available
The list that I just read to you
And that's over a course of like
A year and a two years
They come up with seven instances
Of some deception going on
And that's just about
Staff members stepping in
To cover up because their competition
Sucked or didn't work or broke or they couldn't find
Any sexy winners
Oh man, let me tell you
On the radio
Huh
How many Z100 in New York
W HTZ
Shut up
I'm in the middle of a fantastic thing here
W HTZ in New York
Number one radio station
When I did a weekend shift there
During the
On was at mid 90s
No, early 90s I think
Yeah, late 80s early 90s
We would have
Contest winners
And here's how it would work
It would be collar 100
Right now
On the toll free lines
One hundred two four two zero
One hundred I even remember the number
If you can if you can believe that
It's a clear channel station by the way clear channel
Those guys
And and the instruction
To the phone ops
Who literally would sit there and go
Z100 or call number ones
Z100 or call number two
And they would go that way
Up until they hit one hundred
But they would never say one hundred
At ninety nine
They would wait
And the collar that called in
They would they were trained to listen to their voice
This person had to be someone who was going to be excited
Sometimes the DJ would even say
Make sure it's a girl
And if the collar was collar number one hundred
Was not did not fit the profile
The phone op was trained to say
Z100 or call number ninety nine
Try again later
So you might have five or six people who are call number ninety nine
Until they found one that fit the profile
That person was then collar one hundred
Complete deception this happens all the time
And mainstream media
Now of course as you know for my own personal view point
I love putting the fuck up people on the air
I love people who have speech impediments
And and and weird accents
And because it's human is beautiful
I love it that's a big part of what motivates me
So now onto the interview Michael Grayd
pompous ass
I wish you could see the pictures
Is going to tell you that this is because of market pressure
And bullshit bullshit
What happens
And this is this is worldwide
Production staff
For I'm just going to talk about television in this case
Our kids the kids
You know they have no training
They'll be paying shit because they'll do anything
You know the blow anybody to work in
Quote television being show business
They're really cheap this is how big profits are made
And that's systematic
It's systemic it's inherent to the way the business works
You know we've got to pay Jonathan Ross eight million pounds
You know so we got to make up for that somewhere
By the way when I went to university
I studied broadcasting communications
And there's two things that really got drilled into your mind
Now this was 81
I believe 82 or something like that
And one is equal airtime
Which of course
When is the last time you heard any talk show
Or watch any talk show where there was equal airtime
For both sides of a political debate
Well of course that isn't true anymore
Go listen to Rush Limbaugh
Where's the other side
So somehow that is just that rule that
Regulation has just been thrown overboard
It pops up once in a while and you know people talk about it
Say well you know there's just no way we can't do it
All right
And then there was the infamous case of the 64,000 dollar question
There's been books written about this movies
Remaid movies about it
And that was all about this deception
Where you could not have a game show
That had a contest knew had the fricking answers up front
Just to draw in huge ratings
It was deemed illegal
This regulations about that
It goes on all the time my friends
So Michael Grayd
Who used to work at the BBC is now going to be a real pompous
And say oh is market pressure
And then I want you listen very closely
To a David Cox says
David Cox long time television producer
I have a huge amount of respect for the guy
Listen to what he says about television
And listen to what he says about
His working with David Grayd
The man who was right there saying that
Oh this is something of the last couple of years
That 30 years ago
David Cox and Michael Grayd were deceiving the public together
Well for some perspective on why this has happened
I'm joined by Michael Grayd currently head of ITV
And formally chairman of the BBC's Board of Governors
And David Cox, a TV producer and writer
Who formally edited a weekend world
Do you understand why this has happened
I mean why some producers think it's all right to line this way
No, I can't say I do exactly
I think it's partly to do with casualisation
Of the industry
People on short term contracts
100 tremendous strain
tremendous pressure
Competitive pressure is enormous
Exactly what the BBC is not supposed to have
Is competitive pressure
And I think the culture has
You know this is clearly an epidemic
And it's not just the BBC that's got the problem
I mean I think every broadcaster has got this problem
So are you looking at
We are waiting for Deloitte to deliver there
Their report on our
Premium phone line problem
So listen to this
The guy is actually bringing Deloitte and Toosh to investigate
Deloitte and Toosh are the people who actually put the pay lines in place
A different division of Deloitte and Toosh
Actually has all these SMS text divisions
It's like
Sorry for got to mention that
So Deloitte and Toosh are basically investigating themselves
In a way
I don't know what's in it
But I don't expect to be
Particularly happy about what I'm going to read
But I don't know what's in it
You know I'm just thinking
Have you ever seen those competitions on television
Where they have the accountants come in with the briefcase
And here's the sealed bid
And oh yes
This has been protected
And we have the results
You know how that doesn't happen anymore
How you don't see those guys
You know like when there's a public vote for
Pop idol or American Idol
Or dancing with the stars
The no longer does that happen
Where the guy says okay
It's all protected
And our seal of approval
You know why?
Because they're in the fucking game with them
That's why
Um
This precise reason is why
As the why this is spread
Quite as badly as this across all broadcasts
Not just the BBC
Is it is a function of that pressure
It's a function of short-term contracts
It's a function of lack of training
I just I'm at a loss really to understand
Oh man
This is so beautiful
It's like the nose is growing
I think you have a sense of why this is going on
Why do effects
Okay, so now we go to David Cox
Listen to what he has to say
The same Michael Reds saying all broadcasts
There's one way or another
Well, I'm not surprised
Mark Thompson says he is
That dishonesty has been discovered in television
And I don't feel the need that Michael clearly feels
And Mark is well
To blame the whole thing on some strange short-term factors
And some suddenly have come into play and changed everything
When the industry was once pure and now suddenly it isn't
I think the reality is that television has always
And way had a culture of deception within it
It's in the nature of what it does
Almost everything on television is a
Confection of some kind or other
This isn't really true of other activities
But what television producers have been doing all the time
When they're preparing a documentary
The editing footage
To produce effects that aren't quite
A raw material justifies
Reality shows up here and you learn subsequently
That what's happened has been fixed
Drama docs appear
And what they do is they convert the complexities of real life
Into her heroic dramas
With heroes and unfortunate villains
But this is a little bit of a screen look
As if she's walking out of a room
And she actually was walking into the room
They didn't do that
Was that prevalent?
Well, I think that if you live in this world
Where fake careers part of what you do
The borderline between what's reality
And what's fake
It becomes very blurred
And it shifts it shifts
Especially when you're under pressure
And it's not just nowadays that television people are under pressure
They've always been under colossal pressure
And faced with the problem
That you've got to get your program finish
You've got to get your program out
The temptation always is
To push that borderline a little bit further
And that's what happened with the queen
But it is it worse now because
In your view because
Do you hear what the man is saying
This is a long time television producer
And I just got to applaud this guy
For being completely open and honest
And saying what is?
And he's not ashamed
Which he shouldn't have to be
But by Gali, let's not pretend
Let's not cover this up people
To take the specific case of the BBC
The BBC is trying to do too much
And therefore it's inevitable
If you have much more quantity
You will have much
Ah, I can't wait until you hear what he says about Michael Greed
Perhaps a dilution of quality
And you wouldn't have the editorial control
She had when there's only a couple channels
Now it is hard
The editorial lines of Quran
Quite long these days
Particularly with an independent sector
Although you cannot lay the blame for this
And Tali on the independent sector
Because a lot of these things are in house
BBC problems anyway
But the talent moves around
They don't love them on short
The talent moves around
Because you pay them shit
You pay them shit
And they're completely indispensable
In country
When you want to do that, give them short-term contracts
So here's the reason why
You have a television program
You have people working on it
What happens if the show
All of a sudden fails
Or has to be taken off the air
You're left with the staff of 30 to 50
Maybe even 100 people
You don't want those long-term contracts
That you can't get out of
That's why everyone in television
Is freelance
So you can fire them
When the show goes off the air
Or the season ends
It's how it works
Don't give me this shit
That is part of something new
Of the past couple of years
Term contracts
It is the pressure
Yes there's always been temptation
I agree with David
The temptation is always there
But I agree with you
You're successful in the past
Resisting that temptation
Somehow the pressures were less
Yes there's pressure of course there is
But the skills and the crafts
That go into making television programs
Are now being used
To cross a line
There is a line of deceit
Deliberate intent
To deceive
And that's a line
That I have never seen cross before
If that's true
Can you put Humpty Dumpty together again
Okay so
He says that this is something
Just of the past few years
And I just gave you a couple of examples
From my own experience
From 25 years ago
It has been going on forever
And it's unraveling
Before our very eyes
It's very very important
That we pay attention to this
And use this
Because the spectacle has now turned
On to the media itself
Where the media
Typically
Creates the spectacle about someone else
Now the spectacle is on itself
And because of all the competition
You're going to see
Everybody
All these stations
Going to be killing each other
And we have to feed the beast
My friends
If we want to make independent media
Interesting
And compelling for people
As an alternative
To what they're being spoon fed
And what they're now finding out
Is a bunch of lies
And trickery
And crap
We have to propel this
We've got to throw gas on the fire
The public quite right
They are going to be very skeptical
Everything
They see on television
Now can you rebuild that degree of trust
With all television channels
But particularly the BBC
You depend on public trust
Otherwise there would be many money
Oh and this is so incredibly important
This is why it's a big deal
Because the politicians
Politics knows
They know
That if the people don't trust the media
Then that is their vehicle
That's how politicians communicate
Then people will not trust them
So this is going to be a huge issue
It's going to be so big
Television is going to get incredibly
Boring
Well actually I believe this will happen
I think it's a matter of culture
And I think it goes back a long way
And Michael I worked for you 30 years ago
And we used to get up all kinds of stuff
And don't pretend
You don't go about it
I don't think I will
But
Okay
Did you just hear what happened
This producer said Michael
You guy
Formerly boss of BBC
I presume when he was the boss of the BBC
Of the chairman of the Board of Governors
Or whatever
We deceived the public
He said it right there
Then the freaking news night interview
He was saying
Well you could told us about that
Then of course David Cox
I think wisely says
Well I'm not going to go into it right now
But
Where's the follow-up interview
I believe he has to tell us
If Michael Grade was involved in deception
When he was at the BBC
That needs to come out
And I'm going to make a call out to everybody
And I know there's producers who listen to this show
I know that there are people who've been in audiences
Of programs, television and radio
All mainstream
Listen to the show
I want you to blow the whistle
I want you to call in
I want you to tell me what happened
And we're going to publicize this
This can be a huge deal
Particularly
If this happened to you
In the United States
We have to fan the flames
This is part of the revolution
If you really give a shit about what we're doing
About independent media
An alternative
And something that certainly has more chance
Of being more transparent
Has less ulterior motives
Than mainstream media
It is your duty to come forward
You can do it anonymously
Of course
The truth is that culture is changed
And they change very fast
And they change in the face of dramatic events
I mean smoking
Was something that was part of the culture
Almost overnight
It's become unacceptable
And I think today's events
In themselves will be sufficient
To change everything
In the television industry
And people in the industry
Will have to start treating the viewers
Straight in the way that they haven't in the past
It's going to happen
And it won't happen
Because the BBC's guidelines will get much thicker
Which of course they will
It will happen
Because everybody working
In any part of the industry
Will just know things have changed
They've been rumbled
And they've got to change their ways
In crises like this
So
Now standby
Because he's going to tell you
Why it's unraveling
And why the BBC no one
That ABC NBC CBS CNN
The Fox News BBC ITV
No one can stop it
Because the genius out of the battle
With horror stories
Like today's story
And others that know that
Will come out and stuff
We've seen before
From Channel 4, Channel 5
And our ITV
You will only restore public trust
Through the means by which you handle
The affair
The BBC Trust today
As behaved impeccably
As it was meant to do
I think the honesty and the open
And prompt disclosure
By the BBC of the problems
They found
Will do much
To repair
Public trust
But it's quite clear
From what Mark Thompson said
That he knows he has to deliver
Within a few months
Quite likely
Of course
And we're all trying to handle this
Are you partners
As open and transparent
A manor as possible
It's the only way
That you will quickly restore
Public trust in broadcasting
Which is crucial for
Have you asked your staff to come up with
Yes indeed
They are feeding it
We've got a whistle blowing line
They've got a drive
The only whistle blowing line
You need to know
Or the ones you know at the call
That's right
If you're in the States
And you know of some trickery
Or fraud on mainstream media
You've got to let us know
And the UK
Here's your number
Number
The BBC All Broadcasts could do is just open up everything and say this is how we make television programs.
This is a genuine bit of a concoction as you put it earlier and this is a confection and this isn't.
Yes, I think that's going to happen, but partly it's happening because the viewers are working it all out for themselves.
They're much more aware of how the business works and they used to be.
They look on YouTube and see the inner workings of everything and the viewers are going to make this happen.
The pieces should do nothing that they don't want to read about in the newspapers tomorrow.
There you go.
Do nothing you don't want to read about in the newspapers tomorrow.
You pussies.
Excuse me.
Oh, man, I'm riled up about this.
So, I want to expose all of this and you know what?
I'll come up with a million more examples from my own world.
No problem.
Geez, Louise.
You know, MTV.
Oh, yeah, we've done so much trickery, so much deception.
All in the under the guise of well, that's entertainment.
That show business.
Oh, I'm all right.
I need to just relax for a second.
I don't think I'm going to do anything else on today's show.
But let's just find lies with some good jersey vibes from the Hesh.
Here's your Todd Nyer notes about this guy.
So I'm like a country by Hesh, but I'm in at the side at a time that sounds.
As students come to the can and join and we'll never turn and back.
You know the past that died to me in Jerusalem.
You know, just a show that I'm playing throughout the world.
You know, you know, you shouldn't say anything.
Oh, I don't know where they came in.
You know, there's a moment and if they're our first discovery,
you'll have great battles showing what's up.
You've been told to sing this way.
Who's the only stress and fear it's always on yet your heart ain't strong.
Through your sins and wilders and extreme badms,
when they know what they're tall,
we can speak and shoot to me whenever I say.
When I'm not going to tell you, it's through the same day.
You've been so surprised to know that I'm playing throughout the world.
You've been saying that.
I tell you, so long you won't say,
it was my favorite.
I know, I'm not a father yet.
You show me that you've lost the things that feel.
You show me the moment and you'll be there.
Yet you won't feel this is what never happened in your days.
I couldn't understand why I was such damn shame.
Came isn't backward, desprs respect them and banch the specializzoned back yard.
I think nothing is on, better crash if it re varied.
Oh I have beenasing me about some cartoonish and lame.
Is love starting it's way more happening amusing he may when I know that he rose because I'm,
I think there's the album for me, it's gone so I'll give you reason
To tell you something about it, I'll take it on the road
Wait, stop it for the shoes and get it
It's the way I've never dreamed of something like that
There's miss and love who's ever come on here and they say
It's rock and roll, promises have all faded away
I used to believe I still wanted to believe
But it might already sound damn hard
I still didn't know how it was when I never imagined it
I went to the bars and it backs, we just didn't do it
I fall up there, there's nothing to say
It's been looking for him, passing out
I still rang it, they're finally in the mirror
I waited so long, I said, thanks for the reason
You didn't move so fast
Show me your heart, you're kidding, that's a strong
Something that you raised me
Bruce
Oh man, this guy is good
He gives me the same vibe, Bruce gives me
The fourth instance of our Springsteen guy straight
Southside Johnny, oh crap, what's up with that?
It just ends like that, probably flows through on the album
Alright, so I'm just going to leave it at that for today
Because I've said enough, I'm counting on you guys
To call in, give me, I'll give you another one
Do you know the program TRL, TRL live?
Which the predecessor to that was total request live?
The predecessor to that was something called dial MTV
Every single day, weekday afternoon between
I think it was six and six, 30 or five, 30 and six
I hosted a program called dial MTV, phone lines are open
One, 800 dial MTV, all you have to do is call in
And vote for your favorite video
And you know what happened?
No, what happened?
The list would come down from some magic call center
Go to the office, to the programming department
And then we'll come down to us
So those of you who really got sick of seeing new kids on the block
Which by the way, I like the new kids on the block
I just want to set the record straight
But you know what's seconding, every single day
They were like number one, they would literally change
The number one video to something else
They would lie because they were sick and tired
And then people were calling up and saying stop playing new kids on the block
They would do that, they had nothing to do with the voting
So if you've witnessed this, it is your duty
You got to do some duty, it is your duty
To call in and tell me about the deception you were involved in
I promise you I'll protect your identity if you want to do it
Anonymously, but it's even better if you'll come forward
And you probably probably more people were victim
And just involved in it and not actually the mastermind of it
This is our chance that's a crack in the armor
Let's really really make them bleed
Because we can show the world that there is an alternative
They're ready, they're starting to lick that red pill
Let's push him
DailySourceco.com, Adam at podshow.com
Tomorrow we'll do some cheddar
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear