A Domain Registration is a gift that keeps on giving for all the geeks in your life.
With your shy hit GoDaddy.com.
Listen to this podcast for a special code that you can use to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Hey you Adam, it's Tony from your neighborhood.
First thing, since you're in New York, maybe you can swing by New Jersey.
Come out to the old stop and grounds and record the DSC 563.
You know, hang out with the fellas, you know.
Learning and oddy, sharing, and talk about hot moms.
How about Cecilia?
Yeah.
So the one out to the DSC 563 from the old stop and grounds in Jersey.
After all, your voicemail numbers are Jersey number.
Come on home, Adam, do 563 at home.
No one wants to say in.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm destined to be its pet and courage.
You've had your heart aches.
No! No! No! No! No! No!
I don't know who this is but,
I'm fucking cold, you're down to ammo.
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
She got to get me up, she got a little more sick.
She got to find his glass.
You ever seen, she got to get out sweet.
I want to go, she's still your heart.
So tell you that she'll come.
As you tell you realize that she'll be gone.
You know she's the kind of girl you're gone.
And take it all, she's real.
She got to get her, she got a little more.
She got to prove it looks, she gets it up to you.
She got sexy walk, girl who is legs.
Don't hate your talk, she must be your bitch.
She must tell you that she'll come.
As you tell you realize that she'll be gone.
You know she's the kind of girl you're gone.
And take it all, she's real.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Oh, he is baby.
She's just like Barbie.
Here we go
Play that hooky music baby, play that hooky shit
Play that hooky music baby, I'm getting off on it
You're a game
It's a home
Yes you are
You're so sexy
Beautiful
I'm sharing
She got a caveat
She got a little more to go
She got a body stance
You ever seen it
She got a bit of a swing
I'll make it more
She's still your heart
Come back home
She'll tell you that she'll come home
She's not the kind of girl you're gonna
Take it home
To your world
She's not
Don't just hear it Charlie
Five, six, three
Full bar Friday
How you doing everybody
Delphinium blue
Kicking off today's
Full bar festivities
With beautiful
Different
But listening to his tracks
On the pot's a music network
I was like, oh guys, it's got some of my like it
I don't know what it is
I think I played California
Another track by his
A couple of months ago
Not very appropriate of course
When your show is coming from New York City
And I just realized that on average
Except for yesterday and Monday of course
When there was no show
Because just absolutely impossible
For me to record anything
It's been that
Filmed that jam packed
But I realized that I talked to you guys
More than I talked to my wife
I spoke to Patricia for 10 minutes today
That was and that was at like six o'clock
And we still had two more meetings to go
So yeah
Really is a real football Friday for me
And of course when I say
I spoke to Patricia today at six o'clock
It is Friday
It's 1245 AM
So it is officially the 16th of March
2007, but of course this is being produced for your
Enjoyment on Thursday evening
The day started off really, really fucked up and said
I got an email early in the morning
That could friend of mine
That is a dad at a past away
And it just fucking sucked
It was no way to start the day
I could consider it a little bit
Of course having lost my mom recently
Also friend of runs
And runs that past away a couple of years ago
So you know stuff kind of creeps up on you
You start to think about things again
And so on the one hand
Well completely sad
In his honor
I really felt like enjoying life today
And everything I did I did with passion
And really enjoyed it
Even though
I'm tired and full barred
It felt good
You know it's really enjoying what was going on
And almost a perfect day
The weather wasn't quite as nice as yesterday
When it was sunshine
I mean
New York in that nice kind of spring
Spring weather
Oh man
That's really nice
So even started to drizzle
Mid afternoon
But
So much
I don't even know where to start really
You know what?
Maybe let's do this
I'll tell you what
Why don't we get things started
Freshen up just a little bit with
Some exercise
Or should I say
Oh yeah
Maybe nothing like being on the road
And working on my ass
Maybe max
Hey Adam
Good morning
Afternoon or evening
Have a great time
We're recording today
It doesn't matter
Because it's time to exercise
I'm ready to exercise
We're on the floor today
So do you need to do to get yourself situated
Oh I love being on the floor with you Amy
Okay
This is an ad move
But it definitely works the butt
Okay
I'm ready
Lay down on your back
Alright
Arms to your side
Now legs up to the ceiling
They should be 90 degrees to you
Oh man
That's like
Lower them toward the ground
But only as far as you can
Stretching your back
It's very important to protect that back
Okay
Of course you're squeezing the butt
Yes
Now bring them back up to 90 degrees
Squeeze the abs
Lift the butt toward the ceiling
Yes I feel it
Come back down slowly
And lower the legs again
That's one
You have seven more to go
Oh you're kidding me
These are tough
Lift
Squeeze
Lower
Lift
Squeeze
Oh
Lower
Lift
Squeeze
Don't hold your breath
Squeeze my butt
Amy
Good
Use the arms for balance
Yeah
Okay
Keep those legs straight
But not locked
Give a damn
I can hardly keep you straight
Keep breathing
So stiff
Fantastic
Looks like my work here is done
This is Amy Mac and until next time
I'm just like
Oh man
And it's land nasty laying on a hotel carpet
Don't you know what I mean?
God man, hotel carpet
It's like creep me out
I have like hotel rooms
To do it to have like wood floors
And you know I will not walk
With wet feet on a hotel carpet
Okay
I mean if I can if I can avoid it
I won't walk with bare feet at all
Um
And this is I didn't see any slippers
So I just been wearing my socks
And the bathroom but no slippers
So
Anyway
Tomorrow
Visit to Sirius sideline radio
To see the folks at HQ
Hopefully get some dirt on the mergers
So I'll let you know
Here the New York sounds out there
And of course I'll be leaving tomorrow
Evening flying back to
Back to the UK
And well the expecting snowstorm
Is not convenient
It's three to six inches in New York
The sun's so bad
Ah
We'll see
Luckily
New York knows about it in time
But you'll see people are going to
Well maybe you actually
Maybe a lot of people won't come in and on
We'll just take a long weekend
That will be kind of nice
Because then the city won't be crazy
And we can kind of get out on time
And that will be cool
Let me see
What can I tell you about
Just wrapping up the week
It's almost like I'm talking to Patricia
I could tell you all the stuff that we've been doing
But you know it's like business stuff
Literally did not do anything
Except last night
Ron is wife Marta
And I went out for dinner
And we found this place called
Django's
Which is not far from the hotel
And we had really nice meal
It was really really awesome
What was it?
I had
The
Dorey
That's what I had
And we had some really nice wine
You know we took our time
And we didn't talk about anything
Which meant we were kind of silent for most
Most of the evening
Because we're old white guys
Manly get tired from this shit
But it was a lot of fun hanging out with
With the sales weasels
In New York
So we had of course Chris
And head sales weasel
And sales weasel Greg
And then we have
Jersey sales weasel Andrew
And you know these are the guys that are out there
Making it happen you know
Connecting the dots
You know the advertising
It doesn't happen automatically
Because you know we're not like a Google
We don't you know just
Insert stuff
Randomly or seemingly
It's some kind of relevance
You know we're working on brand advertisers
And that means we're you know
We're talking to
Advertising agencies
And advertisers clients directly
Who are
You know they they want their brand represented properly
They don't just want to be inserted in anything
Or have you know like be a
A banner next to a dating site on a huge social network
You know they want to be
They want their brand recognition within
Really with the audiences
And I think we're getting through to them
And creating content
You know and don't just create an ad
Make content
And it's fucking useful
And you know so
It's I have to say that really does kind of turn me on
You know to be working with people really hard
And trying to get stuff going and
And close deals and help people understand
What our vision is for how
We believe this can work and how
You know and showing the examples of how it has been working
And it's been a very very successful trip
I mean we work really hard
But it well worth it
And it's really cool when like you know
We can close a deal while we're
While we're doing this on the road
You know or at least for us on the road for the guys
And you know it's their home it's their home turf
And we got
I don't know I don't know if I can say it
But I will anyway
So we
We close a deal with cover girl
Cover girl cosmetics
I'm very excited about that
For a number of reasons one
Because it's you know that's prestige
And it's and they have
Really they have extremely good content ideas
For people who will be interested in their product
So they're not going to just be doing some kind of
Positioning beautiful girl running
Running around through a video podcast
You know that we've got a real plan
Where they're going to be creating
Content that's relevant to their customers
So I'm excited about that
Also you know the amount of people involved
And putting this together
It's pretty unique because
Cover girl is a proctor and gamble
From the proctor and gamble company
And they don't mess around
Proctor and gamble very very sophisticated
Company
They have very you know the way that company works
You know it's a regimen
It's it's I'd have to say
In a way
It wouldn't be fair to compare them to Walmart
But they do you know there is a strict regimen
Let's put it that way
You I think when you when you arrive at proctor and gamble
The first thing you learn is how to write memos at proctor and gamble
So really cool that we could
That we can get them on board
And then two agencies media vesta
Is involved and grey advertising
And you know it's I'm excited about it
Very very excited
And that's all I can say right now
Meanwhile we have
Richard Brewer hey who of course was with me in North Carolina
He went from North Carolina after hanging out for another day
Meeting people there which you know I told you that was a lot
A lot of fun and very cool
He went to
Taxis for South by Southwest
A company
Michael Butler the rock and roll geek
And it's interesting because you know my email is I'm still
The email is still popping over
From the Gmail from my original account
It's I think it's going to take like three weeks for these four gigabytes
To be transferred towards South stupid
So you know my email is a little bit messed up
And Richard sends me an email and then he sends me another
Like they came in the wrong order so I didn't quite get it at
It was an update and then he said I'm also
Sending this I'm also calling this in into the voice mail line
And I presume that he meant that this was for the show
Doesn't matter really because as I was listening to it
I'm like this is really interesting if more people from pod show would
Call in to my to the voice mail number and
Hold on a second the voice mail number
And if they could do it just the way I'm hearing Michael
Sorry Michael Michael and Richard do it
It's actually it's I think it's pretty entertaining
So they're basically giving me an update a pretty personal update I have to say
And you know and it's not like they're not announcing stuff that you're saying
Hey this is what we're working on here so we met with
And I was like you know why wouldn't I play this this is really interesting
So um
Check it out
This is the behind the iron curtain of the death star
Hey Adam it's Richard calling from Austin Texas
The I have no idea how the quality of this is going to come out
But just one of the call and let you know that the beer belly tool continues
I have taken my belly now from Wilmington North Carolina
It's Austin Texas for the staff by Southwest Festival
The belly he's now joined by the Butler he's now he's making his bed as I speak
I can't roll
We're in the hotel room here in Austin
Butler's like spinal tap making his bed going
Rock and roll
We just got done with our first big meeting of the week
Michael got a meeting with Jeffrey and Jacqueline from the orchid
Right on which is huge
The world's leading digital distributor of music
With a very good name Michael was pushing the
We wanted to get access to the back catalog
And they seemed very receptive to that so that was very good news
You hear this these guys are out there trying to get more pod save music onto the network
I'm really this is so incredibly cool and this is you know a big part of what Michael Butler does
Um, you know people know about it maybe but it means a real job, you know
He's really working hard on this and
Hard on
I said hard on and I took talking about the need for more hit-up
Which they were very receptive to too
In fact, it was a very productive meeting. We have a very good meeting with them
We're dinner it was about two hours long
And we just wanted to let you know that we think we're going to have a lot more music
I feel like I'm I should be stroking my white pussy cat right now, you know
I'm in command central and everyone's reporting back to me
The network's from them. We already got two loves
We should check out
And who else did they give us Michael
Um, what about that?
You just ran you happy so I think you've already played on your shop
Yep
Yeah, they give us a bunch more stuff right after this is over
A bunch man
A bunch of people
So as you can tell from Michael there's a bunch of stuff out there
I don't know
When you're a daily reports from South Pacific, South West
Excellent
It's going to be of this high quality which we're leaving it now
So this is why you're on your show
So you don't play it on your show
And the breadlets sign up
Hopefully I'm in front of New York
Don't play it on your show
That's what you think
So I would have played that for you yesterday
Um, and they did call in with the second report
And since I don't have a show for the weekend
I'm going to play the second report too because it really gets beautiful
What these guys are doing
Um, oh, and we have another sponsor
Uh, of the network Tylenol PM
And they're sponsoring a show by Angie B
Of course you know Angie with her dulce tones
Uh, she's, you know I'm secretly in low with Angie
But don't tell her
Um, the show is called unwind
And let me just get the, uh, we get this cool little
Briefing, oops, anyone who participates in the campaign
Get some briefing, just open that up for you
Because it had some cool things in there that I wanted to say
So I was talking to Ron about Tylenol PM
And he actually uses it
I don't see, I don't have any problems sleeping
Um, I have accent pains
Um, because that's, I guess that's just what happens
What you hit forward over 40
But I have no problem sleeping and we all know why
Um, so, but I will try it
Now, we'll definitely try it, Ron takes it
Because it's just hard for him to go to sleep
I guess, I don't understand why really
Um, and sales Weasel Greg
I was in, we were in the cab on the way to, on the way to cover girl
Actually, I said, uh, and my neck hurts because yeah, I do get neck pain
I guess because in New York this week has in a way been a pain
You know, neck literally
So you got any aspirin, I figured Greg have, have aspirin
And he has like a bottle and I pull too odd
She says, no, no, don't take those those are blue
Oh, you're right, that's the Tylenol PM
We don't want to take those before the meeting
Uh, because apparently they do work quite well
They relieve pain and sleeplessness
Uh, what does it, here you go
Effective relief from pain and sleeplessness
That is non-habit forming and won't have you groggy in the morning
Right on
So I am going to try those out
And I know someone else who is going to love them
Patricia will love them
Um, because she, um, sometimes she has trouble getting to sleep
And she's a very light sleeper
So I, I think she wouldn't mind
Seeing if that would work for her
She tried all kinds of stuff
Um, in the past
So, and, and now, initial have to come on the show
Because she's, she's got endorsed the product
Oh man, speaking of that
You got to listen to this feedback
This is awesome, this is a total awesome comment for Fubar Friday
Check it out
Graham
Fully
Great, and all fuck
No queer
A queer
It's been a while since we had a chat
Hello mate
You will recall how the dough has shitting jolly
Fucked up my life
And how it was that gave you so much joy
I don't remember how it fucked up your life
I wish you would have reminded me
But it doesn't matter because the rest of the comment is brilliant
You won't, girl
Thank you
But I don't get angry anymore
I'm freshly at a rehab
So instead, I make little lists
Of all the shit you want me to do
That I ain't gonna fucking do
And I've been saving a few up
Anya they are
Number one
I don't give a flying fuck what your house is called
Because we all know
And ain't really your house
A brain to your act, my son
Is your message
Jets off to Holland on a Monday morning
Does it better dance in
Better duck in
Better dive in
Get some boots
And get some bit of a bun from the old restaurant
The royal east
And then flies back home on a Friday night
To Patricia's Pita tear
If you're a Pita tear
I'm telling you
And when I get back home
On Saturday
The next day she leaves
She's gonna do the exact same thing
A little fashion show
Jett off to Holland
Threads and beads
Come on back
To Patricia's Pita tear
Are you right my friend?
Number two
I don't need
Another fucking domain name
All right son
In fact, the only time I want to wear the words
Go Daddy
Is when me house boy Juan
He's naked
And laying across the dining table
Three
I don't
I got us
I got to send that one to go Daddy
They'll enjoy that as an endorsement
He fucking sugar
All right
I don't take fucking for
Trinity
Free train
That would have been a splendor mention
But you forgot that part
And it is not free train
Who gives a flying fuck
You can grab in its tank
You can shit on its seats
Cool like here
You can piss in the washable
I've only got one suggestion about Trinity's son
Swan
Vesta
Swan Vesta
Number six
Do you think you could possibly use your influence
New York contact
To have Eric Bergen come around and come on my face
H-U
H-U show
Keep it up son
Folder
I don't know
Let's ask his mom
Hey Adam
This is Alice and Lee
Calling in from www.craftcats.com
And I just have to let you know
After playing my voicemail comment on your show
The other day
How many men rode in
Wanting to help me out
With my my coming problem
As you can hear
It's fixed
No it's not
So there you go
Shivori is alive and well on the internet
So thanks again Adam
And you know what darling
Your show rocks
We got it
You got to stop giving me humbers like that
Okay
It's an outrage
A serious satellite listeners
Thanks for checking us out once again
We back next week in the PCH's next
I guess
Hi
Adam
Says Eugene
My friends at the ten minute blitz pod cast
I'm going to be celebrating their 100th episode next week
And I'm working on assembling messages
And congratulations to air on their 100th episode
I know you are so busy in New York right now
But can you please record a short
30 seconds max
Short 30 seconds max
Congratulations
Or greeting for them by Thursday afternoon
Oops
And send it to me
If you don't have time for that
Could you make a mention on your next
DSC episode
I will clip it out from there
I know they'll get a thrill from hearing from you
And re-jordan and billiard
All teens who take their pod casting seriously
And you are one of the inspirations
I'll thank you Eugene
So that's ten minute blitz dot pod show dot com
That's cool
Ten as in a number ten minute blitz
BLITZ dot pod show dot com
100 episodes
Crap
I got to listen to that show
Excellent
That's nice
Thank you very much
You know we should probably
Start disregarding 100s of milestone though
I'll tell you why
It's not that you know I don't believe in the milestones
It's not cool to celebrate that
But the morning I was watching
Is it the today show
What's Willard Scott on?
You know because I'm up so early
Or was up so early that
Yeah
I keep watching all the morning shows
Whatever Willard Scott's on
It's sponsored by Zuckers
I know that
I think that segment's been sponsored for
A million years by Zuckers
Jam
So you know I remember Willard Scott
And you know he would always congratulate
People who were celebrating their birthday
And the birthday was pretty much like a hundred years old
You know it was like pop-pap-pap-pap-pap
Fanfare still reads the newspaper without our glasses
You know Granny Annie from Florida
And it was amazed
Because a lot of these birthdays
We know these people were celebrating
And you know you look at the picture
And I don't know if the pictures are current
But you know they look pretty good
As like wow that's pretty fucking space age
You know
That I can remember when people just
It seems like we're living 10 years longer
So maybe
50 is the new 40
And 40 is the new 30
Ah
Now if only I can convince Angelina Jolie that that's true
When I meet her
Next month
Over the course of 19 weeks
One monster filled
Bloody audiobook
Rue to terrifying audience of 30,000 listeners
In the process
He became the number one literary show
One iTunes
And every other podcast chart
On April 1st
Scott Siddler's
Thrilling Hornevel
And Sester
Closet Wayne the Print
On April Fool's Day
Figure out your copy of ancestor
And Amazon.com
Or visit Scott Siddler.net
Kareki
Sound and good Scott
April 1st
Is what it drops
Excellent
Ah
Hey
Whenever old buddies calls in
And he thinks we can't tell who he is
Because he's calling in at any
Different state of mind
Adam
How you're doing?
So I'm back in London
You probably know who this is
By now no it's not James
Although people do often call me James
It's Charles the Drunk Londoner
Except is not drunk
I'm name wrong
Who knows why
So if I'm back in town
Haven't been in touch for a while
Been very busy
Haven't even updated my blog
And all that kind of geeky stuff
But
Trying to think that you were talking about today
Or yesterday or whatever show
I can't remember
But I'd love to have 500
You don't give a shit
You're far too busy and important
For me to bother counting what it is you do
So
Yeah
Of course I would
Usually save up lots of comments
And try and send in something
And usually do it when I'm drunk
And mess it a lot
By the way, that's not really handy
And you know how much I appreciate
You calling in Charles Drunk or not
But it's not handy
When you do a whole bunch of comments together
Because it's like then it's too long
And then you know
It just makes us sing
Just do one
If you don't mind
Probably to be concise
Okay
You were talking about current TV
Or what is your list
Yeah, okay, I understand at point
About a voting
There's some voting that
Yeah, it's lame
It's really old hat
And the big media players
Unfortunately don't seem to understand
What the revolution is all about
But you know what?
We've got to ease them in gently
And
And currently
Have got some
I was chatting with them
A few months back
And they've got some really exciting shit plan
It is going to be one to watch
It really is
And
There's some really excellent ways
Of utilizing
That space for
For marketing and promotion
And selling
We're not dissimilar from the way that you work
Don't get me wrong on that
I like a lot of things that current TV is doing
And of course
Now we're in the middle of a revolution
But
It's going to be such a long time
Before
We've really made mainstream media
Or it's influence
Because I like a lot of mainstream media
But in that regard
When it comes to reporting and news
And current affairs
It's going to take quite a while
Maybe ten, maybe 15 years
It's just going to take a while
You will see it progressing
Very quickly
So this is just a
A cog
Not a cog
It's just one piece of the machinery
And obviously
It's appreciated
But I personally think
That
We're better served doing it online
I don't know why I don't have any
I don't have any real
Well thought out theory
It's just a hunch
That's all just a hunch
I took my hat off to
It's kind of a bold move
I think
Although I have to say
It's yours with eating bolder
The sort of brazen
Hey look I like this
I like that
It's my own brazen
It's honest
And you know what
We will appreciate that
The other thing is
I want to say
What are your feelings about
I don't want to beat
By the hand of two people
I want to say
What are your feelings about
What's going on and by
Now
That's interesting
He says
I don't want to bite the hand
That feeds me
Slag off clients
Charles
What do you do man
You working for the man
You working for Viacun
Hmm
The other thing is I'm going to try and get through
It's real quick
I'll sound the tube
I'll just start working
Yeah
What do I think about Viacun
It's pretty interesting
I spoke to
Is it Abby Klassen
She's the digital reporter
For
Is it ad week
God
So stupid
I don't know
Too fried
Too footballard
Here
You know
What do I think
Oh my gosh
I think the most important thing
Is really
The copyright
Thing is pretty important
And I find it interesting
And I'm just really interested in what people are writing
And I'm amazed
How many people don't really understand
How copyright works
And also how many people don't understand
What kind of effort
And money goes into making something
Whether you're doing it by yourself
Or whether you're Viacun
Creating a show
It just feels like
People don't really understand
And how much work that is
And what kind of value that can have for yourself
And
Whether someone stealing it or not
Just understanding that
It's apparent that a lot of people don't quite get it
And also what type of rights there are
Particularly in mainstream
Right down to
Obviously
The actors
You know there
It's different rules
It's a whole different rules set
It's not just rules
But an infrastructure that's been in place for a long time
To drink something
I would like major league caught in mouth
Hold on
Once even starting to gross me out
Hearing it through the blue max
Personus
Compressor
Now where was I?
Unviacum
It's kind of interesting
I read a lot of people saying hey man
You know you've already made enough money
Viacum
What's your bullshit
You know the people wanted
Why don't you give it to us
And
You know
I think back to
When we made a rather stupid and embarrassing mistake
Of how we presented
RSS feeds when we first launched
Pot show plus and how everyone jumped on our shit
And you know calls us thieves
And shady and evil
And god knows what
Still some people are on about that
That's probably the whole
Reason why Keith and the girl hate me
Or hate pod show or whatever
At least I think that's what I understand
And
You know yet about YouTube
And or go to
And Google video
You know people are pretty laid back about that
Because they're enjoying the content
So
And I think it's
It isn't negotiating
Step
You know Google
It'll be settled
That's for sure
But it'll be interesting to see
You know what
What will be left of the
Of the intrinsic value I guess
Of what it was sold for
Depending on what limitations there are
On monetizing that
So I love YouTube
I like it
For us it's distribution
I love it when one of my shit shows up on YouTube
That's really good
But I think
When it comes to a solid
Base for a media company
No, it's not really
It's not really the way to go
In my opinion
But
On the other hand
I'll say
Wow, you know
It's kind of like my
VCR in a way
If I just wanted to see the best part of the
Daily Show
From the previous evening
No matter where I am in the world
Bingo
You know it shows it to me
So
As a single stop shop
As an aggregation of
Cool shit
And you know it's there
It was at least fantastic
So
Unless
Comedy Central
Starts
Something in a podcast feed
You know it's just going to be a pain in the ass
To go to all these different sites
Maybe that's what I like so much about it
So
Well
We'll see
It's just another
Another step
It'll be another piece of history
Eventually
And I'm going to say that
With a piece of Charles Centin
For another day
Because I want to get to the second
To report
Of the belly tour
Coming to you from South by Southwest
Richard Brewer Hay
And Michael Butler
Together
In their hotel room
And by the way
I guess that it didn't mean for this
To be on the air
But I encourage them to continue
Sending reports
And
Really anybody within Pod Show
Dial something in
This is cool shit
Let me know what you're doing
Adam
It's a beer belly
And Butler
Part two
The beer belly
Pleisty night
It's about court across midnight here in Austin
And we're back in the hotel
And we know we kind of wish that
We're going to try and make it till three
But
It's actually the rock and roll geeky
And I was staying
So I'm going to blame it on him
But we had a pretty good day today
We met with some
Some good folks
We met with the local media
And marketing
We met with Adam
Who's the director of operations
And Jennifer, who's their publicist
And their PR firm
Representing a bunch of independent artists
Some of which were already on our network
And a lot of which we want to get on the network
And we met with the owner
Sideways media in the coal
She's down in LA
And searching her most speech
And she invited us out tonight
She wanted to advance
Junior
They were really good
Michael wasn't
A big fan of him
Because they wore their baseball hat's back
It was a little bit of a jacket
So we could see the bills were enjoying it
They were bouncing up and down
We're just kind of nice
Yeah
And then we met with Adam
Who's the managing director
Of North by Northeast
Which is the equivalent of
South by Southwest
You just imagine these two guys
I mean
You don't know Richard that well, perhaps
I know a lot of people on the network
No Richard
And Michael Butler of course
I think everybody knows
These two guys are staying in one hotel
Room together
South by Southwest
And they're going to show us
Where guys with baseball caps
Backwards to make the girls jump up
And jump up and down
Getting horny
I can tell
I guess 2 graphics equivalent
Up and where is it?
Can it work out if you can
Is it Michael?
That's right
Alright
So that was pretty well
We did a good day
Excellent
So a bunch of bands
Gotta get tired
That's about it
Michael had
What was it you wanted to ask?
Oh yeah
So we had a good night
And Michael was feeling a bit horny
So he was wondering if there's any way
We can expense getting a cold bill
We figured that
We figured you might be able to let us know
So let us know if we can expense a cold bill
And then we'll go ahead and do that
Because we're sharing the hotel room
We figured what to help
And you think it easy
Hopefully you'll appreciate it
Well, cheers
Bye
Have a nice day on TV
We've already had this cold girl
So we've already done it
We just wanted to...
I'm sure I'm full of blood
But...
Uh...
No, you can't expense it
But I'll pay for it
My pleasure
Haha
I'm glad you guys had a good time
And don't worry
If you won't say anything about what
I'm gonna do to Angelina Jolie next month
I won't tell you your wife about what you guys were up to
Okay
There'll be our little secret
Alright
See, we're closing it on 40 minutes
So time to wrap it up
But we can only do that
With one man
Our brand new Papa
Our brand new Pagio Papa
Q
Hi everybody!
Through bars!
And now need your number reactions
I don't need your fingers pointing on
I don't need your alcoholics
I don't need your jurisdictions all up
That when you couldn't get connected
No one now towards listening
I don't do anything now
Well, it can't stop you anyway
You go with the kid you are
And you love to relax in the room
Don't do anything that I ever did
You're finally coming over me
And I didn't know you would feel it
No, no, no, no, no
I don't need your sexual secrets
I don't need your cocktail conversation
Conversation
I don't need your two fake sections
I don't have to worry about nothing
Now that you're gone
And the way it's been lifted
No one else is listening
I don't do anything now
Well, it can't stop you anyway
You go with the kid you are
And you love to relax in the room
I'm doing the best I ever did
You're finally coming over me
And I didn't know you would feel it
No, no, no, no, no
I'm doing the best I ever did
You're finally coming over me
And I didn't know you would feel it
No, no, no, no
The news again
I don't need no, no, no, no
You're in a set
I'm doing the best I ever did
You're finally coming over me
And I didn't know you would feel it
No, no, no, no, no
I'm doing the best I ever did
You're finally coming over me
And I didn't know you would feel it
No, no, no, no
I'm doing the best I ever did
You're finally coming over me
Oh, yeah
Sir Jersey Todd strikes again
The official music college of the Charlie knows exactly what's going down
The Milwaukee's love it
Links, of course
It is source code dot com
It's Friday
Well, I gotta tell you I have a couple of final thoughts of the week
Because it's been quite an interesting one here in New York City
As the snow flurry started to dwindle down
As we just have to stop enjoying the nice spring weather
Looks like goldman winter is going to give us one last blast
Before it's a time for him to head on
Up north, wherever the heli goes
First of all, let me just say that
One of the advantages of going
Being middle-aged
Is, you know, I'm seeing, and especially since I haven't really been
In the advertising scene in New York for quite a while
You know, we've had our trips, but this was really serious
You know, this is the people who really make decisions
By our strategists, creative people, and they're into it
Now it's really deep, and so it's not just us presenting
It's working with these people
And one of the advantages of being middle-aged
It hurts to say this
There's a whole new generation that's come into work
Of these agencies
And the girls are cute
They're hot, love it
Let me see what else that I want to say
Ah yes
Yeah, the definition of luck
Because we see a lot of that
I consider myself to be extremely lucky
But it really is when preparation meets opportunity
And I think you should always bear that in mind
Because you do make your own luck
And then finally, you know, just think it in my body
And that will pass away, it really is true
No matter what you're doing, live your life to the fullest
Live your life with passion
Use their wings, take those day food by Friday
And I'm spinal thought on the reef
Alright, have yourselves a great weekend
We'll talk again on Monday, I'll be back home at the manner
Ah, to care everybody
Bye-bye
Another poncho podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest, served up daily
By the sharpest minds and content delivery
Pajo in my life