Another pod-show pod-cast.
Stick!
We interrupt the show for a special announcement from Pod-show HQ.
Attention pod-casters, viewers and listeners, Pod-show needs you to help us suck less.
Help us suck less, help us suck less, Pod-show needs you to help us suck less.
Hey, it's Cali Lewis from Geek Creek TV.
Pod-show needs your help.
We're always trying to improve, and this time, we need you to help us suck less.
We're creating a special place to pod-show suck less, so let's suck less.
Pod-show.com.
That's right, once you're there, you can join our Superpanel.
Give us your feedback, earn points, and get valuable stuff.
It's fun, it's easy, and most of all, you help us suck less.
Help us suck less, help us suck less, Pod-show needs you to help us suck less.
Now, back to the show.
Delta Sierra Charley, 6-1-1.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Turn this!
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends in it.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
One fasting kiss.
That you're happy.
I was in a lake, and I thought you'd grab it for me
I got to win a fair
I thought you'd do a fair
You thought I'd not do a fair
Well, I can't doubt I'm running out of money
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I forget to pray
You know, I need to throw your lives in cold
Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Those have gone worse then
Now the photo organisations
I thought you'd win a fair
All the leaves are dry, and the sky is ready, and the sky is gray, and the sky is gray,
I am watching all the way on a weather plane, and my little tail,
I am watching all the way, and the sky is gray, and the sky is gray, and the sky is gray,
and the sky is concreted away, and I am not in the same place.
Motherland Board of businesses
international pop festival.
It's California DREAMEN.
How cool is that that is now on the
Pond Safe Music Network?
I could not believe my luck when this showed up today.
And it fits so well because it's almost been a week
that has just been pissing down all across the
United Kingdom, continental Europe.
It's crap.
Yesterday was just a teeny weeny bit better.
But we still had rain throughout the day with big
Columbus Nimbus clouds and just a
accumulation of moisture.
Now, about this song because you're saying, how could this be
Pond Safe?
This is what I love about what's happening with
the back catalog essentially.
Now, you know, the young Palette and I have been working for
about two years now trying to get the hit test up and running
in some form of legal fashion.
I think we have that licked by the way.
And I hope I hope I hope to be able to start
very soon.
But now you see that there are these smart
marketers and smaller really small independent
labels who are picking up back catalog that the mainstream
record companies just can't sell.
Don't have the ability to sell or maybe it's not worth it
to them except for time-life books and time-life
records, of course, which have great collections.
But, you know, who wants to buy that when you see these
like, you know, dead people hockin' him.
Anyway, on this Monterey, actually, let me,
what's the name of this label?
Now, on the Pod Safe Music Network, you can just click on it
and I'll tell me who the label is.
Razer and Ty is the name of this label.
New York-based Razer and Ty, one of the fastest growing
independent entertainment companies in the United States.
Razer and Ty successfully sells audio and video products
through traditional retail distribution,
direct response, television advertising, and e-commerce-based
websites.
And so, from that CD, which they've now turned Pod Safe
very, very smart because I know people are going to buy this.
Let me to play another track.
They have the Who My Generation.
I'm playing this straight from the website.
If you're a member of the Pod Safe Music Network
as a Podcaster, you get access to all these songs
so you can play them in your show.
Oh, hold on a second.
I messed that up, didn't I?
Hey!
I need to flip that little box there.
Let's try it again.
See what?
Oh, man!
Can you believe how cool this is?
So, actually, I'm going to put the player
for this album on mycurry.com site
because then you can listen to all those tracks for free.
And of course, if you want to get more information,
you can go and buy them.
All right, everybody.
It's hump day.
We're halfway through.
Some interesting news already coming to us here
from the UK.
I'm opening up the BBC News website.
Music site, last FM, bought by CBS.
For $280 million, 140 million pounds.
Of course, that is probably the largest ever acquisition
of a UK-based company, which last FM is.
And I think this is very smart of CBS.
Last FM, of course, streams music.
In an interesting way, you know, that, but it's a social,
music network, social, music listening network.
Maybe it should be social, music experience network
is probably better.
A lot of people really love last FM.
And I think rightfully so.
Now, their problem, of course, is with all these streaming rights.
And, you know, we've been talking about the copyright royalty board.
So these guys are probably sitting down and going,
like, shit, what are we going to do?
You know, someone's going to get around to us sooner or later.
And to have CBS, who, of course,
know very well how to negotiate rights with,
with organizations such as ASCAP, BMI, and the RIA.
There'll be perfect, perfect.
So the community, I think, will benefit from this.
And I think this is just a great, great acquisition.
Is that that Quincy guy?
Isn't that Quincy?
What are I hearing in the background here, by the way?
I'm hearing music from something.
Oh, am I playing something?
How the hell does that happen?
Are you hearing that as well?
This is very strange.
Let me see, is it?
Oh, what's that?
It's coming out of...
Where the hell is it coming from?
Hold on, peeps.
Got to check this one out.
Okay, yes.
Okay, found it.
That was the who playing in the background.
Yeah.
I think that's, let me see if it says anything.
Mr. Stixol, who's Mr. Stixol.
Yeah, as part of the acquisition,
the last of him management team, including found this Felix Miller,
Martin Stixol and Richard Jones,
will continue to independently run the online network.
Okay.
There must be someone from CBS saying something.
Hmm.
Right.
Yeah.
Last of course, last of them is one of the fastest growing online communities on there.
Last of him, strength in building communities around.
Music, and it kind of was central to UBM.
BBubbubbubbubbubbubbubbubbub os,
The demographics also play perfectly CBS as ago.
Yep, I think and write very, very smart spot on on that one.
Got an email from Nicholas Coolner,
a Nicholas said I think I found Trinity on Google Maps.
I was playing around with a new street view feature.
Checked out the Pod show.
HQ location.
you location. You've got to see this. This is un-for-can-wheel. There's Trinity. You can see
your ass sticking out. I didn't know about this feature from Google, and it's given me
some new ideas about what to do with Trinity. I told you that when I got back to San
Francisco, I'd be announcing something. And now it's like, oh, man, I can add something
very cool with this feature. Think about what we can do. And the question, of course, is
what does the frequency that these pictures are updated? I know that my apartment, the condo
in San Francisco, is still shows up as a building site, meaning it has to be at least five
years old. That picture, but the street view, how often are these updated? And how does that work?
Does anyone know? Because this is just flipping me out. I totally dig it.
Hey Adam, this is Chris and Germany. And I think you should go with part of Germany to address
an all-life pic because... No, it kind of dropped out there. What are you saying? He's giving
me suggestions on where we should put our headquarters for part-show Germany. And did it just
suggest, just, like, sick? Interesting. Chris and I like to have a lot of growing a lot of growing
economy, excuse me. And I think this would be a good chance to climb with the economy in
East Germany, and to build a big partial HQ here in East and Germany. And I think media
cities like Colone are dying out. I think the next big media city will be Berlin.
That's interesting. Do you think the Colone is dying out? Berlin is going to be a big
couple of people who said Berlin. Apparently there's like the big Sony media center that you
can write offices in. I don't know if we want to do that. I mean, that's not really us.
You know, we're in shortage here in London, which is pretty much the wrong side of the
tracks. Where we feel extremely comfortable, by the way. So I'm not too sure.
Uh, come to East Germany. We have the most beautiful girls here. Uh, come to East Germany. We
have the most beautiful girls here. Okay. Well, I think it's clear we're going to have to make
the decision based upon the quotient of beautiful girls to the city. So the contenders now are
Berlin. We have Munich is still kind of in the running. Colone is a high favorite, but we have
no guarantee that there are cute women there. And Hamburg, I think those are the four contenders
that we should be looking at. And by the way, cute guys, good too. Just send if you're really
cool, then you'll go to your Potcho Plus account, which of course you have. And you'd upload
some pictures of cute boys and girls so we can make a, uh, uh, a fully educated decision.
And then of course, you could just put that into the comments right on daily source code.com.
But if you're the lazy bugger, then go ahead and just email me a picture. Okay.
Let's see, what else? A lot of stuff came in to the email box today. Oh, I want to remind you that
episode number five of boomed is out. That's the original series game show in audio from Potcho.
Johnny Todd. Is that what he's still called?
And on episode number five, it's Dawn and Drew. And it's, uh, it's always great to hear two people
who know each other very well, completely intimately just talking amongst themselves. But to compare
their knowledge is probably even funnier. So you'll want to. And who of course will win the
Nokia N800 web tablet of the two? I have a feeling that the way those guys are, you know,
if like Dawn one and she wouldn't let Drew touch it. Have they, uh, has their, uh, interview
with Ziggy Marley come out yet? Hold on. Uh, that would mean that Ziggy would be on the, because I
thought he was going to put a song on the Pot save music network, hold on. Just do a search for Ziggy
see if it's up yet. I'm surprising, you know, it's like it's hard to keep up with all the things that
are going on there. Ziggy, no, no, no. Yeah, Ziggy Marley, shit. When did that go up? Let's listen to this a bit of
that into the group is the title of it on the Pot save music network. Well, screw me. Who knew, let's
listen for a second.
That's what we've become into the group. Come for the ride.
Ziggy, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no we are talking about something higher.
Change this time
Catch your way
I wanna catch your way
And free your slip
I wanna free my slip
Humanity, your mind
You're not the day you can change this time
I'd love to fly, I'd love to cry
I'd love to fly
Trudus do what
Where will you sort, self just to find behind
Where we get to fly, but you
For we escape from the surface of what we've become
Come for the ride