Hey home fries, it's CC Chapman from accident hash, encouraging you to check out botod.tv slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there, and you can only find it at botod.tv.
It's the DSC 647, which actually stands for the Daily Source Code 647.
But you can also say the Delta Sierra Charlie 647, but you can't say tailwind unless you're a pilot.
Of course, some people just shorten it with the Charlie 647, but that just doesn't sound right.
So here's the DSC 647.
Yeah, but really, I think we should look at that analogy.
Let's look at the road being the network, road system, and let's look at cars.
Cars being the devices you connect to the road, and you use the road with to travel across it.
Yep, if there was just one car that would work for everybody, we'd have to be what I'll be driving Volkswagen.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, pole of the world's most dangerous new content comes the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
I think you better stop.
I think you might have hit the switch bar.
Yeah, it's a crazy lot.
That sort of thing just blows my head off.
Here we are, thumbs up.
Here we are, thumbs up and I'll get our car.
Here we get what's right and what's up.
I knew we were right from the start.
But all you're struggling, you ain't very small hearts.
But you got a lot of hearts.
You might want to keep those new things in your heart.
Here we are, thumbs up.
Here we are, thumbs up and I'll get our car.
Here we get what's right and what's not right.
Getting good, way better.
No more feeling of it.
Can you update my legs there?
Just don't want to go over there.
Here we are, thumbs up.
Here we are, thumbs up and I'll get our car.
Here we get what's right and what's not right.
Here we are, thumbs up.
Here we are, thumbs up and I'll get our car.
Just spot safe and you'll find the link to her at dailysourcecode.com.
Jericho all thumbs up, kickin' off daily sourcecode episode number 647.
Again, a beautiful, beautiful day.
Summer has finally arrived.
I know, I'm inviting the book in the end by saying this,
but I'm upstairs here in the attic.
I've got the windows wide open.
I can hear the birds outside.
There's almost no wind at all.
Beautiful blue sky with some nice white puffy clouds.
Which I'm sure will come back to haunt us a little bit later on in the week.
And for those of you who are interested,
I'm wearing my Al Jazeera Bathrobe today.
Don't ask, just trust me.
Okay.
It's not actually, it's not an Al Jazeera Bathrobe.
I stole it from the Bourgella Rob hotel and Dubai.
But I called my Al Jazeera Bathrobe because it has one of those logos on it.
Because it was late last night.
I didn't get into bed until I think it was 145, probably sleep around 2am.
Just up late talking to San Francisco.
The alarm went at 715 this morning.
As it does every Tuesday morning because it's time to take out the trash.
Oh shoot.
You know what?
I'm just thinking about that.
I wonder if,
well man, I wish I could find that song.
Was that that they might be giant song?
Take out the trash?
That's probably why I like it so much.
I've always had to take out the trash my entire life.
It was way was my main chore growing up.
And for a while there, I didn't have to do it.
You know, we had staff and everything.
When I have to admit, I got kind of tired of the staff.
It's much less aggravating to take out the trash yourself once a week.
And I can't take it out at night because the foxes and God knows what else is around here.
Get into it and they they tear up the bags and it's all over the street.
And that's no good.
And that's just kind of rude.
Anyway, today, going to talk about music, pod safe music,
or music in general actually.
Yeah, the first article that came across my desk this morning is
an article in the inquire, the inquire, not the inquire.
And that's a, I think that that's a British publication, right?
Yeah.
And they're basically recounting a story that wired uncovered that sound exchange.
Now, this is the organization that is collecting royalties from web casting.
And from other online use of licensed music of mainstream licensed music, I should say.
Apparently, these guys are engaging in illegal activity.
Oh, gee, who would have thunk it?
A wide magazine found that sound exchange registered the music first coalition dot or
domain name, May 9th, 2007, and is a founding member of this PR and
lobby group, which of course is a PR and lobby group for the mainstream labels.
It also supports music first financially.
The music first coalition is a public relations outfit who's job is to
be a sound recording performance royalty on terrestrial radio stations.
That's one.
And of course, they do all the, what is it now?
They want to collect money for performers and they want to collect money from web streamers.
What's interesting, let me just go to the wired story because that's actually,
I guess, the source of this is that's not allowed under the auspices of how
they're set up.
I think there's only three main directives that sound exchange as a,
what do you call it as, as the,
I'm a loss for words today.
Anyway, it's a compulsory license.
So that means it's law, which means the collector of this compulsory license fee
has to appear to certain laws according to wired, section 14,
G3 of the copyright act explicitly limits how the nonprofit, which is sound exchange,
can spend the money it collects,
approving just three carefully circumscribed activities.
I'll just give those to you.
So the administration of the collection distribution and calculation of the royalties.
Okay.
Makes sense.
The settlement of disputes relating to the collection and calculation of the royalties.
And the licensing and enforcement of rights with respect to making of,
uh, a femoral recordings and performances subject to licensing blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
So, uh, they're doing some G.
Isn't that amazing that they're doing something illegal, doing something to only
who of themselves?
I'm telling you, people, for those of you still fighting this,
stop fighting, go around it.
It's just not worth it.
Listen to what we're doing.
Adam, Dave from South Florida.
Amen.
Carbon leaves.
You're playing carbon leaves.
I love it.
I absolutely love it.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
I love these guys.
I've seen them tons of times.
And I forget this guy's name who, uh,
who got this, this, uh, them on the network,
but man, holy shit.
It's awesome to hear a band like this, uh, on the network.
I've been following these guys for years.
Parted with them, um, like I said, seen them a ton of times.
Great group of guys.
Really cool to see a band like this on the network.
So, uh, congratulations on this one, man.
This is huge for you guys.
All right.
Take it easy.
Well, congratulations to you.
You seem to be really excited about it.
And other people who've been listening to the song,
it's really for the audience.
You know, Pod Show makes no money out of this.
In fact, it's, uh, it's really, it's a cost center,
because it, uh, it gives us a great resource for programming.
And not just Pod Show, but, uh, anyone who wants to sign up, uh,
for the Pod Take Music license, which you can do with the network.
I should give you the address.
It's music.podshow.com.
And if you just want to listen to some of these tunes,
and you don't want to join the network, uh,
don't have a show.
It's okay.
Go to podshow.com slash music.
And you'll get exactly the same little more, uh,
consumer friendly, uh, with some players.
You can embed on your own webpage, etc.
And you can search, uh, similar and topless.
And all kinds of get Ruby.
You can get them, by the way.
You can put them into a channel, uh, which will play in the
mashboard, etc.
Um, uh, uh, but really, you know, the, uh, the, uh,
the point being that it's working.
And I got a call just before starting, uh,
the show this morning.
Super agent Keith called me.
He said he spoke to the guy over at Cafe Nero.
Remember now, I'm trying to expand the Pod Take Music platform, uh,
uh, by getting music, uh, Pod Take Music played in the 360 Cafe
Nero's currently in the UK.
Soon to be branching out across Europe.
And I'm pretty sure that eventually one day they'll give it a try in the
States.
I don't see whether they wouldn't.
Um, and, um, so Peter Ettenger is the guy, the managing director
and he's the guy that I spoke with and met with and that he,
he spoke with, he's on holiday this week.
But he called super agent Keith from his holiday location and said,
dude, uh, I'm like blown away by this stuff.
I definitely want to do something.
So haven't spoken to him myself, haven't heard it with my own ears,
but I would say that that's a, uh, that's a big up right there.
God, how cool would that be?
How incredibly cool.
If we could, uh, play Pod Take Music, uh,
get Pod Take Music played in, uh, in retail outlets,
but also have the, the actual CDs available for sale there.
I'm telling you, it would be so huge.
And, and what a big, you know, two fingers up to the mainstream
establishment.
Yeah, listen, what's happening?
Remember I played, um, the song I think this is war by Stephen P.
Richards, which was, uh, suggested by, uh, by listener.
Well, here's what happens.
Hey, Adam, this is Stephen Richards, um,
on the song writer.
You play this song on mine.
This is war on your show last week.
Just want to call him personally.
Thank you for that.
I really, really appreciate it.
I've been trying to get that, um,
song out there and start pitching it on.
And, um, it's been kind of difficult in the US as you can imagine
with the political sort of climate here.
But, um, I just wanted to let you know.
It also got picked up on another pod show,
the, uh, galmin show, my turner.
And so, um, I really, really, really appreciate that.
So thank you very much.
And hope you have a good week.
Hope you all will dry over there.
And, um, take care.
Bye-bye.
Oh, Stephen Dome, man.
Thank you.
Thanks for sharing.
And, uh, nowhere.
Well, we're keeping a dry, but it's still pretty bad.
Uh, the flooding.
And, uh, and of course, this is summer.
It's flooding in the summer.
Not only that, but now gulfard has a second outbreak of, uh,
the, uh, foot and mouth disease, which I should just tell you briefly,
because I've, you know, I've, uh, paid attention to this over the, over the past
what, seven years probably, uh, where there have been some huge outbreaks
and, uh, and major calling, which is a different word for killing of animals.
And, and maybe I should just explain, because a lot of people get confused
and, and compare this like mad cow disease, which it is not.
In fact, foot and mouth disease, as far as I know, is curable.
Uh, and, uh, you know, you can cure the animals of this disease.
Uh, if you eat a, uh, foot and mouth disease infected, uh, animals,
you will not die as a human being.
You will also not contract foot and mouth disease.
Uh, in fact, back in the day, it was like, hey, man, uh,
you know, my cattle got foot and mouth disease.
Ah, shit, man, we'll stay away from your place for a couple of weeks,
because it does end.
It, you know, these animals don't die from foot and mouth disease.
The problem.
The problem is you cannot export any meat that has been contaminated
with foot and mouth disease.
So the industry is, is completely out of standstill.
No cattle is moving whatsoever, because it's really about the export of the meat.
Uh, I think there's some European regulations, maybe you can about the sale of it.
But it's not like it's going to kill anybody.
This is purely about business.
I just want you to understand that.
And, you can't wax it.
Well, you can actually, you can vaccinate, uh, against foot and mouth disease.
But then you also can't export the meat because vaccines typically
consist of the disease itself.
So they would still test positive for foot and mouth disease.
And that's just not acceptable, uh, in meat trade apparently.
So, you know, all these animals, which, by the way, would have been killed anyway
to be eaten, uh, are being killed.
I think quite senselessly, just because the industry, uh, can't, you know,
can't handle, uh, a couple of weeks of standstill.
And, uh, and I, as I said yesterday, the industry is completely subsidized.
So just subsidized it's a more, you know,
and, uh, and let's not kill these animals senselessly.
That's my, um, as my position based upon what I know.
Of course, I could be wrong, and I'm sure we'll have some veterinarians
to bounce calling in, at least I hope so.
Dylan Alford, uh, one of a couple of people who sent me, uh,
some feedback about that, uh, about the newspaper postings from Luke Air Force
base that I read out yesterday, um, about, uh,
one letter that was written into local newspaper saying,
hey, what's all this with the, you know, disturbing our shopping morning at the mall,
and it turns out it was a formation fly by for a, uh,
for a burial of, uh, of an airman.
And a couple of people have sent me some backup on that.
First of all, the story is from 2005, which kind of pisses me off,
because, you know, I guess it must have been still circulating around the net,
or maybe just now kind of popped up, but it was presented to me as something new.
Uh, and there is additional information, which I feel I need to,
need to read out to you.
Um, after, uh, lieutenant, uh, Colonel Scott Blues sent back, you know,
uh, also sent in his letter saying, hey, you know, uh,
shut the F up because these guys are flying information for a fallen airman.
Then, uh, the original writer of the original letter, Tom McRae, uh,
sent this to the letter, which was posted as well,
regarding fly by honoring fallen comrade, comrade.
I read with increasing embarrassment and humility,
the response to my unfortunate letter to the republic, as the newspaper,
concerning an air force fly by, quote, a wake-up call from Luke's
jets letters on June 23rd.
I had no idea the significance of the fly by,
and we never have insulted such a fine and respectful display had I known.
I've received many calls from fine from the fine airman who are serving,
or have served at Luke, and I've attempted to explain my side,
and apologize for any discomfort my letter is caused.
It was simply an un-informed citizen complaining about noise.
I've been made aware of both written and verbal communications of the four,
of the four ship fly by.
And my heart goes out to each and every law serviceman and woman in this
war in which we are engaged.
I have been called un-American by an unknown caller,
and I feel that I must address that.
I served in the U.S. Navy and Amoviet now veteran.
I love my country and respect the jobs that service organizations are doing.
Please accept my heartfelt apologies.
Okay, so now that's taken care of.
So I guess everybody jumped to conclusions on that one.
And even worse, I'm only delving into it and jumping to my own conclusions
only two years later.
I need to get away.
Which is, hope it's happening.
Next Wednesday, we're going to the States.
We still don't have a beach house to sit in,
but we're going for the big,
and I heard about your family reunion and interviewing your uncle.
Very much looking forward to that.
You had me excited when you talked about it earlier.
Very, very cool stuff.
Can't wait to hear that interview.
Speaking of great interviews,
David Epolito, that guitarman from Central Park is working on an idea
with the sit burnstein, the man responsible for bringing
not only the Beatles, but the Rolling Stones
and the Raskos and many, many other bands from England
into the US.
So you did point your finger and say that's
the man responsible for the British invasion,
said burnstein would be that man.
David has posted on, I love the video,
a brief interview that he did with said,
he's working to expand that and wants your input.
He could get in contact with him, that'd be cool.
But check it out at time.
I love the video.
I think it's sil,
cv.pro.
Or you can go to that guitarman.com,
get the link from there.
Very, very cool stuff.
Anyway, tick here.
Talk to you later.
Yep.
Indeed.
So first of all,
uh,
yeah, Uncle Don, that's what it was.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to that as well.
He's the CEO of the Korea Society,
very involved in the, in the recent
conversation slash negotiations,
and we'll get his worldview.
I think it'll be, it'll probably be a very long interview
that I'm going to break into multiple parts,
and maybe we'll follow it over a week or something like that.
And that's why I'm hoping for the beach house,
the beach house got to have Wi-Fi,
so I can sit there and edit and do some cool stuff.
And my trunks, you know what I'm saying?
And regarding said burnstein,
David and I've been talking about this for several months,
and I did see the video, it's it's Itv.pto.com.
I love the video.
And here's what I was thinking because,
you know, yes,
sin burnstein responsible for bringing the rolling stones
and the Beatles and the British invasion,
and for a number of other things that I've
nothing to do with the British invasion.
But of course, you know,
lots of people were really responsible.
I mean, you know,
you could say that the Beatles were responsible
in part as the stones were themselves.
But what is important about said is he has ears
and this is something that's really,
you can't learn, you have the talent, and you know how to identify a song that's
going to resonate, you know how to hear hits, and it doesn't go away, you can continue
to hear this throughout your life, as far as I'm concerned. I can still do it, and
I'm still pretty good at it, as Sid Bernstein, of course, is an expert. So what I'd
like to do, if you see that video, it's kind of shot in like a lunchroom cafeteria vibe,
really noisy, and you don't really get the intimate feeling that you want from Sid. I mean,
I don't even think we have to do video. I would just like to run, you know, five songs
a week by Sid Bernstein from the Pod Safe Music Network. See what he says, you know, see
if he can pick him, or maybe, you know, let him listen to 20 songs and haven't picked
his top three favorites, the ones that he thinks will make it. That's the kind of show I want
to do with Sid Bernstein, because that would be obviously a humongous seal of approval.
Adam, what's going on? A scary Alexander from the Ultimate Pod Test.
A scary Alexander by the way, starting to become an official savant of the show. I just
wanted to play this feedback, because he's got something pretty cool going on. He's got a
got a new show that he wants to promote. Thanks, first of all, I have a new show called The
Combat Zone. You can find that at thecomasone.podshow.com. It's an all video show. I go into
Jim's here around the country, and hopefully soon around the world, and interview fighters
as well as cutting men, trainers, nutrition experts. If you see all that on the combat zone,
and I just did a show that you're going to be excited about with Gina Corrano, who is a super hot
fighter that's by my show time. And wow, such a smart girl, as well as beautiful and
talented, and we'll kick your ass. Now moving on, I'm currently in production of another show,
being in Vegas here, I've been out of my show last show that I've done for a couple of months,
actually about five months here, and I've kind of sat around and gotten heavy. I've got on
about 25 pounds, 20 pounds, maybe, and I am in the process of losing weight. Thank goodness,
and I'm going to drop about 25 to 30 pounds, and I'm going to do that specifically through
martial arts training, through boxing, through kick boxing, and we tied you just to,
and mix martial arts training. You're going to see as you go to the new diet, you got to the
interviews with nutritionist, you know, to interviews with with personal trainers,
everything's going to be on this show, and it's going to be all video. So every average show out there
will be able to come to the show, get pointers for workouts as well as nutrition stuff,
and you'll learn about a sport that I know enough really nothing about yet. Which brings me to my
last point. I want everyone to vote for my show. It's been a category called no one understands
my sport. All right. All right. Dude, you are just cranking them out, and I can't wait to see
some of those episodes because they're perfect for the plus. I know I've spoken about this just
just touched on it from time to time, the plus TV, which could very well become a home page for
pod show you never know. We set up a video stream. It's like a video station, it streams in real
time, and it's programmed. So that means that we, you know, basically I wanted to create an MTV
of short video clips, some of it being music, not all of it, and I think we're succeeding. The plus
TV, I can't tell you where to find it, but the plus TV is definitely something you might want to
check out. We're still in like alpha phase, the stream goes up and down, and you know, there's
playlists and stuff that up next that that sometimes breaks, but when you see this thing work
perfectly, the plus TV can't tell you how to find it. I think you'll really enjoy it. If you do
find it, let me know. Also, yesterday worked on getting the free Trinity production up and running a
little bit. You know, we found a Shane and AB bugby who are more than willing to use Trinity on their
here at the wheel. You can find more about them at year at the wheel.podshow.com. They'll be doing
audio and video in this very important election year, traveling around the United States. They have a
root all mapped out. We have to start filling that root up with, well, basically places where they
can stay, or places where they can score some biodiesel, or maybe just some old veggie oil and
take it over to someone else's place and turn it into biodiesel. And my hope had been that I could
get one of the originators of the idea, Doug Pilgrim and his son still involved, and I receive this,
I think about a week ago. Hey, Adam, it's Doug Pilgrim in Boston. I want to preference this call
in here. Brock and I have really gotten a kick out of watching this idea. Take off and morph into
so many different directions, and to come to where it finally is now with a year at the wheel.
I'm very, he thinks it's very, very cool and so do I. But I am afraid the window of opportunity
for Brock and I to be involved with this project has come to a close. Brock has taken a job
as of last week, down in South Boston on the docks, and he's working on a ship repair down there,
and he'll be working that job 12 hours a day, seven days a week, from now until he goes back to the
academy, which is good for him, because it's a type of job that he wanted to do. And Kendall,
Brock's sister, who's just about to get her driver's license, and who was going to be his second
on this trip. Now has a full-time job. She's also doing volunteer work at the local hospital.
At the same time, she's taken a prep class for her SATs. So unfortunately, her time is all used up,
and I have now taken on a second job also to make ends meet. Just your average American family.
So unfortunately, we're not going to have the time to be able to participate, and which is too bad.
I also think it's important that Amy and Shane have a clean slate to start off their project,
and so that they aren't shackled with any of the preconceptions of what this project was all about.
And in that spirit, I have to say, free Trinity is dead, long live a year at the wheel.
So anyway, thanks for including us in all this atom, and I am now formally retired from this project,
but I just want to tell you that I've enjoyed the ride. I will go back to the Pilgrim Think Tank,
and come up with the next new idea. I'll be listening, and I'll talk you later on. Thanks.
Bye-bye.
So a couple of things about that. First of all, a true American. Listen to this.
A true American family. Listen to that. And Doug, dude, do I know what it means to have two jobs?
I have two. I got two on both sides of the Atlantic, other sides of the earth.
But what a lovely family. And everyone doing stuff, and working hard, and I feel really sad on the other hand
that you guys can't participate in the project, and I still want to do something somehow,
even if it's just Trinity coming by to visit you guys. I mean, I just feel kind of crappy about it,
but I really do appreciate the understanding. And let's get Trinity on the road, and I appreciate
your further support, obviously. It's warming up here. You know, if I close the door to the attic,
there's nothing that will help the heat just kind of hovering, hovering above my head,
very hard to get rid of it, and starting to heat up already. I got one more subvant that I
want you to listen to. A atomic rod is back with an update. Of course, a atomic rod is a gentleman who
fully believes that a lot of the answers to our climate issues, but certainly our fuel
and power issues, could be solved by backyard atomic reactors. And you know me, I would love
nothing more than the plant one of those puppies in my backyard. Adam, it's atomic rod,
Adams, your energy, savant. Did you miss me? I haven't had much time for listening, or calling
in recent, I understand your challenge and putting out your daily shows. Time gets away from me
when you're trying to run a growing company. We're just having a lot of some updates on the
atomic world. You might have heard the numerous scary press reports about the effects of a recent
earthquake off the coast of Japan that infamous water that was discharged into the ocean was
almost exactly as radioactive as orange juice. I have some ideas about whether mainstream media
gave it so much attention. Repetition of a slanted event description is one way to obscure the truth.
You know, I'm sure that somewhere someone started by releasing the horrible story of this radioactive
waste, but I wouldn't blame the mainstream media. All they do is just sit there and copy and paste.
You know, they read someone else's article, if it's from a associated press, then it's brand
that is good. It's true. It's real news. Let's copy paste. There are plenty of people who benefit
from sensationalism about minor events at nuclear plants. Unistar nuclear has filed the first
application for a license to construct a nuclear power plant in the United States in 30 years.
Coward Cliffs Maryland, the proposed site, is about 40 miles from my house and 50 miles from Washington.
I am thrilled at the prospects of cleaner air in the local area. Adam's atomic engine projects
are progressing nicely, but it's not yet time for any damned announcements. Take care. No problem.
Here, if you miss a charger too, it is hard to keep up anyway. No pills at all. Life is too much
fun without them. Man, are you kidding me? You've had so many red pills. You're pooping red.
Atomic Rod, cutting through the crap about atomic and energy. I'm still interested, man.
You know, I still haven't read a really convincing story telling me otherwise. Now that I know
that atomic waste isn't like some goo that seeps into the earth, but it's basically like a hard
rock. Could you build houses out of atomic waste? Could we do that? Could you make like sender blocks out
of that stuff? How radioactive is it? Can we put a coating over it so that it's safe?
Ah, these are just the questions I have when I wake up early in the morning.
Let me see. You know, another red pill blue pill thing. This is, I'm not quite sure how long
this will run. I just want to play a little bit. This is from Michelle from whispered pearls.
You'll see in the artwork for today's show. She's one of the bitches of pod show. A nice little
little artwork. She zipped over to me. And she used to work at playboy magazine. And although I'm
sure you know, it's, well, actually, I'm not sure, you know, if you listen to Michelle, she's
going to tell you how few people really understand how much work is done to the pictures that appear
in playboy, which is not the only publication that knows how to use Photoshop.
You know, the thing that I know and I've worked in media my whole life in various forms, but
the thing that I know is that it isn't always, you know, big lies, like that,
antileboots thing with the queen. But it's just as often, little lies, little things here and there
cutting something a certain way, editing something a certain way, air brushing something a certain
way to make something look good. And there are, I think, are two main culprits here. One is
expediency and one is perfectionism. I think the cult of perfectionism is going to kill us if we
don't turn it around. And I think people know that I used to work at playboy and I've seen
both of these things rampant there and everyone, of course, actually, I thought everyone knew this,
but I used to go to conferences and talk to people and the women were just shocked to find out
that the playmates are airbrushed massively. This is so hard to believe. Do women actually
look at these women in playboy magazine and think that they're born that way, that they are naturally
that shape, that that sheen and that sexy? They thought that, you know, women come out of the box
perfect like this and I was like, how many women do you know? Do you know any that actually look
like that? No, they don't look like that. Trust me, they have blemishes, they have tattoos,
they have wrinkles, they have hairs and weird places, they have all kinds of things just like
everybody else. They're not these, you know, airbrushed specimens of perfection that you see in this magazine,
they're not. And every magazine does that to a greater or lesser degree. I mean, the most
egregious ones are magazines like red book that put, you know, a celebrity's face on a totally
different body, you know? I mean, that's just just because you can, doesn't mean you should.
But here comes the reason, one of the reasons I'm bringing this up is because
I'm in recovery and it is really important to me to be honest. And I remember when I first got
sober talking to people in various industries, whether it's media or advertising or sports or
stockbrokers, just, you know, the spectrum of jobs talking to people and, you know,
the way that we operate in recovery is 100% honesty, 100% of the time. But
most of the time, people get tripped up in their jobs and they say, well, okay, I can be honest
with my family and my friends, but I can't be honest on my job because that's not how it works.
And, you know, if I'm helping to lead a revolution in podcasting, that is one of the things
that I would like to change or help to change. Michelle, you are helping so much. You have no idea.
For you to tell these stories and I think she's going to talk about the letters to the editor next.
I could listen to Michelle for hours. I'm sorry. It's just, I love, I, I somehow really get into
the sound of a voice. It's a pretty big, as Adam, so eloquently stated, it's a pretty big animal
to try and change to get, you know, TV, radio, film, you name it, newspapers, magazines, whatever,
to change their tactics and actually tell the truth. Exactly. Go around it. Forget about it.
It's a really big, big thing that Adam is putting on the table here. And I hope, you know what?
I'm 30 more seconds. Everybody, every podcast or everybody who's hearing this takes up this
cause because here's the thing. It's not okay to lie. It's not okay if you're in the media.
It's not okay if you're a politician. It's not okay if you're a friend talking one to one.
Lying is not okay. So let's look at the world with a new world view.
You got to listen to it. Michelle Bell's Hollywood actually is the name of this particular show.
And this is episode number 18. So, you know, and that's I think what people when they first
listen to something that's created independently, which is as open and honest because we really
have no need to not be open and honest. It takes people a second or two to get used to it.
And they say, wait a minute, this is kind of refreshing. You know, this is, hey, it's kind of like
it's got all the warts and all the bumps and everything all over it. And it's, wow, you know,
there's like a human being on the other end of the microphone or the other the other end of the camera.
It really does work. So yes, expose the lies. So people understand what mainstream has been
doing for years and how it works. Nothing wrong with it. By the way, I think you can do a lot for
enemy looks. It comes or lies. They're acted. Nothing wrong with stuff being acted. But don't
try and pawn it off as the truth. And really, the most important message is just go around it,
go around everything. We have everything in place. We just need to build up more audience.
Same thing goes to, you know, goes for what we started talking about the show about the
Podsake Music Network. Hi, Adam Nick here. I just had a quick thought regarding the Podsake
Music Network. I got a podcast. The Nick Menel Show at Nick Reynolds.com. And I was
trolling through the Podsake Music Network to find some tunes to put on my latest show. And I
came across Sydney and Mobile Disco. And I thought fantastic. One of my favorite acts at the moment.
And then on the Podsake Music Network, I can't believe it. So I downloaded the tracks that put
up there, which especially was their entire album, their latest album. And I played some tracks on
my show. And I still can't quite believe it that I'm playing such a sort of hit contemporary
acts. And their tracks are available to me on the PNN, which is fantastic. But it's not dedicated
to me. And it may be slightly paranoid. What's the stock? And I'm scooping this person,
ripping a CD of any artist, and uploading them to the PNN, and pretending to be that artist.
And, unfortunately, giving permission for those tracks to be downloaded and played.
And I'm not an artist, so I've never tried to upload any music. I'm not sure of the hoops
you have to jump through. But it was just a thought, maybe a paranoid one, but just a thought.
All right. Thanks, Adam. And then it'll plug from my show. The Nick Metal Show,
Nick Reynolds.com, every Thursday, saying the best independent music on the internet.
Okay, mate, cheers. All right. All right, Nick. Thank you. Well, you know what? I checked it out for you.
Simeon Mobile Disco, indeed, is on the Podsake Music Network. And their tracks were uploaded by their
label. Their label is the Wichita label. Now, we have two people working full time on the Podsake Music
Network. Again, we make no money with it, but it's really great for getting content out there.
And it's just changing the media industry, if you will, which is a big part of the mission here.
I think it's only happened once that someone uploaded, I can, I can't remember who it was,
but in two and a half years, only one time did someone upload something illegally that wasn't
that didn't have the rights to. And, you know, essentially, that's the culture that we set up.
The culture was, look, this is not for ripping off the John Stuart Show and making programming out of it.
This is for independent producers. That's what Pods Show.com is about. That's what the Podsake Music Network
is about. And it works. And it turns out that, guess what? People aren't really thieves.
You know, there aren't tons of people signing up to rip the stuff off. Because, yeah, I mean,
you don't even have to have a show, I guess. And you could register and you could download
your hards content, but guess what? People aren't thieves. They care about the artist. People
want to promote the artist because they like the music. You know, it's like the, it's like the early
coffee houses of the, of the 60s. It's haspory eight all over again. Eight, eight, eight haspory.
I don't know what the hell I'm talking about. But I do have,
Simeon Mobile disco for you, since it's on the PNN anyway.
You know, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's
like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, you're like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like this, it's like, it's like, it's really, completely, it's like, Yeah, it's like, it's like, it's, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it, it, it, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like,
It's a big
You don't need no imitation
Because this is my creation
It's a big
This is big
I know you know
Now, see, here's a track of like Sid Bernstein to evaluate because it's not entirely my music,
but anyone who joins the Pod State Music Network is a friend of mine.
Sid me in Mobile Disco. It's the beat. You can find out the Pod State Music Network music.
Got Pod Show.com, a link to that, of course, in the show notes at DailySourceCode.com.
Big day tomorrow and it's in London. Hopefully, I'll be able to
seek out a show before I leave. If not, it'll be Thursday. DailySourceCode.com,
Adam at PodShow.com, have a great day talking tomorrow.
Another Pod Show podcast. Stick it in your ear.