Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony
ear buds with style meets sound.
Delta Sierra Charney 703, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, to the next
generation rating content in my ears.
It's hard to believe that it's my first time, to my mind, on the one hand it's
my life together, and so far, so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far,
and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far, and so far,
I can't change, I can't change, I can't believe
And they got the memory of the love that died
It's died, I can't believe it's your fault
And we're thankful for everything
Of a nice little boy
That changed
But dreams can biteędzie
With a equal tenth ring
It's an old lie that you don't wanna bite
I'm changed
And the endreaction pops
Many of you are open up to remember
I was 25 years ago, the height of the Cold War ultra-vots just blew us away with dancing
with tears in my eyes and I got to tell you a bit of a day to prove and not a very
good one.
In fact, those guys were on my very first TV show, I think.
I think it was them and derand Iran and for some reason I'm thinking of really Nelson
that's exactly right.
Oh man, I gotta tell you, my head hurts, not from work, not from the weather, not from
television, but from a book, this book that John Seedivore I gave to me or turned
me on to Confessions of an Economic Hitman, EHM for short, has just really
blown my mind.
I'm now I'm finally seeing the really, really, really big picture, which is, I shut
or even to say that it's bigger than the 9-11, it's bigger than the war in Iraq, it's
much, much larger and all of the pieces of this puzzle that I've been putting together
over the course of, gosh, what has it been now?
Several months, they're finally starting to fall into place.
I don't know if I can articulate it all just yet because it's so simple that it's really
hard to understand.
Does that make any sense?
So some of today's football will be sprinkled with that here and there and I've been
finding just amazing things as I'm going through today's chapter in the soundtrack to my
life.
This is from the Potset Music Network, from a guy named Colin Muchler and he puts up Spoken
Word, check this out.
The markets are starting to question themselves, the bloggers exposing our blisters, just
the everyday words of everyday people are shifting the tone of the televised speeches, and
the artists are starting to question themselves and the poets are speaking like leaders,
and the everyday choices of everyday people are facing the storms and curing diseases.
So go Skype and iPod, pre-mix some wages, but don't forget to make a version for the
sages because when we look beyond our next meal, our next post, we are responsible for
our everyday votes, the ones we use to buy our shoes, to buy our homes, to buy our tunes.
Here's some talking about our dollars, our euros, our pesos, our yen, because what
of the next 20 years are happening again?
If we've already arrived, it's 2025, and the doomsday duos, the war and peace heroes,
haven't avoided the global cooling, the flu-grown zeros, and the forgotten people.
Is the markets are starting to question themselves, and the bloggers exposing our blisters?
Is the everyday words of everyday people are shifting the tone of the televised speeches,
and the artists are starting to question themselves, and the poets are speaking like leaders,
and the everyday choices of everyday people are facing the storms and curing diseases.
Oh yeah, deep shit.
And as I'm thinking about that, I'm thinking, where are all the protests songs?
I can go to any search engine online and I can find tons of protests songs from previous
wars.
Where are they for this one?
Where are the true protests songs?
And I'm looking for the dealings.
I'm looking for the spring steins.
I'm looking for some really, really grabbing shit.
And it's just not that easy to find.
Our commercial mainstream music mechanism, the engine is just pumping out mindless crap.
I think we need something with some lyrics here or there.
Well, here's something maybe that'll jog your memory.
It's the time it ends.
Are you ready to be stumps?
I'm watching the video version, it's Yann and his studio again.
Hey, Yann, hey Adam, this is a hate this number 101.
I'm going to start right away with intro number one.
I'm running out of time.
Ah crap.
Number two.
All right, let's change.
Um, well, it was a name of the song.
You want me, don't you?
It's definitely changed.
I know that for sure.
Is that's one from the decibel radio there?
And this week's final one is intro number three.
Oh, please.
Emergency.
Paging Dr. Beats.
That'll be glorious stuff on the Miami Sound Machine.
But what was that first one?
I know it.
Ah.
And times up in these ideas.
Uh, and some number one is from 1988.
Wait, wait, wait.
Three.
Up.
Uh, nice.
Yann has the album covers now in the video version.
Nice production.
Which wet wetter's answer number one, and this is answer number two, from 1985.
There's a change. This is change. Yeah, let's go together.
One here, one here, one here.
Yeah, I remember the album cover, very well young, looking at it now.
Not a real single, I'm no.
Change is answer number two.
Emergency, aging, Dr. Beat.
And this is answer number three, from 1984.
The Miami Sound Machine, this is Dr. Beat.
It's answer number three, and hit test number one, oh, one.
So, Adam, how did you do?
One and a half stars.
The answers to this hit test, and also the links to iTunes, who can buy these tracks online,
are to be found at hittest.botshow.com.
Thanks for playing, Adam.
Thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for hit this number one or two.
So, until then, take care, and bye-bye.
Yeah, it's really weird, young.
Instead of sending me an MP3, young sent me an MP4, which is the video version.
He's got multi camera set up now. He's got title.
He's got lower thirds. He's got album covers flying through him.
It's a whole production. It's really, really nice.
But young, it's really disturbing.
Please, just send me the MP3 because it's hard to concentrate in your wall of sound
when I'm looking at the video.
And by the way, Podshow, I dropped the C there for some reason you had a,
you had POD, SCHOW.com, like Pod School, only with a W.
Oh, yes.
Funky tunes, man.
I hadn't heard a number of those in a long, long time.
Hey, man. It's Nick from the Bay.
So, have you heard about, I just heard this morning,
there's a new study done by the Associated Press,
and they said that the most disliked of all federal government
organizations is the TSA.
Yeah.
People hated even more than the IRS.
That's pretty impressive.
So, yeah, you got some followers out there.
I just thought that you'd be interested in that little fact toy.
No, yeah, I'm curious.
No, man.
Back at your normal.
You know, the last night I was looking,
I was doing a little bit of research looking into the clear program,
which is this program, which is set up or approved,
I should say, by the TSA.
It's a commercial company in Virginia, low on behold,
who run this program.
And I figured I just look into it.
You know, see, see what it was all about.
And so, I learned a little bit of information about the TSA as well.
Yes, that I compared them to Burger Flippers.
First of all, this is actually quite interesting.
And I'm thinking, am I bringing it up on Noah Genda?
That's the show I do with John C.
We're at once a week at NoahGenda.podshow.com.
Stephen Brill, and this may ring a bell to some people.
I'm pretty sure that John is going to know,
he'll know of him for sure, and he may even have some good dirt on the guy.
At one point, I think I first heard about him when he had Brill's content,
which was like a monthly magazine about the media industry.
And this was a late, actually I'm looking at the page now.
It went belly up in 2001.
So he started clear.
If you can, actually he started a company called Hold on.
The company is called Verified Identity Pass.
And apparently he came up with this genius idea
to basically come up with a national ID card.
When he was visiting Attorney General John Ascroff,
all they asked him for was a driver's license.
And he felt that, you know, that was bad security.
So he came up with, let's see,
his blueprint for was he calling it the National Identification Card.
That's some other tidbits in here.
But anyway, so to this guy created this company,
and then the TSA, and they have a whole section on this,
they awarded Verified Identity Pass
as a part of the, or is it?
The Register Traveler Program,
they allowed them to operate in a number of airports.
I guess it's still, it may still be on trial.
They've had other companies doing this,
but it seems like these guys are winning territory.
So I just thought that was kind of interesting.
More interesting, though, when I looked around,
and I found out what the requirements are
to become a TSA screener.
And all these links, of course,
will be in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
So I went to the TSA website, TSA careers,
and I'm going to write now.
I'm going to pull up the available position
for security officer, particularly screening officer,
hold on.
That's all there seems to be available.
Let's see, there's a couple of states.
How about California San Jose?
Full time?
All right.
And air transportation security officer,
parentheses, screener.
This is also known as a TSO.
So what you'll expect it to be able to perform,
our duty, such as communicate with the public,
giving directions and responding to increase
an professional and courteous manner.
Right.
Maintained focus and awareness with
an environment containing numerous distractions,
people and noise, stand and remain standing
for periods up to four hours without sitting.
How many of those guys you see standing around for four hours?
Repeatedly lift and carry an object weighing up to 70 pounds.
Work within a stressful environment,
which includes noise from alarms, machinery,
and people's distraction, time pressure,
disruptive and angry passengers,
and the requirement to identify and locate potentially
life-threatening devices and devices intended
on creating massive destruction.
Hey, devices of weapons of mass destruction.
And also you need to make effective decisions
in both crisis and routine situations.
And so that's seen pretty, I guess,
pretty normal to me.
But then there was the actual requirements,
which is kind of this, by the way,
is a $23,000-dollar-year job.
This is a non-critical sensitive,
national security position that requires you
to be fingerprinted photograph
and complete appropriate security paperwork,
including an SF86.
A non-critical sensitive,
national security position.
Well, I'm so sorry.
You know, this is really honking me off.
Why don't we have highly skilled,
very professional experts doing this?
You know, in fact, qualifications,
you must be a US citizen or US national
and you must have a high school diploma,
a GED or equivalent or,
or, if you don't have a high school diploma
or a GED equivalency,
at least one year of full-time work experience
insecurity work, which means all those people
who were doing it before 9-11 have come back
and are just back in their same jobs.
If you've done at least one year full-time aviation
screener work or X-ray technician work,
boy.
Your tax dollars at work.
It's only like five or six billion a year
we spend on it.
And listen to this next call,
how incredibly effective these burger flippers are.
By the way, nothing against burger flippers.
You know, Adam, Chris, I'm living down.
So I could give you my little incident with coma and security.
I had the TFA open up my bag.
And I always take my bags in a situation
that I don't know if somebody opened them.
That's preventive load,
and just so I can tell if they were open.
But, um, they,
I flew out the Arizona for rocket launch
and they check my bags.
Wait a minute.
Okay. This is very important.
He flew out to Arizona for rocket launch.
Hold on.
Let me see what this is.
Rocket launch.
Arizona.
Google with me, people.
Uh, rocket launch.
Hmm.
Doesn't really.
Okay.
I guess it's like a burning man for rocket enthusiasts or something like that.
Oh, interesting.
They did not open or check the piece of luggage.
Failed with rockets.
They opened the luggage.
It's a little bit closed.
And right last top, but they did not open the hard gel suitcase full of rockets.
No rock loaders, of course.
You know that your actual prison time is there.
Rocket motor or everybody's.
But the piece was full of rockets.
They opened that one either way.
They're out.
But anyway, I get to know a tell room.
Reaching to my bag and like, like,
I'll help.
I'll free warm in here.
I stick my hand.
The laptop, it burned my hand.
It actually gave me a blister.
The sums of big is it turned on my laptop
and left it on.
I guess the morons could figure out how to turn the thing off.
So they just left it on and stuff the back of the case.
I hate that.
How it gets in die?
I don't know.
I mean, it's a, it's a, it's a no grade laptop.
It's the one you can leave out the rain and stuff.
You can drop it on current creative own effect as well.
I try to excuse.
So from now on, when I travel, I do not leave batteries in anything inside the case.
All my batteries go in my case.
Or rockets.
I don't leave batteries inside the laptop.
Any more for that reason alone.
Just so they can't fry my laptops.
Thankfully, it was okay.
But yeah, what are you going to do?
I just find that ironic that they, you know,
they check the bag with the laptop.
They didn't check the bag full of little missiles.
And a new phrase for you.
Go fuck the running corpse of Homeland Security.
And your mouth will do bushware at it too.
Yeah, right.
Right.
I'm a brother.
That's great.
He called in later with another comment about the electric car, which I'm going to play
free later on.
I looked it up.
It's, I think it's rocketry planet.com.
Yeah, I used to be in model rockets.
I used to be pretty cool.
Obviously, you can't take the actual motors, the actual.
What is that?
Solid, solid fuel.
Cartridges.
Or however, these looks like some serious rockets.
But yeah, I have to agree when there's a suitcase full of missiles.
With or without engines, I think it's pretty important.
That shows up somewhere.
Go as a study that came out today.
So when email me that some hard,
Harvard students found out that, well,
as we all kind of know, that the TSA is, you know,
really senseless.
And it's not really making us any more secure.
And in the TSA, replied by saying,
look, we're ready for any open and honest debate about this.
Okay.
How do you let rockets go through?
Dicks.
Man.
And I kid just because I can.
But again, this is not the, this is not the real problem.
These are just little, little tiny pieces of the machine,
which is so huge and which has been around for 50 years, five decades.
And I have to tell you, I believe that at least some members of my family
have been involved in this huge machine,
which involves humanitarian aid as a cover.
And the IMF and the World Bank and it does indeed revolve around huge companies,
basically stealing money.
They're not even stealing it, taking it legally.
It's even worse, being printed without license
by the Federal Reserve, by the Treasury.
We're in deep shit about this.
And somehow I've got to formulate the real story.
But in the meantime, please go read,
or listen to the audio book, Confessions of an economic hitman.
I mean, through this guy I've gotten to,
that's John Perkins, I've gotten to, who's this other guy?
I'm on a second.
He's a BBC, a BBC journalist.
What's his name?
Greg Palist.
Oh, man.
You should Google him.
Look at a couple of videos that he's got online.
Once you really see it, once you really see what's going on,
it becomes so aware.
It's just an awakening for me.
Okay, now I get it, now I see how it works.
And it's actually, once you can understand
how everything fits together, and that it's not one guy
or some conspiracy of people,
but really a machine that has been built up
and has almost has perpetual motion,
which, of course, it doesn't really look at all the failures
we're seeing now with our currencies and with the banking system.
So it is not a perpetual motion machine,
but man, it has certainly run for a long time.
And it's come crumbling down, and we can push it over the edge.
And it's going to hurt.
It's going to hurt a lot of us.
But it shouldn't be ultimate sacrifice.
It'll just be economic sacrifice.
But I think we have to go through it.
We can actually make a better world.
The one thing no one counted on.
And that's going back to that opening bit that I played.
The one thing that no one counted on
was this series of tubes that became interconnected
on as the interwebs.
They never counted on that free form flow of ideas
and people connecting across or interglobaly connecting,
and knowing that what happens here affects people over there
and being able to share ideas and thoughts.
And so it is our responsibility to take it down.
We've just got, it's like a DMCA request
to the fucking government.
We're taking it down.
We're taking the whole scam down
of lending money to poor countries to come in,
take their territory, take their property, build on that,
make sure they can never pay back the loans, steal the oil.
And it's not just oil in Iraq.
It's about water and strategic position.
Please look at the map and look at what countries surround Iraq.
Please take a look at that.
And I guarantee you pulling out of Iraq is going to hurt.
It's going to hurt a lot.
It's going to hurt in a lot of ways, particularly financially,
but we have to do it.
We have to go through that pain.
Because this scam is just too big.
We're issuing a take-down notice.
This is, we're ending it.
And we're going to end it from all angles.
By changing Congress, if we have to change it again,
by changing who's in the White House.
And by changing the behavior of companies,
changing their literal DNA, which may break some of them.
But others will come out.
I think very successful, because I do believe in capitalism,
but not the way it's been rolled out.
How?
We've really done a disservice to ourselves and to the world.
And I'm quite ashamed.
And now on to something completely different.
We're going to end it from all angles.
Unyyyyy.
How's it going, Adam, it's Jersey topped the official musicologist of The Cha Cha.
In one of my all time favorite things,
as your musicologist is the ability to give you something
brand-spanking new there.
It's actually not going to hear anywhere else you add in theared
slides.
I've got that for you today. I'm very very excited about it. So feel
almost the rock goddess herself has a brand new album coming out in spring 2008.
It's called Revelator. It sounds like it's gonna be really really interesting. It's a
whole brand new thing for her to life in modern-day America concept album with
issues ranging from racism to sexism, internet dating. All I know is that the
rock goddess continues to kick ass. Check this song out. It's brand
spanking new so feel almost for your football Friday. Let me tell you something.
Aw man, doesn't get any better than this. Check this out.
That man. Let me tell you something by these motherfuckers out here.
Let me tell you something. My brain has been washed.
And it's Halloween spanking new.
That wasn't too much much. She's just sitting, sitting,
some spanking back. Jumping in the space of day out.
Let me tell you something. Like a jeez free.
I'm just better than you. I know my brain you too was so fit you all up.
Well, now that's something to do.
Let me tell you something. My mind's been washed.
And I'm coughing. I'm smoking.
That wasn't too much. I'll catch you in my plan. What is this?
To be a righteous dog. Let me tell you something.
Like a restless dog. I'm a human alone. I can't hold it up.
He's thinking about going away. I tell you what being on my heart.
I see his mind about to grab the greatest blow. I'll tell you.
Reach the air. You might have gone too far for the cliff. You're almost at it.
Let me tell you something. My brain's been washed.
And I'm tired of what's left. I can't walk until too much. I'll give this to you.
To be a human. Jumping in the space of day out.
You haven't tell you something. My brain's been washed.
I'm just better than you. I know my brain you too was so fit you all up.
Well, now that's something to do.
I see his mind about to grab the greatest blow. I know how to say.
Oh, Sophia Ramas. Brand new. I was listening to that. I'm like,
man, she sounds almost like Janice Joplin and Jimmy Hendrix. You know,
got completely high. Drank of fifth to Jack and made crazy drug-induced love.
And out pops of fear, man. She's got something going on. Fantastic. Jersey Todd, man.
Thank you so much. They don't call you surfer. Nothing, eh?
Didn't into your show or DSC 700. Do you were talking about a loss of power?
And they struggled to get back on to line and you were talking about switching off of
Janice and things like that. Oh, yeah, that's right. The role for the pilot. That's right.
Just a little detail on that one. In our days on commercial aircrafts,
we do not switch off the power anymore because there is a special thing which is called the
GPCU, which is a ground power control unit, and that will manage all power losses and things like that.
So I believe they've just struggled to get the internal unit back on line. And they're
a little bit later to start up the APU. Well, nevertheless, thank you very much for your show.
I really appreciate. And what should I say? I actually believe me. And I'm great. Love you.
Hi. Thanks, man. Kind of homo. Yeah, I think that thing that's exactly what it was. It was the
even said it was the auxiliary or external power unit APU. That's what they said. But it probably was a
ground unit. But even so, I bet you they had some switch down that should have had switched off
when they reconnected that thing.
That glue took a dress in it all that stuff. I know for sure I'm going to need too much.
Married Jesus and three wise men, Joseph Angels and Bethlehem, come on, let's celebrate
Madness Christmas.
Don't happen once again. If you're in your blues, what's worth with this trip? Come on, let's celebrate.
Man is beauty.
I can't wait to see my kids face, round the tree on Christmas day,
Tarant paper and ribbon spline, I hope they did what I did by my card as matched with.
I don't care, I'll pay the bills, I'm back next year, come on, let's celebrate.
Man, it's Christmas, it's a man in Christmas, let's Christmas that year.
Man, it's Christmas.
Yeah, that's right, and being missed a last minute, man.
They're by, still have not done my Christmas shopping, that'll have to happen this weekend.
It's so typical.
Just going through some of the emails that came in, what is this?
Marco Hoppa.
They call on the Adam Courier Germany, excellent.
He wants me to, okay, he wants me to record something out crap.
You know, people ask me this all the time, I just don't have the time to record stuff, but what I'll do
is I'll do it here and you can kind of out the show and you can use it, okay?
Hi, I am the godfather of podcasting, that sounds lame.
Hi, I am the godfather of podcasting, and I want to tell you something, Hoppa, there'll be some nice Adam Courier.
Fick me!
Okay, hey, anyone could use that for their show, I guess.
Anything else?
I think we've covered it just about, hopefully I'll find some time to, to cut no agenda today.
Otherwise, might have to do that tomorrow after the Christmas shopping.
I kind of depends, we got one more just before the end of the year, big offsite meeting.
I'm way off offsite for the meeting, so that's happening starting at 4 o'clock this afternoon, UK time.
So that may, usually those things last, you know, like into around midnight, my time.
And I have a, I have a, I have a mine there to do a show, maybe Monday, certainly some time next week,
even though all of our offices will be, we'll not entirely closed.
Obviously, since we got a lot of gear running, and there's always people who want to wander and do some shit.
So it'll be people about, but there's no official work all of next week.
So I'll be chilling a little bit, but I probably just won't be able to help myself with all this stuff I'm learning about.
The big swindle that has been taking place right before our very eyes.
And with that, my friends, I tell you, enjoy your freedom and please live life with passion.
And if we don't speak before then, Merry Christmas.
I guess I really don't know what Christmas is all about.
Isn't there anyone who knows what Christmas is all about?
I'm Charlie Brown, I can tell you Christmas is all about.
My, please.
I'm going to be to the moon again.
Stars shining, shining on nature.
Mmm, yeah, shining on nature.
Mmm, yes, well, there is room here.
Oh, I'm going to be to the moon again.
Here we go.
Show me how I've got it all.
Yeah, you.
Some boy and boy, you and me, I got Jesus.
Mmm, yeah, shining on nature.
Mmm, yes, well, there is room here.
Oh, baby, Jesus.
Merry, merry, merry, merry.
Mmm, yes, shining on nature.
Mmm, yes, well, there is room here.
Oh, baby, Jesus.
In their world, the same conversation,
I didn't seem to get lots of the drop by the wall.
I didn't seem to be the Lord, I can't cry.
I can't cry the Lord, John, I'm born.
And they were so strong, and they were so strong,
and they were so strong, and they were so strong, and they were so strong.
And behold, they were the mechanics of the future,
but some people are,
but aren't you?
They used to be the same, they used to be a star.
You are the joy of you!
Show me how I've got it all.
Yeah, you. Show me how I've got it all.
It's our shining shine of nature
Mmm-mm-mm-mm, shine of nature
Mmm-mm-mm-mm-mm, yeah, it's well-dressed, you
All ready to leave
Some calling by you, I think I'm going to do
Mmm-mm-mm-mm, yeah, it's big, I'm going to do
Mmm-mm-mm, yeah, it's great
Hey, I'll cut them from having a 12-bit clock
And loads of beautiful lengths with this beautiful musical disguise
And say, glory to God in the highest
And on earth peace, we'll go toward him
Another pot show pot cast, stick it in your ear
Dromatically reduce ambient noise
By up to 85% with Sony's noise canceling headphones
At work, home or travel
Shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones
Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good