And now, deep inside the curry manner, the DSC-536, with the master of the manner, Adam Curley.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I think in a different day that's all we do.
That's all I do, everything must come and go.
There's nothing left in doing spells.
When life and love is all we've got.
With the memories time forgotten, I'm trying not to hear the cries.
Of all these broken hearts tonight, that's all I need.
You're all I need.
You make me feel, you make me feel so high.
Like life and love and everything is gonna be all right.
And you make me feel, you make me feel all right.
And I'm never gonna have to be lonely again.
And tonight is just a dream, a mental version of ecstasy.
To complicated and cloud the mind.
Keeping everything in life, I close my eyes and fade to black.
Try to let my head relax, that's all I do.
You know that's all I do, take some time to breathe again.
And you're getting everything in, at least that's what I'm gonna do.
Be sure to be on over you.
I've got the thought in some of my, I'll bring you different times.
That's all I need.
You're all I need.
You make me feel, you make me feel so high.
Like life and love and everything is gonna be all right.
And you make me feel, you make me feel all right.
And I'm never gonna have to be alone again.
And I, I, I, I, I, I.
You make me feel, you make me feel so high.
Like life and love and everything is gonna be all right.
And you make me feel, you make me feel all right.
And I'm never gonna have to be alone again at night.
You make me feel, you make me feel so high.
Like life and love and everything is gonna be all right.
And you make the feel
You make the feel so light
That never gonna happen to me alone
In our new night
From Pennsylvania, Rise Phoenix Rise
Boxing Josh
From the pod save music network
Not to go to mall
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code
What was that?
Little burp there at the end
Episode number 536
During that song
I realized that I
hadn't converted the phone messages
It came in today
I'm like, it's interesting
I'm looking at my castblaster play
And I'm thinking of myself
I'm missing stuff
It doesn't seem like I have enough stuff
Loaded up
So while in the last 30 seconds of the song
And as we speak right now
I mean this setup is so fantastic
That I've built here up in Adam's attic
That I could even do my nails
I'll bring you the show
Okay
You may hear some banging
Yeah
Throughout the show
The sky man is here
Nice guy, by the way
David, David the sky man
Yeah, really, really proper
It's like, do you mind if I smoke while I'm
Well, I'm outside
Because he has to put the dish up first
I'm like, um, do you mind if I smoke inside
Well, you're putting the dish up
So he got a lot of work to do
Because we got three
It's like the multi-room view
So I finally want to do it right
Give Christina her own skybox in a room
One for the masturbate room
Yes, you heard properly
And of course the HD
Or is that Britsa the HD
HD
For the viewing room
Which is going to be so freaking awesome
Once it's done
And of course I'm being nice to the guy
Because my HD hasn't actually arrived yet
And I got a whole bunch of warnings from people yesterday
They said, you know, oh dude
If you don't have your HD system there
They won't actually install
So I think I've got them fooled
I think it'll work out
Hey, lots of stuff to talk about today
Of course an update on free Trinity
Had some great conversations yesterday
And let me see
Hop- Hop- Hop- Hop- Hop- Hop- Hop- What should we do first?
Oh, uh, P-Dub
I mean
How can I be so silly
It's been a while since you sent something
So, you know, he can answer all your questions
So all of your problems too
It's P-Dub
Sound library pair man
Coming after you
What's he gonna do
He'll fix your misconceptions
And answer questions too
Turn nothing in the universe
And you can't be free
Sound library pair man
What?
Get lost
Everybody
Yo, Adam, P-Dub
So, oh wow
Your UK listeners question about upper class
Trashing of restrooms
Really struck home
When I was playing with my band
I had a regular weekly gig
A pub that catered to people who spent more for one beer
Than average folk spent for two six packs
After we set up all the equipment on the stage
I would go to the men's room
To wash up and change into my stage clothes
I was one of those people who believed that if you're being paid to perform
Well, you ought to be dressed
Of course
Better than if you were doing yard work
I agree
The bathroom was always clean and tidy
However
When we finished our last set at 3am
Those nice clothes I had put on
We're usually soaked in sweat
So I usually wanted to change back
Into my dry jeans and teach it
So I would head back to the men's room
It was usually destroyed
The floor would be covered with paper towels
toilet paper
Water from the urinals
Which were overflowing because they were so full of gum
If you missed yesterday's show
This isn't response to the question
Our posh people pigs
Guy who works at a...
Was it a law firm?
A lot of really wealthy
So-called sophisticated posh people
He said that the lavatories are just an absolute pigsty
And so his question was
Our posh people pigs
This is what PW was responding to
Big reds and trash
The toilet seats covered with vomit
Or worse than that
To Spencer's were
Brought out
What's worse than vomit
Oh
I'll take shit over vomit
Getting pulled off the wall
Mirror's busted
It actually looked like it was purposefully trashed
Now I'm certain that if I followed any one of the patrons in this pub home
Their own bathrooms would be spotless
Most upper middle class homes are
They think that it says that given an element of anonymity
Even the most educated and well-off person
Will reveal that they really don't give a shit about anyone else
Add the element of alcohol
And they become bold enough to demonstrate that rather deliberately
I
I once taped a note up over urinal in the men's room where I worked
For the British listeners that would be a urinal
It said, hey asshole
Your gum doesn't go away by itself
Some poor slob has to fish it out with their hands every day
You don't realize that
A few hours later when I went back to the men's room
Someone had written on my note
Glad it ain't me
And stuck a lot of gum to the wall
Next to the note
I believe that your real character is revealed by what you do
When nobody can see you do it
Good or bad
And right on PW
I have to say I'm done without analysis
And I think that there isn't added
I think it is a maybe a middle-class problem
You know not quite high up enough on the food chain to be
You know to have servants
But to feel like whoever is cleaning this bathroom is your servant
I think that's what it is
I personally never
Never ever ever
But maybe that's also because I've had businesses with bathrooms
And it's very important to have a clean bathroom in your business
And I watch that shit
I'm not the shit
But I watch that there's no shit
And when else got any experiences with that
Would love to hear from you about that
Comic strip
I think I'm actually getting closer to working this out with CSB
You know I said that I would be willing to work it out with them
And see if we can figure out a date and here we go
Hello Mr. Kerry
Without your blackberry
So maybe I will read email that I have just written to you
So that in case you would like to play it on the seat that you could play it
When it comes to me you don't have to play it
So I read I'm reading
Higher Adam
I am a bald
Said pasta
Who weighs at least two times as you being on the five feet and low
So you made this like seeing me in person
But good interview can be only in person
So I really want to do it in person
Regarding times
Between 12 and 16th February
I will be in Barcelona at 3GSM
The biggest conference about mobile phone industry in Universe
I also have other commitments
So before 3GSM
I can come to London only
Following days of February
The following days of February
Says Saturday
Fourth Sunday
9th Friday
10th Saturday
Please pick one of these dates and tell me three days in advance or earlier
And I will come
Otherwise please propose some time after 3GSM
Yeah
Don't you love it when I do my scheduling
Through the podcast?
Isn't that incredibly interesting?
All right, comments or blogger?
Can we do it like Monday or Tuesday of next week?
I know you're available this weekend but I really want to be home this week
I don't want to go into the city
So I can just stay home and maybe do a Monday or Tuesday or Wednesday
I can coordinate that with the trip to the shortage office
Today there are actually tapings
Crap, I didn't know that it would do it today
Or we could have maybe hooked up today
Anyway, and then I have another question
Can I do some video of the two of us?
Were you interviewed me?
I know there's lots of people who would love to see this short
Fat bald guy is that what you said you were?
I think it would be interesting
So let me know
Patricia and I just got back from
From buying a car actually
She's been complaining about the
About the Super V8
Because it's big
It's like she didn't remember
It could be any car we wanted
As long as it said jaguar on it
And I went for the turbo diesel
And like cool you know what put some biodiesel in it
And she's like, ah, it's small and it doesn't feel like a real car
And guys you've heard this before
From your women
Boy how sexist was that
Yeah, showing you know it's like
Ah, it's too big and I can't fit it anywhere
And I have to admit it
Thank God for the parking sensors
I'm pretty good with those
I can zip it right anywhere
But still it's a big car
So she wanted something small
I've been looking around
And I saw at a
A garage that I've been driving by for the past two years
When we were at the cottage
Of course we're at the manner now
It's sticking the curry manner
I drove by this place for two years
And the guy sells all kinds of interesting cars
It's not like a separate dealership
He does seem to sell a lot of smart cars
If you've never seen the smart car
I had one in Amsterdam
I love them to death
And I saw today as I was driving past
I happened to be in that neighborhood
I saw a smart roadster
Pitch black
Really interesting to look at
And so yeah, it stopped that check that out
What an amazing car
It's I mean if you're familiar with the smart
Then it basically has the same mechanics as the smart
Only it looks very smart
It looks really cute
Very sporty
It's a two-seater
It has an electric roof
That you can actually open while in flight
As I say
Or while you're driving
Has air conditioning
It has CD player
It has heated seats
It's really a nice sporty little vehicle
And so I took Patricia over
And she did a test drive
But she loves it
So
We are now owners of a smart roadster
It'll be here next week sometime
So now I'm actually considering
Trading in the
Super V8 for something
A little bit smaller
It's just ridiculous
You know we've got this circuit
Like an S shape drive way now
Which has really high walls
It's kind of hard to explain
I should do some video of the place
I have promised people pictures and video
But when you see it it's kind of like
Okay, I am now on a Bob's sled track
And I'm trying to make my way down
I also wouldn't mind getting an all-wheel drive vehicle
And so I saw a was an X type
Which is a significantly
cheaper model
Just you know and it's much more
Ford pieces on there if you will
Which I really dislike
But it was an all-wheel drive
It was pretty tricked out
Low profile wheels
Maybe just a much more sensible car
I got to look at that
I mean I'm happy with the jack
And of course Trinity is a gear and up
I got to get a new wheels in San Francisco as well
And of course you cannot for the life of you
By a
Diesel engine in the state of California
Car with a diesel engine
That sounds pretty stupid to me for you know
What is the deal with that?
Why can't you buy a diesel engine in California
It's supposed to be a
Fantastic
It's supposed to be great
It's particularly with biodiesel in it
Hey before I forget I want to say congratulations to Don and Drew
500 shows
Kids
I remember it like yesterday
Insert
Rewind music here
Yeah, it's right. They're about to do their show number 500
God
And Don is doing this advice show
Is it advice with Don dot pot show dot com I think it is?
Oh man, it's fantastic
You should hear
You should hear the one about
Well, I'm not going to tell you you have to go listen to that show
They've come a long way
I think one of the first podcasters to quit their day job do it full time
And then I'm doing video
And the the sky seems to be the limit with these kids
I love you so much
I wish I got more sexy pictures from Don
She used to send him to me
Don't get there anymore that much
Let's see what came in on the voice mail lines
I asked my listeners from down under
The guys who are working at the help desk
What exactly they did
And well the conversation works
They're going to have a look Scott from shit here again
This one's written there that the help desk that we work in
Is an internet related help desk
We actually do support for
Ideas so boil up
Satellite radio services things of that nature
So these are the guys that when your ADSL is not working you got to call them
But we all get you sit around in the morning when the
Value source code comes in
And sit there for
The 40 minutes of your show and then you have a minute of it
That's when when you call in and your DSL isn't working that's when you hear the
The current wait time is
40 minutes
In the cool music that you play in the rock
So yeah, it's like some hard rock for a stay at him
And yeah, we're looking forward to hearing you
The value source code is another thing you used to come
Perhaps you could be around for every day
So yeah, thanks a lot Adam
All right, I'm man, thanks for calling in and let me know what it's all about
Were you guys what you guys are doing
And that's really nice, you know that I don't know how many of the of there of there are how many of
There are you how many there are of you how many guys. Oh, see you squirrel
Haven't seen the squirrel in a long time. We're glad this place is fantastic
I can't wait until the spring and summer. We got a beautiful day today by the way blue skies
Temperature around 13 14 degrees sun is shining really really nice
Was I saying yeah, it's interesting that that you guys are all listening together. Are there any other offices out there that listen to the show together
You know, we can do some fun stuff
Yeah, we can
Yeah, I'm the radio that used to be
All kinds of programs typically between 10 and 10 a.m. and noon and
And then you could call up and congratulate someone they turn the radio up or you could make your boss the boss of the week. Oh, there you go
Let's make let's make your boss the boss of the week. That could be fun
Where you call in with the with a
It just calling to the voice mail lines or even better if you want to send me an audio
Comment through email. That's probably even better
And you know, you tell me why your boss should be boss of the week boss of the day or
Boss of the of the universe, whatever
You know how to do it
Yep, or Adam at podshow.com
You know you guys are getting really good at at feeding back about stuff that's going on in problems and
You know once in a while you just don't quite give me all the data like you know a
Soren went missing on the pod save music network or I can't play it. You know, well, until you need to give me a little more information and tell me exactly what
But the thing is you're calling in at least you're telling me the things aren't working
Here's another example
Be a Adam curry. This is Martin from the Netherlands
I've enjoyed listening to your source code very much
But lately I haven't been able to listen in very much because every time I try to
Play the daily source code on my pub player. It gives me a form of error
This is an item so much that I've been trying to find out where the problems started occurring and I found out that it was introduced
at daily source code number 482
So strangely all the daily source codes up and
an including
481 work perfectly and
Starting at steady source code 482 they stop working that was the 20th of October last year
Goodbye
So that that my friends is almost a perfect report
Because now I can go back we can go back and look at all the logs see if anything change
Maybe there was a de-gap change
Maybe there was a new version of cast blaster it could be a million different things that are going on
So thank you very much that helps the only other thing that would have been great is to know exactly what type of player you're using because
You're the it's so far the only report I've received so it may be a player issue somehow
You know these things can be pretty weird
But as I said I appreciate it
You know what the music means don't you
Time to clean out those pipes and sing along because we're about to free Trinity
USA
Open and make a good time today
I feel that I better watch you go letting everybody know that this is gonna be the better way
One three Trinity Trinity the quintessential luxury Trinity let the bio diesel set you bring
Trinity Trinity all right free Trinity we're about to send this
Child who covered
Child who colored Mercedes 300 turbo diesel station wagon from 1984 fueled entirely by bio diesel
On the west coast of the east coast of the United States and if we're lucky even beyond that yes today
KJ and I KJ being our head sales we saw we had a great conference call with the folks at Nokia Nokia
So yeah, how do you actually pronounce that is there correct?
Not correct pronunciation. I just say Nokia, but maybe it's a Nokia
A Jeff thanks man. I really appreciate the long Trinity song too, by the way, it makes a lot more fun
They are very interested to say the least
Which is good news
So we're working on the on the technology and and on the sponsorship
But yeah, it's not stopping this from from moving on and fact as I go into the into the Gmail here. Let me just see what we've
Okay, so the first thing is
There is a Google group now
Free Trinity save the world when viable prizes of course. I will put a link in the show notes a daily source code.com
So now we have a nail list and we can start communicating
Offline for the show, but online obviously through Google groups and now we can get some stuff set up
Who did that for me
Was that
Pop podcaster
Apollo Alto podcaster? Yeah, that's who did it exactly
Dude, thank you very much. That's a good start
What is this?
This is from from the Apollo Alto podcast. Adam. I was just catching up with the recent episodes data source code totally on board with the free Trinity campaign
Of course my first thought was how can I tie this in with my podcast? But after hearing Jeff Smith's theme song and all the ideas about the road trip
Caravan. I'm not thinking about my show anymore. I'm thinking oh my god. This could be so cool
By the way, on the project planner info management person will be happy to get things rolling. You see this is the stuff that I love now
I've had several offers
I know new
Was it new forward? I think from the UK also offered but you know to have someone actually in in the US and Apollo Alto
I presume you're in Apollo Alto
And oh it's Barbara. She's female too. Oh man
So then there's it would be great if Trinity could make her road show debut at the biodiesel conference
I'm sure she would be the bell of the ball plus there are hundreds of exhibitors signed up
Okay, so I'm I'm liking what I'm seeing here Barbara. I really appreciate you set up the google groups and let's let's open up this dialogue
Let's get it going. I would love to engage you
to help us out
And if you hadn't seen curry dot com I posted a video there or a link to a Jeff Smith's
Was it what's your show? It's Jeff Smith's day job and
And he he drove Trinity's sister unity and it's interesting you see him driving to what would be
Go from like to Louisiana I think and he had some significant trip to do and he
You know it stops off get some biodiesel on the way talks to people and that eats a sandwich
You know all the typical cool stuff we do and it's very entertaining podcast and you know that
That Jeff's gonna be a part of this so he's talking about the bio summit in Texas
That's a lot of stuff going on the Trinity needs to visit. This is why we need this frapper map set up tell on you
An Alex Fennie Fennie Vessie Fennie Vessie. I'm just guessing here. I think it's Alex Fennie Vessie
Has come up with some lyrics to yet another Trinity song. I Adam this is fugly Jay from the big ugly podcast
Hopefully this message hasn't found its way to you too late yet
I was just catching up on the DSC. I have a feeling this is not Alex so this is fugly Jay
Let's listen to him. I'll look for Alex this thing because that was pretty cool too
Monday afternoon
When I heard about the possible giveaway of Trinity the spring I was planning on doing a documentary style
podcast on
biodiesel and alternative fuels
My plan was to talk to automotive engineers mechanics lawyers tax attorneys in the like
Just to get a rundown on what the average consumer should expect if he decides to make the switch to bio fuels
As part of the project I was also planning on buying a diesel truck and
Setting it up for biodiesel or possibly straight vegetable oil
Since then however financial considerations of force me to put the project on hold
But it seems to me
Trinity would be
Perfect for this kind of project and it would be driven daily
Given my day job is a pizza delivery driver
So I just thought I'd throw that out there
Thanks for listening and you can find me at big ugly dot pod show dot com. All right, man. Thank you. Okay, so I don't know what happened there. I I lost
Lost Alex's little song lyrics there crap. All right
Well
I'll look for that tomorrow then for you. Oh shit and while I was talking we went right through we blasted through the freaking satellite window
Whoops, sorry about that Peter
Hi Adam Franco here. Let me tell you. I'm 100% into this free Trinity thing
Here in Italy use and production of biodiesel is severely limited by low so if you need someone driving across Italy
Getting speed tickets while running on illegal fuel. Well. I'm your man. Okay, stay cool up there in the
Curricatta comms
Pronto ciao Franco. All right, man. Excellent. Hey Franco. We're still working on that localization for Italy though as I promised all right
So it looks like
We are rolling again check the show notes for links to the to the Google group
So that we can communicate about this in
In some form of structured manner and I'll see if I can get in touch with barbersee if she can help us out
We get this thing rolling again. All I really need is a frapper map. I know exactly what I need
Where the mash up master is listening to the daily source code, huh?
Delta share a Charlie five three six your daily source code with Pete Hopkins
You got a crank this one up man jam those buds in deep because you'll like it the sound is awesome
title is
Sing
La la la la la there's a little more to map
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la era da da da where la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
To be loved, there's to be strong girl
You can laugh away the pain
Light again the listen to the song
Praise sound, it's like a lullaby
Believe it or just leave it
But you don't know until you feel it
Oh yeah
And then we can sing this song
And it won't feel wrong
To let the melody
Wash away you
Oh yeah
La la la la la la
There's a little more to learn from the brain
One
La la la la la
No one has to have the essence on their
Oh yeah
La la la la la
There's a little more to learn from the brain
One
La la la la la
No one has to have the essence on their
Oh
That's nice isn't it?
It's like a pedopkins
From the pot safe music network title that is become
He's from California
influenced by the Beatles and Stevie Wonder
Yeah, I don't know a little bit of Stevie Wonder in there
That was nice let's say facts
Sing a guitar, songwriter producer
Resides in Hollywood, California
genres, EHR, pop, sol alternative
Influences, Stevie Wonder, Jeff Buckley
And everything in between sounds like Jason
Moraz, Maroon 5, John McFuckett
You sound like yourself man
Who else has played that song let's say
That's what's a cool about the pot safe music
That we can see what other shows have played
Played the artist
Uh oh
We have no connection
Ah
Boy it happens
You know what's going on
Skyman's here
All right
Well that's it for today
I think we accomplished a lot
Thanks for checking us out
Adam at podshow.com
If you want to
Send anything off
And of course daily source code.com for all of the show notes
And links and places to go into surf
I'll talk tomorrow everybody have a good one
Bye bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear