Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony ear buds
were styled meat sound.
There are Charlie, 6, 9, 3.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I can't take the smell, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise.
I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise.
I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise.
I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take
the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the noise, I can't take the E. I have to help while
But keep the like a dango, it's a don't rip, it's seen the loss, because let's sit down at the beach, so watch it on the reef, so she can tell us stories to the girl back home
So, push me, cause I'm close to the edge, I'm tired, not too tired, it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head
And it's too much panic in this town, I'm going in deeper and deeper, I know it's my head, I know it's too much panic in this town, it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head,
I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, this is my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it's my head, I know it
Who's too much panic in this town?
I'm going on deeper and I'm alive
Don't push me
Calls, I'm close to the end
I'm trying to miss
Oh, I'm trying
Oh, I love the light
A little bit of French mash in the middle of the week
DJ Moore did a deep message
On the Daily Source Code episode number 693
Hey everybody, how you doing coming to you from the Curry condo
In Northern California, it is the Daily Source Code
Just as I started kicking things off there
I see Google notebook froze
That's interesting, so I have to get to that later on
Sorry about yesterday
A full intention to do a show for you
But you know how it goes in these long days
Actually, what happened was went out to dinner
Came back at 830
Wasn't bed at 9 o'clock because I knew I had to get up at 630
That is even if I could get through the night
Because these days, six hours, six and a half hours
That's it, I'm wide awake
I was asleep at 915, 930, slept until 630
It was fantastic, I've had such a great day
Really a lot of energy, man
It's nice, nice, nice, nice
And I prepared a pretty good show for you
Lots of good feedback
And in fact, doing a lot of stuff with music
In the past couple of days
And I can't wait until Fubar Friday
It's going to be awesome
I got a lot of songs that I got to share with you guys
All of course, part of the soundtrack to our lives
And well, it's been, was it two times in San
Fran in the past four weeks, more or less
Ranger Craig, still checking in from the rock
Let me know how things are going here
So all of them, how you doing?
It's Ranger Craig from the rock
So here I am driving home from out the trans
After a hard day, work out on the rock
And I see your twitter that you're sitting near the first
So what the hell are the first
F-P-R-F?
I think the sample system for 20 years
I don't know what the first is
Well, let me tell you, this was
Today we were in, we were called
The G-S-N conference room
A G-S-D, I'm sorry
To get shit done conference room
And the lights were all dim
Then with a bunch of geeks and we're all looking
Big monitors and like 8 million MacBook Pro's on the
On the long conference table
And Chris McIntyre
You know podcast Ali Dude, the Firf
Come on man, he's the Firf
Everyone knows the Firf
He's a big Twitter hound
At least I think he is
And now that I have the Mac
Hooked up eye chats so that it receives
Twitters
It's kind of interesting, you know?
I'm following along with
Lots of interesting little tidbits throughout the day
It's kind of like a
I don't know, it's kind of like
The nerd version of breaking news, you know
There's lots of dumb stuff on there
But it's kind of cool because you know
I can follow who I want to follow
And so I follow the Firf, you know, because he's always
Send in a little updates
Excuse me
So
What was I going to say?
Right, so this was kind of a mind-fuck
In a way because now I'm sitting right next
I'm like, you know what?
I'm going to Twitter and I'm going to say I'm sitting next to him
And see if he's online, which he wasn't by the way
Because he didn't respond
But then to come back to the condo
And Ranger Craig to have you say that you saw that
That's that's trippy
That's like a really interesting connection
So I tweeted hoping that I'd find
Chris Mac
You saw it, you called in the voicemail
I'm playing it back on the show
Maybe Chris Macintire will twitter me back
To complete the circle
I tried to send you a twitter back
Don't know if you'll see it or not
Finding out what the Firf is
If I knew what it was, I'd come and join you and sit too
So, well Adam, take care
You know I'm here in San Francisco
You never ever need anything
Come out and visit us on the rock
Or else just give us a call
I don't know if it looks here for a long or longer
Then I have greetings
Adios from the rock
Nice
Right on some social things to do
Interesting, that sounded kind of intriguing
Ranger Craig
What does that mean?
I think I do have a hot date later this week though
Having dinner with a Natalie Delcante
I didn't get to do it last time I was here
So, I have dinner that is
Kind of sad news in the
In the world of rock and roll, Kevin Dubrow
Lead singer of quiet riot
Past away in his home
At his home in Vegas
And I've met Kevin, of course I've met a lot of the
A lot of the dudes from quiet riot
You know that I'm a long time acquaintances
With Rudy Sarzo
Who played bass for a while in the band
And
Actually, I wanted to see
Madpod, you know, crazy as JD
Madpod has a
Kevin Dubrow quiet riot interview
At Madpod.com
I'll put a link in the show notes so you can go
Check that out
I don't see with any other news
I'll just check and see the article here
Hold on
How old was he 52 years old?
Discovered Sunday afternoon
God, that sucks
That's weird man
That's just weird
So many people passing away
Then, of course, he definitely enriched
The soundtrack to my life
He was one of the original glam dudes
So he will be missed for sure
Not just by musical lovers
I'm sure his family is well
So my thoughts are with him
So more, you know, more like really weird stuff
I was in the same get shit
Done conference room
What I sent this twitter as a test
And, you know, I have a sling box
And I haven't been able to get the sling box
The sling player to work with the
Well, I had but not on the Mac
Wasn't able to get it to work
With the one that we have hooked up
To a Tvo at the office here
So I wanted to just do a quick configuration
And I was able to
You know, basically get it to play
And, you know, I was checking out
Geek Brief and stuff like that
And then this message comes in today
Hey Adam Curry, this is Julia from New York
Calling you
I just wanted to let you know
I've been checking out the
You know, the pot show shows
They're actually on the Tvo cast
And I came back to myself
What's going on with some beef TV
And I noticed that the date was October or something
So I went online to see what episode you were up to
And you're actually up to 60 something
But the last episode that I downloaded on the Tvo cast
Is 237
So there must be some kind of
Fiendish you going on with between you and Tvo
Anyway, I hope you get that fixed up
And fuck you, I'm Curry
Oh, dude, thank you so much
That's so kind of you
Yeah, I saw a much more recent episode
So in this of course, it's a pod catcher
Essentially, right?
It's downloading this stuff onto your Tvo's hard drive
And it should be sitting there waiting for you
So for some reason there was a disconnect
Then maybe you missed an episode
I'm really not sure how the
How the Tvo cast works exactly
But I will say it's pretty cool
You know, I told you we have this like
Special pod show Tvo cast
The leader that we've created
And then we have the rating
You know, it's for what ages
It's appropriate and it's cool
It's a really, really high quality
Even though it's looking through the slink player
It was nice to see
So you know what?
I'll find out a little bit more
Actually, I think Brian, no one and PW
They're responsible for a big part of the chain
Because it does include transcoding
And all kinds of stuff that has to happen
To make this television quality for the Tvo folks
I'll ask them if they know exactly how it works
If you can sometimes miss episodes or what happens
And we'll find out
Let me see
I got so much to do today
Oh yeah, this is, this is important
So I've completely missed this one
The hard rock hotel, the hard rock
Is opening up a hotel in San Diego
Which I've been to San Diego
A couple times for some conferences
I didn't mind seeing a conference
Telled at the hard rock in San Diego
I'll tell you that
Brian knew it's going to be
Let me see what they got
This is obviously an advertisement
But there's something cool if you've got a band
Or if you know someone who's got a band
Because they're doing a special promotion
With audiostreet.net
And
Essentially
If they're going to do a battle of the bands
And if your band wins
I'll check this out
You'll be at the grand opening
Of the campaign
Black Eyed Peas
Opening up for you
Grand opening of the hotel
Let me see if there's a date on this
No
But it's pretty cool
You get on the bill with Black Eyed Peas
You'll perform at the brand new hard rock in San Diego
Which I haven't seen a picture yet
And I'll see if I can find a picture
And I'll also post a link
So that if you're in a band and you want to participate in this battle of the bands you can do so
There
Not didn't hurt too much, now did it
Hey Adam, it's Rafael over in 10 years on a
I remember a few episodes back
He were talking about
You know, the next, you know, unscripted reality show
Whatever
Would be like a
A choir or a drum line can show
Well, I was watching
Heroes and Journeyman today on NBC
And well, in the old, I see a commercial for
I can't remember exactly what it's called
But it's a choir show
I think it starts right December 13
There's some like that, but yeah, called it man
Yep, right later
Yeah, I'm telling you, you should take your choir to
That battle of the bands at the hard rock in San Diego
Or of course
These guys might participate
I don't know if they're still around
Some say I sound like the lead singer of this band
When I sing
Which, of course, means it sounds like he's in marble pain
We'll play
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
baby with your clothes, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Get out!
Get out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah,
yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, god or bra.
Now guys today, this, first match are...
podshow.com slash music link in the show notes, of course, a data source code.com.
You know, something else we were talking about at the office over the past couple of days was
this news about the iPhone. I've heard a lot of people talking about it and I've seen some blog posts
that the iPhone and the UK, a lot of the new owners are experiencing signal problems,
literally not able to pick up the, what is it, O2, the O2 signal in certain, and well, apparently,
and lots of spots. I've seen just hundreds and hundreds of postings and, you know, some folks are
saying that if they actually plug it into the dock, then it does work better, which I got to tell you,
this is coming back to me now, because of course, I had a US iPhone and I'll tell you, there's
no difference between the two because the US iPhone, that of course, I took over and I used the
the jailbreak to put in my existing AT&T SIM card, so I could use it over there with my existing
account. I two noticed that there were a couple of spots in the house where I would get
fine reception with the Nokia with the E61I, but I would not get any signal at all with the iPhone.
In particular, you'll just be honest about it in the crapper. I've got my own private
throne where I do my business. It's also where I drop the iPhone into the toilet.
You know, it's tricked out, right? It's got everything, including good Wi-Fi connection and
astraise. You know what I'm talking about? I'm a guy. I like to take my time.
And that's my meditation time. And I've had the iPhone in there when just unable to get a signal
unable to to send text messages, you know, that's actually how I noticed it, because I wasn't
getting any calls. And I was usually just using the Wi-Fi, but with the E61I, not not a
problem. And I too noticed that if I plugged it into the dock upstairs in the attic,
I would get more bars. I get full five bars. And you know, I understand that's RF, you know,
you basically expand the ground plane of your antenna. So I just like to say that I think the
iPhone just has inferior antenna technology built in. Talk about it with John C. DeVore Act today.
We'll probably bring it up on Noah Jenda. He said, well, yeah, it's all made of metal.
I like, yeah, maybe that could be part of it. But also think about all the people who got an iPhone and
had to switch to the new AT&T. And I've had singular and AT&T for a couple of years now. I really
don't have any problems with reception. I just really don't. I think I've said it on the show before.
But you know, those people that were complaining how AT&T sucks so bad, maybe a part of it was
because the iPhone just has inferior antenna technology.
Now, hopefully someone will pick this news up and go investigate it. I know that there's people out there
who understand how to measure antenna effectiveness and the radius. And I mean, you know, there's a lot of
people who understand that shit. It's really, when it comes to RF radio frequencies, it's a lot of
advanced mumbo jumbo science as far as I'm concerned. But there are guys who know how to, and
gals who know how to figure this out. And they should do that. Just you see what the, what the deal is.
I just think it's a design flaw. And I'll bet you that Apple knows about it, too.
I'll bet you they do. And you know, there was something about cramming it all into the nice little
flash, little box that made it all go wrong. Anyway, I'm a couple of other phone questions.
Actually, uh, one about the E61 and the Nokia 810, the internet tablet. I'm loving so much.
How do they sound good? I don't know. Thanks very much. You'll thoughtful response to my question
about the five way navigators on the 810. All right. That's what I talked about on Monday.
He had a question. If since it's now in a different place from the N800,
if it was awkward using it. And, you know, I think honestly, not really, it is different.
It does make a difference. But I'm, you know, I'm using it more with the keyboard open than
using the touch screen. So yeah, there is a difference. Yeah, I think you've, you know,
I take it on the head and it's silly. I'll need to go to Nokia's design skills in deciding
where to put the thing in the first place. It's funny after nearly 10 years of using touch
screens on palms. I've been touch screen free since May with the E61 and it's kind of forgotten
touch screen was even there. Yeah, I got to tell you, you know, you do get used to it. It's,
yeah, you can get used to touch screen, but it's not the end all to be all. You know, I'm,
I'm into the, what you call it, the five way button. It works for me too. I agree that E61,
I don't miss the touch screen at all. Talking of E61, I, which I know you love. Last week
a firmware upgrade came out for the version 1.1 something to the two points. Oh, I got to get
that one. I did mine, eventually, and to change the product code because the Nokia software
update, it kept telling me the update wasn't available, but I used a program called Nemesis. Nemesis
services or NSS to old to the product code to when I found on the internet. That sounds really
user friendly. I've read it successfully. Oh, good. The only thing that isn't so smooth and seamless
is the backup restore because it's got a few badly behaved programs. Yeah, I've noticed that that
backup restore just in general, it doesn't really work. You know, I think that the platform just
doesn't feel that mature, you know, I'm always missing settings and there's all kinds of stuff.
And it's on the E61 eye as well as on the N8010. That's just not completely great yet.
There, uh, disappeared completely despite being backed up and then restored,
allegedly restored, and some that come as corrupted stubs, we then have to be reinstalled.
Yeah. And so much say they're there, but they're not. They're going to ask the open. Yeah.
But by and large, once you get them all back in, the sounds working the way it was with the
new firmware. Yeah. And then you kind of shake it or it was shaking around and then, you know,
bounce it once or twice on the bed and then it works. I know that's my experience as well.
Can't wait to do it again. Can't wait to upgrade the firmware. And it is better in some respects.
So, though, knock it up, publish it, change bugs. They're all falling down in the dark.
Time to work out what exactly has changed. It's not so easy to explain why it's better.
It just hits you so we've got to have it. Anyway. Yeah. Bye, right now. And of course.
Yes. Fuck you. Adam Curry. Thank you. I love it so much when you guys do that.
Dean Regal says Adam, a long time listener of the show. I've come to appreciate your comments and
products that you use. I was wondering if you could tell me how browsing the internet on the
Nokia N95 compares to the iPhone. I want to get one of these two products but can't decide.
I've seen the iPhone and the way you surf the net, but have not seen the Nokia in action.
Thanks. And fuck you, Adam Curry. Am I going to get rid of this? Well, I've
ever lived that one down. Okay. I'll get an N95. I'll let you know. I have looked at it. I've
had it in my hands several times. And Natalie Del Conti was using one today. And Chris Jacob,
Headmaster Sales, Weasel Extraordinary, uses, I think he uses that the most. He has like 18
phones with them all the time. But of course, you know, six Weasel. So I'll find out. I have to say that
you know, I'll stick by it. The whole zooming that pinching thing that that you do with the iPhone.
That's awesome. That is just awesome. It's just a great way to zoom in and just, you know, you can do it.
We want you can be doing everything with one hand. It's cool without a doubt. But it doesn't make
every other device useless. And, you know, my biggest problem is just it's really the battery life.
That's started. It's just the basics of that. You know, my day is just longer than seven hours.
Sorry, Cooper, do you know, can help you? Hey, I have a video from the Daddycast. Just wanted to pass along
that the Sony headphones that you're promoting. I hop on line last night to take a look at them.
And I've got to thank you because now I've got something on my Christmas list that my left
can get. I mean, it's really cool. If I use my, you know, I found you're listening to the iPod,
you're working out, or you're working out in the yard. And the cord always gets in the way.
So I've been looking for the past couple years for something that wasn't totally expensive,
but would still get the job done. And these look to be perfect. They've got different headphones,
styles that are Bluetooth, and in a little iPod, Bluetooth plug-in. So it would be perfect.
And just wanted to say thanks. And it's a great product. If you haven't seen it yet,
they should check it out. I may not talk to you soon. Have fun out on the same frame.
Yo, yo, I'm back. Yo, I'm PD Love. Thanks, man. Appreciate that report.
Yeah, I'm on an Amazon trip these days. I'm posting links to stuff on Amazon so you can go buy it.
And it works. It really does. I'm liking it. So it doesn't even matter if if the product is
from an advertiser or not. I'm just putting links in because, you know, I really just want to see
people going buy stuff. And you do. It's not like I make a ton of money. Because what's funny
with Amazon is, and you put those links in, and then, you know, people may go in because they click on
the N-800-10 link, which, of course, will change. We're getting pretty close to getting all of our
codes and everything sorted out. So we can give you guys a real discount. But already, people are
buying it through that link through Amazon. I know you can't wait. And you're probably going to
wind up paying 50 bucks more at least if, you know, at least 50 bucks more than, uh, than a pod show
will be over to offer it to you for. But yeah, you can't wait. Go ahead. But then you people click
around. They buy other stuff. And they buy books and they buy music. And, and it's fun to watch,
you know, to see what people have bought after just, I guess, going in and getting lost and
surfing around. And I get a hit for that. You know, I get some kind of credit. So it's cool.
Now, let me see two more phone calls. So we do that. Let me just remind everyone of, uh, of the
number you can call if you want to participate in the show.
6, 3, 5, 7.
Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip.
And here is our EU correspondent greetings that I'm carry. Here is CSB with another update
about EU. Good. So, allegedly, the reason why work were the second started was because
Poland, the nice Germany and extraterritorial highway between the main territory of Germany
and the detached eastern part of Germany, called East Prussia. Interesting. I didn't know that that was
the actual moment that World War II started. I know that it started with Poland, in Poland,
involving Poland. I didn't know that part. Thank you. German, it's Os Poison.
Of Poison, yeah. Well, starting December 21st, so very soon, with December 21st, 2007,
there will be no longer any border or passport controls between German and Poland and
such situation as it was during the, what were the second would never be possible now.
You've got it, sir. It was for, for, for. Because that situation would be moved now, such issue.
So, why it is because from the 21st, December 2007, the so-called Schengen Zone,
Schengen is a small village in Luxembourg. Schengen Zone will be extended and will cover now also
Eastern European members of EU. So now it will be possible to go from Finland through Estonia,
Latvia, Itoeania, Poland, Germany, France, to Spain, by car, without any passport or border controls.
So, no, is that good? That's the good news, I think, and the peace in Europe is spreading.
So, thank you and cheers. Thank you very much, CSB. That's cool, man. Of course, it's more important
to go from Spain of North, because Spain has all the good, you know what I'm saying?
Hey Adam, we're coming from the hamster. I'm a run-pull meet-up group organizer and I'm a coacher
for the C. Coast Area for his campaign. I love your support of him. I'm so appreciative.
I know it's helped out a lot, but man, I'm stressed. Come on, man. We need you here. Would you be
possibly willing to come to New Hampshire? We need to win New Hampshire? Okay, hold on a second, this is
interesting. You know, I endorse Ron Paul, would love to see him become president of the United
States. I think he's got a great agenda. His agenda is a very small booklet. You can just google it.
It's called the Constitution. Google Ron Paul, if you want to know more, and I'd love to help out.
I'm not quite sure what I can do, and I'd have to work out the timing, because I guess it's coming
up soon, the New Hampshire primary. So, give me some details. Give me some info. When do I have to be there?
What do I got to do? Do I have to bring the Posse? We need to win Iowa. If you have Iowa,
opportunity at all. To go to Iowa? I know you're far away, man, but it's okay.
Team here and did like a college speaking tour. I got to come up with something else.
This college speaking tour, I don't think is going to work. Let's think of something I can do.
Or we could do, maybe. Should I go meet a whole bunch of people in New Hampshire and Iowa?
If I could make it work in the schedule, I'd try, I'd move stuff around. That could be fun.
The date, I know, but we could whip it together for you. We're amazing here in New Hampshire,
the grassroots. I mean, we could just whip it together, and I'm sure a college tour. I'm sure
all the college students know who you are. Is it possible at all? This is life or death, man.
We've got to have Ron Paul Wynn, and we still have a huge uphill battle here in New Hampshire.
Even though things are going pretty well, we have these evil people.
Julianne and Romney who are just dominating, and I just saw some poll numbers and they actually don't
look that great. What do you mean by that?
1% of people say they would never vote for Ron Paul. Really?
Don't spread that number around, but that's what. A little late for that.
Polls, I don't believe in polls. What companies are doing the polls? How are they polling?
It's it. Please. What I'm really curious about is, do we really have a vast army on the
interwebs who are going to go out and vote for this guy or not? That's what I need to find out.
One thing's for sure. If it's not this time around, it will be there will be another time around.
But this God wouldn't be nice. When we accelerate so much, wouldn't so many great things happen
if we got even just getting Ron Paul through the primaries.
Getting on the Republican ticket. Can you just imagine what that would mean for the power that we
ourselves harness amongst this vast network? We're millions of people who flame and talk and yell
and shout and reach out and are helpful and there's humanity and love and all emotions.
Black and white, all the time running through these wires, these series of tubes.
Now we finally have a chance to go and do something. All it will take is a lot more of what we're
doing already, renting and raving, posting and motivating, being opinionated. And then just on one
day, you got to get your ass out of the house and go take a box. It's really not that hard.
You really don't have to do that much. I know a lot of you are undeclared. You can really make a
difference here. You can really really make a difference. Fuck the polls. That's what the poll
numbers in the hamster look like and so we need and those are just for people being pulled. So
there's a lot of people not being pulled. College students that never voted, they're not being
pulled. So we have an opportunity here to reach some people who were never of age to vote before.
And the college students are going to be one of our biggest supporters. Yeah, that's a good point.
That really is a good point. And they're the ones that are online. So propagate my friends.
We can get through to them. They're really mixed up because they've been brainwashed, man.
They've really been brainwashed by the people who say that government has to be our
nanny. And government has to solve every global problem. And anyway, my name again is Wivkomo,
my number six. Yeah, I'm sorry. I really should have listened to that before. I didn't
listen to the whole thing. If there's any way you can help us. The center of the universe as far
as winning this election, we have to win the answer or come in second. Take it easy, man. And
oh, but fuck you. I fucking do it. I'll be out there. Let me give you some details. Okay, let's
get this going. What can we do? Can we do, uh, we get some potsafe artists? Uh, there's got to be
someone in New Hampshire, somewhere nearby. Can we just hang out? Can we just cause a ruckus?
Yeah. I'm, you know, I'm, you know, all the writing and all the talking. And now it's time for some action.
We got to go ahead and do something. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's the most important question
of the day. Hey. Adam, it's Kevin from Slechter, Noraks. Our line. It was your weekly stalking message. Yeah.
He calls me every single week with the same question. So I'm fine as well. Just to answer him.
It's again the one, no, whatever, Anthony Trinity.
Uh, that whole project has gone to shit.
Big problems with insurance.
Big problems with production insurance.
Uh, sucks.
Uh, a black mark on my career.
Uh, one or no, if you're still not smoking and how that's going for you.
Uh,
No, I've fallen off that wagon.
Relatively severely.
Uh, but there's always the new year.
Also, I want to know if you got the Hulu, uh, invite that I sent you and what you think of that.
Uh, yeah, I did.
And I talked about it on the show and I, uh, I think I thank you.
I appreciate it.
Um, and it's just, you know, it's all right.
It's, uh, it's okay.
It's, uh, it's their shows.
Uh, I'm not going to watch him because the writers aren't being paid for it.
So screw him.
You know, if, if they'll pay the writers for all those great shows that they're putting up online,
I'll go watch him.
I'll watch their advertising.
Oh, by the products.
I know I will.
But out of principle, not screw him.
Not going to go back.
I don't care how good it is.
Fuck you, Adam Curry.
I have a good day.
All right, man.
Thank you.
I want to play one more from the soundtrack to my life for you as, uh,
we kind of, uh, slip over the hump of the week.
And move closer towards the last month of 2007.
Hello.
How are you?
Have you been all right?
Through all those lonely loneliness.
It's about saying.
I tell you everything.
You've become that deadly point.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey.
Are you feeling?
Are you still the same?
Won't you realize the pain for deal with deal?
Well, we've got a dream.
I just can't believe.
If I'll fade it out of you.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, I, oh, oh, no no, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, girl, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I, oh, oh, oh, it, oh,more, going. the side again, come, come,
I love you
Okay, so no one's answering
Can't you just let it ring a little long along
I love you, I'll just stay with you
Who shadows on the night?
Let it ring for never more
Four days
Let it ring
Do it, do it, do it
Like night, do it, do it
I look you through the sky
I love you, I ain't gonna see you through
But now, what new world
The little picture finally comes true
I'm out to let my wife
Give it some time
I'm living in fire
I'm out to let my wife
Give me some time
I'm living in fire
I remember exactly where I was
When I first heard that song, I played it
Almost every single night
On my turn table in my room
I was 14 or 15 years of age
Telephone line, electric light orchestra at the end of today's Charlie
We are taught that when we die
We move on to a better place
Fill with a bliss of unconditional love
Welcome to those who have gone before us
But some of us never complete our journey
Some of us stumble on our path to the light
Some of us remain imprisoned between worlds
Trust not by the living nor the dead
Never wasting me
Never increased
Never free, never free
The journey begins January 2008
At table wrappers.com
DailySourceco.com
Adam at podshow.com
Talk to you tomorrow
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
A magic headphones without wires
Imagine headphones without wires
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset
A rechargeable listening experience
With 11 hours of music playback
So you and your music are free to move
Take up yours at Sony.com slash headphones
Sony wireless headphones
Your music are unplugged