In a world where women were comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you get your entertainment.
This is the pod show network, no big media, no excuses, no BS.
Delta Chericharley 673.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
In the next generation, when you coach anyone here, you should believe in me.
I like the thing I'm trying to make sure I don't be hard-casting.
It's very curry.
I never throw bar just to see the stars and with some face, I can't be bar.
I never bother to read about all the movies.
I never bought hype for MTV.
I mean, Oscar weren't nice to me.
But what do I love to care about your sanity?
The sea up face gets near the end time.
Well, it's not for me to find the power to rise.
Get to you.
So now I wonder, when do we go?
And the time isn't like the feeling it lasts forever.
But do what you can to make some noise.
But try to make it believe it what you do.
And midnight hats are all the same.
You're wearing a mask without any shame.
You need them all to believe that you're their fantasy.
See our face stands still in time.
Well, it's not for me to find the power to rise.
Get to you.
So now I wonder, when do we go?
And the time isn't like the feeling it lasts forever.
Girl, she knows
Why did the mirror change?
What do you want to bring?
Where's that girl she knows?
Where did she go?
See your face dance still in time
World is not for me to find
So I'll laugh at you
That's true
So now I wonder
What do as she goes?
Stand by
When the time is in right
The feeling is never
So now I wonder
What do as she goes?
Just tickles my fancy
I saw that
One of the top ten played songs
This week from the pod save music
Now we're good
Belmonds
Where'd she go?
Of course it's
DataSourceco.com in the show notes
Interesting band from New York
They've seen the buyer here
They've shared the stage with such national artists
As collective soul, vertical horizon, mole
Everclear and winger
Winger
My goodness
Ah guys
You gotta let me know how
Keep Winger's doing
I still have
What do I have?
I have a gold record
And a platinum record on my wall
From back in the
Back in the good old Winger days
Have kipking me a call
A source code
Episode 673
Gray Overcast Day
Here at the manner
In Guilford on the west side of G-town
I'm all spifed up
Shavin
Don't you think I
Smell nice
Nice and clean
In the wife beaters of course
I don't want to
Scrunch up the shirt
Got my black black jeans on
Got my eggs on
Ready to bring you a show
Just before I head off to the city
What's this?
We can't make a habit of doing too many shows a week now
Everyone will get confused
The N800 is load up with the loaded up
With shows to listen to on the commuter
I've got a big meeting with
Unilever
Anglo Dutch company
Who mainly make package goods
So little things you consume
And shiny packages they sell
Worldwide
I think we're meeting with the homo brand
Yes, make all the jokes you want
Meeting with the homo brand today
Hopefully we'll turn something good
For the UK and maybe worldwide
Those guys are pretty aggressive
I'll tell you that
Actually I should say gals
It seems like the entire building
Which is this beautiful
Building on the Victoria
Enbankment in South
I think it's Southwest London
In the Unilever house
It's wall to wall women who run the show
There and I have to say they're all pretty hot
So I'm going along for the ride
For the meeting today
Four o'clock this afternoon
Lots of stuff to do
And before I forget
I had this promo
I've been floating around my desktop
And into my DSC folders
And somehow I didn't get it
Into the show in the past couple days
So please let me
Let me play this for you
Coming 31st of October 2007
It's a big number
What is it?
One of my STD
Oh for God's Satan
They come trying to record a serious promo
For Adam to play on his show
I'll take you on about the pod zones
And in 50
Coincidentally on Halloween
Sorry, let's get that cheap plug in there
No problem
We're going to be almost as old as I'm in carrying
Talking of width
You have a sender thing
It's just glad I'm in the end
When you should say that I was Satan for Halloween
Good call
That way you can look at the pictures
Whilst listen to the pod zones 50 episode
See, I can do cheap plugs too
Oh nice
And he can download it from podzone.bt podshow.com
Exactly
The podzone 50
It's a big number
Podzone.bt podshow.com
Oh and Adam
You know, fuck you
God!
Thank you
Lovely
Ah, that makes me feel good
And alive and loved
One other show I want to bring your attention to
His blabbermouth TV
This is sponsored by CoverGirl
Makeup
It's kind of like
The view for teenage girls
Produced by podshow
I think it but you know
Three teenage girls who really are into this shit
Well of course it includes a lot of Brittany
And Lindsey low hand and
Fashion and stuff
And of course
Makeup tips
So I guess see if I can turn Christine on to that
See if I can get her to endorse it
Blabbermouth.podshow.com
So the the past couple of shows
Starting with last week and certainly
Last Friday
Have stirred up quite a bit of controversy
On the phone lines
Lots of different opinions
Of course the focus has been very specific
You know we've gone from
Conspiracy theories to
Skullfuck the rotting corpse of the TSA
By the way
That never will go away
At least
Not my attitude towards him
Into
Presidential elections in the United States
It's what it has done
Is it significantly
Made the numbers jump up on
Download requests for the show
Although I can't really see what happened yesterday
Something must be broken or whatever
God you have no idea how how
Massive
The amount of data is that comes in for stats
And has to be processing
Whole separate unit now
Like three people
Called the big number project
Who do nothing but massage and crunch
And try to detect the anomalies
And oh man it's it's quite a big deal
So anyway so I don't know how yes
So they did but I did put in my what
We'll get to all that stuff later
First let me
Let's check in with with you guys
The audience who who do have some opinions
About what's going on with with your
Cha Cha
And I'm
I'm really feeling the sucks
I'm driving and it's raining
But anyway I'm just listening to
Monday show here and I heard that you were
Thinking about back here on fall
And so we can check those websites
Seems like a pretty candid
Everything is getting
Internet presence is doing twitter
He's got youtube videos
He's even doing
Looks like just in TV
That's all low and good
But I don't like the idea of an independent company such as
Potso
And your whole thing about being independent
And all this backing
A politician
Whoa
Stop right there my friend
Oh, let me make it very clear
All the opinions expressed on the daily source code
Our mine and mine only
And there's no influence
Either way
From me to Potso or Potso to me
I think that's pretty evident by the fact that
I only do shows when I can do them
So it's not like
I'm being forced to pump out shows
I would never
Never have Potso take any kind of political stance for any reason whatsoever
So this is this is all entirely me my friend
And of course that is the most difficult part of my life
Is separating this part of my life
Which is really talking to an audience
An audience I love dearly
You are my psychiatrist
You're the only ones I get to really
Really open up to when it comes to a whole bunch of issues
That quite frankly other people in my life
For just not interested in or bored
So I'd have to correct you there
I'm not asking Potso to put any resources behind this
This will just be solely me
Just to set that straight
And telling everyone else that we should do and racing money for them
No, no, no, I'm not telling anybody anything
Dude, I'm just talking here, okay?
Seems like you're going into the whole corporate thing
That you were trying to get us all to go away from
Talk about what?
What?
Money in all this
And then you're telling us that
Maybe we could race some money for one of these candidates
But just a
I don't seem to fit
So uh
Well, okay
Look
I desperately want the system to change
I'm over here in the UK and just as an example
And I feel very loved by the British people
I feel very welcome by the British people
But the one thing they all say without fail is
We hate your president
We hate that he dragged Tony Blair into his crap
We hate that
The UK and the USA are so entwined
Into all of these
Global issues that really just
I know the crap out of every citizen as far as I can tell
So I want to change that
I desperately want to change that
And it's my responsibility
Obviously as an American citizen to help change that
And to evaluate
And if I think that there's someone out there with the right message
I'm going to back that person
Not as a podcaster
But as a human being as a citizen as a world citizen actually
How can anyone argue with a lot of the points that Ron Paul is making
Get out of Iraq
Is that what everyone wants?
Isn't that what 75% of the country wants?
Or do we want to go with the
With the Hillary
Slash any other Democrat
I mean any other Democratic agenda
Which is 2013
Come on
So
Yeah
You've got to use the system in order to take over
You have to use it
So the way the system still works in America today
Is by advertising
That's how you get your agenda
Push through
That's how you
That's how we buy
Washing powder
Is by repetition of advertising
Quite honestly
It just works
I hate to tell you
Sometimes a really good ad
Will do
Will do very well
Just by itself
And that of course is what
What I believe the future of advertising will be
Is just turning it into great content
Just one other thing
While I'm on that topic
A couple people sent me this
Let me see if I can find it here
This is from the independent
I'll put a link in the show notes
This article
Oh
All that
Google notebook is failing
The ones again
Here we go
Apparently
Over a ten month period
At least 77 television stations
We're making use of so-called
Video news releases
VNRs
And these are
Frequently put together by
The healthcare industry
But also by
The Bush administration
Apparently
And what it is
It's a pre-packaged news item
That you just send out
It's like an electronic press kit
If you know what those are
So you get some video
You get a slug
Which is like a story line
And what these 77 stations
Have been doing is literally taking
These video news reports from
It says the Bush administration
Not quite sure what that means
But these segments have been
About the success of the war
And Iraq
And of course the healthcare
Video news releases
Have been about a great product
That they happened to own and be selling
And it's illegal
You cannot
On public airways
To take a commercial endorsement paid for
By someone else
And presented his news
So
There's a lot going on in media
And we're just not quite powerful enough
I don't think
Although it seems like the internet
Is doing quite well
For Ron Paul in fundraising
The way to do it is still the old
Fashioned way with advertising
It's just the fact I can't
Can't help it
Yeah
I was
The slug
And
Yeah
Thank you
It doesn't matter what you say
As long as you end up
The call that way
I just feel good about you
Very concerned about our
Buddy James
Who
I think he's been going through
Kind of a rough patch himself
Had some offline email
Conversations
He's been yelling at me
And I'm like dude
What's going on
I got up on the wrong side of bed
But yesterday he called in
Or maybe it was last night
I do want to share this one with you
But again I'm trying again
Not a copy now
I'm just trying again
Because I'm not annoyed
I'm just so dismayed with you
Because as I said before
There's something change with Adam Curry
Very recently
I don't know if it's
Potual and it's success
And the money's rolling in
And Mr. Curry's change is attitude
I know you're a rich man
I know you've never pushed that in
People's faces
But just something seems to change with you
Wow
Okay
So you know
This is again
I said earlier
I love you guys
So whenever a loved one says to you
You've changed
That is pretty much the first
Conversation before a breakup
So I'm extremely worried about what James is saying here
However
Whatever has changed
James, I'm sure you're about to tell us
Don't forget
I am a human being
Human beings go through life
And discover things
And morph themselves
And change and become an image
They want to be
And
And I'm fucking human
So let's see what the problem is with that
The whole American thing
The whole Youngspirce
The Brits seems to be an underlying
Current in the Daily Source
Code
No, that's when the Brits ring
Yeah, okay
Partly have something
Partly say about mountains
But the attitude was no
You're wrong
No, you're wrong
No, no, no, no, no
I don't think I said that
James, I think what I said is
To quote statistics
Comparing a country with
300 million people
And to the number of
Gun related deaths
Versus a country of
6 million people
Is not a fair comparison
You need to do it by percentage
This is nothing to do with
The ranks versus Brits
This just has to do with statistics
No, no, no, no
Not one little bit
We're not seeing where right
We're not seeing that
Great Britain's fantastic
Because there's a lot of alcohol
No, we're not
They're not right
But you're not right
Actually, I think that's one of the
Bonus is of the United Kingdom
When you guys drink alcohol
You get fantastically
Funny, so I see that as a plus
Actually
Golden Guns and the story
It isn't a right
There, it shouldn't be there
Guns should be banned
For stop the river
No, man
Okay, let's ban guns
Full stop the river
Then you know
Look at the amount of guns out there
And what we're actually doing with them
And I'll just say we as the United
States
I won't even involve Britain
Even though you're still in Iraq
And you're still in Afghanistan
And so if guns are evil
Then let's stop it across the board
You know, or
Grab
Unfortunately, James
It's a right that was put into the
Constitution of the United States of America
It's only a couple hundred years old
It's the rules of our country
And if you don't like the rules of the country
Don't come to America
It's okay, it's no problem
I happen to believe that
That it's a pretty interesting
Amendment
And don't necessarily have a problem with it
Because, you know, even though I don't have guns
I do believe that there's a reason for having them
And wow, you know, we could have a whole argument about that
But I'll just leave finish here
People in this story
Now, guns don't kill people, people, people
Yeah, exactly
I'm just so, I don't know
I've already emailed you about this
And I kind of explained it in the other way
It's a very difficult thing to explain
But Adam Curry's changed
And the daily source code's changed
And everything seems very American
And you'll ask comment on the DSC
And I know this is a long comment
And I know you probably won't play it
But enjoy your freedom
That is such a blink at American view
Do you realize how many people in this world
Don't have their freedom
But still
Ah
James
Yes, of course I realize that
Those of you who have it
Should be happy with it
Enjoy your freedom
Absolutely
Enjoy your freedom to walk around
And travel
And have commerce
With other people and countries
And yeah, enjoy your freedom
What's wrong with saying that
If you have it, you should be very happy
If you're really happy about having freedom
Perhaps you'll help other people gain freedom as well
Listen to the daily source code
My big steel and borrowed it
To get a bit of the outside world
Enjoy your freedom
God, that's a fucking stupid thing to say
Huh?
I'm not even going to bother saying
Fuck you, I don't care
Fuck you, I'm fucking horrible
And if you think it's funny
Sorry
Sorry, it's the fucking thing that's funny
Dude
You're free, you're free, man
If you're not, let me know
How you're enslaved
And yes, of course
If part of enjoying your freedom is
If possible, helping other people
Enjoy theirs
A couple other comments on the gun stuff
Hey Adam
I just heard the message from Barkey
Commanding on guns in the United States
It's killing too many people
I'm currently in Switzerland
And I heard that Switzerland
As even less strict laws than the USA
I'm a self from
From the Netherlands, so I'm not too sure about
What exactly the thing is
But it seems that there are over
Three million automatic rifles in Switzerland
Owned by people keeping them in their house
And it's even the case that when Swiss males
Sign off from their tour of duty
That they get to take your gun home
So, if you want to look at it, percentage vice
Probably Switzerland will beat the USA
But still there are not as many shootings
As far as I can see here in Switzerland
And there are in America
Perhaps it is the people killing people instead of guns
So, as I say
Now I get the hell out of Switzerland
It's a calculator
That's an interesting alternative ending there
Yeah, so there you go
Clearly there are other problems of foot in the United States
If that's true
And I believe it is
I'm sure it is
There's a whole bunch of other problems going on
I think the war on drugs
Probably fosters more gunfire and gun killings
And anything else
But that's just my twisted reality
I guess one more about guns killing people
Hi, it's Dean from Tom Bezier California
Are you doing?
Just so I don't forget later
It's fuck you
Wow, nice, nice, nice alternative
Yes
Now I'm listening to conversation about guns
United States and all of line
A couple things from the mind
Guns don't kill people
People do that
That's a great book
Take the idea of the day
It's basically
Guns kill people
The same way spoons
Made Rosie a Donald bat
Now there's that going too
But really I think if you go back to the reason
Not for fathers
Gave us the right to their arms
One of the reasons was
If you were living in England at the time
The only people could have a gun
You could hunt
Where the lords of the manor
So to speak
Nobody else was allowed to do that
That was one of the reasons
That we were
Allowed to carry our arms
And we could go out and hunt
Nobody could keep us from doing that
For feeding our families
The other reason was
If we got invaded
We all had guns
So there was that too
So that's a really good point right there
And I'm just going by the constitution of the United States for a second
This is actually something
Somewhere I saw a video
Where Ron Paul said this as well
And it may sound really twisted
This logic
But just bear with me for a second
Okay
So the original idea I agree
Was to protect from any enemy
Outside or within
That's very critical
Because I believe that the real enemy of the United States right now
Is inside inside the White House
Inside
Capital building
It's inside
So the right to bear arms
Of course to provide and hunt
And all that stuff
But yes, it was intended to protect
So if anyone showed up
And said
We're invading
We say, oh yeah
Well why don't I put a cap in your ass
Motherfucker
And if you kind of
Take that all the way through
Well to 9-11
This is what I saw Ron Paul saying
And as weird as it sounds
I really feel kind of good about the statement
If the airlines had been able to exercise their constitutional rights
And had been able to protect
Their customers
By
Allowing pilots to have guns
Or having some other form of security
Which I do believe is their responsibility
Not the government
It's their responsibility
Just like the trains are responsible
For protecting its customers
Which they don't do
I might add
Just as buses
Or the tube
I think of you know
These services are all responsible for taking care of their passengers
If there had been guns in the cockpit in 9-11
Boxcutters
Clearly would have been no match
And it might have had a different outcome
That's one way to look at it
Or you get completely outraged
And
And I do buy into that
We have a different idea of why they're guns around now
Are there gangs?
Are there people that shouldn't have them
Absolutely
But if you make guns, you'll equal to half
Can only people that are going to have them
Are the bad guys
And that's a fact
Because they're going to get them
And that they're what
There's always going to be a black market for whatever
Government says you can't have
You can't have marijuana
If they tell you you can't have
Have booze
Those guys come in
And can't have these
Lots of money
Doing exactly that
But made those people rich
So yeah
What's much illegalized guns
And make the bad guys the most powerful people around
Because they'll be the only ones with it
All right
Hey, that's my ramp for the day I'll talk to you later
I'm a thank you
Oh boy
This is a very trippy
Trippy
Very tricky subject indeed
Because obviously guns are dangerous
Obviously
But you know, it's the law of the land
It's what was laid down
It's what was set up by the founding fathers
And I think they had a lot of things right
And you know what these guys were fucking revolutionaries
They were rebels
They were definitely not your standard fair citizens
Adam Curry
Yeah
I've called you several times throughout the years
And this Chris
From Seattle
Post the car cast and I
Call you throughout the years several times about different things
I don't think I've ever called you angry before
But today I call you very pissed off
You've said a lot of things on your show
But I've never heard anything as ass-in-ine
And that you must endorse a presidential candidate
Hello
Who the hell do you think you are
And doors again today
Who are you?
Ted Koppel
Adam Curry
You're the leader of the free world
There's a leader of podcap
You're the pod fodder
There's a red pill guy
You're like doors up to the candidate
Guys it's flipping out and pulling it out
It's gonna be
You don't endorse a candidate
No?
Yeah, that's not part of the red pill
That's blue pill
In doors to candidate
Give me a break
You've fallen back into the old ways
So let the plus turn you back into the MTV guy you were before
Poor dad
In doors to candidate
Give me a break
Okay
Well, yeah
I think I'm gonna endorse Ron Paul
And I don't understand what's wrong with it
Otherwise I'm just a talker like everybody else
You know I'm a doer
I like to get out there and do things
I like to make shit happen
There's a guy fucking 72 years old
I like the most unlikely guy in the world
I don't think that this is far beyond my
My traditional motis operandi
I think it's exactly what I should be doing
And I'll go to the mat for this guy
By the way, I did send off an email
To don over at the Ron Paul camp
We're so nice to get back and touch with me
And let me know that they love to have them on the show
No answer yet to the email
So I'm gonna wait for the rest of the day to pass
And then I guess I'll just try a phone call
So far no luck on that
Oh Adam Jason from San Diego
It's funny you're talking about what's at Ron Paul
And driving around San Diego
Not too long ago maybe two or three days ago
I've just seen a few cars
And a few signs
With little cars with signs on them
I'm sorry
Cars with little magnet signs on
I'm in signs and people jarred to say
Google Ron Paul
That's it
And it has a little very very tiny tiny letters
Ron Paul for president
But in big huge letters, Google Ron Paul
So I thought it was an opposite campaign
You know, to find out what's going wrong with this guy
But turns out that's the way he's doing his grassroots
Thought it was interesting, you brought it up
Like
Yeah, okay, please remember how to end all of your comments
Did you call him?
It's quite annoying when you don't
Because there's nothing to laugh at at the end
Yeah, I think he's got a pretty good viral campaign
Going right now
He's trying to raise a 12 million dollars
When he comes on the show
I'm going to ask him how he's going to spend it
What he's going to spend it on
I love the idea of removing
The federal reserve and the IRS
And I can't wait to ask him about how he's going to go about that
I think that this guy would be a transitional president
He would have to be there for at least four years
To get things underway, get things in motion
Increase the what looks to me like a title wave
Of enthusiasm for constitutionalism in the United States
By the way, you may not agree with
If you live outside the US or you're not an American citizen
But I think it's a great way to go
And I've been watching these debates
No one can argue with it
You just can't argue the constitution
In fact, if some of the video I saw clearly from a Ron Paul supporter
And she held up a little booklet
Maybe, you know, like a pamphlet almost
Like the size of
I would say that it was the size of like the tube guide
In London only it was thinner
And that's the constitution of the United States
And then she held up next to it
This huge, you know, unwieldy
Encyclopedic feeling volume
This tone
And that was the internal revenue code
The tax code of the United States
Which by far outweighs outstrips
And out, outgroses
The constitution is just unbelievable
And that really hit home for me
That's a tax payer I might add
Hey Adam, it's Mark from Boulder
Just calling to let you know
That before I forget, yes
As an American citizen, regardless of where you live
Regardless of where you pay taxes
You still have to file an income tax form
With the United States
Which I do do to flee
Just lessen to the Charlie here
Moment of Go
And Aaron Russo's film
America, Freedom to Fascism
Is available
A Netflix
And you can ask a watch
It instantly I believe if you're in the US
Which I did
Back in March
Second
As well the first films that I actually watched
Off of Netflix and New Streaming Service
So for people that are Netflix subscribers
They can view it right then
And there
And I do recommend watching it
It was very interesting and informative
And what you didn't touch on
What it, the premise of its film
Is what Aaron was trying to get to the bottom was
Is why are Americans paying personal income tax?
No where in our constitution
Or in law
Does it specify that we need to pay personal income taxes
Is that then he gets to know all the details
That there was reserve bank
And there was a system
And how this was all created
And what a racket it is
So people can find the full
Film on Netflix
Yeah
Ciao
Thank you
Yeah
That was homework I gave you on
The other day
You definitely need to go watch that film
This is not just some
Conspiracy theory thing
Throne together
From different pieces of information
In fact I see pieces from this documentary
Used in others
It's very well done
It really only applies
If you're an American citizen
But if you're a world citizen
It does give you view
Into how the finances
The world work currently
And where they're going
And that is without a doubt
A follow the money
Mission my friends
Yes Adam
This is at noise from a fearful island
I just wanted to encourage you to
Do whatever you can to support
Rom Paul
Check into what he's doing
On YouTube
And other things
And realize that he's got this massive
Following and it's just growing
Comatically
For example
He's raising more money from
Soldiers
And I rack them all
Of the other Republican candidates
Combined
That tells you something about
What they think
Many other big huge issues
So I hope you can help them out
Thanks a lot
Right on
And you know what
It's just impossible to argue
With a guy who's been an OBGYN
An obstetrician
For so long
Has delivered over 4,000 babies
It's the kind of guy you actually
You're okay
If he examines your wife's vagina
So this is a guy who I can
You know
Bill Clinton might have won
Do that
But this guy is in a different league
And
That gives me great comfort
All right something else here
Yeah
Enough of that
Hopefully those guys will call
And we'll get Ron Paul on this week
It doesn't look like it's going to be until
Thursday or Friday at this pace
But I'm looking for that to happen
Brand new target cast
We're running in partnership with Partita
Toquila
You've probably heard the spots
Running on the network
It's on the Tequila Trail
Chef Mark
Friend of the show here
Went to Mexico
Film the harvesting
And distillation process
Of the agave plant
I think it's pronounced agave isn't it
That's the fruit
From which
Tequila is harvested
This is at the Partita Ranch
That's episode one episode two
They mix it all up
And make some really cool
Tequila drinks
So you can take a look at that
On the Tequila Trail dot
Potcho dot com
Is it advertising?
Yeah
Is it content?
What is it?
Potcho
Comic strip
And you thought the US was bad
CSB is now recording his entry
Into the United Kingdom on audio
And he's pissed off about his treatment
Hi Adam Boy
Say
When your wife
Who is Dutch
Is entering UK
Is British immigration
If he's asking her
Where is she coming from?
Yes
They do
However
That's about all they ask
They never ask how long she's going to stay
Or anything like that
I get a hell of a lot more questions
I mean I get like interrogated
Every single time
But no, they only ask her where she's coming from
Just listen to this
Do you have a mother?
Okay
No
But I don't know
You don't have a mother, right?
And you don't have a mother, right?
Because if I say this, then I have to
Okay
Just listen to this
And even if you can't make any difference
But what do you call?
You can't call me when you are on your way
So you haven't
Dude, you do not want to mess around with those people
You always want to be smiling
I always take off my sunglasses
You always want to be nice to him
Did you hear that?
It doesn't make any difference
Where you're from
I need to know where you're from
From Chile.
Correct yourself.
That's just because I am a new EU citizen.
I'll be it.
Born in a country that has 1,100 years of history.
I'm treated as white Negro,
by British migration.
How does that mean?
Old EU citizens are not being asked this question at all.
No CSB.
That's just not an analogy that is appropriate.
I understand what you're saying.
What you're saying is you're being discriminated against because you are from a different
EU country.
And yes, it's crazy.
If the European Union means it's supposed to be like the United States of Europe, can
you just imagine that happening in the US.
Welcome to Texas.
What state did you come from?
Why?
What are you doing?
I don't want to stay here.
I think we're not far off from that happening in the US, actually, if we don't watch
out.
So clearly work to be done in the European Union.
So the motto of this fairytale is, there is no old and new EU.
There is one EU.
And let us all treat each other equally, or if we cannot, let's dissolve EU now.
Let's stop pretending that there is any community.
And Adam, let's treat each other with respect without incency or fuck you.
OK.
Let's say it.
You.
Our EU correspondent ladies and gentlemen, the one and only comic strip blog.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic
strip, comic strip, comic strip.
1, 2, 1, 6, 2, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7, 5, 7, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7, 7.
Hey, Adam.
This is Blake Morgan from New York CityCon, just want to check in and give you the good news.
We just got words that following your debut of Maybemma made on the Daily Source Code, we got
6,000 paid downloads on the e-m music in the first six weeks following that debut.
So we are still riding high from riding the pod safe music network wave here and more importantly
your support and your spin and debut of that song on the Daily Source Code.
So 6,000 downloads in six weeks is a great start and we are thrilled that just continues to prove
that what bands like Radiohead and Ninestale have already figured out that there is no need to
count out to Giganta Radio or to large, rotten, terrible record labels that pod casting and
the internet and all the stuff that the rest of us already know is really the way to go, especially
when we have people like you on our side. So to kind of celebrate that and also with the Radiohead
thing, I've uploaded three more songs to the PMN from my acoustic album of silence there,
including a very special authorized cover to follow in the tradition of Maybemma made.
So I want to thank you, give you the good news, keep it coming, look what you're doing, it's incredible.
Take care Adam, I'll talk to you soon.
For love like a landfill, a job that slowly kills you,
who says that word here.
You look so tired and happy, brave down the government, they don't, they don't speak for
us.
All day, a quiet life, a handshake of carbon, a knockside, with no alums, and no surprises, no alums,
and no surprises, no alums, and no surprises,
silence, silence, this is my final fit, my final beliac, with no alums,
and no surprises, no alums, and no surprises, no alums, and no surprises,
no surprises, no surprises, no surprises, no surprises,
no surprises, no surprises, no alums, and no surprises, no surprises, no surprises,
a beautiful song, a beautiful story from Lake Morgan, no surprises, his authorized radiohead cover,
which is available on the pod safe music network. There you go, it's taken three years, but we are
definitely whipping the music industry's ass, publishing industry is next, and we'll get to media,
and oh yes, maybe one day we will save the world and win valuable prizes. Let's find out tomorrow
together, adamotpodshow.com, dailysourceco.com, hey, fuck it, enjoy your freedom.