Adam, Adam, Adam. You have DSCs, CSPs, pictures of naked pod show honeys. We follow the
monies, conspiracy, controversy, nylon, classic songs, blue pills, red pills, mashups,
fuckups. My head is starting to spin. The little guy is shafted again. Maybe I'll take a
tile and I'll pee him. Oh man, these things are blue. Adam, curry. Fuck you. Yo. I'll
just share it fairly. $6.71 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass. Done the next
generation radio content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
We listen to the Daily Shorescoe, who are cooler and moodier than any other podcast on the
internet. And when I think moodier, I think Adam Curry.
Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. With all you stupid friends, they chat every
game. They'll follow every inch and no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. The way we're
going. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem.
Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem.
Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem. Yo's no problem.ья's
You're so fabulous
I'm so happy
Daddy's favorite truth
Favorite truth
Ready cards and brand new colors
This is my thank you for all you've been
I'm so happy now
I wasn't party planned
You always get just what you want
So what's the things that my own hands
It hurt me so bad
And you got me right for it
So I love you so good
To be for good
And I know you'll feel good
I'm a little bit older than you
Now you want me to tell you
I love you so good
I hate you
Just give me your love
You need me for all my things
And I know you'll feel good
I love you so good
I'm a little bit older than you
And I know you'll feel good
You need me for all my things
Oh, yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
That's the way to get a school life ride.
Arolan, Chris, I took your boyfriend from the Podsake Music Network.
Find that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
Good to be back.
It's always nice to do at least one Friday show.
I'm not even going to apologize.
You know what I'm doing?
You know, I've been really busy.
I did calculate some of the hours.
It takes me about an hour and a half to get from the curry manner where I'm situated
momentarily for the footballer Friday festivities to the crash pad and shortage in London,
about an hour and a half and about an hour and a half closer to two hours to get back home
at the end of the day, which is usually I don't usually have I haven't been getting home before
like eight at least and closer to eight thirty nine o'clock.
Those are exactly the three hours I need to make my show on a daily basis.
It's just what it takes.
He got to understand today I was staying home.
This is going to be a production day.
It's a couple of administrative things I got to do.
The pile of admin, which is basically crap that comes into our mailbox here at home,
is about the tip over, which means it's time to take a look at it again.
To do some of that stuff today and I started prepping at 11 a.m.
Patricia and I slept in just a little bit to like eight thirty nine o'clock.
It is now two thirty seven.
That's how long it has taken me because it is first of all,
there's some amazing stuff that's going on.
I've been getting a huge lobby group calling into the voice mail number.
So I got to talk to you about that because I'm very excited about some of the messages I'm hearing.
So that's coming up later on today's show.
There were just tons of other voice mail related stuff.
You know, I try to keep the food bar Friday is kind of moving and grooving,
but I can't help myself today.
I got to play some of this stuff for you.
It's crazy.
So for here's something that's nuts that's going on in the Netherlands right now.
You know, I grew up there basically after being born in the states move there when I was seven.
And in the early eighties, I worked at a broadcast company,
which is I don't want the stories too long and complicated to explain exactly how they went from a pirate radio station
situated in the North Sea in the days of Caroline, me and me go radio and North Sea.
They were radio Veronica and they went legit and we're using the public airwaves in the early 80s,
television and radio and I got a gig there doing television and radio as well.
So this was a very dynamic organization.
Very young.
I was 19 when I joined them when I was on television and it was fun.
It was just a crazy ass time.
We were in broadcasting.
You know, our legacy was pirate radio ships.
You know, you can imagine what kind of a company this was.
It was great to work at.
It was just, it was a lot of fun.
It was truly, it determined a lot of the blueprint of Adam Curry trust me.
So a book came out earlier this week.
I don't know the title of the book.
And I haven't read it either.
But this book was put together by a guy who actually I've known for a couple of years.
He produced a radio show with me.
I don't know.
Maybe eight or nine.
Is it that long ago?
Yeah.
No.
Seven.
Five or six years ago.
I don't know.
I was doing like a Friday night show.
This was, this was kind of just before I started with a daily source code.
Anyway.
So this guy wrote a book about those crazy years of Veronica and who was sleeping with who?
And there's some nutty ass stories.
And it's all funny, you know, because first of all, we were all crazy at the time.
We were all, we were just all nuts.
And the whole book is basically filled with all the sex capaids of a radio Veronica.
At least that's what, and television Veronica.
That's what I'm led to believe.
So anyway, let me get to the story.
So this book comes out.
And the guy is now out there promoting the book.
And he interviewed me.
And I was happy to tell him all kinds of stories.
Because it's funny, you know, and it's funny to look back at 25 years of
Sodom, Gamora, and DeBotchery.
And I told him a story about time when I was going out with one of the assistants, like a
Productions, production assistant.
I think she was also 19 at the time.
And we were kind of dating, you know, for a couple of months.
And at the time, the brand new codec disk camera had come out.
If you'll recall that.
And you know, I was always in the gadgets and you kind of got to understand that today
It's real simple to think of a camera as no big deal.
But the codec disk camera, which was a huge flop, by the way.
Technologically crap.
It was really small.
You could slip it into into your pocket.
You could, you know, it was a really easy format to handle.
You still had to have a develop to this film.
But it was something new.
So I got into one of those.
I think for Christmas or something.
What did you do when you're 19?
You're fooling around and say, how long I'm going to take a picture of you?
Let me take another one.
Yeah, well, she's naked.
You know, nothing really outrageous.
But, you know, it's naked pictures.
You know, me.
I always talk about naked pictures.
And as I take a couple snaps, think nothing of it.
I've got the camera.
And a week or so later, maybe a little bit longer than that.
I find myself interviewing the Rolling Stones in London.
This was the time the Harlem shuffle came out.
If you get what the name of the record was.
And remember the Harlem shuffle had to kind of like that cartoon music video.
The guy who did later went on to do Red and Stimpy actually animated that video.
So this is a big press junk.
And the world press was all, you know, we each had our room and our camera crew set up.
And we'd wait for the stones to come by to interview them.
And so of course, you know, this is hours of waiting.
Finally, there's a, you know, like a,
Hey, knock at the door.
Ron Wood and Keith Richards comes stumbling in completely hammered off their ass.
They, you know, like, we got to go Lou and it's the rolling to the bathroom.
They got a big bowie knife scooping coke out of a bag and snorting it straight off the knife.
So I'm like, wow, this is awesome.
You know, this is fantastic.
So I interviewed the guys.
We have a crazy ass interview, you know, sitting on the ground.
I think we threw pillows on the ground to make some kind of different set.
Then your traditional, let's sit on some chairs and let's do over the shoulder interviews.
And so we're done.
And the guy who went along constant mayors who was producing, he said,
Oh, dude, we got to get a picture of you and Ron Wood and Keith Richards.
For the newspaper, and since it was public broadcasting back in the day,
you had, you basically would, it's kind of the BBC in a way.
You know, if you had something that you wanted to publicize,
you take it to the, to the NOS, which is kind of like the,
the overarching organization.
They had their own press relations office.
And you know, you basically hand off your film to them and they'll write the press release,
etc.
So, but we know how to camera.
We're like, does anyone know when brought a steel camera?
And I said, wait a minute, I've got this, I've got this code act disk thing.
And so, no, we take a couple shots, right?
And it's cool.
And Woody and Keith, they, they, they're out.
And, you know, I think we obviously stayed overnight,
no, until I went back the next day.
And, you know, so I said, oh, here's the, the disk.
You can send that off to the, to the PR department at the NOS.
And they can get the pictures off of it and get it in the paper.
And then later that afternoon, I realized that this is the same disk
that has my girlfriend on it naked.
Like, oh man, this is so good.
So, it had already gone over there.
So, I literally, and at the time the PR department was located in the editing facilities
or in the same building.
So, I could get in there.
And I was able to get in, find the envelope, retrieve it.
And I took it to like a, you know, a one hour Photoshop thing.
And, and got the pictures for the PR department.
And, of course, kept the ones that were personal intended for me only.
So, that's, you know, that was pretty funny story.
It's even funnier when you think that this girl,
Caroline, went on to become an extremely famous television presenter in the Netherlands.
I mean, like, big time.
She's, you know, she, all those big shows, like, you know,
the equivalent of like dealer, no deal.
You know, all of these huge shows, she's a, she hosts that.
She's as she makes millions a year.
She's a really big deal.
And so, the story comes out.
And, and people are freaking out about it.
Like, Adam Curry has naked pictures of Caroline Tenson.
And, like, yeah, so, you know, the story was, it was funny that, you know,
this almost got out even before she was famous,
but, you know, that I had to break in and retrieve the pictures.
And now there's like this whole thing going on and people are saying,
well, well, what will he do with him?
You know, are they locked up in your safe?
Oh, dude, they're in some cardboard box for the rest of my naked pictures.
I don't know where they are.
I definitely have them.
So, so the Dutch press is going.
Not so for something that took place 25 years later.
Oh, I got to love it.
Okay, let me see, here we go.
We're going to be talking about a number of things today.
Email from, who's this from?
Guy Clark.
First time you made a long time listener, Adam,
who's on the uselessness of the podcast awards was spot-on.
This is my first year at The New Media.
I knew new, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New and Boy,
and the sense of community was overwhelming.
Regardless of the size of ones, audience, everyone was helpful.
Full of insights.
Ready to share stories are atleast a free cocktail.
Oh, lots of those indeed.
The whole point of this new, MOUDEO Revolution is to create compelling content
for whatever your interest is.
Although there were a way too many dudes.
Fuck the awards.
We need more women in podcasting. Cheers from the Midwest says guy ps that Von Jovi mashup blew my mind
Well, dude. I've got a whole new one for you. You're gonna dig this
It's from mashuptown.com, of course. The Mockingbird Trayer from Iki
You're just found right and he's down on his back you're still
You know what's the matter about day?
What you're following?
She brings all my face for no
You're not for no
She's gonna hold on
You're why we fight? It doesn't make it that much of a make it all the time
We're trying to chill up and that's what I'm holding on
We'll give it a shot
Iki's Mockingbird Prayer
Mixing up M&M's Mockingbird
We're living on a prayer
A little bit of other Banjovi tracks in there
For mashuptown.com, catch that in the show notes at dailysourceport.com
It is the football friday episode number
671 things heating up in the old country
Hold on a second
I had so many problems with cast blaster
The morning was telling me that it couldn't find
Temp.mp3 and I had to go and configure my dot i and i file
And there's anything I hate
It's configuring my dot i and i files
You know what I'm saying?
I don't know
This is you
Still got from Germany on my way to Berlin
And I'm driving here
Pass the football stuff exit
And I was wondering
When do you plan on opening the office in football stuff
First question
Second question
Are you gonna do a launch party in Germany
And if so
Can we all be invited
Bye bye
You sales guy
So two things first of all
We intend to be open by the first quarter
So January 1st
Hopefully if all things go according to plan
It doesn't need to seem that Putzdom is the place that we're going to be
In fact
There's a couple of people complaining about those
Those subsidies
Let me see
Who is it?
Starmont Rae
Says I was listening to DSC67
He just got the part we talk about the German policy of subsidizing
50% of an employee salary
That's only in Putzdom by the way
It's very specific to that area
The only place this money could be coming from would be the employees or employers
To taxes that presume
So it sounds good at first glance
But there's no way a system like that could be both beneficial and sustainable
Well
Yeah, okay
There's a lot to be said about that
But this is the way the system is right now
I look
Later on in this program
I'm gonna try and fix America first
And then we can always go and see if we can fix Germany
Okay
He does end up with a fuck you Adam Curry
Thank you very much
It's nice
How many people have called in
Have taken comic strip bloggers lead
Just to end with a good old fashioned fuck you Adam Curry
Nice
I had them
It's Karen from Rumor Girl
Baby
It's us here from Showgirl
It's Showgirl
It's our land and GBR here
And they're gonna talk to you in just a second
Okay
I wanted to say thank you for being at the PM me
And support us
I don't know what I mean
I showgirls that is
The award that we got
It was so great to see you there
And Pod Show being there
Well
Yeah
And it was awesome
Have you there?
Thanks for flying out from Chicago
Just a final assignment on here
Can't go
Yeah
It was awesome to meet up with you
And
Richard Burrhey
And the whole crew
A pod show
And thank you Adam
It was really great
Looking out into the crowd
And seeing your face when we got that award
And all of Pod Show there
It was really great hanging out with them
And we had that
So thank you very much for coming
Love you guys
Thank you
Thank you girls so much
You don't have to thank me
Thank you
Thank you for doing what you do
Being who you are
And thank you for just even the hint at one day
I'll get some naked pictures
So you too in 25 years
Gonna be the subject of
Controversy and intrigue
Oh man something cool happened at the office
I have to change the names
To protect the innocent
When we had the digital music awards
Was that only last week
I guess it was last week
Well we had a pretty big crew there
I think in total we had 25 people
You know between camera
And editing
And production logistics
We had a bar
A lot of things going on
A lot of moving parts
And we had I think two or three
Makeup people
And one is this beautiful
Latina girl Maya
And you know we had a couple of the folks
From the US over from the poncho hq in San Francisco
Over as well
And you know so the way that kind of works
Is you know they had specific tasks
But we have room in
Because it's kind of like a live work
Type of place the crash pad and shortage
Oh there goes someone flying low today
You hear that shitty weather
So he's got to be probably about a thousand feet
Anyway
So this office you know we have a huge like living room
Open kitchen area
Which is you know it's yes we have about eight desks in there
And a sitting area
But it's also used as studio
Very often it's a natural habitat for a studio
I have to say
Then we have two bedrooms
One bedroom has a bathroom
That is the audio recording room
But it also has one of those couches that folds out into a bed
And then we have the video editing suite
Where we have two editing stations
And again a couch there
Would that you know can fold out into a kind of like
We call those the divon or whatever
Crap you know what I mean
One of those couches that just folds flat into a bed
So one of the pod show San Francisco employees
Cooked up with this beautiful Maya
And we knew he was going out on a date with her
But then I heard yesterday in the office
The most hilarious story
So apparently so he was sleeping in the back room
All the way in the back with the bathroom
But I happen to know that that couch which turns into a bed
It's kind of rickety on its legs
And it's fine to lay on it
But let's say you want to have a proper shag on it
No way because I think the legs would probably break off
So he took this girl into the
Into the video editing suite
And you know did the nasty
But then when he went to open the door
He turned the handle and pulled it
And then the handle on the other side of the door
Fell off
And it was the part that actually has the
The shaft that goes into the door
You can't open it
It's just like a
It's like a little square hole
That you literally have to stick a square peg into in order to turn it
And it's a serious door
It's not like a flimsy thing
So they were both locked in
But naked
And they were there for half an hour
And they couldn't get out until finally he figured
Oh wait a minute and he used some scissors
But he told me yesterday that they literally
were considering they were about to start sending
How emails the people
Staying help
One girl in casting
With Adam Curry
Adam, who are you ready to be stumps
I am
Because he used that
Bring it on
I'm feeling good today
Come on, John
Hey Adam
It's a hit test number 91
Yeah, this one is themed
It's from the 70s
Oh good
I went by the way
Yeah
As you get here
I have the flu
Oh
It's going to be helped
I have some great music for you
So here we go with intro
Bring it on
All right
Time to dance
Dance
The Freda keeps on
Uh
Gipsen Brothers non-stop dance
I think
It's definitely the Gipsen Brothers
Number two
Dance
Is that your
I want
Uh
I want to kiss you all over exile
In number three
Tada
Is that our cocoa batter?
Very mental
Tada
At the coat
It's all right
And time's up and these are the answer
All right we bring it on
Yes
Answer number one in this week's hit test
From 1977
The Gipsen Brothers
And the non-stop dance
Right
You got a feeling
Try to get high
Hey
Hellereaar, good start!
The nonstop, dance.
Dance, dance, dance.
Dance, yeah!
Once the number one, the Gibson Brothers.
The nonstop dance.
So this is Answer Number Two.
From 1978, baby.
This is exile, just you all over.
I'm gonna go with me, gonna light your smile
I hold them and thinkin' about your pain
You won't wanna do that
I know it was massive
I wanna kiss you all alone
I'm over in here
To the night close in me
I answer number two, exile and kiss you all alone
And this is answering number three
From 1979
The real thing
Don't you feel the fall
Okay, can you feel the fall
All right, you're stutting on that one young
Can you feel the fall
Two out of three ain't bad
Great music from the 70's
Like this one
And so number three to real thing
And can you feel the fall
And that concludes this
70's hit test and it's number 91
Alrighty Adam, how did you do?
Got two out of three
And I said nothing
So have them all
No, not quite
Did you at least like them all?
Yeah
Yes, I hope so
Nice man, that was great music
From 977, 978 and 979
Alrighty, the answers to this hit test
And also the links to iTunes
So you can buy these tracks
Can be found at hittestupartshow.com
And next week I'll be back for hittest number 92
I'd like my feel better about this
Until then, take care
And bye bye
We back hit test and gmail.com
In full.com
And p-o-l-g-t-d-o
Hey this is got the folder
I'd guess that
Fuck you look to the daily
I don't want to go with Adam
Hold on, hold on
Yon, what did you see?
I don't listen to these before hand
So hold on a second
With that hell the John say at the end
And back hit test and gmail.com
In full.com
And p-o-l-g-t-d-o
Oh, uh, folder
And, uh, fuck you too
I'm only kidding
No, I'm not
Yes, I'm not
Well, whatever
See ya
Yo!
Hey this is Scott from topdeadcenterpodcast.com
You're listening to the daily source code
With Adam Holy Shit
Look at my hair
Look at my luscious flowing golden hair
Fucker
Fuck you in the neck
I gotta tell you, you guys are just outstanding
I, I don't know what it is
But whenever someone ends a comment
Were that just cracked me up
And I'm curious
Steve again
state you've again, the MTV follow-up question.
So let's say that the plus ticks off the way
codes look at mic.
And do you have any desire?
Not time.
But just do you have any desire to maybe occasionally
do like a guest DJ segment or anything like that?
I'm not imagining that it's going to be like the MTV
these again.
But are you just an executive now in a podcast
or is that kind of thing attract you at all?
Just curious again.
And how is the end?
Fuck you, Adam Cody.
Oh, yes.
Fuck you and your red pill.
Yo.
A very good question.
I'm not a big fan of doing television or video in general.
I just really don't like it.
I've got a mild to ret.
I can't control my hair myself, my wife has to do it.
Isn't it?
This is not really for me.
But I can do it.
And I have to tell you, if the vibe is right,
you can wake me up in the middle of the night
to do a segment if it's fun.
But when it comes to doing something regular,
just being something that I do at a set time each day
or each week, that's just tough for me.
That's just my life just doesn't fit with that anymore.
Please witness La Delta Sierra Charli.
His tough enough just to get a couple shows out a week.
I told you it's going to be this way
until the end of the year.
Then I think I'll be able to cruise into back into normal mode.
And we'll have our weeks.
We'll definitely have our weeks for sure.
And just know that I love you all and I'm really trying.
And it is a full bar Friday.
And we have not had a real proper full bar Friday
for the past couple of weeks
because we haven't had this guy on the show.
Your Honor, I'd like to make a motion
to rock this mother out.
Your Honor, please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give a nod.
Do the hardest work and lawyer.
He's charging time and man, man.
He's charging time.
Neo.
How's it going Adam?
It's Jersey Time.
The official musicologist of The Cha Cha.
Dude, I don't call to come back.
I've been here for years.
Yo, yo, I know I've been away for a little bit,
but you know, I've been listening to the shows
and the music, I've been playing it.
It's all right.
But I got something today for your full bar Friday
that you're just absolutely going to flip out about.
The band is the wild bunch and you've played them before,
but they got a brand new track up on the podcast
of music network.
I like these guys a lot.
They always get me moving.
And you know what?
The song starts off great.
Because it just starts with one word.
It starts with, can I get it from me?
Give me a woo.
Woo.
I'll have a more Friday.
I'm going to get the real, I'm going to let you chill.
I'm going to let you chill.
Let me see.
Oh, man.
There's so many comments about the TSA, which of course has been on my mind lately.
Hey Adam, this is Pavlan from Ireland.
Long time no see.
You are really starting to piss me off.
I am playing at Paris when they're weak.
I know I get this fucking TSA, this TSA.
I'm expecting a fuck of a cavity chair for I leave this bed.
So, thanks.
Holder.
The cavity surgeon did my friend.
Well, that's next.
I'm telling you.
We're not far from it.
Captain Chris.
Of course from playedmadness.com.
He heard me saying that I was just going to start smuggling illegal shit on the plane.
It's just a prove I could do because I know I can do it.
And he says, don't smuggling illegal shit on the airplane.
It'll just come back to bite you and they will win regardless.
Six month flight ban, et cetera, et cetera.
In the meantime, he says, watch this clip.
It'll make you feel better.
And he sent me a link to a clip from Saturday Night Live, which is a very famous live comedy
television program in the United States.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
It's on every Saturday.
Yeah, it is.
I guess every single Saturday night, even if they do reruns around Saturday nights.
I don't know.
I was at 11 or something like that.
11 30 they start.
And they did an awesome skit.
And it's only four minutes.
But I think it works in audio.
The setup is it's a classroom.
There are two TSA security officials.
And a room full of about, of course, it's all the Saturday Night Live cast members.
Six or seven sitting in school benches.
TSA security agents, you know, the guys and gals who you meet.
Whenever you go flying at the security checkpoints.
And I think these guys really nailed it.
I think it's worth listening to.
If you've already seen it, don't want to listen to it again.
Four minutes, 44 seconds.
I hope you enjoy.
Check this out on your football Friday.
Welcome, everybody.
Welcome.
My partner and I here.
We are from the Department of Homeland Security.
And we want to start by saying that those of you gathered here today,
America's last line in the defense against terrorism.
The decisions you make affect the lives of millions every day.
You are a vigilant precise and qualified.
Every one of you has at least a high school equivalent to your degree.
And not one of you has ever been convicted of a felony.
You are the cream of the crop.
You are elite.
You are America's heir, poor security.
You are the TSA.
You're yourselves a fan.
So this week there was a loose thing.
A recent airline restrictions concerning liquids and jails.
And we would like to run through how that will affect policy.
All right.
Let's start with a quick security refresher.
Name some liquids and some jails.
To just yell out some liquids.
Well, name some liquids and or some jails.
They quits and jails.
Anything you got?
Water.
That is a liquid.
Good.
So bad.
There you go.
That is a jail.
Wow.
You guys are doing great.
Turkey sandwich.
Nope.
Not a liquid or a gel.
Right.
But sometimes turkey is a little wet.
Okay.
That doesn't make it a liquid.
What about mustard?
Go at that count.
So a turkey sandwich is a liquid if it has mustard on it.
No.
Because it wouldn't have more than three ounces of mustard on it.
What if you love mustard?
Turkey sandwich is never an liquid.
Okay.
So what if you put a turkey sandwich in a blender?
Why would you do that?
Well, if your job was wired shut.
Hey.
Okay.
The important thing about today is that the TSA
is loosening our restrictions on liquids and jails.
Now, you can bring three ounces of liquids or jails
as long as they are inside of a super baggy.
Why?
Why did it change?
That's a good question.
Good.
Because the FBI did test and found that three ounces of liquids
can't blow up an airplane.
But four ounces of liquid can't blow up an airplane.
We're still not sure on that.
But what is important here is that three ounces can't.
So we're safe as long as we stick with the three.
Well, what's to stop two people from each having three ounces?
And then meeting on the plane to combine them.
Chris, you want to take this one? No.
Excuse me.
I have a whole mess, security question.
Right.
Welcome America's chemical blasts.
It's still woefully underprotected against attacks.
Despite repeated warnings by experts that they are likely
the next terrorist target.
Airplane questions only.
Okay.
What if I am a passenger who does not have three ounces with me?
But is confident I could produce three plus ounces on the flight?
You mean producing a liquid?
Or a gel stop.
No, no, no.
Everybody, okay, here's the skinny.
Here we go.
We under the department of Homeland Security.
And we have way more questions than answers.
Okay.
I don't know why.
We publicize our policies to the terrorists so that they can get one step ahead of us.
You have to take your shoes off.
It's some airports and not others.
But what I do know is that you can't say that we don't.
I don't know what we're doing as long as there's FEMA.
All right.
Have a question.
Great.
Yeah, I have been convicted of felonies.
Much of time, so that can be a problem at all.
So you can clearly tell these guys are, I got to tell you,
a great job.
They're going to get lots of shit when they go through airport security as a personal private
citizens in the individuals.
Just shows the absurdity of it all.
And I'm going to move beyond all of this.
Beyond the 9-11 conspiracies, beyond airport security.
I was almost ready to say I'd move beyond the this thing called the Amaro,
although I get a lot of hate mail people saying I'm full of shit.
Apparently this topic came up on Larry King Live.
Had a mic from Baker School of California.
If somebody hasn't already pointed it out to you, you can go check out a clip of the
Mexico President of the Sunday Fox on Larry King Live from a couple nights ago,
where he basically talks about the I would guess probably the Amaro.
Is what he's talking about unbelievable.
Can I have a fuck you?
No, I guess not.
All right.
So if anyone has a link to that, I couldn't find it that easily on YouTube.
Now they started to clean it up and are basically ruined YouTube.
It's no good.
You know, I actually, I got some music to go with the last part of the show for today.
It's time to save America, ladies and gentlemen.
Save us from the insanity that is the departments like Homeland Security.
And let's save us from the IRS stealing the fruits of our labor.
I've been looking for a candidate to endorse in the upcoming 2008 presidential elections.
You know, I've been doing as much research as I possibly can.
Some people have been joining in and helping out, for instance, Craig Meyer,
went to opensecrets.org.
And he says he put together a spreadsheet of contributions for John McCain.
Remember, I told you if you looked at opensecrets.org, you can see what corporations and why
that's listed, I don't really know.
But you can see which corporations have donated through individuals.
The maximum amount of each individual being a couple thousand dollars.
You can see what companies they work for.
So he, he touted it all up and came up with some very interesting results.
The most amount of money came for John McCain.
That is, came from people who marked down they were retired.
Second was self-employed.
Third was homemaker.
Four was empty.
And then check out these interesting companies.
The federal expressed $24,000.
Merrill Lynch in aggregate $18,000.
MGM grand.
That's no tell.
$9,000.
Nice comp room there.
Blanche, a blank and room LLP.
I think it's a hedge fund.
Echo star, AT&T, Liberty media.
Now, that's very interesting.
I'm sure that these are people who, somehow, I guess they get their employees to either
do a drive or, or they maybe they coerce them into aggregating their maximum amounts of
money donated to a candidate.
And they come up with some interesting amounts.
FedEx had 14 people donate.
And I presume that if they put FedEx down on their donations,
it's because they want FedEx to be associated with the donation.
Why else would you do it?
You could also just say I'm a self-employed or a delivery worker.
Or in that case, maybe a pilot.
I don't know if you were for federal express.
So anyway, I've been looking for a candidate.
I don't give a shit what party affiliation they are.
I just want to get behind somebody.
Someone who, at least have some kind of message that is something that changes.
And well, some random endorsement started to come in through the phone line.
So I guess someone in the
Ron Paul campaign or just some enthusiastic supporters
handed out the phone number.
Let's listen to a couple of them for a second here.
And this is Dan from Maine.
If you've got the, you know,
if you're looking for a presidential candidate to support,
I got one for you.
And the war on drugs,
end of the war in Iraq.
Leave the internet completely alone.
Reduce the power of the presidency.
Restore basic human and constitutional rights.
The U.S. citizens closed military bases around the world.
Cut federal spending.
And the sky rocks.
Of course, this is Ron Paul.
Paul Paul.
So you can imagine.
I'm here on that.
I'm going like, wait a minute.
And in the war on drugs,
drastically reduced government spending.
Close military.
I'm like, wait a minute.
This guy is starting to take all the boxes here for me.
And that all of a sudden I get this call.
This is fantastic.
This is the stoner from Houston, Texas calling again.
This is my second shot at this.
I thought the first one sucked.
I was nervous.
So I figured you won't want to use this on the air.
And if you did that, the first one sucked.
And this I want to hopefully better.
So I'll serve him to catch.
Sorry.
Sorry for asking Houston, Texas.
I was listening to your DSC-670.
And heard that you were looking for a presidential candidate.
I highly recommend you check out Ron Paul.
He's a Texas congressman.
Been in the congress for 10 terms now.
He is for the constitution.
There's a huge, huge grassroots movement going on in the United States right now.
He's raising lots of money.
He got $5 million.
He's got a lot of fantastic ideas.
You know, I hear you when you say that you're frustrated with all the crap that's going on with this war on terror.
And you know, having people with the airports and all the stuff.
You know, it's just terrible.
Anyway, long time listeners, go all the way back to before you call the DSC.
Never called in before, but I want to say,
Hi, let you know who I'm going for in the United States.
And, well, folder.
And he wants to realize marijuana.
Wow.
I'm like, okay.
Now here's a guy.
I can get behind.
And so I start to investigate Ron Paul.
Dr. Ron Paul.
Very interesting guy.
He's a Republican.
And I've said before that if anything, my family is certainly quite Republican.
And I probably have a lot of Republican in me.
I've not definitely not always voted Republican.
Certainly more Democrat and independent once or twice in the years that I've been been allowed to vote.
And so this guy, he was an obstetric, no OBGYN.
Is that what it is?
He's delivered 4,000 babies into the world.
Of course, he's old enough to have done that throughout his medical career.
And this guy's really interesting.
The whole thing is, look, there's a document that the founding fathers of the United States put together.
It's called the Constitution.
And it's been violated consistently throughout its history.
And it's time to ratchet it back and get back to the basics.
And I'm like, okay, that's pretty interesting.
You know, I've read the Constitution.
I stand by it.
I'm an American.
I totally believe in the founding fathers and their strength and their wisdom that they were writing the blueprint for a great country.
And so I went to YouTube.
I want to play for you a couple of pieces from this was,
there's a whole, I know of course I put links in the show notes to this.
YouTube page, which has a whole bunch of Ron Paul related video.
This was, I think, a debate amongst Republicans in, let me see if it says you're South Carolina.
Yeah, it's the, okay, it's the GOP presidential debate.
And there's a whole bunch of questions for Ron Paul.
I think really, they're worth listening to.
Hold on a second.
Let me just queue it up here.
So I can't resist the big fanfare.
Because it's about the elections of the free world, everyone.
It's the bomb fasting on a microphone once again.
All right.
Let's listen to a couple of these questions.
I'm just going to tell you that six of the publicans are back in 2000,
to vote against or authorize and president Bush to use force in Iraq.
Now you say we should pull our troops out.
A recent poll found that 70, 7% of Republicans,
disapprove of the idea of setting a timetable for withdrawal.
Are you running for the nomination of the wrong party?
But you, you have to realize that the base of the Republican party shrunk last year
because of the war issue.
You've got to kind of get past his voice.
He sounds a little Ross Perouille.
And I'm sure he looks much taller than Ross Perouille.
But that's the only bummer about him.
But listen to what this guy has to say.
It's really interesting.
That percentage represents less people.
If you look at 65 to 70% of the American people,
they want us out of there.
They want the war over.
In 2002, I offered an amendment to international relations
to declare war up or down.
And it was nobody voted for the war.
My argument there was if we wanted to go to war
and if we should go to war, the Congress should declare it.
We don't go to war like we did in Vietnam and Korea
because the war is never in.
And I argued the case and made the point that it would be a
quagmar if we go in.
Ronald Reagan in 1983 sent Marines into Lebanon.
And he said he would never turn tail and run.
A few months later, Marines were killed 241 were killed
and the Marines were taken out.
Reagan addressed this subject in his memoirs.
And he says, I said, I would never turn tail and run.
He says, but I never realize the irrationality
of Middle Eastern politics and he changed his policy there.
We need the courage of Ronald Reagan.
Which I think is really great.
You know, because he's talking to the Republican party.
He's a member of the Republican party.
And he's voted against going into Iraq.
And he's saying some really sensible stuff.
He's saying, we got no business doing that.
These long-term wars, the wars, they suck.
They're no good for us.
But he's right up there.
Fighting, I guess, which would be the other candidates.
We'll have to see who else is up there.
Rudy Giuliani is certainly one of them who's on in this panel.
Listen to the next question.
Brian from Fort Wayne asks this question via the editor
that a question about controlling government spending.
Congressman Paul, can you tell me three federal programs
you consider wasteful and would eliminate?
I'd start with the departments.
Department of Education, Department of Energy, Department of Homeland Security,
which we've just, the Republicans put in the Department of Homeland Security.
It's a monstrous type of bureaucracy.
It was supposed to be streamlining our security and it's unmanageable.
I mean, just think of the efficiency of FEMA.
And it's efforts to take care of the floods and the hurricanes.
So yes, there's a lot of things that we can cut.
But we can't cut anything until we change our philosophy about why governments should do.
If you think we can continue to police the world and spend hundreds of billions of dollars overseas,
and spend hundreds of billions of dollars running a welfare state and entitlement system
that has accumulated $60 trillion worth of obligations and think that we can run the economy
this way.
We spend so much money now that we have to borrow nearly $3 billion a day from foreigners
to take care of our consumption.
And we can't afford that.
We can't afford it in the government.
We can't afford it as a nation.
So tax reform should come but spending cuts have to come by changing our attitude
what government ought to be doing for us.
Listen to that.
And he's going to get rid of all the crazy ass departments.
Wow.
I think I'm in love.
Department of Homeland Security in the midst of a war, sir.
Well, I think we should not go to more bureaucracy.
It didn't work.
We were spending $40 billion on security prior to 9.11.
And they had all the information they needed there to deal with the threat.
And it was inefficiency.
So what do we do?
We add a gigantic bureaucracy which they're still working on trying to put it together
and tremendous amount of increase in funds.
So I don't think that the Republican position ought to be more bureaucracy.
I mean, why did we double the size of the Department of Education?
Yeah, man.
It's really, really dirty from here.
Rudy Giuliani is about to jump in and totally play the 9.11 card.
But this guy is saying some really sensible stuff.
I was looking around.
Hold on.
Let me just pick up another quote from him.
Listen to another one of these endorsements.
I got like 50 of them.
It's amazing.
Hi.
This is for Adam Curry.
My name is Jeffrey Schwartz.
I'm a supportive Ron Paul for president.
And I would ask Adam to look into Ron Paul 2008.com and do a Google or YouTube video search
at Ron Paul and see how popular he is.
He's the most popular candidate on the Internet and among young people.
And we'd love to have you learn about him.
And if you get it, possibly like him endorse him.
We'd love that.
So please do that.
Thanks so much.
Bye bye.
All right.
That's a fair enough question.
If all endorse him, well, I have some caveats here and there.
But let's listen to what Ron Paul has to say about the Internet and what his
stance is about our wonderful network.
It doesn't seem to be any official award, but quickly becoming also the best friend of the
Internet.
What do you think about the Internet?
Why should that be important to people?
Well, the Internet to me is the political equalizer of the age because we who use the
Internet a whole lot and the young people who like it and others find out that they can get information
that is unbiased.
And evidently, there's a lot of people in this country.
And especially young people who don't particularly like K and News coming from the major
television networks.
When I was raising my kids, you know, there was a lot of television watching.
I worried about that.
But I don't think kids sit and watch television as much now.
They'll be watching their computers.
And I think this is very good.
Of course, there's always good and bad on everything.
Just as there isn't any publication and television and radio and whatnot.
But at least there's more honest reporting and more honest news.
And you have to be more discretionary on what you're going to pick and look at.
But to me, it is the true equalizer.
I think we're doing very well in our campaign.
A lot better than I had anticipated.
At the same time, there are other candidates have raised a lot more money than we have.
So we have a campaign that is growing rather rapidly, both in fundraising and number of people.
But a lot of our success has come through the Internet.
So we've literally equalized ourselves to those who have had tens of millions of dollars.
The Internet, I think, is that.
The Internet is the big thing.
It doesn't mean that you could do everything on the Internet, but it might be the real organizer.
And literally, the Internet has been spontaneous for us.
But I think our candidacy is different than the others because we're philosophically motivated.
And we're not a top down.
We try our best to be well organized.
True this is we have trouble keeping up with the spontaneous organizations of groups around the country.
Just popping up.
I mean, it's literally freedom.
So when I talk about freedom, and people know about the freedom of the Internet, there must be a connection there.
I have freedom of the Internet.
I can look and go here and pick this and talk to my friends and all this thing.
So, of course, I don't want to ever tax the Internet.
I don't want to regulate the Internet.
And I want that's one thing that really gives us a chance to combat.
This horrendous movement to big government because we can talk to a lot of people.
So I see it as very exciting and something that is very beneficial.
And we ever get wind of the fact that the government wants to regulate our tax.
That is a bad sign.
Of course, it's in the winds.
Even at times, they bring up the UN about regulating the Internet because it's a world phenomenon.
I see this as a very dangerous notion, but right now, I think they're going to have a little trouble
writing in the Internet, and I think it's great.
So this guy, and all these people who called in with endorsements, you're absolutely right.
He ticks almost every single box I'm looking for.
He wants to get rid of all the departments, love that, love it.
He's a very strong supporter of the Second Amendment, which is the right to bear arms.
You know that I am a supporter of this.
For one reason only, the reason why the Constitution, the founding document of the United States of America,
has that amendment in it is in case we're in exactly this situation where the government needs to be taken out.
That's what the right to bear arms is all about.
And of course, there's many arguments for and against, but look, it's what our country was founded on.
Just keep it in there.
There was a reason for it.
Study the documents.
Look at the Constitution.
You have the right to the fruits of your labor, which means you, it is illegal to be taxed
the way the federal government is taxing you.
Well, yeah, love that.
Don't turn it into welfare state.
Yes, absolutely.
I've been a supporter of this for all my life.
I've lived in welfare states.
I hate it.
I think it's destructive demoralizing.
And America, that's what we're about.
It's where we're about the American dream, making a buck philanthropy, helping your neighbors.
Oh, yes.
Now, he also is a strong supporter of overturning the Roe versus Wade.
Judgment, I guess what you call it.
And I think I really have to go back and reread what it's about.
He is saying, what, so here's where I can agree with him because, of course, I'm not a woman.
I don't know what it's like to be pregnant or even contemplated abortion.
That's a very heavy topic that I just can't really, I just am not qualified to discuss it.
But he's saying, look, you know, we need to protect life.
He believes life starts with conception.
Now, of course, he's a doctor, a medical doctor.
So I can understand why he has a different view on the miracle of life.
So religious, and he says somewhere in one of these videos, he says, that is my burden to bear,
which I like the way he positioned that.
And you know, it's like, hey, I believe in God.
I believe in creation and not an evolution.
And that's my problem that I got.
And I like that.
That's great.
Absolutely, it's your problem.
And we have no problem because you're not going to push it on me.
I'm not going to push anything on you.
So that's fantastic.
And he says the only thing he wants to remove.
And I, that's why I need to go back and reread Roe versus Wade.
He says, I do not believe that the government should be paying for abortion.
Okay.
So that's something that we can discuss, but everything else.
You know, and stopping the war against drugs.
He says, that's that's crazy.
The war against drugs.
He says, it's nuts.
We have, you know, three million black American males in prison because of marijuana.
You know my, my stance on that.
So this guy really has got my attention.
One more of those endorsements.
Hi out of my name is Jane Evan.
I'm from Oklahoma.
I was just going to let you know that prison can make you should be supporting as
Ron Paul is my opinion.
I support Ron Paul because he is an honest man and has voted the same for 30 years.
Now, particularly because I agree with those ideas.
Although that's obviously a nice bonus.
I think we need somebody that we can trust and we'll bring transparent government.
Open source government for once.
Because I'm going to keep the internet free and unregulated.
It opposes taxing it in many ways.
It's the free market words.
The internet's perfect example of it.
Ron Paul is the only man for me.
Thanks.
And by the way, if you're going to call in and endorse anyone, please end with
Fuck you.
I don't curry.
Interesting.
So here's, here's what I'd say.
I'd say that just in what I've been reading.
Of course, I'm very open to contradictory opinions.
So if there's something I should know about Dr. Ron Paul, then please let me know.
But so far, I have to agree with everyone that's called in.
This is exactly my kind of guy.
I feel really, really good about it.
And I will go to bat for this candidate.
So here's what I'd like to do.
First of all, I can endorse him until I've spoken with him.
So whoever runs the campaign, whatever your contact is, you've got to set it up.
So I can talk to him on this show because I have some questions to ask.
So that's going to get his, I will endorse him if he calls in on this show.
I will, I might wind up endorsing him anyway because I got to endorse somebody.
Otherwise, what a useless, useless man I would be.
If I didn't endorse somebody.
But if we can get him to call in and I can talk to him, which I think will be really good for him.
And I'll ask, I'll ask the questions.
You know, I got my own, you send in yours.
We'll take care of that.
I'm looking forward to that conversation.
Then I will drive.
I will drive.
I think that we can, we can get this guy elected if we really want to.
And if, again, if I can get the conversation and I can really satisfy all of the questions I have,
then I will go all out for him.
And we're going to track it.
We're going to track and we're going to raise a shit load of money for this guy.
Okay.
I mean a shit load right now Hillary Clinton set to do 100 million before the end of the year.
Barack Obama somewhere in the 40, 50 millions.
So he's only at a tenth.
Dr. Ron Paul's only at a tenth or less of what the democratic potentials have.
But I guess and this is kind of where my knowledge of how sad is it that I don't exactly understand how the.
The elections work with the primaries and and there's one kind of disconcerning note is that I heard in one of the or saw in one of these interviews.
He said, look, if I don't make the Republican nomination.
Which of course has to do with the primaries.
Then I will not run. I will not run as an independent.
So I guess we've got to get him to win the Republican nomination first.
And I think as a part of that, if you are not registered as a Republican and you want to vote in the primaries.
I'm just repeating stuff that I've read.
You have to register today is like the deadline.
Today the 12th, the 12th of October.
So you might want to do that.
Check this guy out Ron Paul 2008 dot com.
And you know, here's another thing we're going to do.
So if we.
And again, I got to talk to the guy first.
But could you imagine if if you donate and instead of putting down federal express, you put down DSC.
I'll cool with that.
And we could tally him up because he had much money we made.
And you know, all I really want is I don't need any special consideration.
I don't need anything for the internet.
He's already made his opinion clear.
So I'm good to go with that.
I just got to talk to the guy.
Get him on the phone for me.
And I will be a loyal supporter forever.
And regardless of that, hats off to anyone.
Anybody, all of the candidates who actually have the guts to go out there and say, hey, I think I can do a good job.
I think I can run this country.
So, you know, that is by definition a very patriotic thing and it's just extremely cool.
So, you know what?
After I'm done with the show today and it's been a long one.
So I'm going to play one more song and then get out.
I'll play like one, two, three, four.
Like five more of those Ron Paul endorsements.
I just want you to hear.
You don't have to tune into.
You can just stop the show after I'm done.
One more email, though, from Jesse, minor, Adam thought you'd enjoy this political track by the dead candidates.
Yes, sure, maybe little dated with the particular references.
But the sentiment is current and totally in line with your current red pill, follow the money discussion.
So please do enjoy.
Of course, you tease a few episodes ago.
You're going to play a moon over Marin by the dead candidates from the pod save music network, but you didn't.
So, hey, dead candidates definitely a part of the soundtrack to my life.
Could you give it a whirl?
Dude, absolutely.
And boy, is it right on the money considering this track as what?
10, 15 years old?
Pinky sex makes the world go round.
7, 20, 20, 20, 30...
...
The State Department of the United States, we have a problem.
The companies want something down about the sluggish world economic situation.
Travits have been running farer than a little thin lately.
We need to stimulate some growth.
Now we know that there's a alarmingly high enough of young people roaming around in your country
to do the stir up trouble for the police and damage private property.
All of us will try to leverage it and shop.
It's about time we did something destructive with these people.
We won thousands of near-two.
They're crawling all over.
The companies think it's time we lost it down.
The series get together and start another war.
President Paul, we need to love the idea.
All of us will be streaming over hands to grow deeper.
People running down the road to get on fire.
Oh, don't get steam up for us.
Or the criminals that get changed for the real thing.
Three years.
Whoa.
We're running a little going away forever for Mr. Freshnath.
Oh, hell.
I can't stand so fun.
What do you say?
Well, we don't even have to win this war.
We just want to cut down on some of these things.
That's the situation.
Now let's just sign up the draft.
The draft is many of those people we can.
We'll call up every last yunkster.
We can get our hands on it.
Give them an hour or two to learn how to use an automatic rifle.
Send them on their way.
Now let's go on.
Now I'm Northern Ireland.
I'm Northern Ireland.
I'm Northern Ireland Screams.
The magpizzle.
I'm Northern Ireland.
I'm Addalph.
I'm Sweden Ireland.
I'm Seoul.
I'm bilateral Ireland.
I'm 19 Australian, Jordan Ireland.
I'm Northern Ireland.
crazy Northern Ireland.
Better needs since we took over.
Just like Vietnam, we had everybody so busy with LSD, they never got to run.
Get the Lord functioning just fine.
It's easy.
Well, we got our college kids so interested in beer.
They don't even hear us.
We've got many factors driven again.
Oh, and if they're spotpiled, they're back out.
They wouldn't even know what it looked like.
Oh, how about it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Bro, here's money.
The Army's manufacturing is telling me,
unless we get our bomb factories of the poor production
the whole economy is going to collapse.
The fog is during the same boat.
We all agree the time has come to the big one.
What do you say?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's excellent.
We knew you to agree.
The companies will be very pleased.
What day is it today?
It's Friday.
Monday Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday.
Food about Friday, Adam's final fun on the Wii.
Well, there you go.
The soundtrack to your life tells you some things about the future.
Don't they know?
Wow, man.
Spin that.
What is this?
I were in 13 minutes crap.
I hope you guys had time to sit through all of this with me.
Final thought of the Wii.
Well, for me, it's just going to be thinking about Ron Paul.
I'm liking this guy.
I could totally, you know, he can't be any worse than anyone else.
And the whole idea of, you know, look, you want my agenda.
Look at the Constitution.
We're taking it back.
We're taking it back to those days.
And, yeah.
Again, if you have a contrary in view,
I'd love to hear it.
You know the phone numbers that are on the data source code.com.
Curry.com.
And I would say, for me, to really go all out on this.
Again, I've got to speak to the man.
So the call is out.
Follow those people who called in and dorsing in.
Get a hold of them.
Let's set it up with a phone call.
A little phone or a button.
We'll just talk to them.
So those five extra endorsements that I think are worth listening to,
coming up right up after, after he closed down the show.
And I will be back Monday, guaranteed.
Adam and podshow.com.
DailySourceco.com.
Thank you for listening.
Live life with passion and have a great weekend.
Take those day food by Friday.
Adam's final thought of the week.
Oh, yeah.
And follow the money.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Hey, this is Anthony machine.
That's a dozen entirely clear.
That I do hope that I'm calling Adam Curry's show.
I'm calling specifically because Adam seems to be thinking for a bit of an independent
support.
And I am really hoping that he will take a close look at Dr. Ron Paul,
who is running for president.
The Republic can pick it.
Unlike many Republicans, of course.
Dr. Paul is against the Iraq war.
And that's going to get some beginning.
He's also an incredibly strong component of tribal liberties.
And the basic philosophy of government is that it should only exist to protect the people's
life, liberty, and the truth of happiness, and other than that.
The government should just leave the people alone to do their own thing,
make their own lives, and make their own decisions about how they want to live.
So I was just calling to really encourage Adam to take a look at Dr. Paul.
You can go to RonPaul2008.com or just Google the name Ron Paul.
They're all kind to create the best.
Thanks so much.
And my name is Betty Wolff.
And my number is 2-0-3.
If you want 4-0-6-9-8.
All right.
My name is Joe.
And I heard that you were looking to use your podcast influence and raise money for a presidential candidate.
You know who?
Well, I'll tell you who.
RonPaul.
He's the last hope that we have that's seeing the restoration of liberty and to Americans.
So you should definitely help promote RonPaul on your station.
I hope you.
All right.
You should support RonPaul because he's the only conservative running for office.
He's against the Iraq War and American imperialism in general.
He supports lower taxes, limited government.
He was against the war on Joe so he should have done nothing for his country.
He should have wasted money.
There's a range of issues.
I think if you look to him up and when he goes up, I think he probably agree with that.
And there's RonPaul from South Carolina.
Hey Adam.
This is Chris.
The stone or Chris Stone from Houston Texas.
He's just wanted to call and say that I heard you on DSE 670.
And heard that you were looking for a presidential candidate.
I highly recommend that you check out RonPaul.
He's a Texas congressman.
Ten terms in Congress.
And amazing man.
A lot of people say that he's a Republican.
By the way, a lot of people say that he can't win.
Honestly, there is a huge huge grassroots movement going on right now.
The United States and actually worldwide.
You can check him out by going to Google, Google and RonPaul or you can go to YouTube.
Just search for RonPaul or you can go to romPaul.meatup.com.
And you can find that right now he has over 53,000 people on meetup.com that are voluntary for hot stuff going on with him.
He's got a great message for the Constitution.
He's an honest man of surprise and link.
Well, you know, there's nobody honest in the Congress right now.
So for him.
And he would make a fantastic president check him out.
And folder.
Bye.
Hello Adam.
If you want to endorse the candidate for your president,
look at RonPaul.
RonPaul, 2008.com.
He's a fantastic dude.
Red.
Can't vote him.
Here's your guy.
Bye.
RonPaul.
Mountain.
mountain.
Come on.
Mountain.
The Best in the Brightest, Saved Up Daily by the Sharpest Mines in Content Delivering Pot Show and Limite.