Hey Adam, it's me, 4.
You know, 4.
The number that comes right after...
Oh, 3?
Yeah, I want to...
What is this?
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3.
You know, even a 3-year-old knows it's 1, 2, 3, 4.
Okay, it's in my contract.
Whenever 3 comes and music's being played, I come along too.
So, you know what?
I'm going to do...
You've got to show coming up, 6, 24?
Well, let's make it 6, 23 again.
We have that 6, 21, 6, 22.
1, 2, 1, 2, whatever you want to call it, okay?
But it's not going to be 6, 24.
You've got to wait 10 more shows to give me a bag.
You've got to own my trust because I'm a little ticked off right now.
You know, 1, 2, 3, no 4.
You know, I'm twice the man that 2 is.
But no, you keep saying 2, 2, 2, 2.
On the DSC, 6, 20.
Yeah, see?
Seems a little blank without me, 4.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Yeah, yeah.
Soundtrack, what's pot to be?
Yeah, I ain't no.
I go about a name off.
A little baby has gold.
Rip it sit in that first thing.
Fifteen.
Yeah.
In this and right here.
I dedicate this and right here.
To all my homies out there, grind it.
We all stand legally and illegally.
Yeah.
Check it out.
First guy that way, he was 6, didn't know when he traced.
Matter of fact.
First time he got on it.
He slept.
Left it on his hip band.
He busted his lip.
Before we could have a talk with a list like this.
Now we're getting the story right here.
But shorty didn't quit.
It was something in the air.
Yeah.
When they said it's getting late.
So sorry young man.
Let's not skate in.
Some kick.
Push, kick.
And a way.
Roll just around the world.
And a place to go.
And so we kick.
And a gun.
And a post.
Wicked out.
Don't let them change.
Yeah.
Or even.
Raise your hands.
Yeah.
Don't let them change.
You're not saying.
Don't, let them change.
Don't let them change.
Yeah.
Oh, no, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
We've been trying to scare
Go now
The perfect way to kick off the Tuesday, Episode 624 the Daily's George Corp.
Could you be kick-pourced and loved as DJ Axel from his brand new mash-up album Break-in-the-Long?
Well, of course, the official supplier of the mash-ups for the Charlie Mashup Town.com.
Check out the show notes of DailySourceco.com for links.
Everybody, how you doing?
It is, well, actually, the morning started off beautiful blue sky.
I was like, oh, man, is this the day that I mean, it doesn't work out.
I can't fly up to nodding him today to go look at Christina's pink mini,
which is still waiting for me after my purchase on eBay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I got to go to London town.
I got a couple meetings this afternoon.
So being picked up at one o'clock to go into the city.
So it's going to be pretty busy.
Still enough time to seek out, you know, where we're rekindling podfinder.
Of course, we have podfinder UK, which you can find at podfinderuk.com with the lovely,
Luscious, Lissivius, Joe Lawrence.
That's the video version.
We're rekindling the US version.
You'll find that at podfinder.podge.com.
I don't think it's all set up yet, but we're doing themes now of packaging the show into themes.
And it's really going to be good.
I'm producing it to actually, I'm just asshole talented this.
Peedub and Brian Know, they're producing it.
It's going to be awesome.
So be able to look out for that.
So I did that this morning.
And of course, want to get a show in for you.
Lots of responses having the lady Patricia on the program yesterday.
One in particular, I guess this is a Yanks versus the Brits thing.
We're just really not good at understanding the dialect yet, I guess.
We were convinced that the news reader on BBC radio 2 in the afternoon,
at least the one who's on the Steve Wright in the afternoon show.
We're convinced that her name was Vanilla Fudge.
Close but no cigar.
I had a little bit of junk work from that Scott.
That's Mrs. Fudge to you.
And it's Vanilla, spell fox or echo in November.
Echo Lima, Lima, Alpha.
Of course, he recently married Mr. Fudge.
She was Vanilla having him.
And she's a good girl right now.
I love it.
That's almost as bad as David guest.
I don't know.
David guest used to be Liza Monelli's husband,
and he was on, I'm a celebrity get me out of here in the jungle.
On the UK version of, is there any other version of the show?
I guess he had the UK version of the show.
And he had convinced all of his jungle mates that his maid's name was of a ginica.
And she married Mr. Seaman.
I know.
Let me see.
Lots of stuff to promote today.
First of all, today is the day the music died.
Although I don't like that slogan.
But thousands of internet radio streams are going dark today.
In protest of the copyright royalty boards fee hike.
That will be, it is mandatory.
Anyone who is creating an internet stream of licensed music,
even music that is not licensed or owned by the RIA, by the way.
Will have to be paid for.
It's a statutory, so read mandatory license.
So basically, all these people who have been creating playlists of songs,
and have been streaming those.
Essentially, to me is the same as sharing your playlist with friends over a stream.
So you're basically programming your friends playlist.
There are other people who are doing proper shows, not a lot.
I get the feeling.
And then, of course, there's a simultaneous streams.
All of those streams are most of them will go dark today in protests of these fee hikes.
They essentially have to pay per listen.
They're paying for the privilege of promoting music, which is so as backwards.
It's so wrong.
Unless, of course, unless they are using music with a pre-existing arrangement,
which is exactly what the pod save music network is about.
Now, okay, you may not find Beyonce on there,
but I'm pretty sure, you know, it doesn't matter.
Now, if you are playing artists who are not on the pod save music network,
and you still want to stream and you don't want to pay for it,
then contact the artists and say, hey, put your stuff up on the pod save music network
and then I can play it.
Royalty free.
Mike says, Dear Mr. Curry, God, it makes me feel old.
I'm emailing you because you seem to be the go-to guy for pod casting in pod show.
I'm the process of setting up an internet radio station,
which I'm hoping to use to showcase pod save music and pod cast.
Since most of the music I use would be from your, your pod save music network.
Thank you.
It's, yeah, we operated, but I feel it's like everybody's.
I thought it'd only be fair to email asking for your permission.
Okay.
Station will play three things primarily.
Pod save music, pod cast promos, pod cast specials,
which would also be, I presume, music based specials.
Awesome.
Mike Kane, send me a link and I'll be happy to put that.
I'll be happy to plug that for you.
And of course, we'll be talking a bit later about the pod show channels,
which are in, in an effect creating a new opportunity for people who want to put together
good music for people to listen to in context.
And tomorrow, the final episode of port city PD of the first season,
the second seat.
I don't know how was that.
Hold on a second.
Let's just see what that is.
Ah, no.
You've come through as identified, just as an unknown caller,
and you get pushed to voicemail.
Season two of port city PD kicks off in July.
And we now have an all iPod only version feed.
So we've got the huge, I don't know if it's high death,
but it's certainly the huge version.
We've got the iPod version.
And you can now go and collect all of season one and get ready for season two.
Now this is the second part of the, the two part season finale,
in which myself and pod show talent pimps and promotions pimps.
Richard Brewer, hey, we both play law enforcement officers.
I'm an undercover asshole FBI agent and Richard is a not undercover asshole agent.
Here.
So actually there's a video trailer.
What I'll do is I'll upload it and I'll put it as an embeddable on dailysourcecode.com
and encourage.com so you can take a look at it.
Listen to the audio for a second.
It's kind of cool.
It looks really awesome.
Ah, hold on.
Here we go.
This is how it should work.
I need you to focus because time is short.
And I hate repeating myself.
Kill them, Alex.
Kill them all.
When he's dead.
You know, you really should be looking at this.
This is a whole bunch of scenes from, I don't know if it's from, I haven't seen these
before.
So I don't know if it's from the season finale episode or if it's from a new episode's
coming, but it's, it's, it's violent, you can probably tell, but the girls in it are
sexy.
There's something really raw about these kids, they're North Carolina where they produce
this whole thing.
And there's a real raw energy in a lot of these performances that I'm totally digging.
Because the girls are beautiful, but they're not your typical like CSI beauties.
You know, these girls get, get roughed up, man.
I really do, why, that's disturbing that I find that hot.
Yeah, there's something else I'm seeing here, oh, Sheila, oh, that's hot.
These aren't Hollywood sets.
These are like real bars and real locations that they scout out in North Carolina.
Oh, that was nice.
That was nice, it's like, tell you what, though.
Well, you guys stand up there right next to us at the press conference when all this
is said.
Yeah, yeah, when my hair's like back, look at like a real douche, port city PD, season
two coming July, port city PD.puncho.com.
That's what we need.
We need Don La Fontaine to do the trailer.
This is how frickin' expensive, but man, does it pay off?
So that's cool.
Oh, there's the voice message we're ever called turning that bit.
Oh, yeah, speaking of calling, very interesting call came in from, I think, quasi-selebrity
in the UK.
Seven, six, eight, one, three, seven, five, three.
So how much is there, there's an edge of, this is, this is, this is very from what
fits the phone in about your code covers, the last Thursday, I plan to listen to your
podcast and I written myself, so I'll miss the folks in the, I'll send it to
you.
I think I've heard this guy on the radio here in the UK and I don't, I'm not sure if
it's an actor or fees for real, but it's like this old dude and he shows, he's like
a media stalker kind of and he calls, I forget what show I heard him in, I think
at a morning radio show or something, I've heard him around and now he's found, he's
found us, my friend, could it be a new savant in the making?
There's a little thing, I wanted to draw the attention to, he's used the word fact, fucking
five or six times, he takes 10 footdics instead of one size and you know, he takes on anyone's
lips, these devil yours is not very nice to listen to, crappy, you said, tell us,
crappy, buy it, tell us, don't know what that is, but crappy was, whoops, whoops, you
said, so could go, said, whoops, screw, that one makes that screw, he said one, and
because fucking boobs hit this and, and, and, man's of delights, which on the ship is
a reference to, I might do, and later is not, you know, you're better than that, I'm
listening to the, the, the podcast, you're better than that, anyway, it's better than what
I'm saying, good luck, we give him up the, the split, I'm telling off now to roam himself
a great thing to do these, from my knowledge.
Barry from Wattford, eh, I can already hear the Jeff Smith making up a jingle for you dude, Barry
from Wattford, indeed.
I've got five copies of Sim City for the first time, I've got five copies of Sim City,
I've got five copies of Sim City, I've got five copies of Sim City, I've got five copies
of Sim City, I've got five copies of Sim City, I've got five copies of Sim City, I've got
five copies of Sim City for the Nintendo DS, to give away now if you want to be one of the first
people to play in the UK, do a pop-along to the show and have a listen, gamesweasel.btpotjo.com,
just answer the simple question and you can be a winner.
This summer, when you buy Coke, you get a music, you can win an iPod or free songs or
nightchains.
You know, Adam, feed up here, I just got to tell you, actually I just got to tell Patricia,
how much I loved hearing Crimea River on the DSC.
They know when I'm sorry, I'm sorry, that was a complete pilot mistake, pilot error,
operator error, because whenever PDoB is on the show, we have to celebrate that fact.
We've got to do a proper, we've got to roll out the jiggle because every supply has a jiggle
to do it on the same thing.
We've got a bit of a satellite repairman coming after a year,
a satellite repairman, watching all of you.
He'll fit your misconceptions and answer questions too.
It's the music I grew up with.
That's the music my dad would be blasting every Sunday in our house.
Patricia got me so worked up, I'm going to give it a go myself.
First I got to turn up the reverb and then I guess I just have to start the track.
Now you say you're lonely.
You cry the whole night through.
I'll go kiddo.
Cry me a river.
I cry the river over you.
And now you say you're sorry.
For being so untrue, will you can cry me a river?
Cry me a river.
I cry a river over you.
You drove me, nearly drove me out of my head.
While you never shed a tear.
Remember, I remember all that you said.
Told me love was too flaming.
Told me you were through with me and that now you say you love me.
We'll just improve that you do.
Come on and cry me a river.
You gotta cry me a river.
Because I cry the river for you.
I cry the river over you.
P.W. Fettin' everybody.
I got a couple of emails from people saying, yeah, thanks for turning me on to that singsong.com.
As I spend five hours over there.
I don't know how those guys do it with the rights.
Of course, we'll be the death of them at the end of the day, which is unfortunate.
Because it's such a great idea.
It's basically American Idol or Pop Idol in a box, if you will.
You go there, you find a song, you sing along, it records it.
There's no actual downloads of the songs involved.
But of course, you can hear how easy it is to use it as a karaoke box.
The lady Patricia didn't pee dub.
So you can record your own songs.
If you know your way around your computer, you can probably get that done very easily.
But it's awesome.
It's a lot of fun because you can listen to other people's versions and you could vote on them.
And of course, the best version pops to the top.
And that's what everyone listens to.
So there's all kinds of social rewards.
I'm sure they can have games and prizes and all kinds of cool stuff in there.
The problem is, is that once that gets really successful,
here comes the recording business and they'll say, well, that's great.
You know, your entire business rests on our commodity.
On our our stuff, our music.
So we'd like you to pay some more for the privilege, please.
That's what always happens.
I wanted to talk about, yeah, warning.
Those of you who don't give a harass ass about the channels.
I'm pretty excited about it, though.
I'm getting emails now.
Clyde Kell.
Thank you for your comments on 622 about the old-time radio group.
Even though I'm no longer part of that group by my own show,
and entity mystery play, internet radio, M.P.I.R. old-time radio.
And he's created a collection, too.
He says, I've got a, I figured out, I can now publish the RSS feed of my channel,
collection on potcha.com.
That's right.
And he puts a link to it.
I'll put that in the show notes as well.
The link to, to his old-time radio channel.
And here's a little secret for those of you who are playing along.
If you look at that URL for, for the RSS feed,
you found that.
Or if you use the one, you'll see that they're all identical.
For, for raw XML, it ends in dot XML.
If you want it to play in, in the real player,
change that to dot SMIL.
If you want it to play in, when am change it to dot M.P.
You, if you want it to play in media player,
change it to dot ASX.
iTunes is really the only one that's different.
You have to change the HTTP to ITPC.
This is all geeky stuff.
I realized, but you know, what's happening now is we're taking all these independent bits that
that we already have built and constructed within pod shell.
We're going to make them functional.
So that you will really have a programming experience,
and not just an individual show experience,
and this is something everyone can participate in,
and also helps you manage all of your media and manage where it goes,
and how it gets there, and you can stream it,
you can download it, you can put it on your iPod,
and you can play it on pod shell.com with the dashboard.
It's really, you know, when we get all this stuff to the front,
as I said, we built our site upside down,
when we invert it, it's going to be awesome.
You know, one of the byproducts of this,
having all the right features at the bottom of the stack,
instead of the top, makes it very hard to explain
what I'm doing and what we're going with these channels.
A lot of you are already catching on,
and if you trackcurry.com, you'll see that I'm publishing
links to click and play different channels all the time now.
But Matt, that's not grass.
He took some time,
and it takes you through the pod show channels
in the inverted pyramid version in a few simple steps.
Have you heard the news?
Pod show has added some amazing features
to their redesign website.
Your experience podcasts are getting a whole new way.
How can I learn about the new pod show you might ask?
Well, front no more.
Navigating the new pod show is easy
with just a few simple instructions.
But rather than me, drone on about it,
let's hear from the pod father himself
to explain to you in just a few easy steps.
Well, I know your anxious to get started,
so let's jump right in.
Step one.
If you register for pod show,
you automatically have a channel.
Step two.
I'm going to search for any term.
Step three.
Find a show.
Click on the show.
It'll take you to the unofficial show guide page.
Step four.
Find an episode.
So not the show.
Just find an episode and click on get it
and then put it into your channel.
Step five.
Now then go to something called my collection.
Step six.
What you see on the side is fucked up and wrong.
Okay.
Step seven.
Go to your collection and you'll see your channel there.
Step eight.
And click on it because you want to modify something.
Step nine.
You can have it play in the dashboard or iTunes or
it has different players or even the raw XML.
Just select iTunes.
Step ten.
Save it.
Step eleven.
Go to the play button on that channel.
Step twelve.
Don't click it.
But right click it.
Okay.
Step thirteen.
And copy that link.
Step fourteen.
Send that link to anybody in email.
Step fifteen.
The click on it.
In iTunes will open up.
Step six.
And then whatever you have collected in that channel.
Shows or episodes.
We'll go to their iPod.
Fantastic.
Step seventeen.
Now here's the advanced fun for people who have been doing this a day or two.
And God, it's so hard to explain it.
Well, we need you to explain it.
You can't really explain it.
Well, I hope you can.
Take the link of your channel.
Or that just explained how you do that.
You want to get the raw XML link.
Step like nineteen.
And import that as a show.
Step twenty.
You just say add show.
Step twenty one.
You can do it in the same channel even if you want.
Which makes it a real mind trip.
Step twenty two.
Once it's imported, you'll see the show is right there.
The same icon will be there that you put in the original channel.
Click on it.
Step twenty three.
You'll now have your channel.
We'll now have an unofficial guide page that people can comment on.
Excellent.
Step twenty four.
That of course is not the way that this is supposed to work.
But that is going to be the type of functionality where people can comment on your channel.
Okay.
And your channel actually becomes like a show.
Awesome.
I love this.
Me too.
I'm not doing a great job really.
I'm explaining it yet.
Just have to kind of do it.
You said it.
So if you'd like to try out the new pod show, go to podshow.com.
Or if you think this is far too many steps, go to the subtlest zone at subtlest.podshow.com.
There is no step twenty eight.
See?
It's simple.
Go to Adam.podshow.com.
Scroll down to my channels.
The pod save internet radio channel is the the one that's the default.
You can set all of that and just hit play channel.
It'll open up the real player and you can listen to some great pod save music.
Some great pod save music shows.
Scroll down.
Look at more channels.
Click play channel.
It's really not all that.
It's really not twenty seven steps.
But what I have asked Andrew Grumman.
I've asked Andrew and Devon.
To clone on the development environment.
I want them to clone the the channel page.
And I want them to put that at a special URL.
So I can expose that.
Because I want you to see how cool it's going to be when you can actually manage the output of a channel.
And I've requested something else.
Sorry about that.
You're rich.
Well, forget.
I'm not going to tell you whatever.
It's it's really coming together.
And it's going to be a great way to discover new shows because just like pod save music where you want to find out what shows have played a particular song.
You'll you'll see an episode or you'll see an episode from a show or a single episode.
And you'll be able to see who has that listed in their channels.
And then you'll be able to look at their channel.
It's almost like the old Napster.
Where if you found a song you'd really like, you could look at that person's hard drive and see all the other songs they like.
So it's kind of like, you know, looking at people's stuff.
It's a little voyeuristic, but and which reminds me I may want to have some kind of private feature to put some of the shows.
Having my collection.
I'd like to switch the private bid on please.
I know I know I'm actually watching or listening to some of those shows.
Hey Adam, it's John Gworkin.
Ask out.
Hey John.
I think last week has to be the week it all happened all together.
If it didn't work just planned.
I used my pod show channel to get the SEC61.
The video podcast.
I used my Nokia E61I and the Nokia pod catching clients to download it from my pod show channel.
And of course I watched the video that you took from your aircraft on the E61I.
On my E61I.
I think that's a full house.
It is a full house.
Very cool.
All right.
So that's cool.
Yeah, then the Nokia's the E series certainly.
And I believe the, yeah, the N series as well.
They have a pod casting application.
So I think it comes pre bundled on most of them.
But you might have to go and download it from Nokia.com slash pod casting.
I think it's slash pod casting.
And you can subscribe to your channels.
It's a real pain in the ass to subscribe to something in this.
So it's much easier if you just put your shows into a channel.
The ones that you want on your Nokia.
And you can manage them from a web browser.
It's a lot easier that way.
It would be fun.
You know, it's Nokia.
We're thinking kind of like Apple, you know, Apple made that one click URL by,
by changing the HTTP to ITPC.
Why does a Nokia do like, you know,
INPC or something like that?
So that it'll, it could, you know,
if you find a link and RSS feed the you want on your Nokia.
You just click on it from the internal web browser.
Man, it's just a thought.
Adam, what's going on man?
There's damn matters.
And from the creepy show.
Hey, I'm in the process of moving from the black hill of South Dakota near the city.
But just want to comment on pod show and the channel feature,
which actually find to be one of the more unique aspects of the site.
Uh, it's people are an example of how it works.
I set up a site at choose or snooze.creepysleepy.com.
And that's uh, left, right, and center political coverage from now until the election.
Uh, and I made a channel.
Uh, it could be sleepy, essential politics channel to stay up on what's going on in the political world and the campaign and the election.
And I just, uh, imported that into WordPress in an RSS reader and then it just displays for people.
And again, you don't have to get geeky.
You can just check it out and see how it works.
It just brings in the latest sources, the newest sources of podcasts that contain the politics and the likes.
And make it really simple for everybody.
So, uh, check it out.
Maybe seeing it will help your listeners figure it out.
Cool, man.
Yeah, I posted a link to that on curry.com yesterday.
I'll put it in today's show notes.
Uh, very cool.
So, um, you can actually, you know, so what Dan is not doing is he is managing a channel of political shows.
And, uh, he doesn't have a lot of control over it right now, but pretty soon he'll be able to, uh,
really put in individual episodes and put them in an order that makes sense.
You know, he may choose to do a, uh, a viewpoint or show that has a democratic nominee guessed on one and have that followed by Republicans.
So it could give almost like an sort of kind of an equal airtime in that channel.
Um, and you can just play it on his channel, uh, page.
Or, uh, it's interesting what he did on it.
He, uh, he imported the channel's feed into his WordPress blog, which I was pretty interesting, uh, which is, of course, completely valid.
This is, the mind boggles, we need, we just really need examples.
So, uh, yeah, Dan, thank you very much. That's cool, dude.
All right, to wrap it up for today, he had him pee Hopkins here. What's up?
Uh, it's been a while since I talked to you.
I don't know if you have any plans to spin my tune become either today or tomorrow,
because if you per chance do, could you please also mention that I'm playing a specific, uh,
a special acoustic show at the Viper room in Los Angeles on Tuesday, June 26.
That's 10 p.m. in Hollywood.
I appreciate the support. Are you kidding me, man?
Pete?
Any excuse to play your song.
Check him out tonight at the Viper room.
It's Pete Hopkins. Here's the come.
My life sentence already is the way I feel.
It's just the way I feel.
But I wouldn't have it any other way.
Life has a funny way.
I think it's what they say.
Yes, what they say.
Uh, surprising you, reaching every day.
So let me sing this song.
And it won't take long.
For the melody, to wash over you.
And meet them, we can sing this song.
As a day is long.
And let the melody set you free.
And it goes along and along, along, along, along, along.
There's a little more to learn from every one.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
No one has had the answer of their own.
Just be loved and become.
Boom, yeah.
So many things to do.
It's the time and nothing ever time and no.
And meet another year, just to get it done.
It's hard to overcome.
I feel like dreams, yet live on dreams.
But I've been human still, we must become.
So let me sing this song.
And it won't take long.
For the melody, to wash over you.
And meet them, we can sing this song.
As a day is long.
And let the melody set you free.
And it goes along and along, along, along, along.
There's a little more to learn from every one.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
No one has had the answers of their own.
To be loved is to be stronger.
You can live on with the pain.
Like I've listened to the fond memories.
Sounds like a lullaby.
Believe it or just leave it.
But you don't know until you feel it.
Ooh, yeah.
And then we can sing this song.
And it won't feel wrong.
To let the melody wash over you.
Ooh, yeah.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
There's a little more to learn from every one.
No one has had the answers of their own.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
There's a little more to learn from every one.
So if you want some awesome part-save music, check out the Viper Room tonight in Hollywood.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
No one has to have the answers of their own.
Pete Hopkins, become from the Podsave Music Network links to that.
In the show notes, a daily source code dot com.
I'm Adam Curry, Adam at podshow.com.
Off to the city.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.