This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
Let's go.
Delta.
Serator.
588.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big media corporations
wet their tiny little pants.
From Poncho, home of the world's most dangerous new content, comes the daily source code with Adam Curry.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Honest and kiss and curry.
Tell me, I know, I need you to know.
Sometimes now forever.
I need it to say in the impossible way.
Sometimes through my window.
I wanted to show how in the kitchen I found the sun.
While you were right.
And if you want me so.
You better tell me so.
Because I want you to see the call of me that can't let go.
Let me know.
I need it to try.
I don't want to go in by.
Sometimes now you need to.
I never can say the way I wanted to say.
But do you ever do?
So tell me, I know, all the things you've done.
Sometimes now forever.
And if you want me so.
You better tell me so.
Because I want you to see the call of me that can't let go.
Let me know.
Can't you see the sun?
Can't only bring you down.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
But do you ever do?
But don't say, I don't stop it, stay.
But don't say, I know, all the things me have to do.
I needed to try as well as going by
Sometimes now you'll need to
I've never been saying the way I wanted to say
But do you ever do you?
I wanted to show how in the beginning I know
That someone's not in the right
And if you won't be so
You better tell me something
Because I want you to see the part of me
I can't let go
Let me tell you
Oh man, is that pretty?
Let me know
Fireings, let me know
The fun things and not worry
Which means you can find it at quadshow.com
Of course you'll find the link to their
Artist page at
The show notes for the show
DailySourceCode.com
By the way, some very cool you can do
If you follow that link
And you've registered with podshow
You can collect all of their songs
You do it by hitting get it
And you can put it in your collection
So whenever you want to hear it
You can go straight into your collection
It's like a bookmark really
But it's a multimedia bookmark
And then you can just play all the songs
You can put it into a collection of other artists
Hey, cool shit
Anyway, it's DailySourceCode
Episode 588 coming to you from a very
Well, it was a very sunny San Francisco
Of course the sun is now gone down over the yard arm
It is the evening, Tuesday evening
So you're here in this Wednesday hopefully
I'm on my west coast recording schedule
And I'm feeling good
I gotta tell you, I got to bed on time last night
10 30 11 o'clock
I actually watched a little bit of news
Which was a ton of waste
I watched a David Letterman's monologue
And I passed out
And I woke up this morning
Before the alarm clock went off
Like 7, 10, 7, 15
It's funny
I can actually program my brain
And say I want to wake up at 7
And at like 7
I will wake up
Maybe 659 or 701
Do you have that?
I know a lot of people who can do that
I wonder how we do that
Lots of good feedback about the new format
I'm so happy you guys are liking it
And there's of course some suggestions
And lots of people sign up to be savants
In the ongoing series of savants
People hawken their family members
And saying they want to be savants
Because their experts in a certain field
This is all fabulous
Because I'm going to take advantage of every single one of you
And I've got a couple of pieces of feedback
Privately and publicly
And it's almost like a challenge
You'll never be able to get a single
I guess on every single day
You'll never be able to pull it off
I'm like
Thank you
I really enjoy that challenge
Because I know I can
I know that I am no more than a couple of phone calls away
From anybody I want to talk to
I'm convinced of that
Now the most people I'm interested in talking to
Of course aren't famous people
They're not the people you see appear on CNN
Or on MTV for that matter
You know it's a people from our own world
Our own savants
And I love you
And I will protect you always
But so that's good
And I will work very hard
And I'm not quite sure
I think I still want to keep
Completely football
I don't want to have a guest
Maybe I'll just do straight music a whole bunch of songs
You know let's shake it up a little bit
You guys seem to be enjoying something different
So that's good
Let me see
I wanted to thank
Doxerals again for appearing on yesterday's show
He of course posted a couple of links on his weblog
He said that he felt
He posted that he felt that he didn't do a really good job
Explaining the issues or what he's working on
Now the vendor
What is it called?
Vendor name system
I understand because I've been reading his weblog
So I know what he's talking about
Basically a way for
Customers who don't have a vendor yet
Or who are just finding a vendor to figure out how to pay them
Something like that
But when Doc has it up and running
I'm sure we'll have him back on
We'll talk about it
So you guys
You can't be lazy on me
Okay, because I'm out there
I'm working the guests
I'm getting them in
I'm getting them on the show
And all of a sudden everything stops
There's no more phone calls
Or almost no more phone calls
There's no more bits being sent in
I mean you know
It has to come
Don't be too lazy
Just be sitting back the whole time
Do something, say something
Or I'm going to have to continue playing this annoying jingle
Yeah, I want you to call in
And let me know what's going on
Or if you have some feedback on a certain topic
You know what to do
I'm actually walking here
I'm trying to pull up
Where the hell is it?
Shit
I hope this is the
Where do I put it?
I hope this is the right one
Yeah
Only person who called in today
I had a prolific program
I'm here from San Francisco
It seems that you are coming
I think you're on Tuesday
I would love to get into the other way
In person
You feel the same way about me
Yes, I do
There for me number is
Okay, well, I won't play as a phone number
So this is of course the downside of having all the savants in the continuing series
Are we done with the number?
To see you this week
I'm available any evenings
After 4-3 evening
That's my home from work
Yeah, so the problem is
I wish I had time to hang out with everybody
I'm here, we're so busy
My life is completely scheduled around meetings that we have at the office
And of course a production of the daily source code
I'll tell you, I wish I could only work on this show
And that's the only thing I was doing all day long
But on the other hand, I do enjoy all the other wacky shit that we're getting into
We're working on some interesting stuff
Yeah, we've been working a lot on lowering our suck quotients
And so you'll be hearing about some exciting ways that you can help us suck less
And it doesn't matter whether you're a podcaster, a pod safe music artist
Or an audience member, in fact that is in many ways preferable
Because we need some help
So that's the stuff we're working on
And you'll be hearing about that in just a couple weeks
How to help pod show suck less
This is the new Jeff Smith jingle that we've rolled out for
I still have to kind of learn the timing
I don't need you to help us suck less
Jeff, I love it, no
Okay, let me see, had a couple of other things I wanted to talk with you about today
Oh, yeah, just regarding Docsurals and the whole web radio
Link in the comments at dailysourcecode.com
Statement from 365.com
About the copyright royalty board, the changes in pricing from music
And I'm not going to read the whole thing of course I'll put a link to it in the show notes
If you haven't already seen it, Brian, no posted that
But so here was an interesting part here
Since live 365 aggregates all of the performances
Stream through our service into a single report
We will be paying millions of dollars to sound exchange
To administer our four quarterly reports when we actually do all the work
On top of that
The new minimum fee would be more than triple live 365's royalty obligation for 2007
And retroactively 2006
Here comes Yahoo real networks in Pandora
And so I guess we could lump a couple of the names in there
Let's just take those three
We'll have minimum fees that exceed $50 million
Although they're combined 2007 internet radio revenues
Will not even approach $100 million
So that's like a $50 million deficit
So of course you can add last step
M to that and a whole bunch of services
And as I reflected a bit more in the conversation
I had with Doc
It is a shame but not
Because well let me put it this way
I agree with him
That programming music
Very much like a DJ does in the clubs
A DJ
It's an art form
And that's the art form I grew up with
The art form I was schooled in
It's creating a vibe and of course that works very well with radio
Because your audience is usually
And a local geographical level
So that's what I grew up with terrestrial radio
So it's raining outside
You play different records and when it's very sunny
Outside stuff like that
But all these themes and the order that the records appear
It's a very very very effective way
Of creating great entertainment
And I just believe that the music industry
Is a shooting themselves in the foot
For doing this, for making it
Virtually unaffordable
And I think it's just dumb
And if anything
I think that
They are
Putting this type of pricing into effect
Are
Proving a huge disservice to society in general
Because you should be able to hear
This music
It is art, it should you know web radio
In effect maybe it should be treated like a museum
And maybe there should be some curator rules and stuff like that
You know the shit that's in a museum
Is more valuable than the music we're talking about
I'm not saying that one is better than the other
But you know there's a higher price tag on most pieces of art
Than there is on MP3 files of songs
But I think that music
The soundtrack to our lives because that is one thing that
Really resonated for both of us
It's important, it's important that that gets passed on
It's exposure and if terrestrial radio
Doesn't have the bandwidth
Literally to provide all of this music
And web radio is one way to do that
Then I do agree that it's very very important
For our
From a social standpoint
Or from a cultural standpoint
Not from a money-making standpoint
No, I don't know if that's going to help
If we can do anything about it or not
So be it
So we did that one
Oh, I got this
A lot of people sent me this link
This is fantastic
Yeah, I'm going to read this is from the BBC
Let me just go to the email
Send this to me Matt
Oh
You're going to love this if you hadn't heard about this
This is nuts
Singer Cheryl Crow has said
A ban on using too much toilet papers
Should be introduced to help the environment
Crow has suggested using only one square per restroom visit
Except, of course, on those pesky occasions
Where two or three would be required
While clearly she doesn't shit like a guy
Are you crazy?
Now
45-year-old who made the comments on her website
Has just toward the US and a biodiesel powered bus to raise awareness about climate change
I am all for the biodiesel bus
That's cool baby
But
This thing about the toilet paper
Hmm
I propose a limitation be put on how many squares of toilet paper can be used in any one sitting
This is
You know, I met Cheryl Crow when she had
Completely blown out hair
And she was singing backups for Michael Jackson on the
I was at the bad tour
I was a very different girl back then
She was one of the band
She was one of the guys
She was burping and farting
And she was funny and she was energetic
And she was
Not a girl who would restrict my paper usage
How am I outraged by this?
She's got more brilliant ideas
She's designed a clothing line with what she calls a dining sleeve
The sleeve is detachable
And can be replaced with another dining sleeve after the diner has used it to wipe his or her mouth
So I guess instead of using paper napkins
Actually, I think that's a pretty good idea
Except why don't we use I mean we can reuse the sleeve after we've wiped off our mouth
We can use the sleeve to wipe off our ass
Of course the entire reason I even mentioned the story so I can play the jingle
Let's find a chair
We got some great savants on the show today
Because we'll be talking about a very hot news story
Which has actually been alive for about a week now
I can't believe we're still talking about it
This is the voice mail that Alan Baldwin left for his 11 year old daughter
And I gotta tell you
The reason why I wanted to bring it up on the Charlie is because
It's a little sick of mainstream media and the way they're trying
I'm like are all these parents so fucking great
All these parents or oh it never you
You're the parent and you should never talk to your child like that
And I gotta tell you I just it doesn't feel like
Reality is being represented
Regarding the story
Let me say it's a travesty this whole thing is taking place
You know for a family to have to go through this that sucks
So I've got some some cool people
And major savants to talk about it
But first let's revisit the voice mail just briefly
You know
I
Know
You know
Before
to me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me,
you know me, you know me, you know me, you know you, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know you, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know me, you know you, know me, you know
top's. They truly are savants of the human psyche and I thought the perfect
people to call today about this. Welcome Robin and Suzanne, Maiden of
Insight Works to the Daily Source Code. How are you guys doing?
We are doing great. Very well. Thank you. I'm so glad you guys could make it. I
appreciate you staying up late. You being on East Coast time, but you guys have
helped me in the past with, I said the human psyche, which of course is, that's a
very, very broad description of what you guys talk about. You want just for the
people who aren't familiar with Insight Works, just give us a brief synopsis of
the show and what you guys do on that? Well, we talk about Insight Insight
into ourselves and we miss fellow at Horrible in our website name. That's INSYTWORKS.com
and I thought it's like we're at the pocho so you can get it there. But we
talk about depth psychology. Suzanne is an active therapist and she's gone to
the Pacifica Graduate Institute and there's a lot of union work and depth
psychology and I'm just a lay person. I've done a lot of reading and we on
our show talk about how people function and using the depth psychology approach
and the things that are in the unconscious, how that manifests in the physical world.
So, when you hear this voicemail from Alec Baldwin, what was your initial reaction
the first time you heard? I don't know if you were together when you heard it
you heard it separately. What was your first reaction? Oh my god, I'd cringe. I just
cringe. Oh, me too. We have a 10 year old and I just couldn't believe it. Yeah, I mean,
you know, and lightly speaking, and when I say lightly, I just mean some of basic
therapeutic standpoint. I mean, it's clearly emotional abuse. There's no
question about that. But I think what you're looking at at a maybe something a
little bit deeper than that, like I'm guessing, and the that be right, is to
why he would do something like that. Well, here's my thought. What really struck
me, and Patricia and I heard it together, and I talked with a couple of my, I don't
really have any friends. So acquaintances about it. And I have to admit that in contrast
to everything I saw and actually your reactions as well on television, if you kind of, if
I look a little bit through the words in the tone, I understood him. And I think that
I too have been at times certainly that pissed off at my daughter who now is almost
17. You can't say anything she kicked my ass. But I certainly would have to say that
I too have in the past been guilty of speaking certainly in that type of tone, have been
that angry, and of course that anger probably was channeled from somewhere else at that
moment, and I think that's what's what's probably happening here as well. But everyone
seems so incredibly shocked, and I'm thinking myself, have the people that I'm seeing
respond to this, never ever spoken to their children like this, because I think I have to admit
that I have, and I've heard other parents say this as well.
Okay, and absolutely, and I guess that distinguishing factor is that, and I too have a child,
we have a little boy, and he's actually close to Alex Baldwin's daughter's age, and
have I lost my temper with my kid? Oh my gosh, have I raised my voice of my screen? Of
course. But the distinguishing factor is, have you called your kid really ugly names? Have
you been really threatening and intimidating? I don't mean threatening like, if you don't
do a, you're going to be grounded, or privileges are going to be taken away. That's
different. But the distinguishing factor is that he's like threatening her. He's like,
I'm going to come out there and blah, blah, straighten you out.
Yeah, but is that wrong? I mean, well, Suzanne, he was basically saying, I'm going to
get on a plane. The way I heard it, and maybe I'm just hearing it differently, is I'm
going to stop my life and come and straighten you out because you need help. And I've
been through this, by the way, with my daughter, the whole phone thing, where, you know,
they reject the call or it's, you know, everyone can, my daughter's on the phone all day.
Everybody can reach her, but when I call, I always get voicemail. You know, it's like, what's
going on with that? And it felt to me like I was saying, I'm going to take, I'm going to
stop everything. I have to fix you, which is, of course, dads are like that. You know,
so kids broken, got to go fix the kid. It felt to me, it, to me, it didn't feel like,
like it was going to go kick her ass or anything, but, you know, sit her down and have
to talk. Okay, but he didn't say we're going to sit down and talk about this. He called
her a rude, thoughtful, little pig who had no brain. Yeah. Okay, that's one of the things
that I took out of this was, yes, I get as angry and I have gotten as angry in this
frustrated sounds like you have. And Alex, you know, Alex Baldwin has, but I always go
after the behavior, I don't go after the person. And in this case, Alex went right
after the person. He called his daughter names. And I think that's very different than talking
about the behavior. And the next level that I'd like to take this to is sort of into what
did this trigger in him? Because it's obviously, you know, a phone call getting rejected,
like you've had done, that, that doesn't merit the response. And that's what people always
get surprised about is how people react to a seemingly small trigger. And that's where
Suzanne and I say it's triggering something in the unconscious. Yeah, this is deep for him.
This is very deep. This is triggering, you know, this type of rage, rage is old anger. When somebody
is fat out of control, rage, that's not new stuff. That's not the event itself. You got to look
back historically. What has gone on with him in the past? I mean, just some of the words that he
used, you know, he was obviously very angry. He was very frustrated. He was insulted. He can say
it has to be the last time he humiliated me. Right. So he felt humiliated and he felt attacked.
Now, were those things really, you know, appropriate for having his daughter reject a phone call?
You know, I think it's from a much deeper wounding from a long time ago, or maybe just a
collection of a lot of experience where he has been humiliated or attacked or insulted.
We're letting so out of control in his life that he's asking kind of his daughter to put him
that responsibility almost on her and saying, I'm going to come out there and straighten you out.
And this is going to be the last goddamn time he humiliated me. What else was going on in his life?
That feels so out of control. So let me just say a couple of things about that.
First of all, I got the distinct feeling that this was not the first time that she hadn't picked
up the phone by prior arrangement or something like that. So that could stem some of the frustration
could stem from that. I will say one other thing, as it comes to family behavior, our family,
particularly my daughter and I, and Patricia is, of course, completely opposite, which is why
our marriage has worked for 20 years. But we're very, we all three of us are very emotional people,
and we talk with a lot of motion, you know, where artists, performers, we're creative people.
And I think I've said much worse things than, you know, I've never called my daughter stupid,
because she's not stupid. But have I said things worse than, you know, then you're a pig? Yeah,
probably. And I think that does come down to what, you know, a family, you know, every family has
its own rules, its own behavioral patterns that are acceptable to them and how they speak to each other.
It may not sound nice on the outside, but, you know, I've seen families that have been together
very happily who just say the most terrific things to each other. Well, there are definitely
standards within the family, you know, that the people operate under, that to the outside world,
have different standards. So, you know, I can agree with you on that. So, and you guys, you know,
have a child as well, so that that makes it a lot easier to talk about this. What do you think
if, well, two things, I guess. First of all, what is a better way to approach these type of
situations with your kids, you know, and I'm not a big believer in huge kumbaya. I have to say,
write up front, you know, like, come on, let's sit down, let's talk about, you know, how, how can you
do that? And perhaps the telephone is just not the right instrument in general. And what should
Alec Baldwin do at this point? Really for the relationship with his daughter and forget everything else,
because obviously his life may be very together, but yeah, does he have some problems with his family?
Yeah, obviously. So, on those two topics, you know, what, what comparisons do to not fall into
this trap, which I obviously is not going to work, you know, I heard it, I was like, well, you know,
the kid is not going to respond to this. What can you do and what should Alec Baldwin do in
his particular case? Wow, well, let's take a second question first, which is what he,
where should he kind of go from here? And I think the first step is just to really talk the heck out of
this, with his, with his daughter. But I don't think that should be, I think there should be some
supervision there. What that looks like? I'm not really quite sure. Should there be a therapist? I don't
think it can be in his ex-wife, you know, that's obviously a pretty, um, it's a non-starter,
is what I'd call it. Yeah, yeah, that's a show stopper right there. So he really needs to just keep
communications. A third grade, some sense when we work with families like this, we're one
parent is more volatile. We could just email. Really? You know, that's just email each other for
right now, instead of doing the comb-by-offing, because the kid might be too resistant to sitting
actually down with him and talking about it. It might be safer to just do the email thing,
so that might be a place to start. Interesting. Then how to respond? Yeah, that's one thing that,
again, we recommend, um, in this type of situation. And then how do you even present from getting
there? But, you know, how did he get where he is right now? He hasn't checked his own stuff. He's
not a control. That's the thing that I go back to and in, in trying to fix the relationship with
the daughter or how do you communicate with the child at this point? Um, I think that's, that's
even trying to figure out a way to do that is almost a band aid to the, to the bigger problem.
Right, because Robin, this really, this is more of a symptom of a problem. His daughter is
not, the daughter's almost an honest issue. Right. I mean, you say, well, maybe with, you know,
Christina, you've tried to call her, and again, she's readable to all of her friends, and then when you
try to call, she's not available. Um, and he had kids do that kind of stuff, of course they do.
And, you know, is there a problem there with that? Well, yeah, maybe okay, but God, his rage was just,
so to me, it was very disproportionate to the event. And I, I go back to, she's in and I always
talk about things and try and look at the world in a symbolic fashion. And so, you know, what was
the trigger in this? It was the daughter not answering the phone. So, symbolically, maybe, you know,
Alec is not getting his phone calls answered, you know, kind of a, in a, in a metaphorical way,
that, that, here he's trying to, you know, maybe get another, you know, another show, another movie,
another whatever, and he's putting this stuff out there, and nobody's calling him. So, that's a
very, that's a great analysis. I like that. Well, but it, I think in a very symbolic fashion,
maybe this was just a trigger that he's been waiting for the, not coming. Nobody's answering
and he just, and then he calls a daughter who, who maybe has done this also in the past, but maybe
he just, you know, it just comes to a head and it's triggering a reaction from all these other things.
And we're not, we're not privy in the news and everything else to all the details of his
environment of what's going on in his life. Obviously, there's a part of him that wants to control
his daughter. And that wants to be heard. Yeah. Pick up the phone, damn it. Yeah, you know,
I think you guys really, really nailed it with that one because I catch myself a lot.
I'll be, you know, busy, I'm doing stuff, you know, it can be stupid as like I'm trying to
configure something and it's not working and then someone will come upstairs, ask something
very benign and I'll snap, you know, and then, and now that I'm a little bit older, I actually
catch myself and say, oh, you know, sorry, I was just a complete asshole. That was not directed to
you, you know, and so I and Patricia really taught me a lot about that too because, you know, she
just being senior in years, you know, what already recognized this and she could just easily
shrug her shoulders instead of letting it explode into an event. But I think you're absolutely right
that, you know, it's completely symbolic and we don't know any of the backstory. And if anything,
I think the the Travis de Hairs that this, you know, that this recording was released completely out of
context, I think that's, that's really the most damaging thing that was done here is just to,
you know, to have this on public display to me seems like a really bad thing.
Right. And it's really, it is so easy to take it out of context because there's just so many things
we don't know. I mean, we can insert things and look at it, you know, symbolically that,
all right. So the the only thing I guess I just want to go out of this is that I personally don't
think that Alec Baldwin is a bad parent and, and it kind of bugged me, I have to say, you know,
just seeing all the news reports and it's, you know, and man on the street interviews and, oh,
you know, how the hell could he ever talk to his child like that and I'm like, well, you know,
I don't think he's a bad guy, but yes, I think he did on the head there.
Right, he's a bad parent and he and he and he and his daughter in other ways might have a
really strong bond and a great relationship. Well, I sure hope they do.
Yeah, I do too. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, guys. Well, listen, I really appreciate you weighing in on this
and and hopefully I can call on you more in the future when we have to deal with the
issues of the psyche. And everybody's my gosh. Everybody's my gosh. Yes, because there's lots of
it floating around. Yeah, including my own. Yeah, including my own. Right on, right on, we've got
baggage and we're proud of it. Damn it. He's hands with Louis Vuitton.
Exactly. I'm black and white. Hey, man, to me, it's indestructible, you know,
can't break my luck. All right. Well, guys, thanks so much. Insideworks.com is the website for the show.
It's really a great show. So make sure you check it out and Robin tailwinds my friend.
All right.
It's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no joke, it's no
It's no joke, it's no joke, it's not joke, it's no joke, it's no good, it's a joke cover dumbfarads keep up with business and shit and shut ya
I'm about to turn on the light in your space There's no smile like the smile on your face
There's no joy like the joy I'm just so coming in
There's no joy like the joy I'm just so coming into
Hey, that's some high-class ship right here, man.
And it's pot safe, Angelic Kigio featuring Peter Gabriel.
And Salala.
Ah, that's awesome, man.
Just know that.
Nice, is that?
On the bio, on the pot safe music network, Angelic Kigio, the four-time Grammy-nominated, much celebrated
singer composer and performer, began in the Beninese port village of Cotonu, where she
launched a career at the age of six, the political turmoil in our country, led her to reload
relocate to Paris, the capital of world music.
Awesome.
That's really, that was really, really nice.
Hey, wasn't it nice to hear Robin and Susanne, I was listening to them speak together.
And they really, what a pair, man.
They fill each other in, and they're almost like a Bob and Ted news team.
Well, Robin, let me tell you, and yes indeed, Susanne, but it's natural, I really like that
a lot.
All right, so outside is beautiful right now.
The sun is completely set, so the city is in that orangeish glow, and like a blue dark sky,
it's fantastic, and just perfect for me to shut down the show and go to something else with
my life.
So thank you very much for listening, I will be back tomorrow, of course.
We'll find another savant to chat with in our continuing series, as I am the Sultan of the
savants.
DailySourceCode.com for links to everything discussed in the show notes today.
And of course, Adam at podshow.com.
Thank you so much for listening, everybody, bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
podshow, and linelight.