Dude! Yeah, what's up? Did you see that chick I was with last night? She was smoking.
Yeah, she gave me your number. Yeah, I got it right here. D.S.C. 5.6.5. Oh man, she left a number off.
Don't know, that's what she wrote. D.S.C. 5.6.5. Who? Adam Curry? Yeah, big-haired fag, pink glasses,
jumpsuit. Yeah, I remember him. Here's no Kurt Loder, but I know who he is. A podcast, daily source code.
Oh man, that sucks! Ah, she was a skank anyway. D.S.C. 5.6.5.5. My ass.
Let's say two heads are better than one, and with this angel from above, there's nothing that they both can't do.
I make you wildest dreams come true, to grab your ear buds and jam a man.
I let the fabulous show begin. It's Adam and Patricia.
Yes, Adam and Patricia. Adam and the lady Patricia. Adam Curry was just a guy with big-haired,
who sold his first company and thought he'd just kick back and take it easy, but he never counted on this.
Adam and Patricia, the king and queen of the manner, or just the lady and the tramp.
Only on the daily source code.
Some folks like to get away, taking holiday from the neighborhood.
Half a flight to Miami Beach, or a Hollywood.
When I'm taking a play hand, on a Hudson River line, I'm in a New York state of mind.
I've seen all the movie stars in their fancy cars and their limousines.
I'm in a New York state of mind.
It was so easy, never, day by day.
I got a touch with the river my blues.
But now I need a little, give out and take the New York time.
It comes down to reality and it's fine with me because I've let it slide.
Don't care if it's Chinatown, or run from the side.
I don't have any reason.
Let them all be high.
I'm in a New York state of mind.
It was so easy, never, day by day.
I got a touch with the river my blues.
But now I need a little, give out and take the New York time.
The daily news won't.
It comes down to reality and it's fine with me because I've let it slide.
Don't care if it's Chinatown, or run from the side.
I don't have any reason.
I left them for me high.
I'm in a New York state of mind.
I'll just take a day out.
But now I need a little, give out and take the New York time.
It was so easy, never, day by day.
I'm in a New York state of mind.
I have to go to jail for your pleasure like that.
I took it off of iTunes and then I re-recorded it to get rid of the digital rights management
and then put it back in the cast blast and it sounded shitty.
It's the lady Patricia in the attic.
It is so good to have you back on the show.
You put me in my place, I think that's what people like the most.
That's a real long time.
How are you doing?
I'm doing good as you know.
I came back from Holland.
I was in San Francisco for eight days, something like that.
Then I came back for a week and I left to New York.
I came back and it was the first thing I said when I saw you.
My God, you look good.
Exactly.
It's this dancing.
Because what did I do?
I don't know.
What did you do?
What was his name?
Well, Carl.
Carl, you have that nice freshly fucked face.
Yes.
No, what I did was I trained a lot and I danced.
I'm still dancing.
The dancing is doing wonders for you.
I believe it is absolutely.
And it's fun.
It's fun.
Because actually going to the gym, I don't like that.
It's too boring.
It's very boring.
That's why I don't go because it's stings and it's boring.
And I'm so disgusted.
And they don't let you smoke your spliff while you're working out.
That's right.
It's a real bummer.
But also, you're touching everything you're sitting in somebody else's sweat.
But sweat, no less.
Oh, I hate that.
Yeah, that's a good point.
I like to be outside.
So I'm doing my walk, which is very convenient here across the road.
Which is, of course, because we moved that area across the street is wonderful.
Yeah.
For, for walking, for power, walk is going up.
It's the shantry woods.
It's very good.
Yes, the shantry woods.
Yes.
And it's a mountain.
So you have to go up.
A mountain.
It's like a hill.
It's not really a mountain.
It's a mountain.
It feels like a mountain.
For Dutch people that may be a mountain.
It's a hill.
And so that's very good.
And then I have weekly, which is actually tonight.
Right.
I have my dance class.
I have got to see this.
These people in the, like, the tight latex suits and the really stuff.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
There's nobody actually.
There are some people.
Other people rehearsing.
But it's just me and my teacher.
I know.
But what is he wearing?
No, he's wearing, uh, blue jeans.
Soft, dancing shoes.
Uh-huh.
And, uh, sort of, very hugging kind of a, um, black.
Like her.
Is it like her?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
And he is, he is younger than I am.
I have to say that.
But he looks older, probably.
Uh, I'm not going to say.
You know.
You never know.
It's not delicious.
I never know who's listening.
But he's, he's very nice.
And we have, it's, it's again, I have a lot of fun.
Well, baby, it becomes you completely.
Because, um, now, not that your butt has ever looked big or anything like that.
Let me just, just claim this right up front.
No, I never had a bit.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
But he's even smaller.
Well, no, but it, the, everything is contracted.
You know, so you would, you would just more woman.
And it's contracted a little bit.
And now you are pretty, I'd say you're close to, uh, when you were 38.
Really?
No, but doesn't make you feel good if I say that.
Come on.
Go on.
Yes, tell me.
Oh, so I come back.
You know, it's like, uh.
We women like that.
I know.
I say that.
That's why I'm saying it.
So I'm doing it for you.
No, I know.
You're, no, for you.
For all other men of the world.
I don't think that.
Yeah, it looks great.
It really does.
Thank you.
So I come back, uh, what's Saturday?
Yeah.
Saturday from New York.
And we have one day.
And of course, I'm completely messed up on that.
The time really messed with me this time.
I'm gonna left you, okay.
Yeah, then you left, man.
At this time, difference, you know, the, the US of A, uh,
changed, uh, to daylight savings time.
A whole month before the rest, before the rest of the world,
to, uh, it was part of what, uh, part of, uh,
the administration's energy saving plan, which I believe kind of makes sense.
Uh, to give us an extra month of, uh, of more daylight,
therefore, yes, like less electricity being used.
Yeah.
That made the difference between New York and London four hours,
which was really weird because I felt like I was near you,
but I wasn't near you.
And it was still, you know, just those four hours
and by the time I got involved.
We can feel worse.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
It does.
One hour can feel worse than then eight hours.
It's unbelievable.
Yeah.
So, uh, anyway.
Uh, this oriented, and then you laughed.
You, you went away.
Yes.
So what did you do?
I went to my friend, uh,
uh, Paul Schult, who is, uh, a fashion designer.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it's good to hear.
Let me guess.
And is he gay?
One of the best.
Very gay, but so sweet.
I love that.
You know, that's so wonderful.
And he loves women.
Mm-hmm.
And he designs for women.
And, uh,
I'm always, um,
in the first part of, um,
trying to get a whole show together.
And then think with him and with him.
And we, we sort of, uh, a team together.
Yeah.
You know, where we, um,
You come up with a thing that we're,
and these are the shows.
You know, these are real productions.
I mean, this is, uh,
real like Hollywood style productions.
Yeah.
Big.
It's big stuff.
So I've already got the next one.
I do the Dutch designers, um,
do their fashion shows,
either weeks before or weeks after,
like the rest of the world,
like Paris, New York.
Well, that's when you, I don't get it.
No, I don't know.
That's, it seems really wrong to me.
Yeah.
I'm not a fashion guru, but it seems like.
But they all do it.
Yeah.
Maybe.
I don't know.
They're not even, I think,
looking at what the other designers are doing.
They're doing their own thing.
They have their own shorts.
Sure.
So what can we expect?
A lot of famous and very wealthy clients.
So for to spring 2007,
what should we be wearing at Lady Patricia?
What is going to be in?
And I'm not talking about what the Dutch designers are saying,
but what is the,
the world of fashion at large say?
I, you know what?
Those panties you had on,
yes, that they were pretty fashionable.
They're cute.
Mm, very cute.
The whole set with the bra.
Very, very.
Very Brigitte Bardau.
I couldn't wait to rip them off.
Very.
Very in and big, big, especially the, the bags.
The bags are huge.
The huge bags.
I see bags carrying women around these days.
It's cool.
You and your bags.
Yeah.
It's out of control.
Carl Agafald calls him the La Grande sack.
Yeah.
Well, I've got a La Grande sack for you right here.
Listen.
This, this.
This bag thing.
It's out of control.
It's very, this.
You know, the more expensive.
I feel this is porn for women.
So it's almost like we've now gone into the, uh, into the double D territory.
You know, it's like, uh, now all sudden it's hot to have really, you know,
porn with really big boobs.
And this is crazy.
Yeah.
This, I mean, these bags are way too big.
What are you coming from boobs to boobs?
No, no, no.
Bags are porn for women.
Yes.
So porn for men.
We have trends, right?
Right now it's very much, uh, she males are very trendy.
Of course I, I like to think I set the trend.
Yeah.
No, but seriously.
But big boobs were, were a big, you know, big trend.
Well, there's, there actually back because if you look at all the, the braziers and the bras,
they're self, they're full with, with stuff in there.
Women are filling up their bras.
They're filling up their panties.
Their butts are all safe.
They have big, big boobs.
I don't get that because it's going to be so disappointed if you take it.
Exactly.
In the future, you know,
Why would you fool yourself?
We're going to have like this, you know,
auto photoshop reality where women walk around in a haze of photoshop and they look beautiful.
And even kids, 15, 16 years old, even younger, all those little bras have those, those air bags in them.
And cur bags and silicone things and I think that's not good, is it?
But anyway, so I was back in Amsterdam.
And every time I'm there, all the photographers, all the photographers just,
How you know that?
Run, how you love it.
Because I'm never there.
Finally, I'm there.
The queen has arrived.
So, you know, they took all those pictures and guess what happened?
Because I was, I was actually a little bit of wearing a vest, a man's vest.
I saw it in the heart.
And I had a little white shirt on a neat open.
Mm-hmm.
And you could see my very beautiful, clean, very neat, but, you know,
Clevage.
So what happened was, I, I, I tear it.
No.
I tried to close it in suddenly, I tear it.
You tore it.
Yeah.
So it was a, a big tear.
It was a big tear.
And I tore it.
It was a big, no you tore it.
You tore it and you had a big tear.
Yeah.
So then, you know, all the, all the photographers,
Oh yeah, they loved that.
The photographers started to,
Perhaps, no common, perhaps not.
That's what they call here, paparazzi, the paparazzi.
The paparazzi.
So started to flash, of course.
Of course, did anything top out?
God.
They needed a white angle length.
I have to say.
They popped out.
Now, not, not really with a nipple, but you can see a lot of brass.
Yeah.
That's something closer to any more.
So that was a nice moment.
Excellent.
I, I, I hope they're happy with it.
You know.
So did you, did you close that go?
I gave him something.
No, I couldn't.
I couldn't.
It was just, it was really, it was, I couldn't throw the way now.
Right.
Okay.
So that's what happened.
And so now tell me, are you going to be doing dancing with the stars again?
What's happening?
No.
I didn't explain that last time.
So they were, when I did the, the special.
We're dancing with the stars.
Yeah.
Or the, you know, it's called here a strictly condense.
Don't.
It's called dancing with the stars in the stage.
Yeah.
I know.
So I did that special Christmas and New Year.
And, well, of course, it was, got a lot of attention.
And so the, the producer and the, what is it?
The broadcaster.
Yeah.
I said, would you like to do the real one?
Right.
Think about it.
Yeah.
Which, of course, is why you immediately went into training.
Because you really wanted to get to mass secret training.
And keep that, you know, the vibe going.
And, and I was in good shape.
So, and I kept that up.
And they actually asked me twice.
And now I didn't hear anything anymore.
And I thought that's strange.
So now.
Typical tellers.
But the girls, I spoke and I said, no, you know what?
They couldn't do it because they got the rules from the BBC.
There's a couple of rules.
And it is.
Once you did the special, you cannot do the real one.
Because you already are ahead of the other.
That's, that's the rules of the format before.
Okay.
Oh, that sucks.
So, and I said, it doesn't mean you can dance.
I only did two dances.
I don't know.
Really?
But I want to try it.
And I'm not the youngest.
No.
So, I think it's, it's a big deal.
But no.
No.
So that.
But I probably, I'm left lame.
I might be a guest or anything.
And there were all kinds of, there were all kinds of rumors about you being a judge on
So you want to be a pop star.
I mean, like, I read at least 20 different newspaper articles that said,
Well, yeah, that's true.
They asked you for them.
They couldn't afford me.
Okay.
Dude, those other guys have it even fucking paid you from dancing with the stars.
That's true.
That sucks.
Oh, man.
I hate that.
And you know, it's like now, and you can't go asking for it.
Because if you, you were going to give it away.
It looks silly.
Yeah.
Because it's not that much.
But, you know, we could give it away for forever.
You were going to give it away.
You said, I want, it's like, it was like nothing.
I want to give it to the animal.
It was like 1,500 bucks or something.
It's totally negative.
What it is, but they're still dead.
Oh, I hate that.
Oh, well, when they ask you for something else next time,
you tell them that you're, uh, your manager in a council wants to talk to us.
Even the dancers.
They didn't get paid either.
No, the UK dances here.
Get so much more.
But then there's a leverage.
Hold on a second.
Don't compare.
Do not compare.
No, no, you can't.
You can't compare the UK market to the Dutch market.
The Dutch market.
There's like 2 million people watch a program.
You know, and here it's like 10 million.
So you can afford a lot more.
But still.
No, no still.
They, they spend a lot.
But on different things.
Yeah.
They do spend a lot.
They just cock suckers.
They should, they should pay everyone.
I know these dancers don't get paid.
They're not paying.
They just go down and be begging for their money.
It's not that complicated.
Everybody's complaining in Holland.
And I spoke to a lot of people that the the, um,
The quality of the, the, um,
The quality of the, of the shows and the program.
Yeah, that's crap.
Okay.
All right.
Who gives it.
Going bang down down.
All right.
I don't care anymore.
I don't live there.
And it's a pity.
It's because they don't want to pay.
me. I had my prize and they said no. Something completely different. Yeah. How about our garden?
Oh, isn't it? I took pictures. I put them up on the website. Yeah. Yeah, did you see them? Oh, man. They're awesome. No, I haven't.
Yeah, but no, actually they're almost done. That's why that's why. Yeah, to be fast. That's why Sunday when it was, was it Sunday? No,
yesterday Monday. No, I fuck. I don't remember Sunday, maybe. Yeah. It was so beautiful here. Look at this
and how does it smell when you open up those French doors of the dining room? It smells like heaven. It smells like spring.
I'm going to show you these pictures in the meantime. I got to play one little promo. There's something big
that's happening on what's today. Today is Tuesday on Thursday. Yeah. Big thing happened. Listen. Oh.
Hey, this is Neil from the Podsafe Revolution podcast. I'm sure you've already heard about this thing
called bum rush the charts. That tiny spark that is turned into a bonfire and is currently burning
up the Podsphere and the blogosphere. I'm sure you've already marked it on your calendars as well.
March 22nd, 2007, but this is a little reminder for those of you who are late to the party.
Here's what's going on. The whole premise is this. On March 22nd, 2007, that's this Thursday.
We're going to stand together to be counted. We'll put our collective dollars where our mouths are.
We'll take two minutes of our time and we'll purchase one song on one day in order to drive
that song to number one on iTunes. Now along the way, we'll be doing something positive for the world.
A world in which record labels think that Payola and Swedish pop songwriters are the only way to make
a difference. All proceeds from our iTunes affiliate link as well as 50% of the band's proceeds
will go towards providing money for a deserving college student to pursue higher education.
Now when we first started this little experiment in social media, the question was, will anyone care?
Well, not only has the online community joined our little Podsafe army, but big media has taken notice.
Bumrush the charts has been represented on the CBC, the BBC, wired blogs, the San Jose Mercury,
and now a little rag called billboard ever heard of it. The world is watching and our time is now.
On March 22, we ask you to join forces with us using the affiliate link found on bumrushthecharts.com,
purchase the song mine again by Black Lab and be a part of history. One day, one song, one voice,
number one on iTunes. Bumrushthecharts.com. I'm in. Are you?
So that's this Thursday. I told you about this, right? What we're doing?
Yeah. We're all going to buy it. That's wonderful. Yeah, so we chose Black Lab because they
were dropped from a major record label. And so now they're independent, they're on the Podsafe music network.
So everyone's going to say, go and buy this song to their audience. And of course,
you know, David Sorscott audience, a lot of them will buy it. It's 99 cents, but what happens is
we're going to show this song, move up the iTunes charts. You know, up until, you know,
where like Beyonce and all that. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So we can show that there's actually a lot of
power and podcasting. Oh, that's good. Yeah, I thought it was a pretty great idea. No, great idea.
Yeah, it wasn't my idea. Oh, I hate to say. Okay. Yeah, but so that's Thursday. More about that tomorrow.
I'm obviously. Hey, great pictures. Don't you like him? Beautiful. Aren't they pretty? Very pretty.
Thank you. I thought so, too. I don't want to keep you too long. So funny. It's like,
why not? Because I got to go. Oh, okay. It's like my grandfather used to say,
oh, lay down, take off the empanies, be out. Oh, well, you wouldn't be abused.
I've just been over the desk. I can't help it. I love with you. Oh, thank you.
I love in lust. I get butterflies in the stomach. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. The butterflies are still there. Absolutely.
People getting nauseous now. I hope so. Yeah. No, women love that shit. Women love that.
When I, when I talked to him. How long are we having butterflies?
The Fox 20 years. Yeah. Twenty twenty-one years. And they're still fluttered. It was October
20 years ago that we came to the States together. Wow. Wow. It's a long time.
It's one big adventure with you, huh?
Emphasis on big.
You're the only woman I know who will make me wait up here in the studio.
Well, I'm coming. Yeah. I was like, well, what do you, would you please hurry up? Well, I'm putting
on my makeup. Is it? It's audio. It's like, it's almost like, um, what were you used to call
um, radio? I was like, you don't even make up for, oh, yeah, for this show. Yeah, well,
I wanted a good for you. Mm-hmm. Yeah, what you do.
For me. All right. So I got to go because I'm, uh, Ron and I'm meeting with Gavin. Yeah. Yeah. You know,
Gavin from our, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. We were in the dinner party. Oh, uh, and good looking
guy to say. Oh, pardon. Uh-huh. Well, no butterflies for him. No butterflies for Gavin. You sure
no. Not even a, a moth? No, no, no. I do have moth. No, no. Uh, I'm not blind. Of course. That's true. Not neither
my. Don't worry. Mm-hmm. I like to flirt in you, too. No, I don't flirt at all. Yes, you do. Yes, I do.
Very big flirt. I know you are. Emphasis on big. And that's good. Just keep it. You know,
makes you look good. Can you buy Tylenol PM here in the UK? No. So it doesn't exist because I was wondering
this yesterday. I told everyone that you want to try them out because it seems like the perfect thing
for women, uh, Tylenol PM sponsoring unwind and G. B's new show. Although I don't take a lot of
pain killers because I'm not in pain. But if, if you are, if you want to go to sleep, it's
nice. Exactly. And I suppose to take it every single day. I guess not. That could be moth or
back pain. But what I understood from you is that, um, well, women have more pain, aches and pains
regardless. Oh, we're one big pain. In the ass. Exactly. But that it's a perfect thing. Will you try it?
It's just, it's just painful to be woman. That's it. Sometimes it's hard to be a woman.
Give it all. What were you doing? Were you doing? Did you just want money? You guys have a little
bit of pain. Oh, then it's not, and then I need like a whole bottle. Oh, I bet headache. That's true.
I wanted to play something for you. I song the off the pod save music network. I want you to evaluate
this. I've played this a couple times. I know you don't listen to the show when you're not on.
No, I hear you the rest of the days. I know I'm, you know, you're one big pod show, don't
this is my husband, the pod show. I want to listen to this tell me what you think, but I thought it was
really good because guys got a big future. Pete Hopkins become from the pod save music network.
I wouldn't have it any other way. Life has a funny way. I think it's what they say. Yes,
what they say. Oh, surprising you each and every day. So let me sing this song
and I want to take more for the melody to wash over you and meet them. We can sing this song
as a day is long and let the melody set you free and it goes. La, la, la, la, la, la, la. There's a little more
to learn from every one. La, la, la, la, la, la, la, no one has had the answer over.
Just been not and become. Oh, yeah, so many things to do is a time and nothing ever
time and love. You need another year just to get it done. It's hard to overcome for
the love dreams. Yeah, live on dreams. But happy human still, we must become. So let me sing this song
and I want to take more for the melody to wash over you and meet them. We can sing this song
as a day is long and let the melody set you free and it goes. La, la, la, la, la, la, la. There's a little more to learn from every one.
La, la, la, la, la, la, no one has had the answers on their own.
So we love this to be stronger. You can laugh away the pain, light again the listening to the
form of a sound, it's like a lullaby. Believe it or just leave it, but you don't know until you feel it.
And then we can sing this song and it won't feel wrong to let the melody wash over you.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la la, la la, la la, la la, la
la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, las.
You like it, don't you?
Yeah, very mellow.
Every single time.
Very much in love.
Mm-hmm.
It reminds me a little bit of the Elessi Brothers kind of,
the vibe, not the singing or the song,
and it's kind of the happiness.
A sort of a Michael Jackson kind of a...
Yeah, that.
The vibrato thing.
Yeah, especially with the stop.
Yeah.
I love that.
When the stop was there...
Like...
Quiet?
Did that remind you of anything?
How do you?
What?
Oh, oh.
On the heavy breeders, they always cold me.
No, whenever I play that song,
people write in, they love it.
This people often scoff.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
Yeah, very nice.
Beautiful. Nice, so harmonies.
So we kind of make up for the Billy Joel violation.
Yeah.
Make it show.
All right.
Will you promise to come on a little more often, baby?
Yes, of course.
Yeah, because...
There's so much that we haven't talked about
that I'm of course I'm going to remember
the minute after we're done with the show.
You want to discuss with me?
Yeah, we have to do it more often.
Yeah, of course I want to discuss.
Oh, you have to be our consultant, you know,
on the cover girl stuff.
Okay.
We're going to do this.
Yeah, yeah.
Definitely need you to consult on that.
And if you wouldn't mind, could you please buy some
Folgers coffee and splendor.
They've splendid here, right?
Just not the...
Yes, yeah, the sugar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's not sugar.
Splendid sugar, too.
Yeah, but it's not sugar.
Exactly.
No, that's not their slogan.
I know.
Yeah.
Could you could because in America,
I'm always drinking Folgers and mixing with Splenda.
Yeah.
And I got nothing to talk about for the commercials.
Yeah, yeah.
I need to have it here.
You're Folgica.
I'm a L'Oréal girl.
You are a L'Oréal girl.
Yes.
For sure.
It's perfect.
I use it for years.
And I'm actually waiting.
But we're not getting paid for this.
What do you do?
I know, but I'm waiting for somebody to...
Oh, you're having a great offer.
Hey, L'Oréal.
I want to be in there.
In the commercials?
Who's doing it now?
And in McDonald, or no, she's not L'Oréal.
No, no, no.
Jane Fonda.
I don't like that commercial that she does.
No, no.
Yeah, you want to slap her.
Yeah, you don't want to buy it.
Yeah.
It's bad.
No, it should be more vital and hip.
Who else is doing it?
More trendy.
It's not you.
It's me.
Yes.
It's you.
Patricia.
Yes.
Of course.
I'm going to be 58.
I thought it wasn't allowed to say that.
I thought we weren't talking about your age.
Yeah, we're not saying it.
Seventh of April, we're going to be 58 too.
You want us to say 60.
I mean, that's it.
You're done.
You're toast.
As long as people, if you go in the street, yes.
Because we do that.
Christine and I do that now.
And she said, this is my mom.
How old do you think she is?
Yeah.
She's stupid.
It's not thinking.
You know, and the kid is saying, well, 35.
And I was like, oh, oh, oh.
I made my day.
Yes.
Would you like some dinner?
Come over to our house.
Still think I'm 35.
That's good.
Yeah, that's good.
And I'm a milk.
Yeah.
What else?
I got to show you this site called milkseeker.com.
Yeah.
It's unbelievable.
Guys take a camera.
It's don't really in.
Mils are totally.
I know.
But check it out.
So they take a camera.
They go into like a mall.
And they pick up mothers.
And they end up in the camera.
So they got this whole wrap of what we're doing.
A student film and blah, blah, blah.
And they get him in the car to their,
So mom's studio, which is nearby.
Which is the top.
What do you mean take off the top?
They fucking, they have sex with them.
No.
And like serious.
Two guys.
To go.
How old are they?
These mils?
No, the guys.
Oh, they're young.
Yeah.
Oh, they're good.
And one of them has a huge shwanshin sticker.
Not that I'm just writing.
I said, guys.
What do you got to go to California?
Really?
Do all mothers dream about that?
I'm telling you, no, no, no.
Is it true?
So often you have these, I mean, you know, me.
I'm a porn official notto.
So so often you see these like the bang busts and all this stuff.
And you can tell that they're paid, right?
It's like, like, hookers walking on the street or porn actresses.
And you know, it's like an act.
But this, you can tell these women are not faking it.
It's real.
And the one for one, they all go with these.
I mean, I don't know how many they struck out.
You got to see it.
It is.
But I know it's going on because I see it when I walk in Guilford here.
The guys are really flirting with you.
You mean, Milford.
Milford.
And Christina says to Mama, they love you.
They love your breasts.
They're looking at you.
And I think what's going on.
I know it's because women these days don't
Exude that sexual energy that women used to.
Yeah, but because now it's all like what we do.
It's like pumped up bras and fake butts and all that.
But you're real.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe that's it.
Maybe they're looking for the real thing.
And they know that those little kids are fake.
Maybe that's it.
Maybe.
I don't know what it is.
Maybe it's just a thing.
Very, very strange what's going on.
I can see it.
But it's true.
It is a milking milking milking.
In fact, I think the females are out and the milks are in for the spring.
Very much.
That's the milky look.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah.
Amazing.
But very nice for our milks.
Milks united.
Yeah.
You're bad.
All right.
I've got to go to London on.
I've got to get out of here.
Right now.
So daily source code dot com.
Adam at pot show dot com.
Anything else you want to say to the other.
No, no.
Have a wonderful day.
It's going to be a bit cold, but.
Yeah.
That's right.
And between our legs.
It's somewhere else.
Yeah.
Thank you for coming on the show.
You're welcome, babe.
And see you again, maybe end of the week.
Yes.
Friday, maybe.
Let's do a Friday show.
A football Friday show.
You know what football means, don't you?
Yeah.
Football.
You don't know what football.
Do you know what football stands for?
F U B A R.
What was that?
Fucked up beyond all.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
God.
I'm so happy you listened to this show.
There's so many things.
If you actually explained it to me before.
If you actually listened.
You'd be horrified.
I'm sure.
Okay.
Yeah.
I believe it.
All right.
Thanks, baby.
I know you're saying awful thing.
But I'm not there.
Does anyone email you and say I can't believe what Adam said?
No.
I only speak.
Oh, you know.
I hear it all the whole day.
So I know.
And I, there's a lot of humor in that.
Okay.
All right.
You're a lot of fun, baby.
Oh, well, thank you.
40 minutes exactly.
Perfect.
All right.
Friday.
Yep.
I'll see the rest of you guys back here tomorrow.
I love you, baby.
I love you too.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best of the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limelight.