Hey home fries, it's CC Chapman from accident hash, encouraging you to check out
BODON.TV slash battle.
It's one of the coolest battle events out there, and you can only find it at BODON.TV.
You're where to miss Thony, from joysie.
Hey, first of all, congrats on your anniversary.
Seems like this yesterdays you was getting yourselves all together.
Yeah, now you're making a big time.
Yeah, I heard you and the families go into New York going to their fire island for the
Big Family reunion.
You know, if you get some time swing by the old neighborhood, we can have some fun, and
You know, we got a tire island.
You know, it's a big stack of tires in my backyard.
We can pretend we're doing whatever.
You know what I'm saying.
Come on down.
We're doing a little cookout, walk around in a wife beaters have a good time.
It's a summer.
You got to relax.
You got to take it easy.
So don't forget us guys down here in the neighborhood.
No, I'm saying.
All right.
Peace out.
And have fun on the DSC 651.
For $60 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky prints.
I like to think I'm flying into this short.
Fantastic.
It's a bedroom curry.
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you love me all the time.
Maybe I'm afraid of the way I love you.
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you pull me out of time.
And hold me on the line.
Maybe I'm amazed at the way I really need you.
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you love me all the time.
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you pull me out of time.
Help me, baby, what you have been on the stand
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you're with me all the time
Maybe I'm afraid of the way I leave you
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you're helping me see my soul
Maybe I'm amazed at the way I really need you
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you're making me Peace
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you're helping me see my soul
Maybe I'm amazed at the way you're helping meOST
Maybe I'm a fan, I'm maybe I'm a lonely man
And I'm maybe like something that he doesn't really understand
Maybe I'm a man, maybe I'm the only one that I could have with me
Maybe I won't you help me, I'm sad
Maybe I'm a man, maybe I'm a man
Oh, maybe I'm a man
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let me just make myself up on the floor for a minute
May it's back
Blake Morgan, ribs are all a new one
Maybe I'm amazed, it's from Blake's album Burning Daylight
And it is pod safe, my friends, that's right
It's on the pod safe music network as of today
Blake with his engine company records has license this
In the proper manner so that he can actually make it pod safe
And there you have it played for your enjoyment on the daily source code
It's for the Burning Daylight album
Which I think comes out today, actually
Awesome
Oh man, link in in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It is episode number 651 coming to you from the west side of G-town
Where the water flows downhill, thank goodness
Because it's still a wet one
In fact, the rain is literally flying horizontally past the attic window
Oh man, it's nasty out today, really, really, really bad
And then you've got these people protesting at Heathrow Airport
They're expecting, I think several thousand people
They're already there, they've got tents and they're going to disrupt Heathrow Airport
I think half of the people are from the surrounding area of the new terminal five
Which they're really pissed off
But I think there's like 4,000 homes, which will probably be rendered pretty useless
When they open up the third runway at Heathrow
So they're protesting, of course
You might know when to go live in near an airport
I hate to say it, but that's just the truth
And other people are there against aviation in general
Not general aviation, but aviation in general
Because of it's effects on the global climate change
And I look out the window today and I say, screw you with your global tour climate change
Where's the warming part of all of this?
I don't know if I'm going to listen to it here, I'm going to repeat that
You got from a car last week, he was giving you a hard time about how much wine
And you do about whether, you know, I'm an amateur astronomer
And I can completely informally relate to it
You know, this time of year, I was going to send from North Carolina
And this time of year, you know, it's got awful heat and humidity and buginess
You know, at night all that moisture just hangs in the air
You know, I'm out in the country and you have a good view of the stars
All I get is just this big murky summer haze
And this time of year, I just hate it
You know, like I said, you know, people, people
Completed about listening to you complaining about the weather
People complained about me complaining about the weather
Which I'm in turn, I'm sure is complaining about something else
I could just totally relate
So why do I wait my friend?
I'll send you some cheese to go with it
All right, why didn't she?
Why didn't she?
Wrap it up.
Thank you very much.
We've got the wine and cheese.
Yeah, I'm wanting about the weather
Luckily, though, we're leaving tomorrow
Towards the muggy humidity of New York, of course,
We'll be out on Fire Island
In the wife beaters running around
That's going to be nice with my sister Willow and her two kids
That'll be nice.
It's going to be fun, man.
I'm looking forward to that
Although I must say there is so much stuff happening here
With BT Pod Show in the UK that I really, from a work standpoint
I really don't want to go
So now, you know, there's some meetings I tried to get hooked up
For today, it's just neat soon.
People got scheduled schedules and agendas
So I'm going to set those up for the week of the 27th
When I come back, which will be a short week
Because then I'm going to go to
The West Coast
September 1st, I believe, is that the Saturday, let me check
I think it is Saturday, Saturday, September 1st
I'm planning on being in Los Angeles
For the big, cost-as-world party
I forget what the party is for
Let me say, let me just go into the Gmail here for a second
Let me see what does
Hmm
Now, of course, I can't find it
Crap
Well, September 1st is some kind of party for cost-as-world
Tony Price, who not only is one of our prized media properties
One of the great shows that we have on the Pod Show network
He also does sales in Los Angeles
And Tony is a great guy
And what I'd really like to encourage you is to, in fact, I'll put a link in the show notes
You've got to listen to cost-as-world
Truly
Tony is, I'd have to say, really a leading voice in young black America
Now the show, in a way you could say, it's almost like an African-American, you know, Howard Stern
But really, it's not, you know, because what Tony does is he tackles all of these topics
See they did the apparent fear
That black man have of homosexuality
That was called No Homo, the name of that show
The most recent one was about Mexican immigrants in California
I mean, really, really hard-hitting issues
And he's got a whole room full of people
And they all step up to the mic
And Tony is definitely a voice of reason
Through all of that
But just I love listening to that show
And I cannot wait to throw down
And party is the white shadow of cost-as-world
Hey, Ed and it's Mark from Hamburg
There's before you disappear into the new world
Give us an update
What's going on with Cochill and John Vark
When this is new show starting
You know, already unsubscribe from the cranky geeks
And I'm afraid I won't get my dose of stroke
So please
I have a couple things there
First of all, John Show tech five is actually it just quadrupled in numbers
Earlier last week
Probably because he started to promote it on devourac.org slash blog
Techfive.podshow.com
Tango Echo Charlie Hotel
And then five, the number five.podshow.com
You can find John's tech five report
I like it, he's really gotten into his own now
And it's essentially the quick news items of the day
He's taken on it and in and out
Which is brew, call, drink, bubbling in the background
But like it very much
I wouldn't unsubscribe from cranky geeks though
Because he's going to continue to do that show
Which I think is a fantastic program
I really enjoy watching it
In fact, I'm going to try and be on it when I'm on San Francisco
First week of September
It's, you know, don't, don't unsubscribe
Or from Twitter for that matter
You know, that's all definitely part of John's empire
But there will be more that he'll be doing for podshow
And he's also, John is also a guy behind the scenes
He does a lot of, you know, a lot of the strategy and thinking
And marketing
And complaining
Which is good
Doug Pilgrim, our friend from Boston, Massachusetts
Sent in an awesome YouTube clip
This is so incredibly funny
It won't really translate
Let me see, I'm going to open it up, regardless
It won't really translate into audio, I don't think
Now this is more about mainstream media
Fulling you
And, you know, fulling, lying, trickery
Or entertaining, maybe it's all the same sides of the same coin
This is from the program Man vs Wild
Which has been a part of this controversy all along
And, well, let me see
So essentially, what you see here is you see a bear
Walking along this, this crevice
Or is it crevice
This crevice
And there's like a lava bridge, you know, not real bridge
But it's just lava rocks and he's like, you know, like the scary music
And he's jumping over those rocks
And then the guy who put this video up on YouTube
Does the same thing, except he reveals a little bit more
Let me see if I can give you the sound
Yeah, listen to that
That is a way to do it
So you see the footage, what's that?
These lava bridges across and over
Sort of the same way, you get snow bridges over crevice
Travasses
So you've got to be really, really careful crossing these
So he's just because you don't know what's solid
And what's hollow underneath
So he does this like daring jump
And now he crosses the crevice
Wow, music up, big drum beats
So the guy who posted this YouTube clip
He's standing in the exact same spot
He's got like, you know, like, dorky shorts on
And a washed out pink tea shirt
And some kind of, like, almost looks like an Australian
Like, out back hat
And he, so he does the same jump
Walks the other side, really casually
Except now the camera continues to pan left
And you see that the crevice ends, you know, about
20 feet down the road
In fact, then the camera zooms in
There's a whole fucking road there with cars driving
But
Oh, it's funny
You've got to see that
Make sure you go to curry.com
Or daily source code.com
And look at the show and I was duck
Thanks so much, buddy, for helping us to digest
More red pill information
Drumming bass and bass
So, let's just mention
Featuring the best of all genres of electronic music
This is Bizzucca Joe
And on this week's Olympic Sticking Nation
We leave Earth far behind
And take a journey with Ambit, musician, and soundsmith
Robert Rich
We'll talk with Robert in here
Select tracks from his life performances
At four Mason and the Morrison Planetarium in San Francisco
I find that when I'm documenting live concerts
There's a different energy to them
And see live albums that I release
tend to be just the improvised concerts
Which I reserve for our surface special occasions
It's less common for me to release something
That is one of the concerts where I play pieces
From other albums
In part because I don't want to repeat pieces
That want every album to be unique
Come listen to the best of all genres of electronic music
On solo-psistic nation
S.O.L.R.T.F.I.S.T.O.C. Nation
Don't call
Chocolate ring
Some stay dry and others feel the pain
A baby born with diabetes
Or the symptom chocolate ring
The school books say it can be here
Again chocolate ring
The prisons make you wonder where
It went chocolate ring
You heard 10 and say the world
It's dry chocolate ring
Zoom her camera out
And see the light chocolate ring
Or has to be falling
Just got a chocolate ring
Only in the past years
What they say chocolate ring
With your neighborhood insurance rates chocolate ring
Makes us happy living in a chocolate ring
Mead me frost the street me early
Day chocolate ring
Mead you turn your head the other way
Chocolate ring
It's trick with the crashing through
Of a chocolate ring
Using you to far back down again chocolate ring
It's trick with the crashing through
Of a chocolate ring
Using you to far back down again chocolate ring
Sound a mention on the radio chocolate ring
It's the fear your leaders car control chocolate ring
Worse than swearing worse than calling in chocolate ring
Say it publicly and your insane chocolate ring
No one wants to hear about enough chocolate ring
Which real hard it goes away somehow chocolate ring
Makes the best of friends begin to fight chocolate ring
But didn't they know each other in the light chocolate ring
Every baby where we washed away chocolate ring
Stayed behind his collar, stellar bright chocolate ring
The same crime has a higher price to pay chocolate ring
The drug ginger is where it's not the best chocolate ring
It's trick with the crashing through your veins chocolate ring
Using you to far back down again chocolate ring
The tipsy Britain economy chocolate ring
Turns that body into a GDP chocolate ring
The milker blames the baby's DNA chocolate ring
But his scores are how much the parents make chocolate ring
Flip in cars and France the other night chocolate ring
Cleans a suit without beneath Mumbai chocolate ring
Cross the world and back it's all the same chocolate ring
Angels crying shake their heads and shame chocolate ring
Lips the arc of power and distance and chocolate ring
Which hard do you think you'll hear than in chocolate ring
More than much and more than past and lot chocolate ring
Remake how we got to where we are chocolate ring
It's trick with the crashing through your veins chocolate ring
Using you to far back down again chocolate ring
Using you to far back down again
Unless you've been living under a rock
You've probably heard this song
It's gotten like 5 million views on YouTube
In fact I think it's the video that really propelled this thing into
Some form of a meme across the tubes
Tazonde and chocolate ring
You've got to see this YouTube video
Kids like 25 sounds like he's 85
And he just looks kind of funky and dorky in the whole package is nice
I like it. I like the song too
Very, very, very deep lyrics
Awesome
Tazonde
Links to that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Let me see
Oh yeah, I knew that after doing my shout out yesterday
That someone would respond pretty quickly
And it was Fred Zelda's
From the Netherlands
You said, Adam, of course
I have the very first daily source code
Three years and a day ago to this date
No number at the time
So it wasn't really DSC001
But it's titled DSC204
2040813.mp3
And in this show
This first one which I recorded in the car in the studio A8
On my way to the Netherlands to break the
To pick up
I think glasses or something
Reading glasses, whatever
We're seeing eyeglasses
I explain the format and the thought behind the daily source code
I thought we'd take about four minutes
And just listen to that opening sequence
From three years and a day ago
Where you can hear exactly what this show is supposed to be about
And I have to say
I think I'm pretty much kept to it
Well, good morning everybody
And welcome to the daily source code
Thank you very much for taking the time to download this MP3 file
Or if some of you may have received it automatically overnight
As an enclosure in your aggregator
In that case, thanks for subscribing
So first, what I'd like to do is explain exactly what this is
What the daily source code is going to be
And well, as the name already suggests
It's something that's going to be daily
And I'd like to elaborate a little bit on
The name
Daily source code and what inspired me to do this
Where that came from
By the way, I'm recording this in my car
I'm on the way
From our home in Belgium
To Brida in the Netherlands
To pick up
Your pair of glasses and contact loops
What do we have here?
Horse and carriage
I think I'm going to have to take another route
Anyway, the daily source code
Let me back up here for a second
I'm going to very narrow country lane
And there's a horse and a drawn carriage coming my way
So, you know what?
I'm going to just step over here
And while I'm talking to you guys
I'll just wait for this guy to pass
When I was on vacation
Just recently in Sorrento Italy
A couple of great things happened
First of all, as if by magic
My wireless microphone, which I had lost
For a few months
I had the receiver part
But just couldn't find the microphone part
It was left over from our
Reality show that we taped over a year ago
And bought a couple of really professional
Wireless mic kits
About $2,000 each
So, this is great as great range
And has a great sound
It's just fantastic
That's professional stuff
And so I found that in a suitcase
I've been lurking there apparently for a couple of months
And I thought, well, all right
Now I can finally start doing some audio
Blogging again
But also, I've loaded up my iPod
You may or may not know that I have
I've created a couple of scripts
That parse some RSS feeds
With enclosures and automatically downloads
The MP3 files and adds them to my iTunes library
And to my iPod
I'm subscribed to the IT Conversations feed
And so I'd loaded that up
Just to wait for this guy here
Sure, buddy
I'm happy to do it
I'd loaded it up
And on there was a couple of conferences
A couple of sessions from the open source
Developers Conference I believe
And I forgot what the speaker was
I'll be sure to find out and link to him
Was talking about what source code really is
Is source code
The actual script that runs
That makes your computer do something
Or the machine code that sits underneath all that
Or is the source code perhaps
Actually the written explanation
Not just the funky English
That a computer can interpret
That explains what a program is supposed to do
And I kind of subscribe to that idea
That maybe even an RFC
Or just a functional description of
Okay, here's what I want this computer program to do
Here's how it should behave
That that is the actual source code
It's the thought behind what eventually gets written
In computer code or in a scripting language
So if you think about a radio program or an audio program like this
You could kind of coincidentally
It's also called a program right
I guess you could say that this is the source code to me
It's Adam source code
And every single day a bit of me is filtered
Through to the web
And I write about what I'm thinking
What I've been reading
The links that I choose
The sites I choose to link to
All that comes from a certain mindset
On any given day or moment
That's what I call the source code
So I figured if I
If I have a weblog and I've got all these links and stories
It might be of some interest to some people
To listen to the source code of where all the ideas come from
Well little did we know what would happen
So although I don't blog that much anymore
Of course the show goes up on the weblog every day
And I do post stuff intermittently
It is still pretty much two to four
Let me just see there was a little bit left here
I heard that's running around in my head
That I can't possibly write down
There you go
That's it
It's stuff running around my head
That I can't possibly write down
That's exactly what this is
It's my life
It's my thoughts
It's my opinions
I think we pretty much held to that
Sounds a lot like an audio blog
Honestly
But notice that there's no music at the beginning
And now it's much more packaged
Oh boy
It really has evolved
It's funny because I found
Actually no I didn't find Fred sent me another link
Two
Daily source code
20040822
So this is a little over a week later
And this was obviously when I was still
Tinkering around with the iPodder script
So what I would do is I would create a little test file
I'd upload it
And then I'd see if my aggregator would actually
Grab it and download it
Here's an example of one of those tests
Okay
If all goes according to plan
Then this was uploaded to my server
Automatically by me dropping it
Into a special folder on my desktop
And a blog post was made
And enclosures were added
And everything went automatically
Let's see if it worked
And indeed it did work
It's cool Fred
Thank you so much man
I really appreciate that
That's awesome
You got me that first episode
It's oh by the way
As a special treat
If you are subscribed to the Daily source code
Channel, the DSC channel
Then you will get this episode
In its entirety
Automatically as you just heard
We're still using the word
If you don't have the channel yet
Go to Atom.podshow.com
You'll see my channels right there
Click on the DSC channel
And then either put on your iPod
Use one of those options
There you can put it on your iPod
You can get the raw XML
Do whatever you want
We can just play it right there
Play the channel
I've made it the first one
In the channel
So it'll start playing immediately
Now let me take you back
To the month of May
When I received the following
Audio Comment
Hey Adam
It's Sam here from London
In the UK
I usually only phone you
To my non-spone
To place like them
To receive right here
But today
I won't be advised to do any of your servants
I'm offended by him
Finally last week
Early on Thursday morning
To recount a bit of a horrifying story
She was welcome at 23 am
When you're extremely ill bang
And the bedroom was full of the concrete smoke
So the first thing she wanted to do was call the fire brigade
So she wanted to pick up her phone
But her phone was in two bits
And the battery was missing
So she panicked
She thought someone was in a house
So ran for the nearest phone box
Fortunately when she got there
There were a piece about on the street
A night social grant
One of the police officers
And said that there might be someone in my house
The house might be on fire
And stuff that would really need to help
The police went back to the house
Fortunately the fire hadn't got any worse
And the smoke could cleared
And you confirmed that there was nobody in our house
But on investigation
They found the mobile phone battery
Now this Nokia mobile phone battery
Had shot
From her mobile phone
Across the side of the room
And underneath the wardrobe
And said itself on fire
There was a pretty much just a molten lump
And the metal underneath the wardrobe
And it sets fire to the carpet
And also it's stuff that suits
Now
That was the story in May
Today
And this has been the most emailed article
I've received in weeks
Nokia announces product advisory
For BL-5C battery
Oh yes
So
Just to go back to that conversation
Of the cell phone
So the battery exploded
I then
Yeah
I think I played the comment on the daily source code
Candyman Luke from Nokia said
Hey dude
We're going to get in touch with this guy
Nokia did
And
Didn't really hear much
I did receive a follow-up comment
But it's like
Okay
First they said it's impossible
And then they said
Well, please send us the phone
And so it looks like some investigation has been going on
As Nokia today
Issue to product advisory
For the Nokia branded BL-5C battery
In fact, it's a battery
Industrial company limited of Japan
Between December 2005
November 2006
This product advisory is not applied
Any other blah, blah, blah, blah
Nokia has identified
Then in very rare cases
The Nokia branded BL-5C batteries
Subject to the product advisory
Could potentially experience overheating
Initiated by a short circuit
Well, charging
Causing the battery to dislodge
Hahaha
Nokia is working closely with
And we'll be cooperating with relevant authorities
To investigate the situation
Dislodge
How about shoot across the fricking room
And explode in a plume of smoke
And fire and flame
Dislodge
Yeah, that's one way of putting it
Cricky
Talk about
Crisis management
I see
Well, it's sent me this on a couple other people sent me that
So apparently this is how many batteries are involved here
46 million batteries are being recalled
I've checked I don't have any of the
Offending BL-5C's
But I'll betcha
I will betcha that it was a BL-5C
I don't know for sure
But I'll betcha that it was one of those that exploded
And
And dislodged
So you heard it here on the Charlie first
As far as I'm concerned friends
First time right here on the Daily Source Code
Tonight you'll bet a step
Rebellion you ruin
Peace and love
When the day in spite of all your lives
We'll come from the land of the ice
And snow from the midnight sun
Without springs glow
The hammer of the gods
We'll drive all ships to new land
To fight the war
Seem crime
Bellhalla
I am coming
Oh my sweet
With this thing all
My only goal will be the West and shot
We'll come from the land of the ice
And snow from the midnight sun
Without springs glow
How soft your feet so green
Can whisper tales of God
How we can't
The ties of war
We are your overload
Always sweet
With fresh sugar
Our only goal will be the West and shot
We'll come from the end of the ice
And snow from the midnight sun
Without springs glow
The hammer of the gods
We'll drive all ships to new land
To fight the war
Seem crime
Bellhalla
I am coming
Onward sweet
With fresh sugar
Our only goal will be the West and shot
And shot
And tight you've been a star
Rebuild all your ruin
He's the love we'll win the day
And spite of all your new days
That one's also for the pot safe music network
And Wilson in the immigrant song
Classic Led Zeppelin
By the way, I was talking about the Elton John
And Wilson collaboration that's on the PMN
You said, yeah, we're two St. Peter
It's the first song ever learned to play on the guitar
I didn't even know it was an Elton John original
Go figure, learn something new every day
From our house, we're coming out of September 11th
And Wilson embracing the pot safe music platform
And revolution to the immigrant song
That's it for today
The source code for today
Tomorrow traveling
Maybe I'll check in from Fire Island
Certainly with a blog post at curry.com
So check out daily sourcecode.com for all the links
Everything discussed in today's program
And drop me a line Adam at podgeo.com
Hey, have yourselves a wet Wednesday
In a nice Tuesday
Another podgeo podcast
Stick it in your ear
Thank you