Hey, this is Michael Butler from the Rock and Roll Geek Show.
Check out one of my favorite TV shows this summer,
Bow Dog Music Battle of the Band.
It's a competition with Johnny Rotten as one of the judges,
and that is quality television, my friends.
Find out more at bowdog.tv slash battle.
And now a man who's not afraid to dig through shit for technology.
Adam Curry in the DSC 650 set.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's Adam Curry.
You've got a boatman in the back home, and I tell the fuck for you.
I need love, love.
Take ease, my man.
I need to find a man.
Someone to call, man.
But mama said, okay, hurry, love.
No, you just have to wait.
She said it out, don't go easy.
It's a game of give and take.
You're okay, hurry, love.
No, you just have to wait.
You gotta trust, give the time.
Don't matter.
If I'm wrong, it takes me a little bit.
That keeps me hanging on me for a minute.
To let me live again.
Right now, we know nothing.
That keeps me hanging on.
When I feel my skin.
Yeah, it's almost done.
I remember mama said.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She said it out, don't go easy.
You know, it's a game of give and take.
You're along the highway.
I'm much more than I take.
If I'm wrong, it takes me a little bit.
You're okay, hurry, love.
No, you just have to wait.
That keeps me hanging on me for a minute.
I know information for a lot.
To come on.
But when I feel the eye.
I can't go.
These precious words keep me hanging on.
I remember mama said.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cover your mouth, okay?
Wake well, breathe out and take mix.
That keeps me hanging on.
I don't get me for a family
To let me live again
Right, I'll leave all of my life
That keeps me hanging on it
But I feel my skin
Yeah, it's almost over
I remember my mistakes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Oh my god
DJ Early Bird
Mashes it up
Discovered on mashuptown.com
It's a classic mashup
I have to say it took me a little while to get used to it
But I know I just can't get this thing out of my head
In fact, that's exactly what it says
On the posting on mashuptown.com
Queens, a hard life
And the Supremes, you can't hurry
Love and you heard it here on episode number
What do we?
657 of the daily source code coming to you
From the affluent suburb of Surrey
Known as Gilford on the west side of G-town
In the curry manner
I got to adjust a little bit of my microphone settings here
I was at...
Hold on a second
Let me just do this
Okay, how's that?
That's a little better
Yeah, and Mark Yoshimura Namcoff is doing some kind of musical
And he's asking lots of people around the network
To sing songs and he gave me some like a boy band song
To sing and so I've been reconfiguring my entire studio
To basically come up with a better recording of me sounding like shit
And off-key
Patricia came up the other night
Say what the hell are you doing?
Because you know, I'd smartly close the doors
And I'd locked everything down
And I'd like...
I don't want the actual singer in the household
To hear what I'm doing
She said, you know what it is?
You're not sure of yourself
And you really...
When I'm gone and she's gone right now, by the way
That's when you just got a way loud and see if you can really
Just put the emotion into the song
Well, I can't wait to do that
It's gonna be...
What is it?
Hellway musical too
Something like that
I don't know what he's up to
But the song's pretty funny
So I'm definitely gonna be a part of that
Sorry about yesterday I'd forewarned you
That I probably wasn't gonna come up with a show
And of course that prediction held true man
He was busy, I was in London
I met up with my...
My new buddy Ray Santilly Ray
I gotta get Ray on this show
He is without a doubt
A savant of conspiracy
And he puts out...
In fact, Ray Santilly, if you google this guy
You'll see that he was the mastermind
Behind the alien autopsy video
If you remember that film
I think it was fox that aired it in a big special
It was aired around the world huge
Huge publicity he made a ton of money on it
And he to this day he's still not tell anyone
Including myself whether it was really true or not
I think from looking at it it was pretty clear
Wasn't
But he's got all kinds of awesome stuff
And you were working on the Lost Elvis Diaries with him
So how to nice lunch with him
And then actually you put together two shows
That are going to air here in the UK
One which will be very applicable
Particularly also for expats
If you're interested in UK sports
Bill Bradley who's pretty well known
Newspaper editor, sports editor
He's going to do a show for his kicking off
End of September I think beginning of October
And another one which I'm very excited about
Is the star babes
The daily star
It's a, I'd call it a tabloid newspaper
That comes out daily here in the UK
And they've got, you know, just like the sun has a
A beautiful babe on page three
And we're going to be doing a show about all of these page three
Babes
Now it's not only that
There is, I mean I'm not going to tell you about it
But it's good
I think it'll go beyond the traditional slow moes
Of half naked chicks
Which of course is a big part of the format
But there's more to it when I entirely that shallow
Hey out of my love you
I have, you're kind of a contrast rate with the trencha
You just got a letter B
Hang, you're always imposing this
That I'm a correctiner
2007 man
He's got a letter E D
B
I was thinking about that
I don't think really do I come across that way
When the lady and I are on the show
And then I kind of came to the conclusion
Yeah, particularly Sunday show
Now here's what happens, you know, but we are
Without a doubt
Completely
We're sparring partners
And, you know, Patricia will sit down sometimes
By the way, she sits down with the full intent
Just to fuck with me and get me angry
And she'll tell me later
Oh, I was just fucking with you
Get angry because it's so funny when you're angry
And I think that
That we essentially
We're always sparring against each other
So maybe that on the show
I was trying to drag some kind of response out of her
That's a possibility
And also I have to say that you know
Having been on vacation with my sister for a week
Patricia was speaking full on Dutch
With with Willow
I think that the language in the house was pretty much Dutch
Some English
And it does take a while to kind of get back into it
So I was maybe trying to prod her along
And poke her a little bit
And you know, and just elicit some form of response
Which I think I was successful at once again
Because I really did like the show
But believe me, man
I got none to say around here
My wife is totally in charge of everything
Ruhiro Sart
Has been tracking Google counts of the word podcast for me
Ever since the word came out
And if you've been around long enough
You remember about two or three years ago
Google would consistently say
Could not find the word podcast
And it would say did you mean broadcast
And it mean while there were millions of hits
Today the word podcast results in 128 million
Google hits
The word pod show
1.3 million Google hits
Adam Curry does a respectable 2.35 million
And what iPhone
1.46 million
Yes, let's talk about that for a second
So the iPhone still
Has not completely come back to life
Other than that everything seems to be working
I can call it it'll indicate it'll ring
I can't answer because the touch screen
No longer functions
And I have a feeling the touch screen is not going to come back
That thing is so sensitive
If there's some moisture stuck somewhere on the side of the screen
In between the casing or some of the connectors
That I'm sure everything got wet
No doubt about that
Maybe that's just turning to crud and sludge
Because you know it was a pre-flushed drop
So
They just may never come back to life
However
I must say
Apple's coming out with a big announcement
Was it September 5th
So that would be Wednesday
And everyone is saying this is going to be the new iPods
And I'm thinking to myself
And this is a part of a bigger
A bigger statement
I want to make about how much I miss web browsing on the iPhone
Would it be possible that Apple would put together an iPod
That has the same touch screen technology
Has
You know all the fantastic new iPod features in interface
That I like quite a bit on on the iPhone
But also just throwing a Wi-Fi transceiver
Of course it'll be an OS 10-based iPod
I would presume it's going to be based on the new operating system
They know how to put it into a small little box
And
And just give us some surfing capabilities
And then maybe
You know maybe open it up a little bit
So we could load some other apps
Wouldn't that be interesting
So just give me the iPod with the web browsing
With Wi-Fi
And enable developers to develop
Just like they've been doing for OS X in general
Oh man, would that make me happy
I believe that I would go for probably
It would be a little bit bigger than the iPhone
I would presume
Just a little bigger area
Screen size
I would totally go for that
I would use two devices
I don't have to have the phone in the iPhone
In fact if anything that's the part that
I kind of like the least
Although a phone is a phone
It's not that big a deal
But going back to the Nokia E61I
Has been
Well this is where you see
It really is in the small little detail
So first of all let me just say
I'm a full believer in
In a mobile web browser
That shows you the context of the entire page
You've gone to
But easily lets you navigate and zoom in
On pieces that are relevant
Because going back to the old way
And looking at the
You know at the especially
Formatted for your device screens
Oh man it just does not give you the context
Even email
Even though I know it's
You know emails the same
It's the same basic thing
But not being able to see
You know a big portion of the inbox
At the same you know at one glance
And I keep seeing my left hand
Or my right hand
Reach out to the screen
I want to do the pinch move
To zoom in on something
Or just double tap something
And it's just a no go
I must say there is some solace
You see who sent me this
It was
Oh crap
We finally find it
Andrew Harron
Andrew
Awesome dude
He sent me a link to
The new mini opera
Beta
Version of the opera browser
And I've actually
I've installed the mini opera
Browser on the on the Nokia before
The new beta version has
Well has
You know one of those kind of like features
It's a bit like the iPhone
Where if you go to a page
It shows you the entire page
And you have a little box that's connected to your
To your cursor to your mouse
Which you control with the
You know the foresighted button in the middle
So you can serve to a spot
Click on it
And it will just like the iPhone
iPhone zoom into that spot
And if you click back it then
Zoom's out
And it's not exactly the same
But it does give you that context
And I have to say
I'm liking that a lot
Of course the the opera mini browser
Give you no way to import your existing bookmarks
Which sucks
I don't understand why they wouldn't just put that in there
Make it so much easier
So I'm going to try this for a while
Because I've been feeling that the iPhone
It's not going to come back to life
And I'm probably going to wait until after
September 5th to see what this big announcement
Is before I invest in an iPhone
In a secondary unit
Looks like someone's
Like a couple of people
I've got some software to unlock it
So you can put it on to a different network
That's kind of cool
We knew that was coming
It'll be very interesting to see what happens
September 5th
If there's going to be something beyond
Just another iPod
If there's going to be something special to it
Because really
That web browsing
I miss it
It's all it's the little things that make life so enjoyable
With Apple products in general
I have to say it's just the finesse
It's just the rounded edges
It is the walnut dashboard
Or fascia
As we would say in the automobile business
It is the leather custom fittings
It's all about that
It's about how the Wi-Fi seamlessly
Switches back and forth between the 3G network
Or the edge network
Who gives a shit?
The mobile network
That ease the way it just happens
And Nokia
Here's the one thing I hate
This is the nuance
Whenever
Let's say I'm in the bathroom
Of course the most dangerous place for any mobile phone
And I'm looking at web pages
And I'm just on the edge of my Wi-Fi coverage
When it can't connect
It'll give you a beep
It's not like a nice little tone
Just a beep
Just a horrible, horrible sound
If it disconnects you go
It just rotates
It's those little things
And don't pop up this dialogue box
I can't click away for three seconds
All that stuff is just shit
And that of course is it's not Nokia per se
It's the symbion operating system
It's a lot left to be desired
But really it is all about those
Those little teeny-winny things
I'm really really missing the web browsing
And I'm going to play around with this
Opera mini
I have to say
The Opera browser in general seems to be much better
than what comes a bundled standard
So it could probably get me through the rough spots
Because I am having a hard time
I really do miss my iPhone
Even for all its shortcomings
Oh man
What is up with that?
Really
I'm trying to process it
I'm trying to figure out why
I don't know
It is something just about the finishing touches
It is all about the little pieces of interface
And I am apparently willing to take on less functionality
Just to be able to get the nice little finishing touches
Curious stuff
I had a big program
I hear from San Francisco
Happy birthday to Christina
It is also my birthday
And I woke up this month
Give a call
At New London Time
I live in for lunch
Anyway, have a good day
Cheers
Well happy birthday
For a living program
To your mom
Yeah, Christina had a nice birthday
You know what kind of low key
Most people weren't back from vacation
On the day of her birthday
It was the bank holiday
So that is kind of a bummer
It is like me
My birthday is Monday
Which was at Labor Day in the States
And I have always had the same thing
You know, either we weren't back at school yet
Or we just were back at school
And there are always new kids
And I was definitely a little introvert and shy
And so I really wouldn't say anything about it
You didn't know anyone
You couldn't invite anybody over for a party
So kind of like those Virgo babies
End of August beginning of September
They all know what I'm talking about
And also you are either precisely the youngest
Or you are going to be precisely the oldest
And in any schooling system
And there you have it
I gave away the fact that I'm traveling on Monday
Not Saturday, not Sunday
Which means yes indeed
The Delta Sierra is done
Hopefully she's going to be brought back on Saturday
So I can do a bit of flying arm
Man, I'm looking forward to that
Now let's open up the phone lines
You know we have a US number in a UK number
And Jingles to go with them
Let's see what's in the voice mail box today
That wasn't anything, how about this?
Hi, this is Christine John with the Defense Department
I had sent a couple of emails
To Adam about being a keynote speaker
In our June 4th or 5th
The 2008 conference on the evening and podcasting
I have not heard back yet or nay
Defense Department
Yeah, let's not do the phone number
Hold on a second
One
Is that it?
Defense Department
I didn't receive any emails from the Defense Department
That's the man
Hold on
Defense
I'm doing a Gmail search as we speak
Defense Department, let me see
No
No, no, no, no
I wonder what he sent the email to
Probably adamaccurry.com
Fool
Doesn't the CIA have better information on me than that?
All right, I will definitely call that guy back
See what's going on
That could be pretty interesting
I'm more about
Nokia
If you have an N95 or an N800
There's something that we've been working on for a while
I don't even know what's supposed to talk about this yet
But you should take a look
Especially those of you that have an N95
It seems to be a lot of you
I'm going to Nokia
Nokia.podshow.com
Take a look at some of the feeds there
I think you want to actually access the
RSS feed links that are attached to the channels that we made there
But this content
Some of our top shows
It automatically gets transcoded into a suitable format
And I think it works in the video center
For the N95 has some kind of, I don't have one
So it has some kind of video center
Excuse me
And the N800 I know has one
Whether it's out or not, I'm not sure
So we're testing stuff
If anyone asks you about that, let's just pretend you didn't hear it from me
Okay
Back to that
Last Elvis Diaries
So I played you just a little bit of that the other day
I don't want to play any more of it
But the Diaries start off when Elvis is very young
And what's been very difficult
Has been to find because we basically cast
The voice of the older Elvis
In case you were confused, it was actually him
We're looking for a younger Elvis sound alike
And it's been really hard
And before we go out and basically spam Craig's list
If you think you can do a younger Elvis
I'm talking like the 20 year old Elvis
If you think you can do his voice, let us know
Because we got a fun project for you to work on
Oh and you'll get paid
In peanuts
For sure
Hi Adam, this is Gilbert
Down in Georgia
I'm looking to your dilemma with the iPhone
I too have dropped mine many times
Unfortunately for me not into the toilet
But I have dropped it since the slide very easily
Anyway
I don't know about your
If you've purchased it by credit card
I know my credit card is such that if I break something
Or lose something or step on it
Or someone steals it with him
The first
I don't know
Power many months
Certainly
For six months
They will replace it
I have had them replace my card
For that very reason
So you might check into that
And see if that might solve your problem
But you know
I think the slow motion moment
As it was
Yeah, I'll believe me
Was it a slow motion moment
Big time
Before we get the water
Hey you know what
I've never gotten any of those
I never get the protection stuff on credit cards
Yeah yeah
Thank you buddy
Never
I'm a firm believer
You probably wind up paying for the device twice
Before something actually happens to it
Christina got a new phone yesterday
Which was a birthday present
And I tried to get it
I tried to push an N95 on
I said look this is what all the cool kids have
This has got all the shit you want
The great camera etc
And of course
The thing she said was
Is it pink
And I don't believe it comes in pink
Nokey and not known for its stylish pink
Although
Wait a minute
Patricia has a nice stylish pink
Phone
The one that's dicey uses on East Enders
So what did she wind up getting?
It was pretty interesting
It's a touch screen phone
Oh it's a it was of course a
Prada touch screen phone
Made by LG
It feels pretty cheap and kind of plasticky to the touch
But and it doesn't have a
You know the touch screen is really just it
Touch screen no dragging or anything like that
Although you can use the scroll bar
Through touch
But she's really happy with it
She's like this is like my my my my my my fake iPhone
It's a and is and she's really happy with it
That's pretty interesting
I think that things are the changes are a foot for how we perceive a mobile device
The whole idea of a touch screen
Where you can actually interact with what's going on
Maybe it's even like the multi touch screen
Where do you call them like the the iPhone
We have the pinched drag you know zoom and stuff
I know what
Here's here's what I'm feeling
I'm feeling
That I'm ready to move back to Apple pretty soon
Now that I can happily run windows
I really only need windows
100% of every single day
To use cast blaster
So that we're that'll work fine with with parallels
And and all the other stuff you know the speed now on the new intel
Duo core thing mobile
He seems to be fine
Um, they're still a bit heavy
I really like the light weightiness of the of the via
But man it just it makes me feel good
I had that's what it is it makes me feel happy and proud to be a computer owner
I can't put it any other way
Maybe it'll happen after the September 5th now
From the pod sake music network now
You know sometimes
I'm so far away from your darling
Eli paperboy read and the true love
That's what I want you to do
While I'm gone
You want to take my love with you
Everywhere you go
I want to take my love baby
In a street
And a cry
When you're alone
All alone
You want to take my love with you
Everywhere you go
When I'm gone
So far away
In your heart
I want to stay
So baby
Keep your mind on me
And we'll have a love
And it's me
For I don't temptation
Can't surround
But you know how I always go around
You're just gonna take my love with you
Everywhere you go
Come on baby
Take my love with you
Everywhere you go
I want to take my love with you
In a street
And a cry
When you're alone
All alone
You've got to take my love with you
Everywhere you go
All alone
You've got to take my love with you
Everywhere you go
I love you, for what if it's me, but you desire
All we can make it gone and throw it back
You know you're just not to take my love with you
Everywhere you go, wow, you're on the train
My love baby, everywhere you go, come on baby
Everywhere you go, you know you need to stop and take my love baby
And now bad for a white boy from Massachusetts, huh?
He like paper boy Reeve from Boston
He's got two songs up on the Podsight Music Network
Pretty cool, give him a listen
It is kind of like back to the old days and so
Yeah, like boy, go
All right, so tomorrow's going to be another nutty day
Because we're just we're kicking ass over here
And it's good because once the asses is kicked everything's in motion
It gives me the time to go piss off for two weeks in the US
Which I'm also really looking forward to there
Once again so many new people at Pod Show
But probably even more exciting
The meeting all the new people and by the way my office is gone
It's been taken over, I think they've got five people in there now from QA
We're still trying to find a suitable new office space for our growth
And the new PodShow.com which has been in development for
Well really from over two and a half years
But I've been playing around with some of the development stuff
I've got access to it from here
You know what, it's really blowing me away
I think that the whole channel editor, the whole cheddar exercise
Really inspired a lot of people it feels like
There's a vision now
And when you look at this thing
You're going to say this is just like
And you won't be able to compare it to anything
You've never seen anything like it before
The best part of the whole interface
Well besides that it's a great discovery mechanism
You can see how you're connected to content
And who else is connected to it
So you really, you can visualize the community around the show
Which is freaking awesome
But also there's this pervasive play thing going on
And if anything, I've always wanted to have something like this
Where you can be playing a show
It can be audio, it can be video
It doesn't take videos in example
And you want to surf around and find other stuff
So you're looking at the show notes
Just doing tons of other things
I've always despised the fact that I would have to open up another tab
Or open a new window to go look at things
And of course invariably if you click on the link or something's playing
It stops playing
And when you go back you have to find where you were
You know all that crap right
I think we've really looked that problem
And you'll see a lot of, oh man you'll see it
You'll see it
I don't know, it's probably going to be
I'm going to be careful
I'd say it's, they've got a good another two months of work
At least but maybe some of this stuff will start slipping out in the meantime
And I'm really excited about it
It is taking, it is really taking podshow.com to a whole new level
And it'll work of course for the entire internet
And that's all kinds of cool shit in there
So I'm looking forward to hooking up with the team
And doing some brainstorming
But it's just looking awesome, I'm very excited about this
Alright everybody
So tomorrow as I said it's going to be pretty busy
All the way through the evening I probably won't get home until 10
Friday should be okay
If not there's always the weekend
And if I get in Monday night
Maybe Monday night I think we're going to work on the night shift
For the shows from San Francisco
So Monday night I'll do one for Tuesday
And then maybe before I leave Sunday I'll do one for Monday
Something like that
And I'm going to have lots to talk about
A guarantee it
DailySourceco.com for all the show notes
Adam at podshow.com
If you want to drop me a line about just anything
Including those naked pictures
I'll talk to you tomorrow or the day after
For the Daily episode
Take care
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear