This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Print Customer 7168120917
I sent you a text to landline message.
Fuck you.
Adam Curry.
Goodby and thank you for using text to landline.
Hey happy.
Watch it to one.
Well, Pearl and Be has this huge to-do list for us as we get Poncho Island ready for the new Love Spirals album release party and Love Spirals concert this week.
Angie B and Love Spirals are going to be on Poncho Island.
Yeah, Tuesday, October 23rd for the CD release party at 7 p.m. and then Saturday October 27th for a live concert with Angie B and Love Spirals at 7 p.m. on Poncho Island.
What can I do to help?
Hmm.
Can you choose the show?
Sure, happy.
Do we forget something?
Oh yeah.
Do you want to curry?
Delta shared Charlie.
Six.
Seven.
With 15 bags, a splinter stuck in our pants.
Sugar.
And 15 bags of toilet paper hanging from our cracks.
We don't need no sticking sugar.
I'd like to think I'd like.
Particularly chicken footier scary.
Let's take a sincere red, and a warm-out tasting it on your hip.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Don i will, don't gonna be glad air, hey, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, probably it's just, yeah, the more in the good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, good.
Yeah, let's take this and soak you in, I want to take it off
Yeah, sweet skin, I owe for my prayer, I want to penetrate it, but don't stop
Don't tell me, I want you, don't stop, now I can't leave it
Don't stop, take it all the way
Baby, baby, baby, come out and show me what you got
Don't stop, run it, run it, I'm trying to create it all the way
Tell me just what turns you on, what did you want?
Baby, baby, come out and show me what you got
Don't stop, run it, run it, I'm trying to create it all the way
Tell me just what turns you on, what did you want?
Baby, baby, baby, come out and show me what you got
Don't stop, run it, I'm trying to create it all the way
Tell me, baby, come out and show me what you got
Baby, baby, baby, come out and show me what you got
Don't stop, run it, run it, I'm trying to create it all the way
Tell me just what turns you on, what did you want?
Take it all the way
All the kids have talkin' about them all, and never after
music network baby baby you might have heard about them on fly post to our brand new
trans intercontinental office music show flypostor.podshow.com if not
bring it home
the show everybody how you doing it's Monday it's going to be another crazy busy week
whether or not too nice today although certainly doable for flying and of course
that's my link to talking about the weekend for the first time and I'm going to say
a couple months I had a full two-day weekend where I didn't necessarily have to do any
podshow related business of course that means I have to catch up on a couple things more
because it's stuff that I could have done over the weekend but really took advantage of just
of the beautiful weather we had here it was utterly stunning clear skies sun almost no wind
which means just perfect perfect conditions temperature was fresh fresh fresh crisp is what I
wanted to say very you know that crispy feeling you get near and on Saturday there was a kind of
an ad hoc organized fly in on the island white wind commander William and the number of his clients
actually all who have aircraft that he maintains decided to go hang out and have a quick lunch and
he came in in the this is the next aircraft I want all man hold on let me just adjust my
mic stand here it's I don't know for some reason maybe it's weather related but we started
slipping a little bit there we go maybe if I change the center of gravity there we go that's better
he came in in a brand new like a hundred hours on this thing King Air 90 GT which is
I was just salivating that what a fantastic aircraft this has got to be my upgrade
it's about uh 10 times the expense of the current one I have but mm well man if I had some time
to fly it I certainly would so that was great to flying the Delta Sierra down it's only a short
flight it's like 20 minutes more or less and I was I was the first one so of course I went in for
the perfect landing thinking those guys would be there at 12 o'clock and I landed like 12 o'clock
three beautiful and there was no one there to see it so the question is did it really happen
um so that was that that was fun you know it was real airplane hangar talk bullshitting about and
then I took off back home had a nice Saturday evening we'll talk about some of Saturday later on
in the show but of course there was the rugby world finals cup that I did watch
and as I said we'll talk about that in a little bit then Sunday I convinced my bride to come with me
also to the island white to the infamous crab in lobster pub which up until I think two o'clock
in the afternoon they serve the most fantastic crab and lobster dishes it's well known
certainly to uh to aviators this is a fantastic destination and so we decided to fly it out
and you know I love having the lady Patricia sitting next to me up front it's uh first of all
so much more attractive than the captain Dan or anyone else who's been up front but it was
it was great just the two of us beautiful flight you know flew in we took a quick it's like a five
minute camera ride from the airfield to uh to the crab and lobster pub we had a great lunch really
leisurely took our time sat outside while eating while looking out over at that point basically the ocean
uh as the vantage point where we were sitting and uh and then so I want to told us that we could
actually walk back to the airfield along the cliff right above the beach and so we did that but
it was really nice about a 35 40 minute walk and it was as I said the conditions were great so
even though it was cold and you know kind of uh yeah crisp fresh fresh fresh fresh we you know
we kind of warmed up and it was a it was fantastic actually bummed out we didn't bring along the dog
as small as he is I'm sure he would have enjoyed that and then departed did a nice circuit all
around the aisle of white at low level so about about a thousand feet so we could really you know
get a good look at it and then and then flew home back to pharaohs now this was about three
thirty quarter to four and even though the wind was pretty much variable and very very light
uh runway two four was in use now they do the switch this around four clock in the afternoon
and I'll tell you what that is if there's no significant uh wind um because you're coming in
basically in a south westernly uh in fact uh in a in a in a westernly uh direction a runway two four
zero so you're flying to that direction which is uh west which of course is directly into the sun
and so often uh obviously at the end of the day if there's no significant wind they'll put
on zero six the other direction so you don't have this sun glaring in your eyes so you know to make
this landing uh it's pretty gnarly uh because also there's all kinds of bugs and shit on your
wind shield and void if they look dirty then when the sun is shining directly on it so it took
some real uh concentration to land smoothly and it was funny because you know so put it down nice
and smooth you know little plows there from the lady pea and then like wow it was I so concentrated
that my mouth like started to smell like shit and yeah I did one of those are breathing to your hand
things and we're still on the runway right rolling out as we're taxing to vacate the runway
I'm like what is that and the smell was so bad it was a really putrid acid acidic like
puke smell and uh and so I got on the radio and I said hey man I don't I don't know what's going on
but it really really smells bad down here on the runway and the tower came back and said well
we've had no other reports so obviously it's you of course it was some kind of manure that
they were putting in the field next door but it was so funny that actually like god man I need
to tick that real quick I smell really bad from this landing anyway so uh onto the current order
of the day brand new week as I said gonna be very very very very busy particularly with Wednesday
show uh Republican candidate Ron Paul uh Dr. Ron Paul will be on this program will be interviewing
Wednesday afternoon UK time so uh sometime in your late morning early afternoon in the US you'll be able
to listen to it very excited about it and of course would love to have all kinds of questions that
that you have come up with send them in and of course you know the protocol by now you you say something
serious and then you get to F. Me off you know F. You said that it's a lot of Steven San Francisco this
is never gonna make it on the show but listen yeah so you say kind of cycle calls up and tells
you about fun go on and fuck you and that's not true the spell is definitely there and actually
me I'm an Italian American it means go do ass really basically do ask whatever you want to do
some long as life but he's saying it like a Northerner and the Northerners as we all know the blonde
hair and the blue eyes are really Southern Germans let's say they're Swiss guys you move south and
whatever they speak sort of Italian but true Italian we're talking about Roman self you don't you know
like an American you'd say song well thank you not fast on cool though it's fun cool not pure ass
so fuck you out of glory it's ongoing I learned something new every day don't we
hey just miss checkin back in he's been real busy setting up the uh the crazy pianos dueling piano bar
in Nashville I think it's going really well from what I understand I couldn't be happier and
I'm really bummed that I missed that to recent to pocho sales trip to Nashville because I really
would have liked to check it out but I'm sure that'll happen the future Jeff is back and he's helping
out as usual
both numbers on the website at data source code dark I am curry glenia from Cape Town South Africa and I
must say I'm so proud to be a South African you just have no idea what that must be feeling like
right now and I'm sure this clip will make England weep and every South African around the world
feel absolutely proud with joy yeah so and so there's like one minute clip that I'm just going to
talk over here for a second of the the final I guess final 10 to yeah five to 10 minutes of the world
cup rugby which was held in France it was the United Kingdom England I should say versus South Africa
and I watched the whole game we got admit a couple of reasons for that one is of course
a jake or Christina's a bow to sure is a rugby player and you know I've been watching a couple
games or a little bit and I've been asking some questions and you know so now I know what a try is
in the line out and of course I do have some knowledge of the game because it's in a way it is similar
to the American football that that I've grown up with but it's I think it's a pretty I like the game
actually now that I'm understand it's actually pretty dynamic and it doesn't stop every single time you
know it's like whereas in an American football you'd have a down and you have four of those and
then you stop and everyone lines up again of course the ultimate time to go to commercial these
guys basically keep the ball in play and I do have to admit I find that pretty compelling it was
fun to watch I understand how the well that's got to mean that's on hold on how uh oh what is this
is one the rugby world captain yeah hold on how would you gluten this second you know so I
understand how it try works and then the conversion and how even in those last five minutes England
totally could have pulled a rabbit out of a hat and and won the game which of course makes it you know
that much more exciting but to England lost unfortunately to South Africa of course congratulate the
South Africans let me see this is seven in the final last night well I want to give you one little
piece of information about this game as I'm sure that you're being an England who are definitely
have known about this oh yeah definitely would have seen and heard everything South Africa the
world champions baby yeah go Bokka woo it was just incredible seeing our president Tom Baky with
these rugby jersey on cheering with the boys celebrating with all right so there was one
little bit of controversy in this game um England scored a try which is a touchdown or a goal
or whatever you want to call it now they do have a video a playback on a lot of these uh in
a lot of particularly in rugby in the professional games so they can see if someone might have been
out of bounds and the England player indeed did go out of lines or uh I would they call it
uh we I call it out of bounds maybe they call it uh on the line off the line whatever it is
out of bounds out of play essentially uh so the the touchdown or the goal or the try didn't count
now in this type of a game right uh particularly with England supporters
if this had been football or soccer it would have we would have had fucking dead people in the stands
and it was quite amazing to me that uh well incredibly disappointing and while all of England was
really pulling for their team and and the supporters and fans were very very enthusiastic there was
no rioting you know there was no fans killing each other in the stands it was very sportsmen like
and and I did it in fact there's more bloodshed at a rugby match on the field and that's incredible
I saw guys like get their head ripped open and then you know there's like a short uh technical
time out while the guy literally gets a bandage wrapped around his head it just continues to play
I must say I'm I'm kind of into this game so I'm looking forward to uh to the next season and
and rooting for the England team a good job they really tried but uh even I as a novice I felt I could
see that South Africa was was definitely stronger so congratulations to you guys uh well deserved
and looking forward to beating your uh as next time I hope hey Adam it's done long time
listener from the west coast of Canada uh just wanted to comment on the DSC672 and the nine
long comments um the beard of your show whether it's daily weekly monthly or once in any on
doesn't really matter but uh what you do is even though you do have your own opinion about a lot of
things you throw the stuff out there for us to talk about trust the comments about and you do get a
lot of really good comments and a lot of good feedback back uh the nylon into fucking waste of space
if you're deteriorated to renting and raving and as much as I'd like to say fuck you Adam curry
I'm gonna have to give that the nylon's very fuck you nylon just coming out okay by special
permission not a problem yeah I do am enjoying this asynchronous uh you know I call the conversation
you guys call the conversation it's an asynchronous conversation because of course I'm talking
then you're talking and you come in a couple days later and it's uh honestly it's really
difficult to manage this show where I'm moving on the next topics and people who are catching
up are just jumping in with really good stuff but of course it's all appreciated uh hey I'll
play one of those obnoxious voice mill jingles in a moment so you can call in anytime
comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip from Poland by way of Germany here's
our EU correspondent the comic strip blogger hello Adam here's your European Union correspondent
so the new EU treaty has been just agreed and it brings EU president and the removes
vetoed right in some viter areas this treaty is necessary because EU has been enlarged and it has
the number of parliament members because it's smaller and so on and so on unfortunately due to
the new treaty UK wants to quit EU and UK wants just to have only a free trade agreement with EU so
I have to say we all are fucked up and please ask your own poll what is his view on USA EU relationships
and fuck you very much you're going a little bit out of bounds there CSB don't need any uh it's
just FU that's all we need okay yeah of course I will ask Ron Paul that although I'm pretty sure
as answer will be hey we should be trading with the Europeans but we shouldn't be allied with them
as his uh his belief as a constitutionalist which hopefully you've done your homework and you've
been taking a look at the constitution classes I'll put them in the show notes once again today so
you can take a look at that so you can understand where America's coming from a lot of people
assume incorrectly that it's a democracy it is a republic so that's something to bear in mind
learn a little bit today if you have some time at work fuck the boss take some time and read
about the constitution yeah we're going to talk about Ron Paul as well in a second and uh I found
this on the pod save music network which I just wanted to share with you it's uh and farms worth
there's a couple songs up there it's just awesome for like a Sunday afternoon or maybe a lazy
Monday you're laying in bed breakfast in bed a couple of crumbs T-Stayin here there you and your
loved one basking in the glow of that early morning subland
come
You know, maybe it's not just a nice sunlit Monday morning, maybe it's a bit of a Christmas vibe that I'm feeling.
There's something going on, I can kind of smell the cherries, cinnamon scents in the high
students I walk through the high street of Gilford, high appropriately of course.
I see things going on in the UK over the weekend, television was dominated again by a news
of the BBC cutbacks, which was interesting to see how the BBC is reporting on its own
but also this, I saw this on a couple of weblogs around TVLinks.co.uk.
You might have seen this somewhere, set up by some 26-year-old guy from
Cheltenham in the UK, he was arrested. Now the TVLinks.co.uk is a site that I've seen before, I've
used before, there are a couple of sites out there like it. In essence, there are search engine
specifically for television programs. So it's just links, links that point to primarily Google
videos and YouTube videos and it just kind of organizes episodes. So people who've put up episodes
of let me give you an example, Dr. Who is a big one. You know, they've been put up on YouTube
and on Google video and other video sites and TVLinks just basically points to all of
those different places. They are not not storing anything on their server. In essence,
they're doing exactly what Google does. In fact, if you were to look for Dr. Who video on Google
and do a Google search, you'll find it. Actually, now I think about they're not doing exactly
the same. Are they? They're categorizing and listing as opposed to searching. I wonder if that
would have made a difference if you could just say, you know, give me everything for Dr. Who and
it then would have formatted a nice output. It may have made a difference, but legally,
probably not. I find this very, very interesting. The spokesperson for the Federation against
copyright theft known as FACT said, sites such as TVLinks contribute to and profit from copyright
infringement by identifying, posting, organizing and indexing links to infringing content found
on the internet that users can then view on demand by visiting the easy legal sites. Wow, I hope
they, I really hope they don't apply this to my favorite MP3 site, which is seekpod.com.
Sierra Echo, Echo, Quebec, Papa Oscar Delta, because man, you can get anything on that. But that's
more a search engine where you can create a playlist later versus playlisting itself. But then again,
this is, I don't know, I need a lawyer to check it on this. If you profit, because they're
saying that the TVLinks.co.uk profits from copyright infringement by pointing it out.
That's his really tough man. It's really difficult, shit.
But sadden on the less. It's, yeah, that's totally beat. Well, I hope that someone can,
can help these guys out because, you know, or let's just figure it out. So we understand what we can and we
can't do. Today is also the last day for comments on TSA's secure flight program, the transportation
security agency. Let me see, I'll read this kind of verbatim, David Wank. Adam, apologies if you've
covered this on DSC, sorry, I'm about six months behind. Dude, forget about it. Just skip up to today.
Going to be really disappointed about a lot of things, particularly this Wednesday. If you're just now
catching up, briefly, the TSA, we've talked about this is proposing a secure flight program, which
threatens to severely curtail individual's freedom to travel by air to the US. Under this program,
all travelers would automatically be obliged to obtain individualized prior permission for all
journeys by air to from overflying or even within the USA. And from what I understand, that will be a
72 hour period minimum. Now, you can put comment on against, and I'm sure you can do it in
number of ways, but you can also do it online, which is nice. And of course, link in the show notes
as expected, a daily source code.com. You need to put your comments in before five o'clock DC
time, Washington DC time, today. And there's only like a handful of comments up there right now.
Not all of them are really good, but a lot of them focus on individual rights, the individual
right to travel. And just in general, this would be so bad for business, so bad for so many people,
and really restrictive, and it does not fucking compute at all. So please get that in, if you
want to comment on that, I'm going to put my own comment up there later on today, because I do
believe it's bad, it's, you know what, how many times can I say this? If it was only the airlines
that were a threat, okay, I'll be willing to consider if we were under constant threat,
but how come we don't have this very same type of security for other places where terrorism has
struck. Namely, trains, buses, and tubes. Now the only reason I can find is because it's
horseshit and it's meant to terrorize you and restrict you and restrict your freedom.
All right, let's hit the voice mail phone lines for a second, couple more before we get out of here
for today. Hey Adam, oh man, this is killing me. I'm listening to your podcast right now. I'm a new
listener. I started listening because somebody from Milan Paul forums told me to go listen and
yada yada yada, and I love your show. So now on the stand, see it works both ways. Anyway, listen,
it kills me when I hear somebody talking. I know it's not your fault man, but man, it kills me when I
hear someone say, Ron Paul's campaign wants you to go to November fifth calm and vote on November fifth,
blah, blah, blah. Ron Paul's campaign is nothing to do with that. There's a difference between
grassroots campaigning and what the Ron Paul campaign is doing. Okay, so I got a couple of comments
about this. In fact, someone sent me an email and said, you know, the Ron Paul campaign is
against this November fifth drive. And the whole idea is kind of a bum rush the charts where
you donate money on November fifth to really make the needle move. It was interesting because what
and this is a question I'll probably then I guess address with with Dr. Ron is let me see if I can find
the exact email that might be a little bit better. Hold on, I know the keyword, so I can
easily find it in Gmail. Hold on a second. Bear with me. Come on, Gmail. Do it, baby. Yeah,
this is from Chris, Miss, Miss, Miss, Miss, Miss, Miss, I think. Just sort of calling
your show about the November fifth fundraiser for Ron Paul. The caller left the impression this
is a product of the official campaign, but they are really not involved at all. Some of the more
conservative people in the grassroots campaign are actually battling against the idea because they
are afraid of the media picking it up and spinning it as Ron Paul supports supporters celebrating
terrorism. Huh? How can that be equated to Ron Paul supporting terrorism? I just don't understand
it. And quite honestly, I'm really not digging this, you know, grassroots versus official vibe.
I think the campaign is everyone, not just the, quote, official campaign. This is what you
guys are flying on. So if that's the organic root that that and I will call it the campaign,
grassroots official or otherwise, if that's the root that the campaign is taking, you need to let that,
this is this is how you've cracked the code of the internet, okay? This is how Dr. Ron Paul
is going to is making a lot of waves and we'll make many more because the internet is rolling out
and it's on the loose and this kind of stuff happens. Now, if someone can really explain to me why
that this could be equated to the candidate sponsoring or supporting terrorism, please let me know
because that would be a serious consideration. But I can only see this being a great thing for the
media to pick up on, you know, it shows true power. Look what we did with, um, bum rush the charge for
Christ's sex. Sorry, there was no reason for me to take Jesus Christ's name,
invade in that particular statement. For fuck's sake, okay? Now there's one other thing that I have
serious serious concerns about. Before real is about the way that the money is going to be spent
that is being raised. And of course, I would presume after a key, you know, staff is paid and
expenses are paid, which I know this campaign is keeping very, very low and there's lots of volunteers.
And of course, you need full-time staffers and people have to be able to eat even though they just
believe in a cause. Please, look at podcasting and independent media. I, but I'm not digging the,
uh, the way the money is being spent. Now that it's being spent on advertising, but the kind of
advertising, someone sent me an official radio ad for Dr. Ron Paul. Have a listen to this. What are the
so-called Republican front runners for President support? Amnesty for illegal aliens, like liberals?
How to control spending? Like the Democrats? Nation building overseas? Wasn't that bill Clinton's policy?
Flip flopping on the issues? What's Republican about any of that? The real Republican is Ron Paul.
The Republicans are losing because they did not keep their promise to end big government at home
and nation building overseas. My record is different. Yes, Ron Paul's record is different.
Ron Paul is never voted for a tax increase or an unbalanced budget. Ron Paul voted against
Amnesty for illegal aliens. Ron Paul voted against nation building overseas. Ron Paul
photos the Constitution, not the lawyers, not the lobbyists, not the latest poll.
Learn more about Ron Paul. The real Republican running for President, go to RonPaul2008.com.
That's Ron Paul2008.com. This is Ron Paul, candidate for President, and I approve this message
before by Ron Paul2008, PCC. All right, I hate this. This is a crap commercial. I hate it.
It is so incredibly opposite what the, what the entire message has been. This is
going into the mainstream with the same stupid fucking message as everybody else.
I didn't do this. I didn't do that. I'm like, I'm not like those guys. Who gives a shit?
What I want to hear is the catch phrases. Where's the Google Ron Paul? Want to know more?
Google Ron Paul. That's what I want to hear. Want to know what Ron Paul's all about. Read this
little book. It's easy to read. It's called the Constitution. That's the kind of message that
the campaign needs to be getting out. I will not donate any money. I will not support it.
This is what it's going to be spent on. Who the Frick is running the advertising over there?
We've got this incredible movement. We've got thousands of YouTube videos, all kinds of
slogans, support statements, initiatives. And this is the advertising that comes out of it. It's
despicable. It's traditional. It is not the message. And it is lame. Capital L, lame.
Now, man, I need any, what agency did you guys hire to do this? Fire them. They suck. They do not
know what you're talking about. And your supporters are actually creating this, you know, it sounds
like I've had this meeting. I've had this meeting. I have it with advertisers every single day.
Every day. I said, this, it's independent media is where you are going to sell your next billion
dollars worth of products. And you need to conform to a new message. You're not limited to 30 seconds.
Okay. So mainstream, you're limited to 30 seconds. But why does that have to be the same
message that everyone else does? I'm coughing up my guts. Oh, no. Very disappointing. Very,
disappointing. So now, you know me, I'm not just a complainer. Well, I love complaining. But I'm not
just a complainer. I'm a doer. And I know that many of you out there in what I have to say is a vastly
growing audience. Ever since this political conversation started, the numbers are out of control. So
welcome everyone who's a new listener. Create, you create a spot. Make it 30 seconds. Make it the
message of Ron Paul. I'll submit these to. I'll play them for them. I'm going to have them on
the phone on Wednesday. I'm going to play. I'm going to say, don't you think this is the better commercial?
You know, and you know what people will do it for a fraction of the cost of whoever is dreaming
this shit up for you. They'll probably do it for free and look at the diversity of content that you
can have to promote what you're doing. But this, oh, no. Just nasty. I'm sure many of you agree,
but don't just agree. Make a better one. Okay, promise? Thank you. Hey Adam. This is Andy from Oakland.
I'm just listening to today's source of listening to your sisters recording and responding to it
and about Ron Paul. She says, well, what about abortions? You have to travel to another state to
get an abortion. You said, yeah, so what? Well, that's great. If you're rich, if you can afford to go to
another state and think about it, so you're essentially saying services and abortions and other things
are fine for rich people, people in your category, maybe in my category. What about people who can't
afford it? And that's really unthinking. Think through some of these issues before you just sign
on blindly. All right. Goodbye. All right. So the reason I play this comment is because I got a lot of
very similar ones. And I just want to make my understanding clear that it's really a multipart issue.
So one is the freedom of choice. Now, of course, you have the right to your body. I believe you have
the right to put anything into that body. You want to take anything out of it. Do whatever you want
with your own body, as long as you don't hurt someone else. Of course, there's a whole major
point of contention there. But it's still, it's my body. If there's another body and that has some
rights, it's inside my body. Okay. And I get to choose over what's inside my body. Let's just say,
I'm stating that clearly. So that doesn't matter if your man, woman, I think child,
animal for that manner. I guess. I don't know if they have right. They don't have human rights.
They've animal rights. Let's not go down that route. Any man or woman has that inalienable
right. Now, the problem is healthcare has become outrageously expensive because of the system that
has been set up. I think I've been through this before. But essentially, when you create a system
where a large number of people are relying on, let's call Medicare or centralized healthcare or
the national health service or whatever all these different schemas are in different countries,
essentially it's centralized medical care. What happens is the price is automatically go up and the
drug companies are in this scam and the hospitals are in this scam. And there's, you know, there's price
setting. And when you have a contract with the government, it's very easy to to, to, to, to over time
come up with enormous fees. Who was telling me the other day that their daughter was born prematurely
and they didn't have health coverage and the, the bill for several months of incubation time and
all kinds of procedures was half a million dollars. There's lots of rich people who can't afford that
either, half a million dollars. But is it really, is it really that expensive? Do doctors necessarily
have to be rich guys driving BMWs and porches and, and having beautiful expensive homes and
going on vacation and golfing and having a wonderful rich life? Is that why they became doctors? No,
why are those fees so high? Well, they've been artificially created that high by the market place.
But the marketplace effectively controlled by the government. And you can kind of see where there's
a lot of room for crap that goes on in that system because it's now you're not negotiating as
negotiating as individuals, but as government government has all kinds of agendas, there's all kinds of
I mean, all of it, what is it? E Street or D Street or Astrid or Crap Street and D.C. We're all the
lobbyists are that's where these prices are jacked up. And that is because of the incorrect construction
of government and entitlements and centralized care. So it's really two issues.
You know, because the I think what Roe versus Wade is also about is about the government paying for
said abortion. Well, of course, this type of care should be available, it should be affordable to
anyone or some form of insurance should be affordable to anyone because the price of the services
and the medications involved have to be affordable and they're not. That's the most jacked up
industry there is. So please, you know, don't think that I'm trying to make this a world for wealthy
people only. I also, honestly, I don't think Dr. Ron Paul has a shot at becoming president.
You know, for a number of reasons, the main one being that he's a Republican and he will not run
independently if he's not nominated for the Republican candidacy. Quite honestly, his ideas are so
back to grassroots and in many traditional eyes today seen as so radical that he'll never make that.
I don't think it will happen. It would be miraculous and I it can and it would be wonderful if
it did. But I think what he's really doing is he's starting up a wave and this wave is growing
in this wave is extremely important and it's a lot of it's about rights, about privileges,
about property, about the Constitution and its subsequent amendments and that's a conversation
that needs to proliferate and what I believe will happen as we get closer and we have a whole
year to go. There's so much that can happen and I'm not going to be talking about this for a whole year.
Although we should be talking about a lot, you know, I believe that maybe one of the other
Republican candidates will see that this thing that is cracking the code of the internet through
the simplicity of freedom, which is very popular and the Constitution of the United States of America,
that other candidates will pick up on this and we just might get someone else who will change
their tune a little bit. Excuse me. So obviously this is not the end of the conversation, but please
don't think that these things are not exclusive. They go hand in hand. You can't just say,
all right, that's it and not fix the medical care situation. I believe that Dr. Ron as a physician
by the way has never ever accepted a Medicare payment because he is opposed to that system and has
done a lot of procedures for free or at a decent cost. I don't have the documentation on it,
but that's what I've been led to believe and again great stuff to talk about with him when he
comes on this show Wednesday the 24th I think. So somewhere around 4 or 5 o'clock in the afternoon
UK time this will be posted. So that'll be was it around noon or late morning early afternoon
in the U.S. And of course that'll be on Saturday down under in the Australian looking for a way to
help make a difference in the life of a military service member this holiday season. Email our
military provides a safe way for people to support and encourage our service members with a personal touch.
Email email our military volunteers come from all walks of life and understand that regardless of
our political views, our military service members deserve our respect, support and encouragement.
Service members register with email our military and are matched with civilians who sign up and send
and show their support. Won't you help keep the support motivation and encouragement going to our
troops by joining the effort? Visit email ourmilitary.com this holiday season. Email our military
supporting our military one email at a time. Military service members email our military once
you to receive support of course. So stop by email ourmilitary.com today. You know another one of
those crappy mainstream commercials but the message is important this time that's why I put her here
all right so we wind it up pretty big some big power cords coming to you from the big apple
new wave of yorka. Here's girls don't cry and american boy on your chat chat charlie
jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu j
jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu
jiu jiu jiu jiu
jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu kiu jiu menos
jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiucing jiu jiu teammate
jiu jiu jiu jiu sev team jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu jiu
When I see five really cute girls and they're playing instruments, they get my attention.
From the podcast, music, that word girls don't cry American boy.
They are from New York and you'll find a link to them in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Hopefully, another show tomorrow and of course, Wednesday, the big day, I believe I'm going to stay overnight in the city, Wednesday and Thursday.
So, I expect, of course, a show on Friday, then that's kind of the layout for the week.
So, please enjoy your freedom.
And wherever you are, I hope you have it.
If you don't, you need to call me immediately.
We'll come bust you out.
And whatever you do today, this week in particular, live your life with passion.
Another podcast, stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
punch show and line weight.