Potion needs you to help us suck the less.
Yeah, I'm getting sick of it too.
I have this sprint with Potion Radio.
The bottom line is this.
As soon as this shows over, go over to suckless.potion.com.
Get in, get out, and for God's sake, get out with your life.
Because if you don't...
Help us suck less help us suck less potion.
Eat you to help us suck less.
It's his Tony and Tony.
And you're listening to the DSE 612.
Yeah, no animals were actually hurt in the making of the DSE 612.
But there are two sheep and a bunny that were a little mentally scotch, I would say.
And he dumped us.
I want my cat back.
Oh, yeah, dumped us.
Tony, let's just get back.
I knew you could be.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Don't want to wake you, you know me better.
Let's once again talk about the time together.
Not the dream, not the time you said.
Every little baby, no one's in one's life.
every little baby, no one's in one's life.
He's so cute, he's so cute, he's so cute, he's so cute
He's so cute, he's so cute, he's so cute
He's so cute, he's so cute
He's so lovely, he's so cute
The first video we focused on
and the first video we worked on
The third video we filmed
Suburb of Suri known as Gilford,
we're on the west side of Utah.
I'm bringing you everything completely,
full barred and with lots of music.
It's like I picked a wrong week, please smoke it.
It's got a syrups of shit in it.
Gilford's got a moon on it.
The race is dead and it made me feel better.
Someone's bound to die.
Let's go.
We're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah.
We're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of
Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the east side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the east side of Utah and we're on the east side of Utah and we're on the east side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the south side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the east side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on the west side of Utah and we're on
To the supermarket, it's great people in the face, I'll live here, let's do it
When it's around the corner, but I don't think I'm making it there
Because it's almost right at it, I don't care
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
There from Los Angeles, California, and of course proud members of the Podsake Music Network
The Hot Rods almost Friday night, and indeed it is, and oh, I can't tell you how horrible
I feel about missing yesterday's show, it just didn't happen
After I went to the crash pad early, well relatively early
I did of course prepare a lot of stuff for the show, and you know, had a photo shoot for this Vaughn magazine
Which is Doug Monies, I think it's his editor over there, so I'll do anything for Doug Monies
Never even read the magazine, but for Doug I'll do anything
Yeah, and then the phone calls just came in, it started at, oh man, it started like at five o'clock and did not cease until almost midnight
So I'm sorry
Very adamant, you've passed some sending it, again, I didn't realize after
Calling you earlier today that if timing works out
My info for episode 613, which I hope very much that you got
Will end up being for a football Friday episode
I see this is why I just feel so bad is because you've got to put the sentence episode 613 opener
In a long time ago, and he was kind of expecting it to fit with the football Friday
And there I go, I'm messed them all up
I'll use it on Monday though, I promise
I'm making it all of our property to say, it's got lots of room
I've never bought a bunch of loneses
I hope you got that
I'm looking for that
I like that, man, it's your bunch of loneses, everybody, it's a football Friday
And so, keep up the great work, and we look forward to seeing you again, stay excited
Stay clean, fashion healthy, oh and make up in
Make up in?
And before, of course, fall over
Yeah, make up out!
I'll show you a bunch of loneses, everybody
I'm going to go listen, do I have a 613
Some here somewhere here, let me see
I may have an already in the archives
Anyway, if you think that was bad
Oh man, I messed up so bad a couple of days ago
Remember, I was talking about Ziggy Marley appearing on Dawn and Drew
And day viewing his brand new single
Into the groove
I played promos and
Yeah, look, I'm just a guy here producing this thing by myself
So, I play that, you know, well, it was a weird
Dawn and Drew were on bone
So, I'm talking about Dawn and Drew, how they're going to do this
Or how that I thought they probably even did this whole big thing with Ziggy Marley
Because I look for Ziggy Marley on the Poncek music network
And the track was there
It was just available to be found by search and guess what
It was, yeah, it was supposed to be available to be found by search
It was already put into our system so we could roll out
You know, we've got a whole content management system
That allows
Once an assets are in, then you can put it on the homepage
You can rotate things
We really want to promote this interview
And the fact that the Marley family
And please note that Rita owns everything Bob's done
She has the power to put this stuff on the Poncek music network
So, for the Marley family and Ziggy in particular to put out
Their music on the Poncek music network and to entrust
Their art
And their livelihood
To us podcasts
Of course, phenomenal
And highly appreciated
And of course, the only thing we had to promise
Was that the song would not be played before June 1st
There I go, I just pick it up
Totally our bad, totally messed it up
May it call, but putting the hand to my own chest there
I really messed that up
However, the song is now, of course, officially available on the Poncek music network
It is exclusive to the PMN
You can hear it, you can play it in your show
And of course, if you go to dawn on do.com
That's where you will hear the interview
And it was painful for me to listen to this interview
Because my girlfriend Don was really coming on to Ziggy, man
That was just Tom
Friday, full bar Friday, maximum music, of course
We go over to the garden state where we find
The lawyer with the cars
When he's not chasing ambulances
He's the official musical
To make a motion
To practice for the loud
To turn his roll around
And it's a full bar Friday
With tells me time that you're on it
It's a full bar Friday
Yo, what's up Adam Man, how's it going?
It's Jersey Todd, your official musical
The shot shot
Dude, dude, I love it
Love it, love it when a band puts only one song up on the pot safe music network
Because you know it says to me one thing
That they're testing it out, that they're trying it out
See how it's going to work out for them
But you know, you know that they're going to put their best song up their first
And that's exactly what I think is happening with the band
Luma out of Oklahoma
I love this song that I'm going to play for you
It's really really just stuck in my head
The band is just a hard rock and bunch of guys
And 80s kind of sound to them, not really
It's kind of an updated sound
But I just dig it, there's something really really great about it
Check this out, the band is called Luma
The song is called Wake Up
And I know you're going to dig it on a full bar Friday
Check this out
Your time has come
And I know you're going to dig it on a full bar
You're going to dig it on a full bar
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, thanks for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I
and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you
In the next videos and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you for the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you on the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and
like an event.
Let's go and down in the archives.
Still to come on today's maximum music Fubar Friday, Fubar of course stands for fucked
up beyond all repair.
We've got to exercise with the adorable Amy Mack trying to firm up my ass and back
by popular demand and under new legislation, young pull that's hit test.
Don't be skipping forward, just stay right where you are because there's plenty
of good stuff to come.
Yeah.
Hi, is that the escort service?
Cool.
Okay.
My name is Adam Currie.
I was calling in to see what type of girl you have in there.
Right.
Now, there's three in there.
She changed it for 30.
Okay.
Cool.
Because last time I went there, I really had a great time, but I got to tell you, it kind
of sucked a little too much for my taste.
Okay.
It's too much sucking.
So, I'm looking for something that suck less.
What do I mean?
Hey, everyone.
This is Yazif from the Scam Tunes podcast and not everybody likes it when it sucks too much.
So help us suck less.
Just visit the suckless zone.
That's suckless.pacho.com and help us suck less.
I love it, man.
It's going in rotation.
If you're a listener, if you're a producer of podcast or send a man, we'll put him in
rotation.
We've already, I think today, it should start.
We've swapped, we have like five new suckless promos coming on and let me just reiterate
that the suckless zone is the opportunity for you to join a panel and in research
when you're researching products or services, or in this case podcasting, in general and
in a pod show, in particular, and even more focus on certain shows and advertisers.
If you are on a panel, then you will be subject, and I'm saying it, you will be subject
to surveys, like I think one a month or something, and there will be new forms of advertising
that it's almost like have you ever been asked to preview a movie or to, yeah, the preview
movie is a good analogy.
So you'll be hearing, there'll be audio that you'll have to respond to, there will be video
that you'll be responding to, and all the while you're actually going to make advertising
suckless, you're going to make podcasting suckless because this information will be aggregated,
will be published, it will be shared, a lot of the insight, excuse me, his title ppm is still
sponsoring NGB because if not, they just got a freebie from me.
So you know, become a part of the super panel.
There's a small incentive where you can, you get points for each survey, you complete,
and you can, you can get stuff, some valuable stuff, I might add.
But really helping us suckless, helping the show, you listen to suckless, and one of the
things we learn right off the bat is, well, the one minute promo, a lot of people thought
that sucked, we're making that suckless, and there's other things as well.
Hi, I'm Paul Parkinson, just ringing, just listening to DSC this morning, talking about
the podcast, suckless, and I, too, have tried to get into the podcast, suckless, but I
would think I was a bit more successful, I actually got to the part of the system where
I was allowed to tell you where I am, unfortunately, the two choices are United States
America or other, so being in the UK, I pressed other, and it told me to go away and come
back another time.
When are we going to be able to play, too?
Cheers.
Yeah.
Actually, you know, when we were testing this whole thing, I went through the survey as
well, and I'm always the guy that comes up with the stuff that doesn't work from other
countries.
And so I was like, I had the same reaction, like, other, the hell was that?
So you know that the surveys are done with an official third party, so it doesn't actually
run on our systems.
And I've found that a lot of these official companies who do this stuff and are trusted
third party, they're very web 1.0, I would have to say, because for them, this is also
relatively new, they've been doing surveys for a long time.
We're working with E-pole on this, and, and of course, we're making the whole suckless
zone, suckless at the same time, so we do say that this is for US only, the reason being
that this first survey is only for US respondents, and there was no way for our partner
in this E-pole, which was disappointing, I agree, to segregate that out with other countries.
And also the advertisements that we'll be running in subsequent surveys are for the US
market only.
Other countries going to get the play, yes, of course.
So I totally agree that that's a disappointment, but you will get to play, but it's going
to be at least six to eight weeks, I think, before everyone's ready to handle other
countries.
You know what, we haven't done this in a long time, hold on a second, where is it?
What's playing on?
Adults first, and I find it perfect for a footballer Friday, this is where I grab my first
generation iPod.
It's one of those thick ones, it doesn't hold quite as many songs and looks nothing
like an iPhone.
However, it does have my entire collection from the illegal Napster days, it's from the
first days when we were beginning with podcasting, and you never know what's going to
come rolling out of this thing, so today I'm not going to put it on the Friday playlist,
I'm just going to let it go completely around, haven't seen what we show up with, coming
off of Adam's first gen iPod.
What's this?
I love the high quality sound of it, I don't know what this is, this is on my iPod.
Oh, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom.
Oh, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension
ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat
Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, of course, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, the fifth dimension ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, the fifth dimension
ever about it, Shabbat Shalom, and we still die of oil. The left side and the left side are the power manufactured in circumventines and are the rest of the other parts.
Where are you?
I'm telling you, that a sunshine
Bear the sunshine in the sunshine
I'm telling you, that a sunshine in the sunshine
Bear the sunshine in the sunshine in the sunshine
Bear the sunshine in the sunshine
I'm talking about the moon.
Just wanna be a home.
To shine on you, you got me in it.
I'm so proud you got me in it.
All right, I'll be in not have a smile on your face.
I have to be hearing that song.
And Jesus Christ superstar at the soundtrack.
By the way, you just don't hear the song.
I'm the radio anymore.
Ever.
And a shout out to Kiri Akras, Lily Kakas from Athens.
Well, I know who likes this song.
All right, so I've started a new organization.
I don't have a website up yet or anything.
The organization is called the organization.
The organization for preservation of the soundtrack of our life.
And I feel this is a very important.
This organization is going to do very important work.
Right now it only has one task or one goal in mind,
which is the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
Which, of course, is slowly withering away due to the fact
that these songs, the soundtrack to our lives is just not played on the short playlist radio
that we have.
Of course, these songs are also rarely, if ever played an alternative media,
such as podcasts, and they've become unaffordable to play on streaming web radio.
However, under the Fair Use Act, the organization for preservation to the soundtrack of our life
has concluded that it is possible for us to bring you a weekly hit test.
Use by the one and only young poet to help preserve that soundtrack to our lives.
Now, of course, you won't hear these songs in their entirety.
Your memory will be jogged just a little bit by a snippet.
You'll have an opportunity to race the clock and compete against me to see if you can guess which songs they are.
Then you'll hear the answer to pay off.
You feel good about these songs.
And perhaps, as has been proven over and over again,
you will head off to iTunes or the music store of your choice to go purchase the track.
And perhaps other tracks at the same time.
Now, I believe we're setting up hittest.podshow.com.
Young poet is fully on board with this.
Now, young, of course, puts a lot of energy into these hit tests.
Please do not take likely the amount of work it takes to produce this.
Particularly, you know, making the answers sound kind of good by chopping the songs together.
And it's work.
So, young's got to get paid.
And we're trying something new here.
We start today with our premier sponsor of the hittest.
Hittest number 72 brought to you by state farm insurance.
And let me tell you about state farm.
I've always had state farm insurance.
I don't know why.
I could sing that jingle.
You know, like a good neighbor.
State farm is there.
And all I can say is I've never had a problem.
We've had our scrapes, our bumps, our nicks, our little,
well, I've had some accidents.
Patricia never has.
I've never had a problem with them.
I really like the kind of like the familiar neighborhood agent you can go to
when there's something you need to take care of.
So, without further ado, thanks to state farm and the organization for
preservation to the soundtrack of our lives.
Here is young, put it with the hittest.
Hey, Adam.
We'll let with the 72nd edition of the hittest for the daily source code.
Well, not much has changed.
The intros are very short.
Two of them are around half a second to one.
It's a little bit longer, but under a second.
And the intros are even shorter than usual.
They're around 30 seconds.
So, extensive editing had to be done to accomplish that.
And therefore, singing along may cause some problems.
I'll give it some problems.
So, please don't do that.
Roll it out.
Why is my force so low?
Oh, yeah.
You might ask, what?
And that's due to some hay fever stuff.
It can be helped.
That's what they're all doing.
Next time, it will be better.
All righty.
Three intros.
Let's go.
What?
I got to think about it.
No, it's true, maybe.
Oh, I know that one.
That's a give away.
That is Miami-Saramachine.
Do the Congo.
Yeah, do the Congo.
And the final one is number three.
Huh, huh.
Yon, how can I not know this one?
This is from my pirate radio days.
Brooklyn Bronx and Queen's band, BB and Q, with on the beat.
Well, that's it.
That's all you got.
I think it is.
He's answering number one.
What was one?
From 1977.
It's Leo Sam.
You got to know it.
I was right.
Stand in here.
I belong with you.
Wonderful.
It is that I'm supposed to do.
I live under in my heart.
But I just can't control.
But I just don't know.
Oh, unbelievable.
From one to another.
I'm still going strong this second.
Leo Sayer and Thunder in my heart is answering number one.
And this is number two.
From 1986.
The Miami Sound Machine.
This is Kanga.
From 86.
Gloria Stefan and the Miami Sound Machine in Kanga.
And this is number three.
Charlemagne.
Charlemagne and night to remember.
Shit.
I'm wrong.
I can't believe I had a wrong.
I thought it was BB and Q band.
The song for which I had to do the most extensive editing.
Charlemagne from 1982 and a night to remember.
Well, that's it for I hit this number 72.
I hope you hadn't done all of them.
They were not really too difficult, I think.
Well, until next time, maybe next week.
And well, until then, take care.
I have fun and see you later.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
I will do it all over again.
Next week.
I was convinced it was the BB and Q band.
I think that's the maybe that I was confused with the theme song you use.
Oh, wow.
That felt good.
Did you guys sing along?
You feel good?
Do you feel like you need to...
Oh, I know what we need.
Let me open up the other mic here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, Adam, it's Amy Mack.
Hello.
I love these music Fridays.
That's the perfect upbeat mood for exercise.
Don't you think?
Hi, great.
Let's do some.
All right. Are you ready?
Yeah, well, tell me what to do.
We're going to start standing tall standing tall.
Same forward.
Four low shoulders back, stomach tight and hold your arms out to the side.
Arms out to the side.
Now lift your right leg out to the right and bend your knee to 90 degrees
and lift it as high as you can without leaning or falling over.
Oh.
Hold it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Squeeze.
And now swing it around and cross it in front of you as far as it'll go.
Now back and forth five more times and then switch sides.
Okay.
Really use your abs and your posture to keep balance.
Breathe.
I always forget that part.
Also looking at the same spot in front of you will help keep you upright.
All right. That's like helicopter hovering.
Okay.
Now switch to the left leg.
Lift it up to the left side and then cross it in front of you.
Great.
Five more.
It feels.
It's a nice stretch.
Keep those shoulders back.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
So shut up.
Breathe.
Yes.
Squeeze that butt.
Yeah.
I don't think it's going to be fantastic.
Well, that's it for this week.
This is Amy Mack.
And until next time.
That's what's inside.
Yeah.
I feel kind of good.
You get the exercises as it's on show by the way.
If you just want to.
If you just want to firm up a little bit, you know.
It could happen.
You could need it.
Yeah.
I'm at Stoke Pilgrim in Boston.
So you're visited by two angels.
And they told you that in cannot smoke.
Gange anymore.
Be aware of the eyes of September.
Well, that's a bummer.
And that must give you the blues.
And when I've got the blues.
I want to hear blues music.
So I turn to the always relevant pod save music network.
This cut is from Big George Jackson Blues Band with Boo Boo Data
Singing from Black and Ten Records.
Son, it's tell me what to do.
10 this one.
I told no.
Get high.
It's not a deal at all.
My good job too.
It ain't good at all.
What a good boy.
Yeah.
Great job.
Oh, my good job.
Finding my job.
Nothing.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Holy good boy, that's got that good boy y'all
Yeah.
You don't need to know.
Oh, I thought you'd be alone.
Yeah.
Oh, that's good for you.
Oh.
Don't let go for your own little thing.
You've got a little on.
Oh.
Yeah, you've got a little on.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
Get a good bus.
Let's go.
Let's go, man.
Make your Jackson Blues band.
Yeah.
Doug Griller,
the insigator of free Trinity.
You know, so I called Don and Drew actually spoke to Miss Micelli yesterday about the whole Ziggy Marley cock up that I did.
And she said, basically, I think she said,
that's okay.
Just give me a car, bitch.
Something like that.
So my immediate thought was maybe I could just get rid of all the hatred with,
with by pawning off Trinity.
And then I'm thinking,
maybe Doug, you and your kids still interested.
You come on out and you guys drive over to Don and Drew.
And then have the minions pick it up from there.
Is that a thought perhaps?
I'd love to hear from you.
So Adam, this is Jonathan Doe.
I made a long time Charlie this morning.
I am not running for president.
However, if I were, there would be a few things I'd like to say.
And I've got them out if I were ready for president.com.
And like to invite you and my fellow Charlie listeners to come up and take a look.
Thanks.
Yeah, and I did that.
If I were president.com, you should take a look at that side.
Because it's, it's nice.
I don't know.
It's just something about it that I thought this is an interesting way of,
of protesting what's happening now and what you'd like to see in your future.
Leader, leader of the free world and for your country.
Enjoy that a lot, dude.
If I were president.com.
And here's a piece of music I want to play for you that comes from YouTube.
It's been all over the Dutch papers.
There's a girl, a singer in the Netherlands called S.M.
Denters.
And I think she's, she's really just known from YouTube.
Although I think she may have done.
Maybe she was a contestant on, you know, pop idol or ex-factor or something.
I've heard the name somewhere before.
But there's this awesome video.
And it's just her standing in a recording studio.
And she's singing Justin Timberlake song.
And in fact, at one point, you actually think that she's singing along with like a karaoke version.
Because you hear kind of Justin's voice going in and out.
I mean, I, I, there's no way to tell you this without actually spoiling.
You know, I'm not going to spoil it.
I want you to listen to this.
I'm going to listen to her singing.
And then at the very end, where the shot zooms out, all is revealed.
And I want you to listen to this.
Let me, I'm actually fired up from, from the web browser just from YouTube.
So this is what goes around by S.M. Denters.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I just can't seem to understand, though it was you and me bay, me and you, once you, the end, but I guess I was wrong.
To want to think about it, to want to talk about it, just so sick about it, can't believe it's in and is way, so confused about it, then the blues are about it, I just can't do it, don't you tell me if it's fair, is it so waste, really going down?
Is this how we say goodbye, babe?
I shouldn't know better when you came around, but you were going to make me cry,
I was breaking my heart to watch you run around, and that you live in a lie,
But that's okay, babe, because in time you will find what goes around goes around goes around,
and on others all the way, that carau,
What goes around goes aroundods around lambs all the way, that carau,
Who goes around goes around baby, he goes around with Where man crown of a woman crown,
Back around
Hey
What goes around baby
Comes around baby
Back around
Hey
What goes around
Comes around
Back around
Yeah
She's my son
She's my son better than me
No, that's not true
So the camera pulls out
And it's actually
Just in Timberlake playing the piano
And he was singing along
And she was apparently just standing there
And that gives me goosebumps
Man, you're just standing there singing
Timberlake song
Just the piano
And her in the studio
It's just phenomenal
And this thing is off the hook
It's got like a million views
But it's awesome
Really really cool
Highlight error
To me, who's this big
Good luckings
And over is me
But just try to worry
Just met him at the podcast
Day 2006 last year
But that's not the topic
I won't jump into this
Wherever locate the put show
HR stuff kind of
Discussion, Colone
Just love Berlin, Munich, Hamburg
But there was a statement
In the Charlie's 610 of
Johannes and
I want to try to play this again
Might be something
And Johannes
Colone would be the perfect location for the German
Pontchurch queue
Very big in all kinds of media
And it's a very nice city which is often described
As Italy's northern most city
I like the sound of that
Oh no, Johannes
I'm really not a big patriotic kind of guy
But you know that Munich is
Known as Italians
Most northern city, not even Colone
You do, you do have your fun on your own
And you may be a big media city
As we are
Immunic
But I want to just
Get this clear for the
Listeners of the Charlie
If you want to live a Italian style in Germany
You have to go to Munich
So wherever you plane will take you
You will come
But just please
Keep on trying
Sucking less with the Pontchurch
I tell them
Dude, you got some pipes there
You should do a couple of drops for the show
I don't know
I love the resonance of your voice
Record something, send the to me
Show me how to suck less
Ernie
Says Adam the best place in Germany is outside Germany
Namely in Switzerland
One of the most liberal and competitive economies in the world
No wonder a Google set up their major European offices in Zurich
Even more and more German companies move to Switzerland recently for good reasons
Adam moved
Podschot a Zurich and do the German market
From here I promise you
Will remember my words once the German bureaucracy and tax officers are after you
Ha ha ha ha ha
I don't scare me
Randy
Randy C. Sturgel
Says Heidelberg is the only place in Germany
In Germany deserving to be your headquarters period
End of discussion
Tell me this is off the hook
I'm getting a lot of these
So this is who is this from?
Frank Jonas, Frank Syregulner
Make sure that you don't think it's going to be easy to get a DSL line
It's not ubiquitous
Our landlines are operated by Inbecils
Deutsch telecom
Probably the single most ideal company in the world
Oh, that's nice
Er
Let's see
Is that what he's suggesting?
Here's another one from Munich who is this from Michelle
Oh from whispered pearls
Munich Adam have Podschot Germany immunity
Not only because that's my sister's base of operations
Well, that's a fine reason right there Michelle
But that also is where all the cool RT people are
They're centers there for film TV radio all sorts of old media
Munich would be the first choice Berlin would be the second
I'll see if I can get my sister to weigh in on this as well
Wow
Okay, but that's kind of cheating
What's that?
Is that all it?
Oh, here's oh my goodness
This is probably from Alex again
Oh, and he's got like a whole, you know, a whole sheet of a whole ratings sheet
This is this is much appreciated
Oh, I think we have to do a tour
We should probably do it we didn't in the UK
We should do a
Well, I guess we'll have to do a couple of meat and greets right drafts and darts
So what will it be?
The
That's not cool enough. Hey, let's come up with a couple locations couple ideas
I'd like to check out Munich
I'd like to check out what else did we have on the radar
A clone was on the radar
Berlin is on the radar, and I believe Hamburg is still just on the radar
All right, I got two more songs for you
This is one that cheers you up to guests
In the guys actually from Jersey
This name is Steve Robinson
Class clown
He's from Florida
He wasfrom Florida
He's from Atlanta
He's from Florida
They're storming to be known
I need to be excused and possibly stay there
Because that I got stuck on you
And then I came and blew it
And now we're separated
And I can't stand this
And I can't sleep
Because you don't see me and hell high
And you don't think me
You don't know why
I am smiling, looks like down
Offer down to the last one
Teach us that I'm not
But I have a God, a good obsession
And then I'll let you know
I'll get on you
Teach us that I'm just this
Steve Robinson
This is influences as Neil Finn Richard Thompson
The Beatles, Neil Young, XTC
And Crosby Still's Nation Young
And he used to play with Roger McWinn
I guess it's the guy from the birds, right?
Hey, this is Tracarton from Tracartonpodcast.com
Podshow needs you to help us suck less
Just go to suckless.podshow.com for complete details
Angie B sent me a note
And I love it when she starts off with a baby
And she sent me a picture, nude picture
Since this is me seated with my German girlfriend
Christiana
Back when I had black hair
Just got the next scan that thought I'd share
By the way, thanks for playing my online promo the other day
And then she sent me a track off of her
A new CD coming out October 2007
Love Spirals, of course with Ryan
I didn't know this song was anonymous, which makes it
Almost by default pod safe
It's the motherless child
And you'll know the song
You'll love the way Angie laid it down
Love Spirals
Sometimes I feel like a mother's child
But not the ways from home
Sometimes I feel like I'm almost gone
And I'm always alone
So I feel like I'm almost gone
I love spirals, muddleless child on a maximum music
Football Friday
It's Friday
Well, it starts up in pretty much focused on one thing smoking
And how much I'd like to do it
But I'm not
And it gets obsessive
And I try to distract myself and eat something
And it just makes it worse
But what I'm noticing is I've got a great support network
And that's really you guys
And people in the house here they've all heard this quick and stuff before
So they just try to be supported
But they don't really want to say anything
They don't want to catch me in the wrong mood
They're smart
But I really do appreciate all of the emails and the audio comments
And voice mail that people in the calling in with
That's really nice
It really does help
And I do feel much better
What do we know?
I haven't counted this time
Which I think is probably better
And I'm in week two somewhere
It's just those certain moments
Particularly the moments that I share with you guys
When I'm doing the shows
When I want to smoke the most
So having you sitting there
Yelling back at me
To not do it
It's really helpful
So I'm going to try and be supported for someone else
Who's doing something difficult
I'm not sure what and I'm probably doing some of that already somewhere
But I'm going to make a conscious effort
Because it really does make this whole world kind of work
Doesn't it?
So that's it
The final thought of the week
Okay, here's the plan
Tomorrow I take the lady Patricia to the lowlands
Dropping her off in Amsterdam
She has a live TV show on Sunday, Sunday afternoon
So I will be flying out
Whether permitting of course on Monday
To Antwerp pick up the good old wing commander
We'll come back
We'll pick up Patricia on the way back
And then he's going to take the aircraft back
To Antwerp to take it to the radio shop
Because we definitely have a problem with the radios
And I want it fixed
And since I'm going away
I think I'm in New York Tuesday morning
I have a really early morning flight out
I'm going to be in New York for the rest of the week
And then I think off to San Francisco in the weekend
So I will be on the road for a considerable
A considerable amount of time
And I hope you join me along the way
Oh, by the way
It's a soft launch but tech five dot podshow dot com
Have a listen
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Served up daily by the sharpest mines in content delivery
Podshow in line light