Hey, this is Trucker Tom from TruckerTomPodcast.com, PodShow needs you to help us suck less.
Just go to suckless.podshow.com for complete details.
You're Adam, installing.
You'll, for the DSC-617, I got to set the record straight.
You was talking about the ending of the sopranos, well,
it seems that my nephew at water has stolen the ending to the sopranos.
That's all worry about it. We're going to get it back. I got a baseball bat with his name on it.
I got a bunch of the boys. We're going to hunt them down and get back the ending, but
yeah, I was like you. I didn't know what was going on. I was in the backyard trying to adjust the
satellite dish because I thought I had lost my satellite, but not water stole the ending of the
sopranos, because nobody in the right mind would end a show like that. So anyway, on the DSC-617,
let everybody know that we'll get the ending back and let everyone to sopranos fans
will be satisfied. Capiche. Hi.
Now.
Like the way you're doing. There's a time. It's myself. There's one more.
Because it ain't a crime, too. I really enjoy my life.
For love I know where you're suffering and there's time where you're out.
I love why I carried on and tell I showed up in love.
I love that love. There's never any need to try and guide that far.
Yeah.
To try and find out who I am.
This is a monster.
Yeah.
That's the one.
This is it.
It's the one-off song from the summer.
We heard it here.
I'm in the name of the source code.
Aren't you happy?
Yeah.
It's Koopa from the Pate Music Network.
It's another one of those Nigel Specials.
We've been bringing us all kinds of awesome music.
Bring it on to the Pate Music Network.
I just clicked on a link off of one of its weekly emails.
You sent them out to a whole bunch of podcasts.
No idea.
I have no idea what he's doing.
I got to interview this guy.
That's for a future daily source code.
Today was episode number 617 coming to you from the curry condo in San Francisco, Northern California.
How are you doing?
Wow.
What a day.
First of all, to be in the office and to be working with everybody.
A lot of new faces.
At least new faces to me.
The place is jammed.
We have two offices now.
Actually, I think we're very close to signing a lease on a new space.
But this is this non-smoking thing.
For some reason, I've been completely energized.
And today was a really, really good day.
And I'd like to start with the end of the day first to tell you that I got really excited
by the keynote, the Steve Jobs keynote that he did here.
As I told you yesterday, and you probably know, the Apple worldwide developer conference
is being held here in San Francisco.
So the place is crawling with macheads.
And as we've come to expect from Steve, he did a keynote.
Now, this, of course, a little more technically oriented.
Although, still pretty consumer-ish, I would have to say.
Showing new features and, you know, of the mac and, I mean, you have, if you are, obviously,
if you're a machead, you probably already watched this thing.
You might have even watched it live.
Now, you have to see this.
I got to tell you, I've got major wood for leopard.
Okay.
I'm just horny for this thing.
The way Steve Jobs presents that stuff.
Yeah.
And there's all, it's just, there's cool, cool features.
And I'm sure by the time leopard comes out, there'll be a new faster
max to run it on.
And, you know, we'll be able to take advantage of the 64-bit architecture.
I mean, all the stuff that just, I have to make, it gives me really, really excited.
And my via was just sitting there, you know, with its melted alt key from some
debris burning debris that fell on it.
It's just kind of sitting there going, you, you thinking about their women.
And I have to admit, I'm thinking of a woman, her name is leopard.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And interesting move there by, by Apple to enable development on the iPhone by essentially
saying, hey, you know, you can pretty much do anything you want.
You can access all the functions of the forthcoming iPhone without having to, you know,
actually load an application onto it.
Just use the Safari browser.
It's the full Safari browser, the Safari engine.
They say, I guess with engine, it means that that engine can tap into, you know, so you could
write an Ajax web 2.0 script or web page to call a number or to access some of the
Google map functionality or G wouldn't be nice if you could do something with it to
access the iPod part.
No mention of that, but it will be really nice for accessing podcasts.
But, you know, so essentially, it's, it's not a bad idea.
And I also kind of thought, hey, you know, what's all this mumbling and grumbling about
developers?
When the iPhone was announced, it's like, oh, it's a close box and no one could develop on
it.
And I'm thinking, you know, all the apps I really need are accessed either through Wi-Fi or
through through the cellular network.
And so I presume that in order to get developers interested, they had to release a version
of the Safari engine for Windows, which they did.
I downloaded it immediately.
I'd say not quite ready for prime time yet.
And with that, I mean, it's incredibly fast.
I have to admit it seems that the test that he showed that it really is faster than Firefox.
But there's a couple of gnarly things in there.
And I'm not, you know, there's no way for me to provide data feedback.
But I'll tell you what's a couple of things are wrong right off the bat.
First of all, sometimes like Google notebook doesn't function with it.
You can click the buttons.
It'll add a new note for you.
When you click in the field, you don't actually see any typing show up.
In fact, checking in other browser, no typing showed up.
No text was entered.
So that's one problem.
In Gmail, when you use that, I can just tab once or twice depending on what field I'm in.
If I'm in the editing field, editing a message or composing a message, just hit the tab.
It's the focus is on send and I just have to hit return.
So I never actually have to use the mouse.
That doesn't work.
That function.
It'll, it'll go to the send button.
But when I hit enter, it doesn't actually.
Maybe I have to hit to something else.
Is there a difference between enter and return in this case?
I don't think I have a, I only have an enter key, which is the return key on my, on my IO.
So anyway, so that's just makes it completely unusable.
No way to import my existing bookmarks.
Sorry, that's not going to fly.
I spend a lot of time on taking those bookmarks exactly what I want them to be.
No plugin for, for the Google notebook.
So no contextual menu.
All stuff that I use is really important.
And I'm sure it'll get there.
But right now, it's just not quite ready for prime time for me.
But still, I want one of them freaking phones too.
I'm sorry.
It's just like, ah, I've won it.
Oh, what is it?
What is it?
God, man, that stuff is so inspiring to me.
And I look at, you know, some of the, some of the jokes he puts into his presentation.
I'm like, wow, man, when you're really cruising,
and you've got awesome products that people just really want and are crying about.
And you can have so much fun.
And I'm, I'm not envious, but I'm just, I'm inspired.
I'm really inspired by that.
And so that with some, some things that happen today,
just, you know, sitting down face to face with, with some folks working on a number of different things.
One of course is is continuing to make podshow.com or we believe it should be.
And we're starting to surface things very, very slowly.
And I've actually, I'd like to involve you in a test if you don't mind as, as listeners to the show.
So we have this channel architecture.
And I, I don't want to go too deep into it right now.
But it's, it is significantly different from any other site out there,
the way they're using channels.
You'll, you've probably noticed if you visit podshow.com that a lot of,
actually, two things have really started to surface almost everywhere.
Play buttons and get buttons.
And they're very distinct now.
You can't miss them.
And, and, you know, please, just see this as a sandbox for right now.
Because things are going to change pretty rapidly over the next couple of weeks.
You're literally going to see podshow.com change before your eyes.
So one of the things that you may not have, you know, quite seen or used yet
is the fact that everything that you find in podshow.
Oh, that was disgusting. Excuse me.
Everything you find in podshow, you can get.
So if you create a channel and let's just, you know,
not even think about what that is, but you get a channel by default.
So you have a default channel in podshow.
When you see a little get button next to a show,
then you click on that and it'll give you a list of all the channels you have available.
If you, if you only have, you never create a new channel, then you just have one default channel.
That's fine. Just use that.
So you can add it to that channel.
And whenever that show updates,
the newest episode will be available in that channel.
So if you go to your channel module, you can hit play channel,
and it'll just kind of play.
Now, all, we have so many amazing features that are completely hidden away,
which, of course, we have to now start surfacing up.
One of those features is that you can put a channel onto a mobile device.
You can do that through an RSS link.
Oh, and actually any other device doesn't have to be mobile.
Well, let's just make it real simple.
You can put it on your iPod.
And as you know, the way to get stuff on the iPod is through iTunes.
So you can create a channel, and I have several of these.
In fact, I don't subscribe to single podcast anymore.
I use, because this is some of the stuff we're talking about today.
Like, you know, what do I really use pod show for?
Well, once in a while, surf around, you know, look for stuff,
or I'll see who is listening to a show and see what else they're listening to.
And of course, if I see someone who just looks hot, I'll click on them.
Just to see what's going on.
But I really use it to manage.
I don't use the iPod at all, practically.
I use my Nokia phone, the E61 India.
And it has a podcasting application in it.
And all I need, basically, is an RSS feed or podcast feed or channel feed,
or just it's a URL.
And I enter that in and up comes my channel.
And it automatically updates on my phone overnight.
And the newest shows episodes, I should say,
of shows that are in each channel appear.
So I have an on the go channel, which is a combination of, actually,
I can tell you exactly what it is.
Let me just go to my channels.
I just have that all set up at atom.podshow.com.
I'm getting to an interesting point here where I want you to help me out.
So just bear with me.
I just want to try and make this clear as possible.
So you might on the go channel.
I have quite a few shows, actually.
I've got the New York Times front page on the media,
BBC NewsPod, the promo feed,
national inquire, or legend, Mike Walker's, the gossip game,
Pacific Coast Hellway.
So you can actually see that if you go to atom.podshow.com,
you can see what I have in each of my channels.
So not all of these shows update to daily,
but when one updates, then it appears in the feed,
and therefore appears on my Nokia.
So the on the go is really, you know,
I even named the channel.
It's for the train rides to shortage.
So when I go to London, I know that the latest stuff in this channel
is just and it's short stuff.
You know, it's like these are like 10 to 15 minutes show.
Some of them live longer, but they just show up in date order,
chronological order.
So that's essentially how I use podshow.
And if I don't like a show anymore,
then I'll just get it out of my channel
and it won't show up on my phone anymore.
If I find something new somewhere in podshow,
you know, a new show that I like,
then I can add it to that channel,
or any of my other channels for that matter.
And some channels, I have show up in different devices.
You know, like I have a,
we call Microsoft.
What do you call that thing?
Media Center.
So I have some channels that I subscribe to there.
Now, what we've done within podshow is
not just can you just get or collect or subscribe to shows,
but you can also do it for individual episodes.
You can do it for the songs made available by an artist.
All of these have a little get buttons next to them.
And you can even do it for images.
And I believe, and we've kind of held back in a couple things
because it can get really confusing.
It's already quite a mind trip
when you, if you can follow along when I'm about to tell you.
So because you can get individual shows,
I can create a channel that you can,
that'll just, with stuff that'll automatically show up on your iPod,
or wherever you use this channel, wherever it is.
So it's really, it's meant for two type of uses.
One is to play the channel in a web browser.
And you can just do that by clicking play channel.
And it'll just pop up a window.
And the other use is to put this on a different device.
So let's just say an iPod to make it simple.
So when you, after you've listened to the show, or if you're in front of your computer right now,
you can do it now if you want.
Just go to dailysourcecode.com and you see the DSC channel.
And there'll be two links.
One to put it on your iPod.
And the other one is a pure RSS link.
So you can put that on anything that will understand RSS with enclosures.
Nice little technical info there.
We'll understand that feed.
Now what I've done in there is I've put in a couple of episodes
that I think are worth watching or listening to.
So I put what I put in there.
I put just a random hit test episode episode number 42
just to kind of show that I can get something from way back when I put in.
Oh, episode 85.
I think of this week in tech.
This week in tech.
Twitter.
The one that I was a guest on.
And I also put in an intro to the channel.
All just by using a mouse.
So I didn't have to code anything.
I didn't have to write anything.
Anything I found online or if I searched for it because,
you know, we, of course, search across podcast,
Ali and Andy Potter.org.
And you know, we have a, I'd have to say pretty much,
a very extensive certainly of independent mainstream shows.
And we also searched in the episodes.
The search is not perfect yet totally down with that,
but it ain't all that bad.
Anything you find you can add a single episode.
You can add to your channel.
So it's a kind of a different way of broadcasting if you will.
Now I could use it as a companion.
So for instance, if there, you know, I listened to a lot of stuff.
So for me, if I, if I hear an episode that I think will be funny,
or you know, that I want you to listen to,
I'll just add that single episode to the feed.
And it'll just stay there until I remove it,
which is another thing I can do.
I can remove stuff from the feed and replace it.
I could change the whole channel overnight.
Now, of course, the stuff you already downloaded
would remain on your, on your iPod that would automatically
been brought in.
But anything new would be introduced right there.
And it'd be there automatically.
And, you know, I cut an intro for the video.
Which is pretty stupid one by the way.
But I cut a video intro for the channel.
But you don't have to do that.
You know, it could be anything.
It could be any type.
Literally any type of media that you want.
It could, it could just be a picture.
So this channel will perform differently,
depending on where you're using it.
Of course, if you have, if you don't have a video iPod,
video stuff is not going to play.
I'm not sure about the pictures.
I think pictures will probably display on a video iPod.
But certainly everything will work in the dashboard.
And so there's, you know, it's funky, right?
We're figuring this stuff out.
So I'm trying to keep it pretty simple.
Keeping it just very limited to audio and video.
I am doing a mixed channel.
And I want you to take a look at that.
And please, put it on your iPod.
And, you know, let's just get a feel for it.
And see if it's an actual experience that you like and let me know.
And if there's anything that, you know, that you dig.
Obviously, you can go out and you can get that show for yourself.
And by now, I'm sure you understand that you can clearly.
You can create your own channel and do this very same thing.
So it's, it's kind of using Poncho.com as a utility.
But in a very interesting way, because, you know, for me to be able to create.
And now, of course, I'm going to create a channel with single episodes for Patricia.
That'll just go on an iPod actually on iTunes.
She doesn't, well, she's used my iPod.
But she just, she understands iTunes.
And she'll understand how to go into it.
And, you know, into a, just open up one little folder there and see if there's something new to play.
And she'll get that.
And so I can put all kinds of stuff in there.
And I'm really moderating that channel or, or on the editor of the channel or maybe
maybe I'm just kind of like a broadcaster in some kind of bizarre to it twisted way.
So again, go to dailysourcecode.com or query.com.
You'll see the link there.
It should open up iTunes automatically.
Get the channel for you.
And if you're using something else, there's an RSS feed for you.
Hey, let's play.
You will know by name.
Question.
answered.
podcasting communities done the word podcasting a huge disservice and
and the technology, it's not even technology, it's the presentation of
crap. It's because we can't explain it. It's like Tivo.
You know, Tivo has spent $300 million trying to explain to people what the
frick of Tivo is. And they failed miserably at it. But you know, when people
get a Tivo, guess what? They don't want you know, try and take it away from them.
They'll stab you and they will. They'll bite you whatever it takes to do not
remove the Tivo. So it's one of those things that you just have to show
people in order for them to understand. And you know, and again, I'm going back to
the whole job's thing today when he claims that there's half a billion downloads
of iTunes onto Windows computers. You know, I don't, that seems like a lot. But
anyway, when I want to ask someone, you got an iPod. Yeah, I got an iPod. Well,
have you ever seen the little word podcast in iTunes? No, I haven't seen it.
You know, the people that just don't see it. You know, it's just not on the radar
like that. But if I said, Hey, man, let me send you an email and you just click
on that link and you'll have a channel of of what we can call podcasts or let's
just say you'll have a channel of cool shit on your iPod. Now that, you know,
you don't have to explain it. It's like, ah, it got some cool shit. I don't
cool shit. Look, it's like, it's like shit. It's in trying to explain a podcast
thing. You said that people understand internet radio better than podcast. And I
was thinking, it's really not just internet radio. But it's kind of like internet
radio with something like TV or digital video recording. Yeah, okay. So that's my
point. And I appreciate what you're saying, but I don't think we should compound
the problem by trying to say podcasting is internet TV. It's not
just getting your shows from internet. But your computer actually collects your shows
in a way that a digital video recorded does so that they're downloaded and
organized and ready to do it. And those people are advertisers are afraid of
digital video recorders. Although I saw a survey somewhere where some results
of a survey crap. I wish I had that. I probably saved it somewhere. It said
that when Tvo users, um, misquoting is I think it was like when Tvo users
watch ads, um, they really want 30 second ads and not 15. So I don't know what
the hell it was. But I still, you know, hey, look, make the ads entertaining.
Make people want to watch it. There are ads I watch and there are ads I'll stop
for because they're funny. Even the dam, uh, what is it? Uh, 1 1 8 1 1 8.com
ads that they had on before and after lost on channel. Or I watch that. Those guys
are dumb and makes me feel good to watch. Anyway, just thought it was a better
analogy. Love the show. Absolutely. Thanks a lot, Adam. Take care. I appreciate it so
much. Janice, will you please call back more often? And let me know what you do. And, uh,
well, I'll be remiss if I didn't ask for some naked pictures. Oh, shit. This is the one.
Let's have a word with the nylon spread and the news with the smile on where the
wrong old right window for light. Let's listen for the wild and the nylon. Oh, yes,
he's back. And I don't know if I'm just missing his comments because he refers to it
as if comments are being sent. He's calling in every single day. But here he is. And he's
got a lot of crap on his mind. The nylon everybody. Yeah, I'm the nylon. I must be a little
reluctant to play some of my calls these days. Hey, that's what I'm talking about. I don't
receive your calls, okay? I don't know what you're doing, but they're not coming to me. This is the
first time I've received one since the last time you said I don't play your calls. It's too critical,
but I'll keep going. So first point is, um, John DeVoilac. This guy is a vice president of your
organization and vice president and most company means he's an officer of the company. Yeah,
no, no, no, no. If you're an officer of the company, you're an officer of the company. If
you're a vice president, vice president is not like an officer. Officer would be a chief executive
officer or chief technology officer. BP is vice president, not officer. But I think your point is
well made. You know, he's he's, he's dedicated to the success of the company. Yes, he's a stakeholder.
And I, uh, yeah, stakeholder. And, you know, he's committed to maximizing the value of the company.
Well, as is everyone at Pod Show, everyone at Pod Show is a stakeholder in the form of options.
So they, uh, they absolutely have a stake in, uh, in a number of different types of outcome.
I found them a couple of times. The guy doesn't know what his job is. You know, the
PR release you put in, devour, devour act is always trying to stumble to say,
I, what is Ron Bloom mean by all this hyperbole? Guy is in our particular about what he does.
And it's now three weeks. And I'm sure we hear something. But I think most of your listeners
and audience are also confused. You know, you know, nylon, um, after you, hopefully just listen to
my whole rant about channels, go back and reread the press release. And by the way, you know, I had
John on the show. Ah, something stuck in my nose. Hold on. I had John on the show. And we
laughed about the press release. It's a press release. It's for the press. It's not for bloggers
and nyloners. It's a press release. You know, old school, old world. You know, there is still
a need for that. And it's sometimes is quite useful. Now, but go back and reread that and maybe
something will start to dawn on you as to how we're putting all this stuff together.
The icing on the cake is Twitter 100. He's on there with Leo. Leo is the show by saying, John,
anything you want to plug? John plugs his blog. Nothing else. He's a vice president,
a part show. He should be plugging. Nothing. Two minutes later, Leo prompts some. Leo comes back
and prompts him and says, how about part show, John? And then John comes in. What kind of officer
of a company needs prompting to talk about his company? So two things there. First of all,
we're very happy with the work that John already does. His writing, his own blog,
cranky geeks, his appearances on CNBC. And of course, this week in tech. And I mean, how
lame would it be if he went around and all these shows, all of a sudden promoting his, you know,
he doesn't, well, he does promote his blog. But not like, hey, you know, I've got a blog. It's,
you know, he'll say, I wrote about this on my blog. And I'm sure in the future,
we'll say, oh, I said this on tech five, which is unofficially soft launched, whatever the hell,
that means tech five dot pod show dot com to ECH five. I think tech five FIV might also work,
which should. You know, so when it's in reference, then it's relevant. And of course,
we'll talk about it. But there's, you know, we didn't buy, you know, if I wanted to be on Leo show
with a pod show commercial, I'd fucking buy a commercial. You know, that's not, that's, you know,
these are existing things, existing existing work he was doing. There's no need to do that.
That's just kind of lame. And Leo prompted him. That's right, Leo really asked him, I heard the show.
And so John told him, I think that John was even, you could probably hear he was unprepared for the
question. He wasn't intending on talking about it at all. You know, there's a right time and for things
and a right place for things and a right moment. And, and that wasn't it. So I think, you know,
maybe just being, uh, fucking decent nylon. Um, quite the confused. He doesn't talk about it on cranky geeks.
You know, this sounds like a very titular fuzzy sort of relationship to have.
I give it one year, you know, the guy doesn't seem to be totally aligned and engaged and committed.
Good. You know, what are you? Now we'll sudden you're the media pundit. I give it one year.
Shut up. See attributes for a single officer. Last and not least is back to Trinity. You may not
want to hear it, but, you know, this meant my ride. You know, this is a great idea five months ago.
It was audience generated, audience energize, audience customize, everyone was pushing the ports for
open. They wanted to get on the Trinity band, Reagan. Nothing's happened because you're trying
to get a sponsor's logo on poor little Trinity. Let's not monetize Trinity. It was a good idea.
The audience was behind it. Let's get it over with. Run the thing, of course, the US, let everyone
pedal 25 miles back home. Um, you know, three Trinity is free from the tent. Stop monetizing everything.
It's the hall. It was a nice idea. The audience loved it five months ago, and by
forgetting that it's an avenue focused on your audience. What's going to bring them some joy. So,
oh, I don't know. All right. I'm going to say you're you're right on some of that. Absolutely. The heat
was on five months ago. Now, I totally believed that the heat is there. But there's a couple of things.
First of all, um, in putting this together, you know, this is a corporation where they're
you like it or not. Uh, and I am an extension of a corporation. And so there's a couple of things
that we have to do properly. Um, insurance is really part of it. So, you know, and so the minute you
even start looking into that shit, guess what? I'm busy. And I hate looking at that. So I got to
get a producer to do it. You know, producers not free. Yeah, because, of course, I could get someone
to do it for free. And I could, you know, find people just enthusiastic. But I want things done right.
I think this is a big project. And it's, and honestly, it's much bigger than I ever expected
to be just thinking through the logistics of it. And no, I mean, I don't want, uh, to have to rely
on people spending their own money to do deadhead trips. You know, in one way, because, you know,
you're going to drive some part of the right. You have to get back somehow, eventually, unless you
had it planned that way. So then you're into logistics. You know, there's a lot, a lot of logistics.
Yeah, we could have seen where we got with it. But it's my fucking car. You know, I want to do this
ride. It's not like, oh, I'm just throwing my car. It's my car, all right. And, you know, the car is
also has had a lot of problems. Oh, Rosie, she hadn't even told me about the latest, uh, Trinity
Clamter Port on us. Uh, apparently she would not no longer accept the key. Uh, I'm going to
get a locksmith over and it's like 200 bucks for a new lock ignition, the ignition. So she's in the
garage now here at the condo. And, uh, you know, as I think everything that that could have broken
has broken and everything that need to be fixed has been fixed. So anyway, there's definitely
costs associated with it. But I want us to have fun with it. And so you're right, you know,
I was, I was ill-prepared, um, to take advantage of the, the, the wave that came.
Although I do totally believe we can rekindle that when the time is right. And that time is going to
come. And yes, um, I am actively looking for a sponsor. It's not necessarily me monetization,
okay? It's like saying NPR monetizes on their sponsorships. You know, sometimes you just need to
sponsorship to make something work. I just don't want to do this ad hoc. There's just too much
involved. Um, for me, I mean, someone would have to manage it regardless, regardless. You know,
Barbara was putting all together. She put a proposal together. And she wanted decent money, you know,
to manage the whole thing. Uh, and you have to pay anyone, anyone's a decent money. And it's a,
it's not like a day project. It's a three to, it's like a three-month project, I think,
with preparation, with a trip, you know, this actual work involved. Now, that said, we, I think we're
very close. And that's what I alluded to last week. We're very, very close, um, to a relevant sponsor
who really wants to step up and step into this project. And, you know, I'm excited about that.
And so if that possibility is out there, and that's for real. And as I said, I would
have an update on that this week, you know, then I think it's worth waiting for.
I think we can still have fun. There's a saying in Dutch about did it to fotsit for your
need. Uh, and of course, it, uh, has not translated it all. Uh, but whatever's in the barrel
is isn't going to go sour. Adam, I beg you, don't become tip my call version 2.0,
3 20. Don't let Madison Avenue and logos touch her. It was a great idea.
Ah, I feel better. You're so, uh, my one.
Nylon. Um, I really don't like you, but I really, really, really do appreciate
you calling in and giving me a piece of your mind. Whoa, he's an island.
Fucking expatriate. He's in London, buddy. He's from New York. Whoa, he's my
love. Country versus the island. He's in London, buddy. He's from New York.
All right, how about we kick it right now with some new black lab. This will be in the
pod save music network later this week. Here's transformer.
Transformers.
From the sky above, it's not that you can do. You're fair, the strike will be in the place
the world, where your call was through the crimp, and how the evil make it strong,
transformers, more than he's the Earth, transformers,
move on to the sky, strong enough to break the braveest heart.
We have to fall together, because it was a part,
standin' by the wheel of Charlie Paul, until I'll talk to someone,
I will save a song, transformers, more than he's the Earth, transformers,
move on to the sky, transformers, all of us, ways have bound to destroy the evil force alone.
Let the static out.
Transformers.
All right, I stand corrected.
It's not exactly going to be pod save any time soon.
Turns out the official Transformers theme sucks.
So, fallen in, you're back a lot beside a date.
It looks a little take on the official theme, but the fans aside.
Leave a lot of evolution and be my friends.
There'll be a video out on YouTube of that tomorrow.
Which reminds me, I'm just waiting around now. I don't really have time to go trolling YouTube,
but I'm so convinced that within a day or two we're going to see the real
official ending of the sopranos. I think there's going to be a viral explosion of people creating
funny endings, dramatic endings, endings they act themselves, endings that will be spoofed,
takeoffs, etc. And quite honestly, I'm really looking forward to it.
We talked a lot today about a lot of stuff. One more thing, I know I'm asking a lot of you,
so besides clicking on a link, I know it's quite a task and check out what you think of my channel
in iTunes, or maybe just some of you may check it out on your iPod, others, only on iTunes,
or whatever you are. Let me know how that goes for you. And if you have a chance, I'd like you to
become a member of the super panel. This is a whole suckless thing you've been talking about.
We really want to understand more about you. I want to understand more about you as my audience,
and we'll know that you're a DSC listener, and you'll also indicate what other things you
listen to. And if you're a part of the super panel, then it kind of continues. And you don't have to
do every single survey. I realize that what I'm doing here is basically saying to you as a friend,
hey, just put my arm around you. Hey, when we go down to the mall, and when those people ask you
to take the survey, take it, okay? Now I understand. It can be a pain in the ass, but I really
would appreciate it. And soon advertisers will also be asking you through us as a part of the
super panel, what you think of ads and how they're placed in podcasts, talking about pre-roll,
post-roll, host endorsements, all this stuff. We get lots of feedback and you tell us lots of things
about what you feel and what you think, but here's an opportunity to actually tell us. So the
questions, very basic right now, but they are going to become extremely targeted also for other
countries. You know, this is going to be a long campaign that's going to, you know, the
suckless inserts are going to go away, you know, within a relatively short time, you know,
the whole point is we got your attention for a number, in a number of ways, I'd really like that
and I really appreciate if you take the survey for me. And I'll send you one of my naked pictures.
DailySourceco.com, add on podshow.com, looking forward to talking to you guys tomorrow. Bye.
The best and the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery,
podshow and lightweight.