Ladies and gentlemen, I present Padshal's poet laureate Melvin P. LeBeth.
Roses are ready. My sweater is beige. For your domain name needs, you should go to this page. GoDaddy.com.
Alright, let's see. I've got everything set up now. I've got my brand new microphone plugged into my brand new mixer and the tube compressor. Everything just like Adam Curry.
So now I just need to, well, before I start podcasting my first show, I'm going to get some words of wisdom from Adam Curry, the pod father.
I'm just going to go straight to the middle of an episode and see what he has to say and just inspire me to put this together.
I think it, um, okay, so we should probably, alright, I got to think about this. You already here, I'm getting diarrhea of the mouth. Oh boy, I hope I can find all my receipts.
Maybe the DSC 578 will be better.
The 60 million dollars worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
in the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying to the future.
I'm the hero of the song, the flame's dead, and the fire's gone.
All this empty minutes and night alone.
And we are the last and one.
Everybody out there.
I just gotta go.
If you really care, you really care.
I'm the hero of the song, the flame's dead, and the fire's gone.
All this empty minutes and night alone.
I just gotta go.
I'm the hero of the song, the flame's dead, and the fire's gone.
All this empty minutes and night alone.
I just gotta go.
If you really care, you really care.
I'm the hero of the song, the flame's dead, and the fire's gone.
All this empty minutes and night alone.
Everybody out there, everybody out there.
I'm just a god of love
If you really care, you really care
From the full head
I'm just a god of love
I've just got to go
You can really care
That's a way to kick off a full bar Friday
In my hammer house
Deflapper Fulin
Straight from Napster to your ears
Purchase for 99 cents
I encourage you to go out and buy that
Oh man
I was just perusing
I was looking for a song for something else
And I came across Deflapper
Actually it was one of those suggestions
Other tracks you might want to
I was looking for AC DC
Believe it or not
Do you know that AC DC is unfindable on iTunes
And on Napster
What's up with that
I was looking for back and back
For a different reason
And I came across this and like
Oh man
I played this record so many times
In the 80s
Geez
I think I was almost honorary fan club
Presidents
Deflapper
Those guys are recording in Hilversum
In the visilord studios
For a long, long time
With the magic of mud lying I might add
Fantastic
Everybody is your food bar Friday
It is daily source code
Episode number 578
The last one for this trip
Out west in Northern California
From the Curry condo
It is
A very early Friday morning
It is late Thursday night
It is early Friday morning
It is a little bit foggy
Which means it may not be that nice
Tomorrow
Hopefully you are checking this out
It is nice and sunny
Where you are
I know it is great in the UK today
I call the ladies
I am a Patricia sister
Is over visiting with Patricia
So they got like no time for me
So
Five minutes of a phone call
And I am sorry
We are off somewhere else
We are doing this
We are doing that
I came home
Ron and I had this dinner
At the San Francisco home of Mike Moritz
Mike Moritz is a senior partner
It is a coia capital
One of the investors in pod show
I guess he does this on a regular basis
It is called a founders dinner
There is a founders of companies
That is a coia
Invest in
Where they are
First of all
Dude has got a fucking awesome pad
Here
I am not quite sure what part of San Francisco
It is a massive house
High up on the hill
Like 280 degree view
Everything from the Golden Gate
All the way downtown
Really nice
Nice pad
But it was interesting
Let us see
Jason Calicanas
I did not get a chance to talk to him
Ron and I were late
Because unlike the other founders
We were actually working
And so we showed up around 6.30
And just before dinner
But sat next to a former employee of ours
Phil Kaplan
Better known as pud
To us
He worked in the engineering department
He was a web developer
I think new ideas
Company that Ron and I started in New York
And took public
And successfully sold in 1999
And Philip of course went on to start
To start the website
Fuck the company
And then of course he wrote the book
And then he started ad-bright
And ad-bright is extremely successful
And cool thing about Phil is
It's still Phil
It's exactly the same guy
No difference whatsoever
See who else was
Who was the name of the guy
He has a funky name
I forgot it
He's a Tesla
The electric sports car company
Is his
And he just shot a rocket into space
Or some shit like that
I don't know
I was interested in conversation
Who else was there
Sean Fanning
Is that his name?
From a bit torrent
Didn't get a chance to talk to him
Either unfortunately
So you know
It was just a room kind of full
Like geeky nerdy guys
And a food was excellent
And then I rushed home
Because I had some stuff to do
Some stuff to produce
As well as of course
Bring you your favorite
Food Bar Friday
For those of you who are new to the show
Food Bar stands for fucked up
Beyond a whole repair
And so you know
You know you can walk into your house
And you know immediately
Something is very very wrong
Like almost like the air is different
I walked in and like
Whoa what's going on
And I'm looking I couldn't find
Anything wrong
But then I saw it
There was
Right on the countertop
In the kitchen
A Jack in the box
Coke
So you know like one of those
Takeout
Medium Cokes
With a straw
From Jack in the box
Sitting right there
I'm like holy shit
This is weird
I got it got creeped out
For a second
Then I saw the Baker's rack
Was actually moved about half a foot
And then I figured it out
That they'd come into fix
The leaking blinds or whatever it is
But man they could have done
They could have at least
I don't know
They didn't even tell me they were doing that
No but freaky
Okay it is
Food Bar Friday means we've got a lot of
The standard stuff that we're going to be doing
Let me just see
If there's anything I want to talk about
Right off the bat
Oh yes this is really
This is quite important actually
Yesterday
I kind of made a faux pub
I played you a clip of this
Robert Newman
It was sent to me by Neil Cocker
And you said you've got to check out this
Video or this
The show that was on TV
Comedy slash lecture
Is the way Neil described it
Robert Newman's history of oil
And I
I only listened to
I just played the opening for you
And listened to it
And I said I'm bored already
And I moved on
But then later as the show was uploading
I actually fired that up and looked at it
Holy crap
You must
I repeat
You must see this
You will
Love watching this
Either
To the end of the tonight
Or over the way
I do it over the weekend
Saturday or Sunday
Just take 45 minutes
And watch this
The history of oil
It is fascinating
It seems like the guy has done his homework
And what's beautiful about this
Is his thesis or hypothesis
Perhaps I should say
Of why
The United States invaded Iraq
Is brilliant
And it's something I have read about
Before
But I must say it kind of slipped away
I don't want to spoil it for you
But let me just give it to you
In a nutshell
At a certain point
All of the OPEC countries
Who have always traded
Oil has always been traded in dollars
That was determined
I believe in the early 70s
Like 71
When OPEC said
OK
The currency that you can buy
And sell oil in
Is US dollars
Which of course
Oh, hold on a second
This is not a good thing
I see that
Oh shit
It's not good
When my desk is spinning around
What is it?
What's the name of that program?
The virus can is
Checking my desk
Not good when you're recording
OK
So that rule was set up in 71
Which of course means that every country that wants to buy oil
That needs oil
Well, that's every single country in the world
Has to buy dollars first
So when you are buying dollars
That props up the
Currency
Or it makes the currency valuable
It's a blind demand
It's real simple economic stuff
But then around 2000
And I can't remember which country started it
Maybe it was
Seria, Egypt
I can't remember
It doesn't matter
Because eventually all OPEC countries
Started to say
Hey, you know what?
We'd like to change our
Dollar account into euros
Because we're going to start doing this in euros
Now what does that mean?
And this is
It's so feasible
But I think it's just brilliant
Not to have even seen this
That this guy
Robert Newman caught onto it
So if oil is now being traded in euros
And you have a whole shitload of dollars
What do you have to do?
Exactly
You've got to sell your dollars
What does that do?
Supplying demand?
It devalues the dollar
And I must say
Although there is no reason
Ever to go to war
And considering that almost every single war
Has been for economic reasons
And this is a part of this whole
Stand-up that you have to see
I mean it's taking out of context
It just doesn't work
But let's just say
Let's just agree that most wars are started
For economic reasons
It makes a hell of a lot of sense
It's been done in the past many many times
It's like hey, wait a minute
We've got to protect the value of our currency
You know hey you guys
You fuckers
Don't be selling our dollars
You've got to be buying our dollars
Now you have to see this
Because when he he does
Comparisons to
Silvatore Dolly
And his infamous way of getting out of
Paying for things
It's it is just phenomenal
So you will you will not regret it
Take a look at this
Fantastic
It's Robert Newman's history of oil
Of course a link
To that video in the show
No
Oh yes
Hey hey hey
Hi Amy
Do you remember what we talked about
Remember what we talked about earlier this week
Amy
Hello
Hey Adam
Oh yeah
When we talked earlier this week
You said that we should try making the evening
Assurcerizes a little sexier
Yeah, oh yeah
So I thought we'd slip into something a little more comfortable
Okay, I'm ready
What do you say?
What are you wearing?
I mean like something really
Yeah
I don't think I can pull the sex kit and thing off
I don't know
I felt like a moron
No, you sound hot
They do a move laying on the ground
So you can pretend sexy
Okay, I'm here
I'm ready to say
Wait a minute
All right
I'm ready
Hold your arms so you can rest your head on them
Okay
Now lift the legs a few inches off the ground
Oh
I don't
We survived
And beefy heels together
Could you just help yourself
And separate them about six inches
And then repeat
You want a quick and controlled
Okay
We're going for 20 seconds
Oh crap
Quick
Don't forget to breathe
Squeeze that butt
Oh yeah I I I
This move is also working your legs
Which you can help me feel
Oh kidding Amy
Oh yeah
Keep breathing
All right
Good job
It might not have been a sexier's
You can't say it
But you can't say it and give it a try
Until next time.
Oh Amy, Amy, Amy, Amy.
Thank you so much.
I thought you pulled it off quite admirably there.
Your sex kit and vibe.
See, you think that you can't pull it off, but you are so wrong.
It really comes across well.
I would encourage you to do that a little bit more.
Now, of course, I don't have to ask Amy for naked pictures,
because we have a working relationship, and I'd never ask for that.
But I've met her so many times, I guess I could imagine it.
I did receive an exciting email.
Remember, I played Caconee, Caconee for you on the show the other day,
and checked out her page on the Podsake Music Network,
and immediately requested a naked picture.
Why is it?
Why is it that no one will just really send me a real naked picture?
Yeah, it's funny.
It's like, you know, they'll send me pictures of them as a baby.
And of course, Caconee wasn't really a naked picture.
It was a photo montage of like a cartoon thing.
I mean, when I finally, seriously,
you can get a naked picture out of doing this shit.
Then we'll know that Pod casting is really derived.
Hello.
Calling all atoms.
Well, the real atom curry, please stand up.
I was my girlfriend.
Hey, Adam and I.
It's Brittany Mason.
And I've heard that you've been tutoring.
Is it true?
Is it really you?
So what does it feel like to be impersonated?
I mean, so famous that you are that someone is pretending to be you.
So have you taken over yet?
And how does it feel?
Yeah, this was pretty interesting.
I got an email from a guy named Bill.
It was some indist or non-descript Gmail email address yesterday.
Apparently, for the past, I don't know how long,
I presume longer than a week.
He's been signed up to Twitter.
This is the phenomenon.
The phenomenon phenomenon.
That exciting thing that people are talking about,
particularly in the United States,
where you send messages back and forth,
you can subscribe to someone's message stream.
And you can also do it on your cell phone.
And people are enjoying this.
I, of course, signed up for this one first came out.
I signed up not under Adam Curry,
but under one of my many online pseudonyms.
And, you know, I tried it out.
And I don't know.
I was just like, I use SMS text messaging for important stuff.
Not for stream of consciousness.
It's really important to me because when something comes in as a text message,
you know, it's someone who is approved by me,
because it actually doesn't ring or vibrate if it's an unknown,
unknown sender.
You know, I'll know that this is important for me.
And I don't want to be waiting through a whole box of messages,
and just didn't interest me.
So no problem.
It's okay.
It's not, you know, it's not for everybody.
It's just not for me.
So this guy apparently had been out there.
Twittering away as twitter.com slash Adam Curry.
So obviously it seems like it's me.
He's been doing a lot of direct messaging with with people.
I'm God knows what he's what kind of relationship he's built up.
But he emailed me and said, all right, dude.
Well, I've been faking everybody out and pretending I was you.
And here I want to hand you the keys to the car.
So he gave me the password and login.
And there were already 400 followers and say,
yeah, it was nice that he built up the audience.
But it's pretty freaky when that happens when that, you know,
I have no idea what he was saying to certain people or anybody who was
following and that's kind of freaky when that happens to be honest.
But you know, it's happened on my space.
I mean, there's lots of out of Curry my space pages and, you know,
whatever.
You know, when when when the internet climb up on granddaddies
knee here for a second, when the internet's were just beginning.
And I had MTV dot com.
There was a guy I wish I could find him.
It was friday was from I can't remember which it was from a dot
EDU address.
I really can't remember.
It was I thought I think of Midwestern University.
And he had set up a web page, which which replicated MTV dot com at the
time, which was pretty much an HTML page with a list of stuff with the
infamous infamous red bullets.
The red dot gift.
And I think we also had the green dot gift.
These were used quite widely on the internet at the time.
A very successful piece of piece of artwork.
And he had set up Madam Furries MTV dot com.
And it was the best parody I've ever seen.
And oh, since there's been nothing like it.
And I wonder if the guy is still around or if that page is still around.
I think I've looked for it on the way back machine without any success.
But, you know, it's I guess it's the sincerest form of flattery.
The imitation or even hijacking for that matter.
But you gotta be kind of careful with that shit.
Oh, I just realized that since I,
oh, second to oh boy.
Oh, this is not good.
I don't have his jingle.
You know, I had to reconfigure my whole cast blaster install so that it worked again.
So I had to actually clear everything out.
Something I've been dreading doing because I haven't loaded up with,
I don't know, like 40 different elements.
And, and I couldn't copy and paste the whole file over anyway.
Long drawn out explanation is to why there's no comic strip blaster jingle.
Hello Adam.
I see that you have a new sponsor, which is a Tylenol PM or Tylenol PM.
Tylenol PM, which is a cure to sleeplessness.
But unfortunately, I can help you here mate.
I myself can sleep under any conditions, totally any conditions.
Also, if TV and radio are switched on.
So I don't need it.
Sorry, but I reckon that some people will find it very useful.
Anyways, so on May the 4th,
I am dropping by to London in vicinity of which you'll get for the virgins located.
So maybe we could meet up there on May the 4th.
In the pot show UK office, for example.
What do you say Adam?
You don't respond to textual emails, so I thought that voice feedback would get through.
Or in it.
By the way, I hear in your latest podcasts that you have some pain, some problems, some issues.
So let me say the obvious Adam.
Be happy, Adam Kerry.
Don't you dare to worry, because when you worry, you make your travel double or something.
Your comic strip, comic strip.
Very different type of sound there, CSB.
What's going on, man?
Sounded like you were driving with the top down cruising around.
And wherever you live, Germany, I guess.
Of course, dude, we'll try and hook it up.
I'll see if I can make myself available.
I think I'm going to be in the UK in that week.
Oh, man, everything is running together.
There's so much I got to do before we leave on vacation as well.
Let me see how we do in time-wise.
Okay.
Dear Adam, says Dan Silver, my friend is running for Vice President of our law school.
And it's been informed that we can only place endorsements on flyers if they are true and with consent.
Unfortunately, you'll no longer be able to run on the motto in Dorsed by Scooter Libby.
I was hoping that you would be willing to endorse Josh Locke for Rutgers,
Camden Law School Vice President.
Josh is a phenomenal person in a huge fan of old school MTV.
He's also a fan of yours for your role in pioneering podcasting.
Yeah, nice suck up bullshit.
Josh will certainly bring a lot of enthusiasm to our school.
Please let me know if we may list you as an endorser.
I thought about this.
And I thought, you know, that may not be a bad idea to do that because it's these kinds of guys that eventually, you know,
go on to great power may even become president.
And you'll only want.
So hi, this is Adam Curry.
And I want to firmly endorse.
What's his name?
Josh Locke for Rutgers, Camden Law School Vice President.
Not only is he a huge fan of old school MTV, but he's also a phenomenal person.
And his package looks pretty good as well.
So vote for Josh.
Okay.
I'm always willing to help.
Oh, that's been saving this one all week for you guys.
This is Jessica Malat.
I'm a 17 year old pop rock singer from Maryland.
And the winner of the Los Angeles News Award for pop female singer songwriter of the year for two thousand.
The tip of the set for two is some set for you.
It's just for the moment.
In June, I'll be flying to Nashville to record my first full-length pop rock beating.
I'm so excited about it.
Make sure to check out my website.
www.jackaccommelat.com
And www.myspace.com slash Jessica Malat.
I hope you're from Houston.
Very cool.
Alright.
Let's keep it rolling on a footballer Friday with Mike Harwood.
I love it.
Yeah.
Good.
I love you.
What do you think?
Oh, yeah.
So much.
But.
Man, that's a way to close down a Charlie and finish up a week is that my car would
A little bit of moonshot on the Charlie five seven eight
It's Friday
Well, I've been talking about it all week, so of course it is almost logical that my final thought of the week has to do with the 15
Seaman and one to a 14 semen and one seed woman who were captured in
Apparently
The rock waters and held
In captivity for oh, I was like a
10 days or something like that
Anyway, so as we were talking about it as I was talking to you about it last night
Of course this morning
Yesterday morning or truck. I don't know. I wish I lived in Australia than it would then you wouldn't matter what day I said
Iran's president Maumut Maumut. I'm a dinnerjad
Released the release release the 15 British sailors and Marines and I got to tell you a particularly after and please
You really have to see this video. That is my final thought of the week for you
As you must see this video that I talked about the history of oil because when you know that history and
You know, you can burn some from history believe it or not
I didn't quite if they'd only taught me this shit in history in school. I would have been fucking interested
crap. We never talked about stuff like this. So
But it takes me to another thought of how we should teach history anyway. Let me get through this part
Disguise I
Think did a he has a brilliant move. I think that
President Ahmadina Jad deserves the Nobel Peace Prize
Because if you look at the history particularly of Britain and Iran
Forming on his Persia and
And this is a 100 more than a hundred year history
He had every reason and means and
Motivation I would say
To have this end very very differently and he's telled about big middle finger and said fuck you
You know just showing you we're nice guys. You know we don't want you we're giving you a gift oh man
I was like making you say uncle three times and you know what
We live another day without nuclear war and so I think this guy is fantastic
I'm really really really like what he did there of course
I can't say that everything Iran does is fantastic because it's not like that but then again
Look at us here in the United States what are we doing
So anyway, I see that as a major move
I'm always looking for the olive branch and when someone hands it I'll like that
I got to say props and and actually I haven't really read around the blogosphere a lot
But I think that we everyone should be giving this guy props and that it's a very good move
I don't think he was afraid of anything. He just said hey, okay just so you know
You know you guys didn't do anything we worked this off and here you're your guys back and
Let's chill out a little bit
That was my general feeling
So maybe the final thought
Is if we're gonna teach our kids history why don't we start with what's in the paper today?
Open up the paper and then work backwards and show the kids what history really is and how you can learn from it
And why things today are happening because of events that took place over the past one hundred years
Please take that into consideration and let that be your final thought of the week
So it's
DailySourceco.com Adam and podshow.com
I will talk to you Monday morning from Los Angeles Southern California right here on the Charlie
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery podshow and
Lightweight