And the Grammy for best episode of a podcast goes to.
Oh no surprise here, it's Adam Curry and the Daily Source Code 544.
The $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's Adam Curry.
Give him a sit here sir.
Keep your beauty.
Don't miss your early 544.
Not all of us can say what bullshit is made of, but we know it when we smell it.
There are many shades of grey, but any of us know when we're being left in the dark.
That's fine.
Time to call the lie lie.
If facts were faces, they'd be staring at us.
The lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie
lie lie I lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie ideals lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie trying lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lies lie lie lie lie lie lie lieheen lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lied lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lie lies lie lie lie lie lie
The rain, and the news as no analysis, it's not hard to understand.
When one side says a man, it is sandwich, and the other says the sandwich ain't the man.
That's why, time for everyone to rise.
Pick up some soap and water and to scrub away the lies.
The hard truth, the hard truth.
It's your fundamental duty.
Speak to truth, see the truth.
Like you and the light for beauty.
The hard truth, the hard truth.
Excuse me, did you hear that the whole time?
I had my mic open and you were hearing me snondering throughout the entire song.
Just noticed the mic was open during the entire song.
So you probably did hear me snorting up a wad if you couldn't tell by the nasal qualities of my voice.
Well, then you kind of understand what kind of weekend I had.
The lady Patricia just as much out and down for the count.
Excuse me.
Crap.
Luckily, it's half-term.
Midterm, half-term, half-term, I think.
So we didn't have to get a burly Christina didn't have to go to school.
And Indiana, my son-in-law, he was over for most of the weekend.
And he helped out.
And the kids were good.
So that didn't make a difference.
But when mom and dad are both sick, it really does blow major chunks.
I've been collecting stuff over the weekend.
I couldn't do much.
I was completely the third jig, too.
Actually, went for a nice walk across the road here, across from the curry matter.
The shantries that we look out upon, and that was really nice.
You know, got a little bit of oxygen, walked for a good hour or so.
And then totally collapsed in front of a bowl of Patricia's chicken soup with ginger.
I tried to watch some of the red carpet coverage from both the BAFTA awards.
That's the British Film and Television Awards.
Which seems to have more Americans than Brits winning awards as well as in the audience.
And then the Grammy Awards, which, and this was all the E red carpet coverage,
which usually is fun, but man, it's gotten down to such a machine.
You know, it's no longer the excitement of seeing the stars.
It's like, you know, this Warren Bady is scheduled to be here at 137.
And the question, and who are you wearing?
And who are you wearing?
I'd have fuck you.
I went out and bought my own shit.
Hey, hey, hey.
No, that's not true.
I'd accept all kinds of clothes and jewelry, earrings.
Send them to me.
So collecting stuff, listening to the voice mail this morning,
of course, people understand exactly how I feel and want to keep me in a good mood.
For I 42, you're fucking calm.
And you won't go to fucking calm.
You're fucking young.
And you're fucking calm.
You're fucking cold.
Hey, you go.
I'm not a fucking parmium of fucking young and a faggot.
Thank you.
I feel so much better now.
Hi, Adam.
This is Randy from Germany.
And do you want to improve your German?
Okay.
Let's give it a try.
How do you say in German to urinate sitting?
Sit in pink room.
Nah.
What?
It's not...
Sit in pink room.
Pink room.
It's...
Sit in pink room.
Pink room, but...
It's better to say...
In...
Sit in pink room.
In sit in pink room.
Okay.
Repeat.
Is it pink room or pink room?
Pink room?
In sit in pink room.
Okay, repeat.
Ready.
In sit in pink room.
Well done.
Okay.
And...
This is better than exercise.
In sit in pink room.
Ah, now seven more times.
I'm someone new-nating to think.
I have to say...
I think...
In sit in...
Ah, I...
I think...
In sit in...
Okay.
And...
Now you can see...
I think...
In sit in pink room.
Ah!
I think...
Pink room.
In sit in pink room.
So...
I think...
Okay.
Well done.
In sit in pink room.
Yeah.
In joy.
Sit in pink room.
Yeah.
In those more German lessons you can find at...
Blockcast.potcho.com.
Excellent.
I've been in sit in pink room.
Good day.
I get juice.
Grisgot.
Achtual.
So...
I've been thinking a lot lately about go daddy.
And over the years you've heard other podcasts you're saying.
Use my code and enter in it at the time of checkout and you'll get $2 off.
Dude, that's not how we roll with the jersey touch.
So tonight I'm going to get you $200 off very, very simply.
Go over to godaddy.com and get yourself 100 domain names.
Yeah.
I know you think you don't need them now.
But over the course of your lifetime I got with the...
With the internet and the way the things are going with the future and all the domain names that you're going to need.
You might as well just buy them all tonight.
I mean, you need it.
Your kids need it.
Your legacy demands that you buy yourself 100 domain names.
Well, normally that's going to cost you about $895.
But tonight, if you enter in the code jersey three at the time of checkout,
bam right there $695.
You can't beat that.
Of course, if you only want to order one domain name and who can live with just one domain name,
it's going to cost you $695 if you enter in the code jersey three at the time of checkout.
But really, when it comes down to it, when it's all about domain names,
it's all about godaddy and it's all about ordering in bulk.
JT.
S.J.T. Sergio Zetad trying to hawk his domain names through the source code.
Interesting.
You know, we could actually start a whole option business in domain names.
You know, where you don't actually have to pay, but you take an option.
So maybe you pay a tenth of the price.
So like, would be like 60 or 70 cents.
Excuse me, Fulger's coffee with Splenda makes a wonderful combination.
Those gourmet blends can't wait Friday.
I think I'm flying out to the States.
If my head isn't like a frickin' rock piece of the rock.
Hey.
Yeah, you could do a real, there could be a real option business.
You know, so just look at the godaddy.
So incredibly successful.
That thing's just like printing money.
It's unreal.
Bob Parsons, smart fucker.
Really.
I learned something very important.
Do not repeat.
Do not keep Google notebook open on multiple computers.
You know, since we moved into the manner and since,
and of course, the wireless capabilities here and I've set up the studio.
I still have about 10 or 11 boxes left.
So I'm getting there.
But I'm using the via is pretty much docked 24.7.
It's docked at the studio station.
And it also has the flight sim on it, which is the station next to it.
I just had to extend the cables.
And I've got the big Apple cinema display and the flight controls.
Next to it.
And then I'm using a secondary via.
Much less powerful one, but the same nice big keyboard keys that I like.
I'm using that at my desk, which is in the middle of the room.
Or if in the morning, I'm sitting in the big ugly green thing with my cup of tea.
Next to the heater, the fireplace.
Then I use that.
And of course, throughout the rest of the house, I've been using the Nokia N800 internet tablet with great success.
It really is perfect just for keeping tabs and having something nearby.
And there's just no reason to log anything else around.
Unless I really want to sit down and type something serious.
And then I want a full keyboard.
I don't care.
The display is also important at that point.
What the hell was I going to talk about?
What was my point?
Ah, right.
So I've been keeping my Google notebooks open on multiple computers.
And what I've noticed can happen is you can have a whole list of stuff that you've added to your notebook.
You go to the other computer.
And then you look at the notebook and it has a much shorter list than then you refresh it.
And if you close the wrong one at the wrong time, it's going to save an older copy.
So you understand what I'm saying?
Basically, these things are continuously.
I guess whenever you touch it, it writes a copy to the Google notebook server.
And if it sees a different notebook, I don't think it's just smart enough yet to understand that no,
there's a newer version.
And I want to update this one with the newer version.
At least it's not working that way.
You have to actually physically close it and reopen it.
Not doing that could result in tears.
I mean, really big tears.
So throughout the week and had some time to look around it stuff online.
You know, project plus is I think definitely come in together.
And I saw another episode of the Brittany Mason show Brittany Mason.
My girlfriend from second life and I haven't seen her in about a year.
But she's not doing a show, which and for the first time,
if you've seen her in second life, maybe at the pod show island,
you know, she doesn't really have a voice.
Doesn't talk there.
But you can hear talking in this show.
And it's what does it review from the grid or something like that?
Which is kind of cool.
You should check that out Brittany Mason show dot pod show dot com.
And thank you to several people who inquired if I was okay.
Because a small aircraft, private aircraft.
In this case, it was a paper.
I think it was a four-seater.
A crashed in a crashed in France.
American father mother and child on board.
And people were very were even though they knew that it probably wasn't me.
And I get this a lot when something crashes anywhere in the.
On the western side of the continent or anywhere on the eastern side of the island.
I get, I get a lot of those calls and emails.
Thank you very much for being concerned.
It really sucks for those people.
I have no idea what happened.
And we had another paper air crash just last week.
Also, I think off the, was it the southern coast, south western coast of England?
Man, those things are just like falling out of the sky.
I don't want to say too much about, you know, about papers.
But I would like to know what's happening.
With thousands of songs in all genres, the pot safe music network is the best place
to find truly pot safe music for your show.
If you're a band or musician looking to expose your music to a worldwide audience,
then look no further than the pot safe music network.
Showcase your music and let thousands of podcasters help market your songs
and the best part, it's all free.
Visit music.potshow.com and create your free profile.
If you're a musician or a band upload your music, if you're a podcaster, then download.
The pot safe music network is easy to use, but the huge variety of music
find upcoming unsigned bands or music from the hottest in your major labels.
Don't get burned by copyright infringement and don't get left behind by the new media.
Play, play, play, play, play, play.
The pot safe music network, music.potshow.com.
Yeah, I like that.
With that, I'll send that to me home on Instagram.
I'm using pot safe.
Here I am just doing a Google Gmail search,
love it.
Pot safe commercial is what I type in.
Gmail goes to work comes back and gives me a couple of options.
Yes, no.
No, that wasn't it.
It came up with the, came up with the Jeff Smith.
Crap.
We got to send that to me.
Well, I like it anyway.
It's a good idea to have a commercial for the pot set music network,
which reminds me I completely forgot to tell you that the first song today was Jim's
Big ego.
Pot safe music network veteran with support the truth.
And I like that a lot because, you know, it sounds like support the troops,
but it's saying something else.
And it's a, you know, I like it.
I like it when stuff is right on the money when it comes to music.
When the lyrics, you know, can, can really hit home.
And we can do these things so quickly now.
They don't have to wait half, you know, half a year to release.
You're politically motivated song through some arcane channel.
Pretty interesting.
I, although, of course, I didn't see the Grammy Awards because I don't think they were even
being carried live last night, but it would have been too late anyway.
Dixie chick's big winners, five Grammys.
Ah, boy.
How we swing from one side to the, to the other.
You know what, they deserve such a big apology.
And I bet you there's a lot of people there who, who, who, who, who, who are now cheering
them.
That hypocrites.
Hi.
I'm, uh, Schema, sorry.
Had enough semesters.
You mentioned on the NC 540.
And again, that the, uh, the comments.
Congratulations.
You know, the I'm the charger for Nokia.
You know, it, it, it, it's taken me two years, but I can actually
understand what the guy is saying.
I miss pronounce his name.
And it's actually Schema's, not Schema's, but Schema's.
And there's your age, age problem entering again.
And he's, and he's talking about the ant dick plug for all new Nokia devices.
Just setting up, yanks.
And not only people miss a nice, my name, not a problem.
But it's a links to the, the, the heaps versus each of the
questions you've been having.
Because my name is Stelk.
As if it should be when I'd seen this.
But it's, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the Schema's.
He knew the, uh, the Schema's still there with him.
What, um, the other thing regarding it's ant hits, uh, is an interesting, uh,
thing, I'm from Northern Ireland, and not part of the world.
Heaps versus each is an example of what's called a cible, which is, uh,
where a pronunciation of a word or a letter shows a membership of a social
or ethnic group.
And the case of, uh, the North of Ireland, uh,
say it's, and traffic's a hitch, uh, to big data, not part of the world,
unfortunately, but, uh, a shouldn't be, um, just as you'd like to hear this,
as I know you have your lucky charms.
I'm scared.
And the sides of Ireland, uh,'re, uh, luck email like to hear some of the
road listeners from North as well.
I like you, uh, like he charms.
And keep up with charge, uh, my, uh,
Ian Folger.
Of course you're not a scruncher, not a folder, but a
But a fulger.
Yeah.
Bless me like he's like a chams.
I'm like he stars me like he chams.
Good to have your board.
Of course, there's people of North listening.
I'm amazed at how many people from the UK are now
turning into the show.
I look at the stats the other day.
I'm like, wow, that's, as probably about almost 30%
of the audience is real.
And it's not just the UK.
It's also further east in Europe.
You know, I had a, this is Matthias calling in from Bonn in Germany.
I just wanted to tell you how much I like putster.com.
I just found a thing that you stopped me a little.
Being that when you set up a new putster, you could select default messages
either messages, languages, either an English or Spanish.
Now, I don't want you to translate the whole thing in German,
but it would be cool if you could select your putster's German.
Now, that's all for now.
Thank you.
Bye.
That's photo.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah, I don't care.
Thomas, that's interesting.
I'll, you know, engineering listens to the show.
So I know that they're going to check it out.
It doesn't make a lot of sense.
That's it.
There would only be two types of languages that you can produce shows in being English
and Spanish.
I believe that those tags are meant solely for metadata information.
They probably are of some influence on the iTunes.
You know, we add all of the iTunes tags and the category stuff.
And they have their whole incredible namespace that you have to add in to your RSS feeds.
If you want to get proper ranking and search results within iTunes, it should have any
multitude of languages.
Those are basically abbreviations.
The list should be no different from a list of states in the United States.
It's a pre-populated list.
So I'll check out it for sure.
In the meantime, if you select English, it's not going to do anything.
It won't hurt anything.
That's for sure.
And you can always go back and change it, so I'll look into it for you.
I was so disappointed.
John Glasscox sent me a note that the Ignation Boys, Alex and Kevin, they did the most
recent show on board Virgin Atlantic US Airbus A320, which of course, you know, the airline
isn't flying yet, you know, Virgin US or Virgin America or everything going to call it.
But it seems like they have some kind of sponsorship with Ignation.
Oh, I'm really hurt.
I'm really am.
I can't believe it.
It doesn't, well, you know, I think they're going to do their first show on board.
I don't know.
I have no idea what it is, but for some reason, they're on board the Virgin plane, and
I'm not.
And I got to tell you, you can stake your stinking red eye pot and shove it with a son-done
shine, Mr. Virgin CEO, you know, come on.
I want the Daily Source Code listeners to have a shot at having a party on board of your
A320.
Well, we'll make a party out of it all right, but come on, the Ignation guy is going to be
a break.
Hey, Adam, it's a look speaking, just landed here at the Amsterdam Airport of my way to
Barcelona, you know, the 3GSM madness.
That's just a question for you, just wondering if you haven't been out of everybody
knows what is the longest podcast ever, or let's say the longest regular podcast.
I'm subscribed to the Silhobit.com podcast, and they have started now with a weekly show of
two and a half hours of progressive rock, which is kind of brutal to listen to, of course,
two and a half hours of podcasting.
Anyway, I just thought it might be serious to know what's the longest podcast ever.
Thanks, Mike.
All right, there's Luke Montezway to the 3GSM conference.
Watch out for comics for blogger.
He's looking right behind your back.
It seems to be a pretty big deal.
I was reading in the newspaper over the weekend that was at 60,000 attendees or something
for this conference.
That's pretty major.
Of course, this is where everyone rolls out their vision for the future, not
of it compatible with anyone else's vision coincidentally.
The longest podcast, I don't know, you'd probably have to look at music podcasts, and
are you talking about longest episode, or if you put all the daily source codes back
to back, you'd have one pretty big, I wonder.
Could you fit it on an iPod?
Let me see.
Average was probably an average of 25 megabytes, okay, hold on, let's do this now.
I could give away daily source code, I filled iPods.
That's a cool idea.
Hold on.
Let me just pull up the calculator here, I have my brain associated.
So it's 25 million, 3456 times 544 is 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Is it 1,000?
No, hold on, how many zeros I have, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
So that would be 13,000, 13,000 megabytes is 13 gigs.
No, you couldn't actually fit it on to one iPod, is there, no, no, of course you could.
One of my saying, there's iPods with much more than 3.
You couldn't fit it on the new iPhone though.
Speaking of phones.
Did you find yourself singin' along with that at any point?
It took me two plays when listening to one of the voicemail before it hit me, I, yes, I know
what that is.
4, 4, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
By the way, that also works for all you serious satellite radio listeners out there listening
to serious channel 102, you're probably in the States if you are, so use this number.
I remember the plus is for extra savings and if you travel outside of the continental
US with your mobile phone.
Okay, they're gone.
Let's see, I have like two more voicemail messages I want to go through and then a beautiful
song that I found on the part that actually was one of the top ten played songs last
week.
No yesterday, I'm sorry, the part that music network, some classical stuff which I think
you're like.
I'm just picking on some, I'm not even telling you, I'm wrong and stop the comment
if you want to.
I'm not going to pick up on this yet.
I sometimes just know this from here, listen to the DSC and this point of people probably
pay for anything.
Whenever tampons or anything to do with menstrual cycles mentioned, you're seen to
have all the bleep fringe and sooner this system wrong, that doesn't.
Well, it's only been you, I think, has been calling in with men.
Well, you know what, it's just because I can already imagine the met and I know what
mess people can make when it comes to sanitary napkins and tampons, I'm sorry, I'm just
not interested in sharing that with the audience.
But I think I understand where you're coming from, let's listen to the DSC.
I'm not sure if my go through a problem with my daughter or my daughter, then somebody
previous in our life was like that and she's only to stop around the fact that it's
quite normal to be right at home and probably should be celebrated.
Yeah, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a very fair point James.
No, and Christina has already gone through her initial stages.
And no, we celebrated it too, that's like a, it's like a big moment to sing in life.
Even though she was really fucking grouchy when we were celebrating.
But no, no, no, no, no, no.
None of that at home.
This is just purely because I don't, well, I don't think people are interested in hearing
about it.
They get the picture, I guess, is what I'm saying.
Anyway, that's the season, you know, you, you see my mind, see the ceremony chair and
cringe when you heard it.
The other things, I'm not, what a completely idea.
And you mentioned on Trinity, win valuable prizes.
But I'm a bit baffled as to why I put your reports to see the win valuable prizes.
The last thing I ever heard of anybody winning from Portugal on the daily source call
was an iPod and that was quite a while back.
You know, I won a free iPod.com or whatever.
And I'm just wondering, you know, let us know what valuable prizes, what come people
win if the part taken this, if they're going to win Trinity, you know, if they're going to win
that jump from a bio deal, if they're going to win the party.
I don't know.
Oh, James, no, no, no, no, no, you're so confused.
The whole point is save the world win valuable prizes.
And you save the world.
Don't you think there'll be some very valuable prizes that will win James, like life?
Oh, look at for free fucking iPod.
Alright.
So another, another new friend of the show who's been around for a while.
And he sent in so many audio comments, but I've played relatively few because he's so difficult
to understand, prolific programmer.
Dude, I think you've really got, I think you've got your shit down.
All over the free Trinity Google Group with posting code that he says will work on the
on the Nokia N800.
And I think the guy might actually have his chops down.
I'm just waiting, you know, because a couple other people in the list who are involved
in the conversation.
If you're of tin foil hat nature, you may want to go and check it out.
And I was bitching about my Gmail space that, you know, for the past year, I've been
just at 99% on my four gigabytes of storage, which, of course, is a special deal.
Everybody else is about 2.8 now, but I get a, you know, friends and family could get more.
But it's still not enough.
And I'm willing to pay for it.
Just tell me, can I get enough to keep me going?
You know, I'm sure I'll be up to 10 gigs by the end of the year.
If I actually were to save every single attachment that came my way.
But I'm willing to pay for it, not a problem.
You know, so, of course, I get no response, you know.
But I do get some suggestion from that very same prolific programmer.
But father, this is the prolific programmer from San Francisco, also in the sun.
I was listening to your show, DSC 543, and you were iranting about Gmail for about
the 100th time or something about Gmail having free space.
I have come up with the solution.
I personally, you know, what you think is at prolificprogrammer.com.
Ask the LOG and the, and the, and the,
think it, and this is how to achieve limitless stimuli today.
Let me know what you think.
Either by person to comment or on your podcast.
We'll be listening.
Cheers.
All right.
Guy almost needs a jingle.
I'm just going to prolificprogrammer.com slash blog.
Here it is.
Was listening to Adam rant about not having enough Gmail storage space and realize it
come up with a scheme to solve his problem.
Okay.
He noted in a previous episode that he wouldn't mind paying Google for the space.
But Adam, do you mind paying Amazon?
Well, no, how about how is Amazon going to give me more Gmail space?
Because S3 advertisers write, read, and delete objects containing from one to five gigabytes of data each.
The number of objects you can store is unlimited.
In other words, since
Charis is Gmail account.
Huh?
Who's Charis?
Whatever.
Holds 2,815 megabytes or 2.8 gigs.
You can back up your whole Gmail archive for less than 25 pens.
First we need to retrieve message messages and serialize this list.
Then divide this into five gigabytes blocks and put them on S3.
Then go back to Gmail and delete them.
Presto more space on Gmail.
Yeah.
But prolific programmer.
The whole point of having that in Gmail is so that I can search through it.
That's the power of Gmail.
Besides there's short cut key commands.
You know, the J and K and the H and J and K, essentially.
And oh, which, you know, I'm used to being an old command line guy.
And just old in general.
You know, the whole point is having the search.
So if you can figure out a way to do that and have it search across Amazon's S3.
Shit, yeah.
I mean, I'll pay you to implement for me.
Hi, Adam.
This is Mal and Amsterdam.
I run the segue to this here.
My company's name and URL is a glide.cc.
We were in contact by email back in 2005.
When I set up my segue towards operation here.
And I had to react to your comment on Friday.
How it's impossible to make it.
There's an entrepreneur in the Netherlands.
Because the state has recently put me out of business.
Oh, surprise there.
This is a guy who I spoke to when I was creating.
I still have the segue, by the way.
It's got two flat tires or empty tires.
I don't think they're punctured.
I got to pump it up.
And we could mess around with it here.
This is when I was big into the segue.
I thought it was, you know, cool.
Obviously brought one over from the states.
And so this guy started a business segue towards very much like my body
Mike has done in Miami.
Where, you know, you can tour around the city.
Amsterdam was perfect for this.
But of course, you know, you have such a left wing government,
which actually we don't even have a government yet.
I don't think they're.
But the mayor Amsterdam is without a doubt left wing.
They're going to outlaw that shit.
No fun anymore.
I don't know if you heard that the Dutch police made writing segues anywhere.
On public roads or sidewalks illegal as are the beginning of the year.
This after almost two years when they were allowed.
How full bar is that?
Yeah.
We've been working under agreements made with local offices in the city.
And those whole two years and we had no problems at all with safety.
No accidents, no incidents.
I think you know how safe these machines are once you're trained to ride them.
If there's some bureaucratic thing, please.
It's decided that come the new year.
They would be illegal again.
Well, dude, it wasn't the police.
They're only supposed to enforce it.
The police are making that shit up.
Then you're in real trouble.
But I don't think that's it.
I think it's the local municipality has made that decision.
It could have been a national thing.
You'd have to look into it.
You really should because if the police are making that shit up,
I don't think they have the right to.
Maddie investment in sales made by the local Dutch seguid distributors.
No matter my own investment in setting up and running tours.
I don't even know if you're going to accuse me of trying to grab some promo gear off the Charlie.
That is for my segue tours in Amsterdam day and evening.
My company website at the URL galid.cc.
Since as I said, the law here is set me down.
Although I assume that this ban will be overturned sooner or later.
I realize you've had your own encounters with the Dutch authorities while trying to
innovate projects.
So if you have any tips on what to do or who to contact solve this thing,
I'd be grateful to get them.
Yeah.
All the guys I know got kicked out.
Mark from the horse.
Other people left.
Yeah.
So I don't think I can help you there anymore.
Amsterdam is going completely left wing.
They're also, they decided against privatizing civil airport,
which is about economically speaking.
The stupidest thing you can do.
Oh, man.
Watch Frank for a grow like an MF now.
Yeah.
It's a hub.
You've got to be able to expand.
Yeah.
It sucks if you live under the flight path.
But you know, you knew you were living under the flight path.
You knew it could get busier.
No, dude.
I don't think I feel bad for it.
But I don't think there's going to be any overturning of that ruling.
Don't we sell the same thing?
Remember those zapies, the electric scooters, same thing?
Yeah.
Maybe you should convert to bikes.
It's about the only thing I can think of for you.
And when segues do become legal again here, whenever that is.
I'd be pleased to take you in the ladies around on my slate of machines.
Maybe along with one of my safety assistance.
So keep that in mind that we don't usually go pick up our customers.
But we have done that before in front of the Amstel Hotel.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that was not for making teeth in the boys.
But anyway, I'd be glad to do that again for you.
Or you say you're too busy even to have dinner with somebody.
Okay.
Then maybe just to write around with the ladies and maybe with your son-in-law.
Just get in touch through our website.
That's your glide.cc.
And flipper.
Yeah.
With my son-in-law indeed.
That's what I need, dude.
I need pictures of me and my extended family riding around on segues and Amsterdam.
Yeah.
That's really, that's keeping a low profile.
Don't you think?
All right.
Who knows what the rest of the week is going to bring us?
Hopefully a little bit better health.
I hope you're feeling okay.
It seems that I, you know, first I got the US variant of this flu.
I got through that, which involved a lot of coughing.
And now I have the UK variant.
I guess either I never really fully recovered.
Was too weak or there's just no way you can resist both strains of it.
Whatever it is, it sucks.
So I'm going to leave you with a beautiful piece of music that I found from the
cello journey podcast.
I should say the cello journey podcast.
That's cello with a h.
Without the h.
A preserves.
My God, be out for.
Thank you.
That too was available at the pod save music network.
Go to podshow.com slash music.
Check it out.
That's nice, isn't it?
I love the cello.
It's a beautiful instrument.
Sounds so nice.
And it kind of fits the.
The mode that my head is in for today.
So I hope you didn't mind.
Okay, everybody.
Remember to go visit the Trinity Google group at groups.google.com slash group slash free
Trinity daily source code dot com for all the show notes on today's podcast.
Send me something at the adam at podshow.com.
Take care, everybody.
I'll talk you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.