This is Chef Mark from Remarkable Palette and Jennifer from Food Philosophy.
We've got the perfect recipe for seasoning your pocho experience to perfection.
Start with a network full of informative content and talented podcasters.
Add a heaping tablespoon of great listeners who can make the experience even better with their feedback.
Perhaps your dashboard isn't mashing or you're having trouble locating that fantastic podsafe song you heard.
Pocho wants to know how you want your entertainment served.
Just head on over to survey.pocho.com and register to add your own spice to the dish.
And we like it spicy.
Hello Adam, this is contractura.
As you would podge or seek to suck less, I want to assure your listeners on the DSC 618 that I can't drag you if I want to suck more.
The thirst for blood has never been any better.
Excuse me why I step out for a bite.
And there really is such a brilliant thing.
You can feel my heart breath passing by the stairs.
When I'm asleep, there's layers on the floor.
And suddenly you can hear us.
I think it's, I think the quality is just too good.
I don't want to be on TV anymore.
I was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I don't want to be on TV anymore.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
I'm testing this Adam Curry.
When you go to my room,
I've got to stay on my way down.
You're stuck in the sky.
You're put to smile.
When you go to my room,
I've got to stay out with you.
You're put to smile.
When you go to my room,
I've got to stay out with you.
You're put to smile.
When you go to my room,
When you go to your room,
You're put to smile.
When you go to my room,
You're put to smiled.
You're put to smile.
When you go to my room,
Oh, that was kind of a wrap it in there. Yes, if you want to grab that mash up for free
Just to go check out the show knows daily source code calm. Hey, it's episode 618 a daily source code
I'm back from Los Angeles. It was very early to rise this morning up at 5 o'clock for a 720 amp flight
Boy, do I miss the Delta Sierra on days like this, huh?
Although it's it's never really good to have to fly yourself when you're going to do business because then you can make stupid decisions
Uh, so the, you know, as I do in the morning up and at him
And let's just do a quick I always do a quick check of email on my phone in bed
And the first email I got is from good old PW Fenton who said well, I'm sure you're already aware of this but
A curry dot com has expired and so there's a couple of ugly secrets that of course immediately are exposed
I'm one of those lazy bastards, you know, I still haven't fixed my not completely fixed my email problem at curry dot com
Well, so so to have I not transferred curry dot com to a go daddy
So extra egg on my face this morning
Luckily I was able to renew it's funny because it's like it was it was bound to happen because you know the email
This is one of these domains I registered for 10 years, you know, so you know you forget about that stuff
Curry dot com of course it had it a long time and
You know, I'm sure that they were sending emails to me saying I do it is about the expire along with a couple of other choice domains
I might add
But of course I wasn't getting that email the curry dot com email and ask just one bad loop
What else did I renew but dot org refer dot net? Yes, all kinds of a wonderful domains
I want to hold on to and I don't want to have expire under my very nose
Hey, it got a lot of stuff to go through with you today
Just so many calls that came in and so many fun things and I mean just prepping for the show today
I was laughing my ass off and you know, what do you expect when you've got like
Comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip
How did it all add on your aggregation of podcast feeds into channels would be more useful if
Users would be able to slice podcasts and gather pieces of podcasts too
CSB cutting right to the bone man. I got a lot of feedback on the on the DSC channel that I created
I'll put the link into these show notes once again
So you just click on it and it'll open up your iTunes and automatically bring in everything that is intended to come in
It's kind of a test, but it's also me showing off something that's coming very soon in something
You can start playing with today already and you must have gotten 15 different emails
People who are you know, lights are going off in their heads about about how powerful this really is
And how cool it's going to be and how cool it is today when you can actually use some of that stuff
And CSB yeah, you know, so besides being able to create a channel which of course you can put on your iPod or anything else that understands RSS
Those of you who give a shit
You can also put on your Apple TV let's put it that way anything that you think up with iTunes, I guess so including your iPhone
And you can also do single episodes this more that you can do, but I'm just going to keep it with shows and episodes at this particular point
So what CSB is saying is very much like our search if you search for anything
It'll not only bring up shows with the relevant to what your search term but also episodes that have something relevant in there
So you know we're already parsing a lot of that and we're already looking at show notes and obviously it would be just a small step
Although I'm sure an engineering nightmare, but a small step to integrate an engine that understands that so good point to CSB but baby steps first
And not just whole episodes, you know such channels with user-defined podcast clips
Regarding the work I don't agree with nylon and I recognize that he's a very able addition to pod show after all it was me myself or I who suggested
In co-coff between myself and Marcus Shemotonium Coff that pod show needs tech podcasts by the way everybody, please check podfinderuk.pot show.com
Where boobly issues just a thin Lawrence was talking about myself in episode number 13 and Adam Kerry please stop masturbating to keynotes of Steve Jobs
Good say
CSB
Yeah, man, it's so good when you send something in you just never you never disappoint my friend
I
Speaking of masturbating, Steve Jobs
Keynote, hold on a second
I got a great email
And I have to go and find that it was someone told his wife, okay, I'll tell the story
So he was telling his wife about I'm sure I had that email somewhere
You know about how geeky I was talking about stuff including the sound of the Commodore VIC-20 computer program
Well, okay, I seem to have misplaced the email
I don't understand that let me check one more time, do you mind?
Like you you can always just fast forward until a crap anyway
So it was wife calls in on the or leaves an I think he sent an audio comment
And that she sounds really hot
Take away the Jaguar
Leave behind your precious Cessna 182 RG
Strip away your trinkets of fame and fortune
VIC-20, Nokia E61 I
Crackberry
Let go of your big hair Adam
Tape up the bridge of those rose colored glasses and admit it
Come on Adam
I admit it
You're a fucking key
I found it
Share her name is Barbara
Darren Wall's wife
Oh dude
Send a picture next time
Don't you guys understand
So
I don't know which one to play first
You know so there's something that's starting to happen now with in pod show
That I'm really liking and I wish more people in pod show would do it
Guys and gals who work at the company
I'm now calling into the show and talking about you know whatever they're doing
And whatever they're working on
And so we've got this new guy Adam
Who we call A to the B so we don't confuse it with A to the C
And he came in and he fell in like second week
He was in charge of the the the super panel
This is the the suck less zone
Which I'm sure you've heard a lot about
And so he's basically it's his job to track this
Make sure the campaign is running
And it's a pretty big one and and it's pretty intense as you can imagine
Particularly just because of the the massive sweep of that word that we spread out to kick this off
And now it's really up to the the members of the network
To really make this work if you will
And so here's A to the B with a
Haha
Dude you're gonna get ripped or shreds
I'm warning you now
Erie is with a status report
And now on to the quick cyclist update
So one feedback's awesome
The the stuff that's written the stuff that's filled out in the survey
It's fantastic
We're measuring the ever living stuff out of this thing
Ever living crap out of it
We add it to new measurements the other day
And it's very interesting
I am basically just so jazzed about what we're learning
And I can't wait to talk to some of our podcasters about it
Update number three
We got it over a dozen audio. Do you have some place now
And then point four we got the video and audio
Who's the worst ones kicking in
So that's it for the suck less update
Alright A C more single less noise man
This is A to B
I'm out broke
Alright buddy
I made him send it back I send it back him three times and said dude
I'm not gonna play your three minute update
Even I don't care that much
So you know what next time you call in
Adam
Please give us some information
To be a what have you learned
What is so interesting I want to know you got to tell me
Hi Adam
It's Jamie here from Birmingham
I've been for a lot of listening to the past couple of days
About the also testing
I've been catching up on my podcast for I've been away
And I didn't really think much about it all actually
To be honest
But I was just watching texture
And I've just seen the video version of the
Cirquef advert
And you know I'm a man I'm quite even slayed
But oh my god how foxy
This sock of your look
And because of that
As soon as I'm getting into work
I'm putting out a questionnaire man
See if it's a good work
I know I love the video version
The video version is it's it's awesome
Excuse me
Sorry to me to do that in your ear
And I'll get that
One little wet spot out
Yeah
We were in Los Angeles today
And soccer girl came up actually
You know and I can't tell you exactly what we're doing
But obviously no damn announcements
You're here about it
It could be extremely cool if everything works out
But you know so it's a meeting
And there's some you know some folks there
And some of them had suits on
And you know and that was this
And then I'll send the somehow that it's typical Hollywood right
The and by the way my computer was hooked up to a huge LCD
I used plasma screen and that really good sound in this room
So you know from time to time as we were talking
I was showing different things
From the network and playing different audio
Drops and bits like that
And so you know someone said well you know
But I was talking about
Lonely girl 15
And yeah they're coming out with that
What did they call it
I was like deep product integration
Yeah so I lonely girl 15 with deep product integration
I mean like host endorsements that they're covering up
Unlike where we're just saying it
And then I and then I I had
The the soccer girl episode
Where she's in the burka which by the way
Is one of the best pieces of work I've ever seen soccer girl do
And just to back that up I'm going to put that
Into the daily source code channel feed
After I'm done with the show
So you can see that that particular episode
It's awesome and it really is
I already love soccer girl
But when I saw that you know that's that is raw talent
And I popped that up man with the burka
Cause it starts off really funny and then it gets real serious
And then just like rip your heart out
Um and I said this
Is the real lonely girl
Then the new one improved
She's called soccer girl dude
Okay
Fuck lonely girl
It's fake this is soccer girl
She's an actress she's an author
She's a hot librarian
She's soccer girl
This is Mike one half of the kids wife work live show
I am thrilled to be part of the wave of new media
And I am doing my best to make it better with every episode of kids wife work life
Unfortunately I can't do it alone
I need your help
Please take a moment to go to superpanel.podshow.com
And join the pod show super panel
This is your chance to let us know what you think
And it will help to make the world of new media a better place
Awesome dude
Thank you
Hey you've got a new sponsor
For the UK
Now of course I have a
World audience
But there is a lot of people in the UK listening
And it's kind of interesting
This is kind of a traditional way of promoting something
But what the heck
It's not too bothersome I don't think
This summer when you buy coke
You get music
You can win an iPod
Or free songs or nightchains
Right on
Oh man
That's our way to make a living
Isn't it?
Guys think to say we got a couple of phone lines
You can call here's the UK number
And the rest is on the site
Plus 4 4
To 0 7
6 8 1
3 7 5 3
Plus 4 4
To 0 7
6 8 1
3 7 5 3
Hey Adam this is your seat mate from
Why is that already morning?
Just a blue flight set
He's 25
Echo
That's a middle seat
Last row just to refresh your neck
This ladies and gentlemen is
Greg Mann
The original sales weasel
Sales weasel
Oh gee
That's right
We flew back together on JetBlue
Right you know right next to the
A durable gurgling baby and mother
You answered your favorite sales
Dad Greg
Oh you were totally hitting on
You were totally hitting on the on the on the mom
And you're and she was breastfeeding next to us
And I saw you looking
And I saw
Dude
Actually we didn't discuss that part
Did we?
Anyway I was calling to comment on
DSC 616
I know a couple days behind
But you were talking about the great fun
We had in watching Mark Goodman
Those VH1's best road trips
Songs
Just a jogging refresh your memory here
The absolute travesty of the entire thing
Was it number 20 out of the top 20
Was the Eagles hotel
Yeah
Yes
Oh I'm so glad you called him
When this couldn't remember when I was telling the story
We talked about the fact that it was number 20
For the next 10 songs
And even a bigger travesty
Was that number 1
Was Sammy Haguears
I can't drive 55
Absolutely ridiculous
Yeah
I hope you will give me proper credit
However with by predicting
At the song number 19
That boosts trainsteens
Born to run would be in the top 5
And it's in fact
Good come in at number 3
Anyway just wanted to give you a
Heads up on that
To refresh your memory
It's off for me
It's off and back to work to pay the bills
Thanks Adam
You can tell he was in radio
Can't you?
Hey Greg man
Tell me what you're doing
What are you working on?
It's just us
Yeah what like the some secret intelligence
You can't tell anyone
How do you pay the bills?
I wouldn't mind sharing that
You might even be elevated to savants
Status my friend
Chris from plainmadness.com
By the way Chris
I love your show
It's an awesome awesome show
You could turn down the radio
A little bit in the background
Because it's sometimes
Just you know
Particularly as a pilot
I'm sorry
Scratch that
As an airman
You know I'm tuned into listening to what's being said on the radio
I find myself listening through you
To what is going on in the background
So maybe just turn down a little bit
I said hey I click the link
iTunes brought up the link in the podcast
We know low to the data
Change the link to a channel name
And down came the shows
Pretty cool I must say
Everything works fine for me so far
What's interesting
He says I speculate that
Potio now also becomes a library
Data of sorts
That we can export to iTunes if we wish
Why yes
You can do that today
Did you know that?
But then you do lose the control over it
From you know the
You lose control over creating the channels
That's what's so cool about what we're doing with these channels
In fact
For those of you who've been following along
You know
Or for those of you who are new to this story
Let me put it that way
I go to dailysourcecode.com
You'll see a link for the DSC channel
Just click it
If you have items on your computer
I'll also put a traditional RSS feed in there for the more adventurous
Just click it if you have iTunes
Or if you have an iPod then presumably you also have iTunes
It'll open up
It'll open up this channel
And it'll start to download
I do a video intro for the channel
So it's almost like
Gosh
I stop smoking
And I got all this flowing my throat
So it's a different way of distributing
Serialized content
I guess
But it's really fun
Because I can put stuff in that
Updates automatically
I can put a show in there
Just a single episode
Now here's something
If you've been playing around this for a day or two
Try this
So first
Oh man
Maybe I should just say
If you want to try this
Here's how you do it
If you register for pod show
You automatically have a channel
Go into search for any term
Find a show
Click on the show
It'll take you to the unofficial show guide page
And from there
Find an episode
Not the show
Just find an episode
And click on get it
And then put it into your channel
Which will be the name of your login
Whatever your user name is
Now then go to something called my collection
And this is all the shit
We're going to simplify
We're very close to having this right
And what you see on the side is
Fucked up and wrong
But it's going to be awesome
Go to your collection
And you'll see your channel there
And click on it because you want to
Modify something
And you'll see that you can have it
Play in the mashboard or iTunes
Or it has different players
Or even the raw XML
Just select iTunes
Save it
And then go to the play button
On that channel
Don't click it
But right click it
And copy that link
Okay
That is the link that anyone can use
You send that link to anybody
And email
They click on it
And iTunes will open up
And then whatever you have collected in that channel
Shows or episodes
We'll go to their iPod
Now here's the advanced fund
For people who've been doing this a day or two
And God, it's so hard to explain
It's almost like Tevo
You can't really explain it
Take the link of your channel
Would I just explain how you do that
You want to get the raw XML link
Okay
And import that
As a show
Okay
You just say add show
You can do it in the same channel even if you want
Which makes it a real mind trip
Once it's imported
You'll see the show is right there
The same icon will be there
That you put in the original channel
Click on it
You'll now have your channel
We'll now have an unofficial guide page
That people can comment on
So that of course is not the way that this is supposed to work
But that is going to be the type of functionality
Where people can comment on your channel
And your channel actually becomes like a show
I love this
I'm not doing a great job really
I'm explaining it yet
You just have to kind of do it
Christian Teberg says
Just a quick reminder
My pod breeze app
Pod breeze dot wordpress dot com
For the data side
Can import your pod show channels
And subscribe to them
For those of us who don't want to use items
Awesome
This is what's a nice about it
It all just kind of all works together
Oh man
When we get this channel stuff pushed out
It's going to be awesome
Let me see
Was there anything else that I had
In my Gmail
Oh no
But we do have another sabond coming your way
Not a big program
Hi Adam
Hello
I'm Jessica
This is the SC617
With the guarding me nine long comments
Nylon
Um
I'm ready to take up free training
Wherever you are my friends
So let me know
I know you can I can count on you prolific program
I know when we're ready for training
You'll be ready by the way
Big meeting
Sales with a Greg
In New York
Thursday
On it
Um
Regarding the
Sexless
Me
With very simply practicing at this point
Um
Yes, the meme
There is a set in law that says
There is a
Container
Suckiness
Suckness in the world
Oh
Oh, I didn't hear
Suckiness
Suckness in the woods
There is a
Container
Suckiness
Okay, I got it
There is a law that there is a certain amount of
Suckiness in the world is that it
There is a Container
Suckiness
Suckness in the world
So I guess cultural ones
As podcasts
Suck as opposed to you
And I refer it this way
Anyway
Here's what
Help me to say
Right
I don't want anyone to suck more
I want us to suck less
What did you say at the end there?
Anyway
Anyway, here's
Up to me here soon
Right
Okay, cheers
Talk to you soon
Ha ha ha
The prolific program everybody
Whoa
He's an island
Outspoken expatriate
What can we do?
Whoa
He's an island
Controversely an island
But he's from New York
Toooo
Hey, I haven't missed the nylon
I've just finished taking three Tylenol PMs
I think it's actually been like me
That was devastating
But the Tylenol does work
I don't even know
Sorry
At least the heartache is gone
I like you
I just disagree
I can believe
Did I say I hate you?
I guess I did say I hate you
But I love you that you call in
I love you that you have a different opinion
So please don't let that stop you from calling in
And as long as
I shoot man
I mean already you've stolen my heart today
You're pimpin' out Tylenol PM for me
I want to come back to the John DeForex thing
And again, I have nothing to just John
He's well respected
More accomplished and famous than I'll ever be
Yeah, so far we got like two savons again
She men
We got the prolific programmer
He's against you
And comics are blogger
And he's pretty much against everything I do
to start with
I thought YouTube would have agreed on this
So you're in the minority
My friend is better be good
My organization of point of view
It seems like this is a guy who you have to pull
Screaming and dragging to promote potential
So my last couple of data points
One, not much hype on cranky deeks
Two and even though you reference the press release
The corporate thing
Not a very good one
How many press releases have you seen
Where the last paragraph says a quote
You know, so you're not even a quote from John
Saying along the typical things of
I'm so happy to be associated with part show
It's a leading company and I'm so glad
No, that's bullshit
That's bullshit now
Our bullshit's much better than that
What press release were you reading?
Hold on a second
I had it here somewhere
Uh
Crap
Here it is
Partial press room
One
Open this up
Hot these lenses
I gotta get rid of these lenses
Why is it
Oh man, Google notebook
It doesn't quite cut it
Does it?
Okay, here it is
There's a quote from John C.
Dvorak here
Um
Technology has given us this massive
Distribution medium
He had our approach to producing
Technology content has been in the same old
Productible style
Comments Dvorak
I work with pod shows new channel format
We can combine entertainment and insight
And take the concept of integrated programming
To an entirely new level
If that doesn't say pod show fucking rocks
I don't know what
So though the hype
You think of these telecolt from John
So all I'm saying is that for a guy who's a VP
Imagine editor of your organization
It seems like he reluctantly talks about it
And very rarely
So
Yeah, but dude, you know
You're talking about other people's media properties
It's just not appropriate
He doesn't own cranky geeks
He is a hired gun
It's not his show
He doesn't own twit
It's just not appropriate
Okay
Don't worry
You know, he's working right now
He's not on the pimp
He's a smart guy
He's not going to go on pimp shit
Like I'm doing about these channels
Into the channels are working properly
And he's got the channels up and running
He's smart
He's laying low
And those press releases
That's corporate shit
Trust me
Okay
Go to pressroom.potshow.com
And you can see
They're all the same
It's the same format
I think we even still put the hash marks at the end
For teletype
By that the AP newsroom
It's just one thing you do
Okay
You know
It's a leadership issue
That's all
And I know a little bit about that
I work with companies on those sort of issues
And I'm just saying you have a disconnect
For my point of view
In your leadership team
And you just think that connect those dots
Dude, where do you work?
Do you have a leadership team?
This is a leadership team
And a senior management
Come on man
Ah
Nothing
Because John
Nothing against you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
It's just that thing
And he probably goes with the twins
And he probably goes with Christy
Nothing against you
Either nylon
And he probably goes with him to John
You know
For guy who's got a new job
If you wish
He doesn't talk about it
There's no passion
So I'm just saying
Get the guy on board
Dude
Go listen to tech5.pacho.com
He's getting his gear together
He's doing a daily test show
If you will
TECH5.pacho.com
He's getting ready man
Take it easy
You're on the inside
Okay
You're with all the cool kids
That's why you know these things
Before anyone else really does
Okay
You know
And make a more line
And that way
It won't seem to me
I'm all the other
That you know
He's kind of a
Okay
nylon
You're killing me
That's all
Let me go take another time
I'm all
I'm sure you're going to say something
To upset me again
Oh
Burke
nylon
I love you man
Please, I mean
If I didn't truly respect you
I mean, would I be
Would I be playing this?
Let's have a word
With the nylon
Spreading the news
With the smile on
Where the wrong old right
We'll go for light
Let's listen
We'll go wild
To the nylon
Ah
Okay
Let's talk about some other shit
For a second
Oh it's
Yeah
It's Eric Bergen's mom
You're my buddy
It's in Jersey Boys
Now it's Los Angeles
With the hot girlfriend
Who's also in the cast
Hello
Hi Adam
Oh hi baby
You're from Kraftcast
Also known as Eric Bergen's mother
I gotta tell you
The house shit
I'll wait until you're done
Speaking of
Thank you so much for that
Oh reading of his review
On your show there
That was very sweet of you
Thank you
And I just wanted you to know that
I'm listening
I'm not there
Listening every day
So
Oh
And I'm just wanted to also say
Congrats on that
Not smoking thing
I know how far this stuff is to do
And I'm proud of you
It's very inspiring
So
Good for you
Okay
And then
Can I tell you
Alice and Tarty
And drove for a second
But
Today
Um
Except when I got up this morning
I did not think about smoking
The entire day
Until I got back home
We started doing the show
Until I saw you all
Listening to
Let's see today is Tuesday
Today's show
Tuesday morning
I just wanted to fill you in on something
I dropped you an email way back
This whole channel thing
Building your own channels
That's what happened to me with my show
What happened was
Someone hijacked my feed
And
Used it for a craft channel
So
Loan behold when I went on to their
Their site
And played my show
It started with a promo
And a commercial
For a particular craft company
Yes
I did contact them
And I love their excuse
Their excuse was which always cracks me up
Technical
You weren't supposed to see that
Oh
And then
Blame it on the serve
I knew it
I knew serve people
Blame it on the serve
They released that
Let me just let me just clarify one thing
Dear
There is a difference between your show
And your feed
Okay
They took your show
All right
They took it off your server
And
They made a copy of it
And we're redistributing a copy
This is something completely different
What we're talking about
The thing that we're doing with feeds
I mean it has a real
Techn...
Our entire system was built on this
And we've
Typical Ron and Adam fashion
We've built everything upside down
Okay
I'm telling you
We've built everything upside down
We're going to infer that fucker
And it's all going to become clear
We're not supposed to hear that
Anyway
They removed it
But the upshot of that is
They sold it
To someone as a craft channel
I think four different shows
To a sponsor
There's interest in it
So
Yes, you know
I always find the positive side of everything
And that
You're so right, Alison
And there you go
Do you think that if you have John C.
To Vorac hosting a channel
Technology shows that it's marketable
I think so
He was just
We have some of that
And every category I think
Sort of just said
Hey
This is working
So
You know
It's all happening
And I listen with big open ears
Mmm
Every day
So
Just wanted to you to know that
Thinking about you
I'm listening to you
And I look forward to listening to more
So big hug babe
Bye
Oh
Hey
Now I've got dreams about
Yeah
By you
Eric's girlfriend
Fuck, I didn't even do Eric, you guys are all just so hot
Yeah
How do I do?
And this is David Cohen from Jersey, another Jersey boy called Michelle
Yeah, you were mentioning Bill Filming
Yeah
On one of the most recent episodes
And I thought you could get a kick out of it
That I'm watching last time
Extending tonight
And guess who the host is
Is this here
That's right, your boy
Well awesome
Wait
Dude, cool
I just missed that
He was on the way to see
I didn't watch it
Because you know
I don't know, I got ready for the show
I'm happy to hear that
If anyone sees Bill Bill
Let me just tell him I said hey
Okay
Hi Adam
It's Michael Liff
Are you okay?
I'm okay
I just
I think I've been listening to
And you were talking about
You know, radio being stream
And podcasts
And you know, we're asking really what the difference is
And you're really picked up on it
And none of the last episodes
One thing I wanted to mention
I've never heard you talking about this
I'm actually using a Wi-Fi video
Which is called the
The Im Magic Box
Impeasant
India
Michael
Peter
Papa
And it's
It's India Mike Papa
Actually it's India Mike Papa
Radio.com
I'll let
I'll end it for a second
It's really good
It links into your Wi-Fi network
And when I bought it last year
It was basically possible to
You know, listen to any stream
So it's a little box that runs Linux
And you're basically able to
To listen to like
8,000 something
Radio streams and stations on the internet
But one thing that's added recently
To the firmware is
There you can also now access podcasts
Which is something I requested
And asked for last year on one of the four runs
I hope you heard that
This is something really significant that you just heard
So first of all
I checked that I looked it up online
I'll put the link in the show notes
Imperadio.com
IMP
India Mike Papa
And it's a kind of
Stylist looking radio
Like a kitchen radio
Table top type radio
And
And you know it looks great for
For internet radio and streaming stations
But now apparently it's also
Aware of how to get our type of media
To get our version of internet radio
And the third thing that I thought was interesting
And that is that they added that
Into this radio
Into this consumer product
After he requested it
How cool is that
I mean that's awesome
I'd love to know a little bit more about
Exactly how it works
And you know how the streaming
That works does it
Take a feed or in this case
Have you loaded a pod show channel on it?
That's all I want to know
Just let me know how that went
I'd love to hear more
And it works really really well
So that's one thing
It's basically one place that
Combined pot cast and streams
In a really good way
And I've got one of those in my kitchen
It's a great little gadget
Rock on
The other thing I wanted to say is
I'm a German living in the UK
And I just wanted to thank you for the things
You said recently about Germany and everything
And I understand that you spend a lot of time
If you're used in the Netherlands
And you sort of grew up there
And
Well, you know the place where I come from
It's really close to the Dutch border
And
Well, you know, I don't know
I always have been during the time when I grew up
And they have always been a lot of
Any more cities is colliding like that
Between the Dutch and the Germans
And I've seen a couple of pretty ugly things
So for someone who's grown up in the Netherlands
And then sort of now experience as the German side
And I thought it was a really nice thing to say
And it's great that the Germans could
Can surprise you in such a way
And you talk about the Germans being
Curtiss and things
Just very kind and nice and huge experience
But that's great. Anyway, I'll kind of show it
And it's enough now
Great show, keep up a bit of work
All the best, bye
Yeah, I really appreciate you saying that
And it's funny because I was talking about that
Was wrong today
As you know, we're about ready to make our move into Germany
And I think I actually said it again
You know, I said I'm really digging the Germans man
It's like they're motivated
They're really sharp, they're alert
They're like, aren't you Curtiss?
Extremely Curtiss
And you know, I kind of have a hypothesis about that
Now I moved to the Netherlands in 1972
And so that was only
About 30 years after the Second World War ended
Some odd, yeah, about 30 some odd years
But that's not a lot of years, even less than that
It's not a lot of years
That's a generation
A generation to half maybe
So you know, you can only imagine
What was being passed down
The Germans really fucking annihilated
A lot of that country
And I know a lot about this
Having spoken a lot with my with my in laws
Who both from Rotterdam
Go have a look at Rotterdam and Wikipedia
Even Wikipedia can't miss that
Fact that it was bombed to shit in the Second World War
It's completely destroyed, beautiful, beautiful city
And you know, I always noticed that
There's some very stereotypical things
That the Dutch will say about the Germans
One is they always come
Because the Germany has no beach
So they come see words towards the Netherlands
And what the big joke is
Oh, here come the Germans
Because they're going to big dig holes in the beach
And then put up their windbreaker screens around it
And the other joke
Although I'm sure several cultures joke about this
Or generalize by saying
Oh, you know, if you're on vacation to hotel somewhere
At 6 a.m. the Germans are always downstairs
Putting towels on the on the beds near the pool
To like reserve them
But I'll tell you, man
I'm really excited about doing stuff in Germany
I truly am
And I look forward to learning a lot
I think I think the Germans have been getting a bum wrap
And what's funny is that
Even while that situation certainly existed
You know, 15, 20 years ago
Was probably still pretty prevalent
Maybe even longer ago
Think about, you know, your thoughts about Iranians
Or Iraqis
Dude, I've been to Iraq
Fucking normal people
We got along fine
Got a beef with them
I gotta be with any people that we may or may not be at war
With or threatened by or whatever
Been in Russia too, same thing
And not like all KGB
Low and behold
And I think that's really what the internet is brought us
Is
And even though you don't stop to think about it
Oh, this is maybe something for the thought of the final thought of the week
But, you know
All right, it used to be maybe that we were just sold a big ass
Bunch of goods like these are evil people
And the way people were portrayed on the media
And now we have our own media
We communicate with each other across
Vass geographic distances
And hey, you know
We all got a fucking mice-based image
All right, the world is upside down
The hardship I calm us upside down
A barbed gentry
Has just the lyrics
Describe how I feel
I've been talking in my sleep
When I'm waking
Well, my tongue is tight
I've been thinking I should leave
Instead of waiting for her when the time is right
I've backed the bags under my eyes
Well, I've seen enough to know what it's like
It's turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking up the downside
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just stick around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body
Till now
I've been walking in my sleep
When I'm waking up
Well, my legs are tight
I've been thinking I should leave
Put the window up
It's a mare tonight
I've been dreaming I could fly it
Well, I'm free enough
But I'm still way down
It's turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking up the downside
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just stick around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body
Till now
I've been afraid to just walk out
Ain't no way to stop me now
It's turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking up the downside
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just stick around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
All I can do is try it
Tell me what I've done wrong now
When all rules got changed somehow
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
All I can do is try it
Oh my god
It's so beautiful
Bob Gentry
The pod safe music network misses you
It's been two years and you posted some of your beautiful art
Please come back
And I'll be back tomorrow
DailySourceCode.com
Adam at podshow.com
Have a good one everybody
Bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily
By the sharpest minds in content delivery
Podshow and Livelight