It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
Warning. The content of this show is for mature audiences only.
It's not work safe, or family safe, or carpool safe, or even safe to be listened to in daylight.
It's not boat safe, walking the dog safe, and certainly not safe for anyone with a pacemaker.
It's not safe for your pets, for the morbidly obese, or for people who live in fear of chimichangas.
It's not safe for alcoholics, nor is it bathroom safe, kitchen safe, and certainly not safe for trainees.
At least for the moment.
This show is not being inserted into any bodily orifice, though anyone doing so should wait at least 20 minutes before going into the water.
And last of all.
For the next five days, this show is mined bitches, so drop your cocks and grab your socks.
This is the Daily Source Code.
With Mark Yoshimodo Nemkoff.
You're listening to the Daily Source Code with Mark Yoshimodo Nemkoff.
Some people in our government, they want to regulate.
Don't we get to think of how I try to masturbate slowly, they erode.
All right, the choice while people like us, we ain't got no voice, they ain't think we don't know.
Think we don't see.
Motherfuckers, they all lie at the media about why, on a water date, or in their rack, tell me how the fuck do I get my country back from.
Pretty long, because you don't give a fuck, sir, for how to get rich and how to make a fuck.
Time for us to call them motherfuckers.
But you can't just open your window and chat for this fuck, that fuck you fuck, bro.
I burn a fuck and take your dog and police show.
I'm here for a scene, a little unkind, but it's time for me to say what's on my mind, yo.
But casting is a new revolution.
Podcasting is the new revolution.
Get off your ass, be part of the solution.
Criminal radio is just noise pollution.
Clip channel, motherfuckers suck as well.
10, because a bro premise of a damn Paris Hilton.
Same fucking songs off fucking day long.
I've run the dirt no water, I had to, I'm curious, bond, then listen to that shit.
I need something fresh, I'm gonna give this boy a little goose flesh.
Gotta make it at home, turn on the microphone.
She's blowing up bigger than the Chinese Indra.
When I'm up in my mouth, I get myself in trouble.
Like I get a fuck hell, I ain't a Mr. Bottle trying to keep this shit clean.
That ain't my fucking deal, say why don't I walk?
How I feel keeping it fucking real?
Clip channel, you can lick my balls if you think you own those kids in the malls.
Cause less people listen to you every day, so maybe hit my word when I fucking say yo.
Podcasting is a new revolution.
Podcasting is the new revolution.
Get off your ass, be part of the solution.
Corporate radio is just noise pollution.
Podcasting is the new revolution.
Get off your ass, be part of the solution
Podcasting is a new revolution
Corporate radio is just noise pollution
Get off your ass, be part of the solution
Podcasting is a new revolution
We're not эту a new revolution
This seems to be shocking
But all you need to do is tell me
I gotta tell you it's pretty nice
Welcome to the Daily Source.
I'm gonna call up for the next week
The Daily Cold
Everybody okay?
Oh, no, no, no.
Keep fucking, you okay duck taped.
Hold on.
Alright, that's better.
Alright, well, uh, tell you what, we're gonna keep Adam locked up in a safe place for the next few days.
We're gonna put him in the closet.
Jesus, fancy fucking shit, you got there.
It's one hell of a closet, Adam.
They're probably ventilation, right?
I guess, I will, well, whatever.
Okay, so, uh, okay, we got 18 more minutes to kill.
Just kidding.
If you're listening to us on series stars one or two,
you're like, what the fuck is fucking, what,
but don't worry about it, just play along.
So, it's moments like this.
Or ask myself, oh, what would Jesus do?
And though the answer may involve, uh, some kind of a lap dance.
Uh, I'll just defer to what would Adam do?
Well, Adam would probably do a story, right?
Well, you're not getting what?
No, I'm just kidding.
I saw this the other day on, um, was ABC News?
Does it fucking matter?
I saw this on the news.
And I had to do with, uh, music and piracy.
Now, um, that's kind of interesting.
So I re-wound the tempo and I plugged in, I think.
That doesn't really matter.
So I plugged in my iPod kind of,
uh, with the dongle and the thingy and the thing that goes here.
And I thought I'd, uh, you know, take the audio.
And I'd play it for you.
Check this out.
They used to be the music industry's best customers.
Now, they're rates biggest pirates, college kids.
Instead of buying songs for 99 cents each legally
on sites like iTunes, the internet has given them instant access
to free music.
It seems so easy that it's almost not like stealing.
You basically illegally download all your music?
I, not all of it.
But most of it, say these university of southern California students,
even though the recording industry has sent threatening letters here.
So these letters don't scare you.
No matter what they do, it's never going to stop completely.
See for yourself how big the problem is.
You're watching a real-time readout of eelsongs and other entertainment media.
People are seeking out for free online right now.
They go buy in the hundreds per second.
Request for Buddy Holly, Miles Davis, Avril Levine.
These are big numbers.
We're looking out here.
Yeah, they're terrifying numbers to the recording industry.
Eric Garland has big champagne, a research group that tracks illegal traffic.
Today alone, 137,000 times.
For every song that is downloaded legally.
How many are downloaded illegally?
At least very conservatively, at least 20.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold the fuck on.
Did he just say 20?
That's right, 20 to one.
It took iTunes five years to sell two billion songs.
But there are a billion illegal downloads.
I guess it's music for free.
It gets its music online and gets its music without permission.
That's broken.
That is not a marketplace.
And if the music industry can't find a solution,
it's looking more and more like the song is over.
Anthony Mason, CBS News, Los Angeles.
CBS News, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And you may have heard there were a couple of like little parts of our cutout.
That wasn't me editing the thing.
I was just a fault in the recording.
There's some reason my iPod skipped.
Well, whatever, it doesn't matter.
But I think you got the gist of the whole story.
According to this company, big champagne.
Some fucking consultant to the RIA,
which I believe stands for really ignorant arrogant assholes.
So this fucking consultant company is claiming
that songs are pirated at a rate of 20 to 1 versus songs being purchased legally.
Now I gotta say, as a pretty outrageous numbers.
But am I really surprised?
That's the fucking question.
But honestly, I guess it really doesn't fucking matter
if I believe that or not.
What really matters is that the really ignorant arrogant assholes
believe it.
And you better believe they do.
Especially that douchebag, Doug Morris,
who runs the Universal Music Group.
That's right, Doug.
I called you a fucking douchebag.
Do something about it.
So here's the thing.
Now, when we were doing bummerish the chart,
I'm not gonna tell you, I hope bummerish the thing.
I know we've talked this to death,
but here's one thing I wanted to mention.
You know, we're a lot of people who were like,
I'm thinking about, can't you,
DRM and blah, blah, blah, blah.
And the funny thing was,
I noticed on dig.com,
when there was a like 1,500,
1,800 comments, whenever that one day.
There were a number of people who were like,
yeah, man, DRM is wrong, man,
and I'm not gonna do it because of DRM.
And yeah, man, and you know what?
Fuck you, because I downloaded it off a lime wire.
So their whole thing was, they were anti DRM,
because it prevented them from actually
pirating the song.
Right, which is about as fucking stupid
as being one of these pro-life nut jobs
who has to kill an abortion doctor
to prove their point.
That fetus got her at to live,
which is why I'm gonna shoot you.
You would abortion, perform a doctor.
The world is full of stupid people.
Just look around you on the bus
or the cubicle next to you.
That guy, see that guy?
That guy picks his nose and eats it.
And you know what struck me the other day?
Well, the frying pan that my wife threw.
But after that, I was thinking about the grateful dead.
Now, you got to understand.
I can't fucking stand the grateful dead.
But I was thinking about something.
The grateful dead had one of the most amazing,
well, they still do, I guess, right?
They kind of tore right?
Jerry Garcia out in a glass coffin, right?
Or something, I don't know.
But they had this audience deadheads
that followed them to the ends of the earth
out of their own pockets.
Sure, you know, they were like 15 of them sleeping in van
and unwashed.
But this is an audience of deadheads
that marketing cannot buy.
And it's actually something that Pearl Jam is doing now.
So the grateful dead.
They have this huge loyal following.
And one of the things that they did was allow their fans
from the very beginning mind you.
They allowed their fans.
Raise your hand if you know where this is going.
They allowed their fans to taper cord concerts.
That's right.
Now, I know that, you know, every two dead songs,
they all sound alike to me.
And apparently, you know, any two concerts are different
because the way, you know, they go from sugar magnolia
and the trucking and blah, blah, blah, who fucking cares?
But the point is that the grateful dead
basically gave you cart blanche to tape
and swap their material.
And they said, be free.
You flower children, smelly people.
And this was file sharing, right?
This was hippie file sharing with, you know,
with sneaker net.
And they would trade cassettes in real-to-real tapes
and whatever those old fucking hippies used to record shit on.
You know, wax cylinder, I don't fucking know.
But that was a huge part of being a deadhead.
Well, that and dropping acid and ending up naked
with some fat chick, but the whole point is
they had an amazing audience
that they let pirate their own material
and the audience just became more loyal.
And you're asking yourself,
would this work for Chris Dodtree?
Would this work get a Chris Dodtree concert?
The answer is probably no,
because, you know,
teaching a young teenage girl how to operate a tape recorder.
You probably have a better chance
teaching a dog to read.
But that is not the point.
The point is that record companies
still think that you're ripping them off.
And you know what?
I want to hear what you think about it.
So this is what you're going to do.
You're going to send me some feedback.
And email it to me at where is Adam Curry at gmail.com
where you could also send it to Adam Curry's gay
at gmail.com.
It's your choice.
I'm leaving that up to you.
That's the kind of guy I am.
And since I can't figure out for the life of me,
how to access Adam's voice mail here.
Hold on.
Let me give it another shot.
We're sorry.
You'll call.
Cannot be completed.
Fuck.
All right. Whatever.
So for the time being this week,
call the PCH Commonline at 1-800-875-09995.
Like I said, I want to hear from you.
You better call.
I know where you live.
Hold on.
There's some stuff here on Adam's laptop.
What's this?
Oh.
Okay.
Hello, Adam.
This is a prolific program.
I've been trying to catch up on some of the oldest sort of code
just from back before I discovered your podcast.
I just wanted to give you some information you asked about
in one of your oldest shows.
Back on your DST-234,
you asked if it was possible to stream pornography
from your iPod.
If it was sitting and home connected to your desktop,
I wrote a utility that you could do that with.
You have to use a C++ compiler under Linux
on your home machine for it to work.
I have all the source code in the small library
even crude files that you need in my website.
I need to warn you that there are pictures on my website
of my operation.
So if you're at all squeamish about seeing bloody genitals
and various operative stages,
then I think you should avoid looking at picture number
for number 9 and then 11 through 46.
From 47 on, I'm pretty much healed.
The C files and the H files in the make files are all at
HTT-P-Colent-4-4-4-3-8.113.169.238.222.2-4-4-8
overcase P overcase P over slash question mark
and present Sparvanoxia,
built just like it sounds forward slash
ampersand ampersand mentalhealth.ph forward slash
till the monkey grind.htm.
Goodbye Adam.
I don't know about you,
but I was on the edge of my city,
but I was on the edge of my city the whole time.
You know, standing there with a rope around my neck
tied to a beam that I know will support my body weight,
but nonetheless, on the edge of my city.
Hold on, what's that?
Oh, I think I hear Adam, hold on.
Dude, dude.
What?
No, I tap, tap against the door.
No, tap once, okay, okay.
You're there in there, right?
Tap once for yes?
And tap twice for no.
Okay, I have no idea
with three times means.
Hold on, I'm going to have to check on this.
Dude, I heard you lagged
Godfather or the podfather or something,
and I got a URL that I want.
People is not checking out,
but no one's even to come to me.
I don't know why.
You go to www.3wafuckpapy.com.
It's a nickname, man, I'm a gaming when I was four,
and I don't know why no one will come to my site.
But I'd really like if you had the attention
to come on, man, you come on.
Do you waifuckpapy.com?
It's a great URL.
I've had a shit with God daddy
and used your code and everything.
But nobody come.
Nobody comes to the site.
And I really wasn't visible.
So if you can pay attention,
I'd appreciate it.
But I know I understand if you won't
because you're a busy guy.
I mean, if I had a hard job
to try to be fast cars
and playing the casual.
But in your hack all the way.
To www.3wafuckpapy.com
Thank you pod, person, poor people, whatever you are.
And...
I gotta go.
Bye.
You heard the guy.
Go to www.3wafuckpapy.com.
Why do you want that is?
But if you find pictures of Hillary there,
just don't blame me.
So...
If you find naked pictures of Hillary there,
don't blame me.
Hi, am I ruining your daily source code
listening experience yet?
Anyway, Adam's okay.
He's okay.
He just had to hit him a couple of times
with the cattle prod.
What the...
Yeah.
Funny thing was, I didn't even bring the cattle prod.
It was something that I found here on the desk.
And I never actually seen a cattle prod
with a rubber foulus on the end of it.
But you know.
Hey.
Whatever flow to boat.
All right, hold on.
Let's see what else is on Adam's laptop here.
Ooh.
Check?
Oh yeah.
Another one of the savants.
Oh, dig it.
What?
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me click on here.
Comics strip.
comics strip.
And um, it's comics strip luck here.
I am so pissed off today.
You know that thing where they say, there are two scoops of raisins and every box of raisin brand.
There is only one scoop. Those bastards only give me one scoop of raisins and pisses me off. I'm so pissed off.
And I'm you sock, you're the only one who pays attention to me.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip.
I don't know. Was that the real comic strip blogger?
I'm not sure, because I know that Adam's been working on a project, comic strip blogger, the musical,
and it's going to be cast entirely with hairless young boys.
So I don't know if that was a fuck.
I better ask him when he regains consciousness.
Oh, it sucks. The only savant we didn't hear from was a nylon.
Hold on. Let me check.
This laptop fucking porn, porn, porn, okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, sweet.
Let's have a word with the nylon.
Spreading the news with the smile on, where the roll is right.
Ringo for light. Let's listen roll a while to the nylon.
Hold on. Did anybody else understand that?
I just...
I couldn't make out what nylon was saying, because it sounded like he had something in his throat,
something deep, something big and hairy, deep within his throat.
I hope it wasn't an important message. I kind of doubt it.
But so, hey, if you're not listening to bone, what the fuck are you thinking?
Go to bone.podshow.com.
Bone is this really great game show that I created for Pod Show.
It's a trivia game show, and I got to tell you.
If you're in a trivia, if you like stuff like this, it's a lot of fun.
And our good buddy Luke from Nokia, and we're giving away Nokia N800s,
as the grand prize on bone, an episode three through six.
I was just fucking blown away by this, because I have one of these things I have an N800,
and it's fucking amazing.
I mean, I use this thing actually.
I write Shadow Falls Badlands on an N800, using the on screen keyboard.
Believe it or not, I lie in bed at night.
And I sit there, and I write this thing, boom, boom, boom, boom,
and then I email it to myself.
Yeah, just like that, boom, boom, boom, boom, and email it to myself.
And then in the morning, I have this document, and I just cut and paste it in there,
and just, you know, fix my typos and stuff.
But there it is.
Instead of journaling into a, you know, notebook with a paper and pencil,
I have all my stuff there.
I don't have to recap it.
It's fucking amazing.
I love my N800, and we're giving away these fucking things on bone.
I am so psyched about that.
So check it out, bone.podshow.com.
Oh, shit.
Hold on, the satellite window is coming to a close.
Hey, serious one or two listeners, you're just going to have to go to dailysourceco.podshow.com.
And trust me, I'm going to be back here tomorrow.
Fucking up the joint again.
Oh, yes, they're gone.
Now it's just us alone.
You look so nice in that.
That thing you're wearing.
Yeah.
Here we're to like a drink.
What do you mean, no?
Have a drink.
Please.
No, I insist.
Have a drink.
No.
Drink it.
I don't care if there's a busy tablet at the bottom of it.
Oh my god.
I just flashed back to my last date.
Oh shit.
Oh.
Oh, these meds.
I'm on.
Oh, I got to tell you.
I got to fix this shit before it.
Oh, look, my pants are wet.
Okay.
Well, I guess I better wrap things up here.
Tell you what.
You know what I'm going to play for you today?
I had a couple of different ideas.
What song I was going to play at the end of the show.
But if you're a PCH listener,
that's my regular show.
Just if it goes to all I.
If you're a PCH listener,
you already know that I'm a huge Kevin Gilbert fan.
Now for those of you who don't know Kevin Gilbert.
Kevin was actually the guy who discovered Cheryl Crow.
That's the best shorthand I can give you.
He had this band at the time called Toy Matinee,
which you may or may not remember.
They had a couple of, it a couple of hits at the time.
You know, last playing out,
turning it on Salvador.
You know, we're talking like early 90s.
So when they were putting together the touring band for Toy Matinee,
which actually, well, that's a long story.
The keyboard player that they auditioned,
one of the keyboard players,
was a young lady named Cheryl Crow.
And Cheryl didn't get the gig,
but basically Kevin started to happener.
And they started dating and,
here's the true story.
Kevin had this group of friends that would get together,
you know, very well known.
Well, for LA, I guess, well known.
A session, guys.
And they'd all get together once a week,
and you know, smoke a little and hang out and play in right tunes.
And they did it on Tuesday night.
And it was called the Tuesday night music club.
And Kevin invited Cheryl to come hang out with the boys,
you know, jam and stuff.
And then what happened was they ended up writing a bunch of songs
that she got a deal with.
And then, including all I want to do,
her first big hit, which Kevin co-wrote
and co-one the Grammy on.
And then what happened was, well,
it got kind of ugly from there,
because Cheryl started to become a big star
and her promise to help Kevin get a record deal
didn't quite pan out,
because she basically told him to fuck off.
And so it ended pretty badly.
And what really happened was Kevin,
Kevin co-wrote.
Like all the songs on the record.
And what I heard is that he wrote
almost all the songs on her record.
But he gave songwriting credit to the other guys
in the Tuesday night music club,
who all ended up being in Cheryl's band
and recording the record with her,
because that was the kind of guy he was.
And I can vouch for Kevin Gilbert
because I went to school with Kevin Gilbert
at Berkeley College of Music.
I only had one class with the guy,
and my memories of him are vague.
But I just remember him being a pretty cool and funny guy.
And so I was ecstatic when I heard that he had gotten a deal
after school, so on and so forth.
And very sad when I heard later on that Kevin Gilbert died
from Autorotic asphyxiation, a sword of God.
So it's tragic.
And I got to tell you, Kevin was a really talented guy.
And at the time of his death, he was working on an album
called Shaming of the True.
And it was a rock opera about the music industry
was about a character named Johnny Virgil,
who basically comes from nowhere
to LA with these big rock and roll dreams.
And then he gets a record deal and becomes famous.
And then learns how emotionally bankrupt and shallow
the music industry really is.
So it's an amazing piece of work that was left unfinished
that the time was death and Kevin's friends
got together and they finished it.
So basically using the tracks that Kevin had left
and notes that he had left and just having worked with him
as much as they had to the best of their abilities.
They finished this.
But there were a few tracks that were pretty much completed
at the time of Kevin's death.
And one of them is like my favorite track on the record.
So I'm going to play that for you now.
So off of the album, the Shaming of the True.
This is the City of the Sun.
We sang a bar that hardly rang a bell.
I'm not born to make a lie.
The ball is in previnitions and fleeting thoughts
but I must admit that I tried to avoid it still.
So didn't want to see him see himself in me
with a look of an extinguish flame
that might be lurking there.
What she said with dripping drag
come on out total, get off my leg.
You've got to remember we're not in Kansas anymore.
Remember always a look for ways to please
and thank you for coming to twice
and before you go the sacred dinosaur.
Where are the birds?
In ports and things to say
We're here to help you make a new start
We're not gonna take your heart away
You stand before us like a veil figure
The end of a long gallery
Distant and forever mysterious
It flies from the tasteless to the bland
Watch all that magic from your hands
Make it so we might understand
Good morning, gracious
Good morning, special
And God knows for you
God knows for real, yes, yes, yes
Every one of you listening to this broadcast
I want you to pack your life
You're not going on a vacation
But we all move and I can't get your shall amen
Don't mind
Because we're moving into the city of the sun
Where we can enjoy all of this play
We're happy to get your rest
Is this the shame you want to like it
To be I get to your heart of fire
Do you understand more
Do you understand
Don't read the places where the big waves meet
We'll come to the city of the sun
Oh, Johnny, you got to see it in your hand, it's the seed of your demise.
Ambition's gonna lure you away into the land of compromise.
You stand before us like a brash of a ripened nectarine,
and someone better pick you soon.
Advice for the dying from the dead,
silence the voices in your hand,
wouldn't you rather eat instead?
Hi, you've reached the dilapidated shack of Johnny Virgil,
so I can't come to the phone at the moment,
please leave a name number after the F sharp.
City of the Sun by Kevin Gilbert,
and big big thanks to the estate of Kevin Gilbert
for giving me permission to play it.
I only wish you could get this album on iTunes.
I think the only place you can get it is you have to order the CD online
at a place called PopPlus1.com.
I'll put it in the show notes.
I should really place a more shit from this album
because it's just fucking mind blowing,
so as a concept record.
Tell you what, all week,
I'm going to play tunes that are from my private vault,
that you're not really going to hear most anywhere else.
Okay, that's my promise to you for sticking around.
Okay?
Hey, and a big shout out to my buddy Bob Parsons,
CEO of GoDaddy,
and to Nima Jones in the crew over at life online,
the radio show of the Bob Parsons says,
I can't say enough about GoDaddy.
I mean, fucking great company,
and I had a chance to go there and meet the people out there,
really nice people.
And I'm so used to people from LA
that when somebody actually says,
thank you to me and please,
and hello,
I'm actually surprised.
I'm overwhelmed by their kindness.
So,
you know, I'm a huge fan of GoDaddy,
because not only have they been a sponsor of Pacifico's Hellway
for like a year now,
but they have great service.
I use their service all the time.
Whenever I need a domain name for something,
I go to GoDaddy,
and it's true.
It's true.
I got a bunch of domains registered with GoDaddy.
Like my favorite one,
of course, is FuckCorpardRadio.com,
which takes you right to CC Chapman's accident hash.
That's also fun to type in.
So, yeah, FuckCorpardRadio.com,
and I got that for 6.95 a year,
using Pro Locode PCH3 during checkout.
And yes, I'm going to print my fucking promo code,
because Adam already has enough money.
And,
So,
if you're looking for a domain name,
I mean, come on.
Who else are you going to go to?
GoDaddy is the number one domain
registered in the world,
and it's because of their service.
Who are you going to go just fucking,
I don't even know who else is out there.
I mean,
register flight.
Did you hear what happened to register fly?
Oh, my God.
I had my original domains.
When I first started like podcasting and shit,
we're with register fly.
Actually, that's not true.
Well, we're with net firms.
But I registered some other domain names at register fly.
And then I moved them, you know, like a year ago.
And then maybe a couple of months ago,
the story came out that the,
and correct me if I'm wrong.
That founders, the chairman,
the top guys at register fly,
were misappropriating funds,
and the money,
I swear to God,
this is true.
The money was being used for
liposuction,
and male escort.
Okay.
I swear to God.
So they had their registered,
nest thing pulled canceled.
So register fly got,
you know, basically put out a business.
Because there were shitty company.
And if you ever tried to use their fucking control panel,
it was like,
you know, trying to shit out a ball of fish hooks.
It was just about that pleasant.
But go daddy, it's fucking great.
I love go daddy.
And so if you're inclined,
go to godaddy.com,
start a website,
because you get free hosting,
free quick blog free email.
How the fuck can you beat that?
For 695 a year.
Just use promo code,
PCH3,
during checkout.
Okay.
I think I'm going to call it a day,
and go recharge this,
dildo-tipped cattle prod,
I found here.
See if I can get Adam to tell me where he hid
all of his leprechaun gold.
But stick around,
because I'm going to play a couple of promos here.
And,
you're going to want to hear these.
So remember,
you can shoot me an email.
And where is Adam Curry at gmail.com or?
Adam Curry's gay at gmail.com.
Take your pick.
We're calling me on the PCH comment line.
At 1-800-875-0995.
All right,
I'm out of here.
Get ready for some pimping.
A,
Vienna,
B, Berlin,
C,
Munich.
One of these is the city
where Beethoven is buried.
Music
Listen to what people are saying about the phone.
Here's the word on the streets.
Johnny Todd is sexy.
Tony is the sexy one.
Wow.
Oh my god, you like her?
Yeah.
Wow.
Yeah, I know Johnny Todd.
You know, talk about snarky.
It's kind of an ass.
But I thought the trivia was cool.
Hey, how do I get on the show?
I guess took a duty in my pants.
You got changed for a dollar.
Hey, this is Johnny Todd.
You're always verboned.
This is what people are talking about.
They're monks.
They don't hurt things.
Peter.
Come on.
And they're sweetheart.
And I like your sweetheart, please.
Drinking if you got him.
Pardon me well for my beer.
Sounds good to me.
Yeah, there's only soft bones now.
Who knew who new magic was playing in the Olympics?
And I'll always have some fun trivia to share with you.
So my favorite bonehead put down that hacksaw for yourself a drink and go to bone.pacho.com
and check it out.
Oh.
And the answer to our Beethoven is buried.
It's a Vienna.
And if you didn't know that, you just might get bone.
Oh, you guys ain't like a winner.
Oh, be to be that crap cut and burn.
The century and a half before the tragic events at Shadow Falls, one ex-soldiers' visions
of the future will lead him on a cross-country journey to unlock the secrets held inside
his nightmares.
But what he finds behind Destiny's door may be a darkness beyond his control.
From the mind of Mark Yuchimodo Nemkov comes the chilling audio book, prequel, Shadow
Falls, Badlands.
Be part of the revelation at Shadow Falls.pacho.com.
The best of the brightest, subdupped daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering
the pop show and limelight.