Hey Tony, what are you doing?
Uh, trying to find something good on the tube, you know, just serve in the channels.
Tony, you'll never find anything like that because you're doing it old school.
That's the old channels.
You need to search the new channels, the podshow channels.
Go over to podshow.com, check out the channels.
You got all kinds of channels.
You got geek brief TV.
Ah, that Kelly Lewis really does something to my hard drive.
Uh, yeah.
And you got channels from music, you got channels from video.
Josie Todd's got a whole bunch of channels over there.
So go check those out.
This is the new wave.
It's a new wave of media and it's the new channel surf and riding the new wave.
You know what I'm talking about, Tony?
Just listen to the DSC 643 and Adam's going to tell us all about the channels.
He calls him Cheddar.
The, like, the cheese?
Yeah, Tony.
You're smart as a whip.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing you, Adam Curry.
Feet Furrier in of the sun.
Girl you know you got no dream.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah,
Let me, all right, we'll watch it in the front of our hearts
Girl, you never want to kiss me
I love you, it's not here for you
Always want you with me, I'll play Bobby and you play with me
If you smoke that smoke too, that's how much I'm in love with you
Crazy is, we're crazy too
Crazy alone, we're crazy for you
Let me, let me, I don't sin it, I saw all of my life
To me, let me, all right, we'll watch it in the front of our hearts
Why are you so insecure, we got passionate love
Girl, we're always framing our machines
They got up in the lead, we got to another scene
We got that I need you, you must have caught at me
Kid, that's why you don't believe me
Look, you need me
Guilty because you are a Car
Guilty that's right a crazy girl
Guilty that's right a girl
Guilty that's right a DJ
Get me, let me, any of your words
Let me, let me。 Let me, let me
Let me, any of your words
let me let me let me let you make it so you know
let me let me let me let you watch it at the amaha
Give me, give me, and you send it as song for love.
Give me, give me, give me.
I don't know what you know for dinner.
I don't want you to die.
Mash that a lino, watching it die.
I'm just thinking of your pipe.
I ain't no for dinner.
And I'm so good.
I ain't no for dinner, sir.
What?
How the hell?
DJ Max entropy.
The funk with my favorite son.
Of course, CCR mixed up with Black Eyed Peas.
Kicking off episode 643 of the Daily Source Code.
Hey, everybody.
I don't know about you, but I am officially neckard.
I don't know if it's the correct use of the word, but man, man, man, man.
You know, this is tough.
I long for the days when all I have to do is just sit around and make a show.
Boy, what I make a great show for you every single day would be so
perfectly pre-produced.
Sorry about yesterday.
I warned you though.
You know, whenever I say, oh, I think I'll do a show later on.
What happens is I don't get home until nine o'clock.
You know, I have my dinner.
Nine o'clock, of course, I got to watch a big brother while the
dinner is rolling.
By the way, I'm still Brian to win on this thing here in the UK.
And, you know, that's 10 o'clock.
And then essentially, we're taking up until one to pre-produce,
produce, and then, you know, do all the post-production, uploading, etc.
It would be like three hours.
It's kind of what it is.
I just didn't have, I just didn't have, I'm an old man.
I'm sorry.
Just don't have it anymore.
Although I, increasingly, I'm finding people still, you know,
will just won't skip an episode.
And some are like a month behind.
So maybe it's a good way to help people catch up.
In that regard, at least it is.
Hey, the music business is really messed up.
I got this link.
What is it?
Actually, by the way, I want to thank Dr. Art for hooking me up with that,
that mashup that we kicked off with today.
And Dr. Art, he's interested in dental medicine.
The next meeting I have with my professionals is to determine
color and size.
If that helps at all.
So apparently, this is from betanews.com.
I'll put a link in the show notes.
There was a subcommittee of Congress about performers royalties
for being played on the radio.
You've got to read this thing because what's happening now.
It's, you know, amidst all of this debate about, you know,
streaming web radio, paying compulsory fees for all music,
which is not just mainstream.
It's not just any one's music licensed, you know,
signed to a record company or not.
Unless you have a pre-existing arrangement,
such as the Pod Save Music Network.
Now, this is about, you know,
basically it's a bunch of old artists.
And you see this happening every year.
Cliff Richard started yamoring about copyrights expiring
in the UK after 50 years.
He wants to extend it to 70 years because his shit's
coming up for public domain pretty soon.
I understand why he's pissed off about it.
You know, what we can't just keep changing the rules
when we get old, you know, and they're like,
oh, well, this is going to fuck me up.
This is what this isn't what I signed up for, you know.
Now, what's it?
What did I see that was a Roger Daltre of the Who
was doing the same thing?
And now, this is a different issue.
Judy Collins, who sang, uh,
send in the clowns.
One of the songs I dislike the most, I have to say,
just by coincidence.
She's saying, look, you know,
we get record companies made millions on this.
And then we got nothing out of it because we didn't get paid
for every single time we were played on the radio.
So here comes the big raging debate is broad.
And by the way, that's only in the US.
It's not the same in other countries because there are
performance royalty organizations such as the
SNA, the SNEA.
And I believe CSAC also does some of that as well.
But that's beside the point.
This is really about the United States in this particular
instance.
And, you know, it's like, so they're saying, well,
you know, we're being ripped off by the broadcasters because
they're getting a free ride.
And I have to kind of take the side of the broadcasters
in this because, you know, it is promotional.
And, you know, and it gives you read this.
It's the most absurd thing you've ever read in your life.
I feel bad for artists getting screwed by their
record companies.
But I totally disagree with this whole idea of, you know what?
Fuck you.
Fuck you, Judy Collins.
I'm not going to play your song.
I'll never play your send in the clowns song.
You know, it's, it is about promotion.
You know, if everybody in the world who does something creative,
you know, it just stands in with a handout.
We're going to get nowhere.
You know, there's got to be some hand-offs.
And, clearly, it works because the pod safe music network is growing.
In fact, got a great story about that at the end of the show
about a new band on the network.
And it works.
You know, they understand that, you know,
making money off of the music alone just isn't the way to do it anymore.
And I'm sorry if you feel that you're too old to go out and do gigs.
You know, there used to be a lot of jobs that no longer
exists.
It's just that we're just what happens.
It's what happens with technological innovation.
It really does.
You know, I used to get paid a lot more than I get paid now to do a lot less work
in broadcasting.
It's just the way it works.
We're in a transitional phase, which could last 10, 15, 20 years.
I don't know.
See, there was some, as a feedback about this actually.
Hey, Adam and listeners of the Charlie Howard Greenstein here in New York.
And I just came across an editorial in the bit player blog on the LA times
about the webcasting royalty issues.
There's some research now that says that the, it came actually from my 365
and said that more than 55% of the music played on its channels came from independent artists,
which is a hugely disproportionate share compared to CD sales and regular airplay,
which is usually about 87% of the major markets.
So basically, people who are doing webcasts on things like live 365 are playing a huge amount
more independent music, which basically translates to the fact that the indie music world
has a lot more incentive to keep webcasting alive.
It has a lot more incentive to have a more rich and open and independent and free set of music
for people to play than the majors and the radio stations and the folks who are basically pushing
for the rate increase for independent web gestures.
So some more fuel for the fire is how Greenstein in New York and I hope everyone has great day.
Yeah, Howard, I appreciate that.
Good friend of the show there, Howard is.
But you know what, Howard and others who are looking at this.
First of all, it's all, it's all food bar.
Every single angle you come at this, it's just a waste of energy.
Route around it already.
Just forget about it.
There's no way you're going to change people's minds and be very careful of the Indies.
Because the Indies are in the big, you know, they're at the big table as well.
And, you know, their Indies doesn't necessarily mean independent people who just put their music up.
You know, these are smaller versions of record companies as they exist today.
With smarter marketing plans, I think better packaging ideas,
but essentially the same business model, making money off of the artists.
So, and not, I'm not saying this anything wrong with it, but just be careful.
You know, it's like, it's not like just because independent, independent labels are being played more on web
strip streams that it makes any difference that they would necessarily not want their artists to be compensated per person listening.
I think they probably do in many cases.
Probably because they may actually have a back end deal on that.
So, you know, I don't have the answers, but I do know that whatever we're doing,
it's a lot better in my humble opinion to put all of our energy and resources into routing around this and fire in the entire train wreck.
You know, please, and don't rub or neck while you're driving by.
But let's just drive by.
Today a very exciting day, I think it's been months.
I can't even count the months how long it's been since this savant has been on the show.
And today he returns in true form, my friend.
Hello, I'm Roger here.
You asked us more examples of mainstream media deception.
You have a nice, lovely video called High School House for the intrigue.
There's a thing closely, I noticed it's ever chilly,
you're getting spit roasted with a leaked fat here's old.
But then it seems to be a girl on there, wasn't your age.
So, just another example of a blatant lie surrounding the TV industry.
Why can't this respond?
It's why everyone gets so obsessed about things come for 25 times by a big brother lie.
Yeah, when we spend billions of pounds on a wall based on a lie, no one gives us up.
So, that's something he needs to discuss on your show.
Right now?
Oh, my goodness.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, a round of applause for Roger Smalls who totally nails it.
What the hell are we thinking?
Yeah.
But you know Roger, and of course your point is so well taken.
Why are we making such a big deal out of being ripped off of a couple of quid for some lies
when there's billions being spent surrounding one huge lie?
Yeah.
By the way, I think the millions still would have spent and we probably still would have gone for a presence in the Middle East.
But the fact that it was brought to us and presented to us as a huge terrifying war on terror lie.
Yeah, that's pretty frickin' offensive for sure.
But I love how you hone right in on that Roger.
By the way, I'm still getting tons and tons of feedback on people's experiences with mainstream media primarily.
And a most banister sent me a great link to a YouTube video which I'll put in the show notes as well.
It's called Reality TV Editing.
If you really want to see the power of television and how you can take one scene, just one scene captured with multiple cameras and how you can edit that to fit the storyline.
I think it's from BBC Four.
So I'm happy that that's up there illegally on YouTube.
Get the link while you can.
It will blow you away.
It's really, really well done.
Just an example.
So the presenter of this show says, okay, so I'm going to tell it really lame joke.
And then he shows two scenarios.
One where people are laughing and the other one where people are going, huh?
And then he shows, okay, I can make this girl look like she's totally coming on to me or like she's totally not interested.
And literally with the same material just by using digital editing techniques, they show you how it's done.
And it's, it's awesome.
Awesome.
It's almost as good as watching the Zen TV experiment.
If you watch Big Brother or any of these reality shows, have a look at this.
And I mean, if look, I love Big Brother.
I know how it works.
I love it.
I totally enjoyed a story unfolding in front of me.
And I do not see it as reality.
I see it as a wonderfully told story done by amazing professionals.
It's no more no less.
That's why it's so easy for me to say Brian to win because I know how this stuff works.
Oh, oh, crikey.
Something from the hell way once again.
We're Mississippi Coast Highway.
And you, my big reggae.
But we're here to fucking say hey.
Go to my casterwords.com and the Ferras.
We'll go bang your mom and wipe our cheeks on her dress.
It's not family safer parents.
Go there every day and vote.
Or we'll come kick you in a swirls.
Did I mention that?
That we're all boys.
To both the Razzard.
You suck.
Both the Razzard.
Don't go be up.
Big schmuck.
Both the Razzard.
You suck.
Valenti says ball of bullshit.
Hollywood is bullshit.
Everything is bullshit.
So, for Ferras, bit far you go insane.
To both the Razzard.
You suck.
Both the Razzard.
To both the Razzard.
We're fucked.
Both the Razzard.
You suck.
Keep that.
Chiroky.
I think it's pretty clear that Pacifico's
Hellwise has been nominated for a podcast award.
And I have received, probably, 30.
40 different.
Please.
People saying.
Oh, please.
Tell your listeners to vote for us.
This is what I hate about awards.
It's fucking lame.
But I know Mark actually played the music and everything on that song too.
So.
They're not playing it for him.
How many pod show network podcasters are nominated this year?
I wonder, I don't know.
But, you know, it's, I don't believe in awards
that the work this way, I don't believe in awards at all.
I just want to see a nice red carpet show
with hot actresses and beautiful dresses
with millions of dollars worth of diamonds.
That's all I really care about when it comes to award shows.
And I'll even look at the magazine
coverage of it later at that, I like, you know,
I like seeing how everybody looks.
That's really what it's for.
You know, from me, who's this from Paul, Paul Parkinson.
Yeah, ITV is admitted that an Alzheimer's patient
who, quote, passes away in the final scene of a documentary
they did actually died three days later.
They're copping to it now, another story of mainstream media
unraveling.
Yeah, it's the big, it's the big deception thing.
How many, there's been so many interesting things
on television, Panorama on the BBC,
did I tell you this?
Maybe I did, no, I didn't, I think.
I think it was Monday night.
They had a huge thing about YouTube
and these happy slap videos where kids are basically
beating each other up.
And other kids' filming on their mobiles
and they put it up on YouTube, which is, you know,
it's not rampant the way it was described.
But yeah, it certainly exists.
And in this country, the happy slapy thing is,
it certainly got a lot of press and was a bit out of control.
I don't think it's all that bad, actually.
School yard fights, I mean, I've been around him,
but just, there was never an audience that was worldwide.
And so I'm not condemning or condoning any of this,
but what was interesting is they went to some
of the big brand sponsors here in the UK,
like O2, a lot of tell-com sponsors, of course,
because, you know, they love advertising on YouTube
and said, hey, you know, here's your brand right next to this kid
getting his head kicked in, how do you feel about that?
So I would say we'd watch some of the profits
of YouTube go down, because I've heard this story
has been repeated in a couple of different countries.
It's being picked up in the States, you know,
advertisers are not stupid.
They do not want to be associated with stuff like that.
That's why I know episodic programming where you have audiences
that are predictable and, and love to be a part of whatever
the community of that show is that that's a valuable property.
You know, just about those, the royalties,
know all that, and the government, and, oh crap,
don't wait, before I get to that, Keith Murray sent me this awesome
picture.
I before and after Photoshop,
I'm almost second, what was this, let me just see.
It was a red book, there you go.
Faith Hill on the cover of red book.
Now I'm not quite sure how they did it.
If they had the original picture or what it was, but
they've done the before, so the before and after the picture
and like an animated gift file.
And so you see Faith Hill who looks stunningly beautiful by the way
without any photoshopping and then you see your photoshopped
and I'm looking at the changes right now and literally
skinnier, shadows, you know, some grooves in her face
diminished a little bit.
Her arm was made much, much skinnier.
Ah, excuse me, it just makes me sick to my stomach.
If ruling a perfectly good woman, ruining her,
and tricking her is all.
Because we want to be tricked by friends, that's why.
So about about the government and royalties and, you know, old people
wanting to change the the laws when they get old
and they affect them negatively, you know, the next presidential elections,
I'm just going to vote for the youngest person.
I don't give a shit who it is.
Just someone who's young, you know, it's sure you don't have the experience.
But, you know, and the youngest person will never win,
but at least we can raise a profile and get something going.
You know, we got to get more young people in politics.
This is crazy.
This is absolutely crazy.
We're not stupid.
Young people in Iran are not stupid, you know.
Now, by the way, I think a lot of our, you know, let the world be
loving, you know, all together, a kumbaya place, that will never work either.
Because there are a lot of stupid people across all countries who could do a lot of stupid things.
But, uh, but no one, no one who's in politics right now represents me whatsoever.
And I'm not even young.
And all these, this shit actually does affect me as a singer, as a blue singer, from, you know,
the old stacks records days.
Hey, Alex Bernie.
And I wanted to call and reply to Captain Adama, who was on.
And you were talking about channels, which I think is a terrific idea.
And he was talking about the fact that he doesn't want podcasts to disappear from his iPod.
But he wants to know whether or not he's listening to them,
and he wants them to kind of fall off the playlist.
This is not a channel thing.
This is just a basic iTunes thing.
Go in and create a smart playlist that says, put all my podcasts on this playlist.
Keep them sorted out by name.
And you can tell it, play count equals zero.
So once you've played something, the play count goes up to one.
And guess what happens?
When you think the iPod again, it falls off of the playlist.
So your playlist is constantly there and just the podcast.
You haven't listened to yet.
I have a shuffle, and that's what you have to do.
You have to create playlists of your podcast,
because the shuffle doesn't support podcasting.
So I had to figure out the way around it.
But you know what?
That'll work for just a regular iPod listener, too.
So channels is still a great idea.
And now you can create a channel and put it into that smart playlist.
And then, as you listen to the stuff on the channel,
it'll fall off that playlist.
So you're still getting that same kind of interactivity.
And you can still have all the cool features of channels.
And not have to worry about it.
I listened to this already, because you know what?
iTunes will help you take care of it.
So keep up the great work, Adam.
Sorry, I kind of dropped off the grid for a while,
but I'm hoping to be back soon.
Look at for a job, if anything's gone out there,
this is burning.
I'll kill you later.
Hey, man, thank you.
Yeah, I got a job for you.
Create some kind of widget or script or something that sets people's iTunes up
for the, for the pod show channels.
I'll pay you for that, man.
Absolutely.
And for Windows, right?
Because Mac, I know we could do an Apple script or something
relatively simple.
How do you do it?
How do you set someone's smart playlist up like that,
you know, automatically, just to get them going,
because this stuff is hard, you know, people are,
are simplistic when it comes to technology.
The majority, you know, if we really want to get big audience,
we've got to make it even easier than that.
And iTunes doesn't funky shit.
They don't actually take information out of your feed about an episode.
They take the information out of the episode,
which is completely contrary to the way everyone else does it.
So we got to work around that.
And, man, I'd love it if we had some kind of set up script.
There's something you like double click on.
It immediately, it says, okay, you know,
what's your channel?
Not even better.
It's like, you want to put your channel on your iPod,
you click a button, it downloads something,
you click it, it installs, it puts your channel on your iPod
with a smart playlist, the playlist, equal play count, equal zero,
all that stuff.
Get that, I'll pay you for it.
Now, of course, this is all about the channel editing functionality.
And I'm seeing some awesome channels popping up.
I learned, by the way, that by putting my channel feed into a grazer,
golfromio AlphaZuluRomio.com, a grazer widget,
it only takes one more click to put that widget onto my Facebook.
And I don't use Facebook at all, other than to test
shit out on Facebook and it worked.
And it's pretty, pretty freaking nifty.
But it's not, it's not really a fully released feature yet.
You know, remember, I'd kind of alluded
that we're keeping this a bit hidden.
It's not really hidden, but it's not in the logical places
where you might expect it.
And well, as one Charlie had found out, it's, you know,
if you don't know where to go, looking for the cheese.
Well, even if you're a rat, you can't find it.
Hey, Adam, John Arnold here from the photo walkthrough podcast,
out photo walkthrough.btpunchow.com.
Dude, just quickly on the subject of channels,
I've had channels on my pot show account since pretty much
our signed up with pot show, which is way less November, I think.
Anyway, so I really like the idea back then,
and I figured it long last, I ought to go in and have a go with this
cheddar thing.
First thing I did was go to the pot show website
and click on my collection at the top of the page,
because I knew enough about channels to know
that there were channels stuff mentioned in the collection page.
So I went to my collection, and I'm searching down the page,
and there's my channels there, and I can see the two channels
I created a way back.
And I can see an ad show button, and that pops up a little window,
that doesn't look anything like cheddar, and I can see a button
for adding a channel, and that pops up a little window,
that doesn't look anything like cheddar.
And if I click on the text from my channel name,
it says click it to edit this channel, and if I click on that,
it pops up a window that, guess what, doesn't look anything like cheddar.
So I'm sitting here thinking, how the hell do I get to cheddar?
So I start browsing through curie.com,
and I find your post new media, new pot show media channels,
and I click on one of those, and eventually I'm looking at
somebody else's channels, and I'm thinking,
you're hang on a minute, maybe if I click on the person's profile,
and then click on the view my channels button,
then I'll get to the cheddar thing, and guess what, that works.
So I just wanted to give you some feedback that.
You seem to have two interfaces to channels right now on the website,
and it isn't as in so many other things on the pot show website,
entirely natural or intuitive, how you might find these things.
So even though I've been a long time pot show user,
and even though I know the pot show website,
probably better than most, I still couldn't find cheddar,
not without having to do a lot of searching,
way more than your typical users going to want to do.
So I figured I'd just give you that little bit of feedback,
up to you whether you use it on the show,
but in case you do, repill.
All right, sir.
Yeah, back at your buddy.
Yeah, I'm not going to use that on the show because it's too embarrassing.
No, no, as I said, we purposely did not put it anywhere else.
The only way to get to the cheddar functionality
is go to your profile, click on my channels,
and then you'll see edit channel.
From there, you can also create a new channel,
if you click on the edit channels button.
That's the only way to get to it.
But it's also the best way to display your channels,
because that's where all your channels are in one beautiful place.
So yeah, of course, it's not consistent.
And we are working on changing crap around.
Had a very interesting day yesterday.
We found something really nice.
We found that a lot of the shows that we have.
In fact, just about every single show that we have on our network,
I'm talking really about UK only now,
because that's where I've been focusing a lot of my attention
for the past weeks.
There is a print publication out there that loves the content
that that show makes.
So the first example of this new thing that we've kind of discovered,
working as news of the world, huge tabloid, weekly newspaper,
9 million readers, really big.
And Dr. Cockney, as the editor's already had guessed,
completely resonates with their audience.
So we've struck a deal, and this deal is really, really beautiful.
All of these newspapers, all magazines,
they all want to get into the video game,
because it's really the only way they can differentiate
between what they do in print and what they do online,
which is still also just words and pictures.
But they're not set up to do this.
They have no department.
They don't, the bandwidth is too expensive.
You know, all these reasons, but they have the content
and the knowledge of what an existing audience already wants.
So we're forming these partnerships,
and the first one is with the news of the world,
and it's really awesome, because they get Dr. Cockney,
co-branded as a news of the world,
and they promote them in the newspaper.
And then obviously, we have to split revenue with them
on selling ads, but that's really easy.
So we're going to do two more with news of the world.
Yesterday, I met with the editor of OK Magazine,
who, by the way, is Smokin' Hot, 32 Smokin' Hot.
And this was very interesting.
So we went to her building this, the northern shell building,
whatever it is.
It's one big publishing conglomerate, Richmond Desmond, I think,
his name is.
And she said, OK, well, a glad deal here for the meeting.
It's like 130, right?
Just let's go.
So we went out.
And we had a meeting over a bottle of white wine.
And you know, you guys, you know me, I don't drink.
So I, you know, just to be courteous, I drank,
like a whole glass and a half, whatever.
Great meeting.
Totally understands it.
We have some shows that fit into her category,
and she'd actually like to create something with us,
fantastic.
Next meeting is with,
wow, it's a call, the Daily Express.
Another one of these fabulous magazines.
And they're looking at some other shows that we have on the network.
They'd also like to work with us on.
And again, the model is, you get the promotion in the newspaper.
The video lives on their site.
It also lives at VT Podgetta.com.
It's all served from the same place.
And we get just tons and tons of new viewers.
And it's unbelievable what's happening with the good doctor.
So the proof is in the pudding.
And then, oh, and by the way, had a beer.
Went to some terrace with this editor, had a beer.
And then the third one was this,
this is named Bill Richardson, I think,
a famous sports editor for the express.
I think the Daily Star was the other one.
He's the express.
Yeah, it was three o'clock in the afternoon.
Oh, let's go out and we'll have some spritzers.
It's like, it's like five o'clock.
It's like, I've done three meetings.
And I'm completely wasted.
And of course, it was a beautiful day yesterday.
So what happens if you, with me is like one glass
alcohol consumed at any time is going to make me woozy.
But then it's warm and you had like three glasses of alcohol.
But what a day.
And then I walked from like, God knows where I was back to the office.
Got lost.
You know, I wanted to walk in the streets of shortage for about an hour.
Finally rolled into the office around six.
You know, the people still work in there.
The portable airco units are on high blast.
You know, basically just recirculating warm air.
I had to take off my shirt and walk around my wife beaters.
It was that that disgusting.
But I'm very, very excited because it seems like we found some perfect matches,
some perfect partnerships to really, really get our network of programming out there.
And what a way to do it.
Never knew that that would work.
Very, very interesting.
So while I'm out here, shit's happening back state side.
Yeah, we had them.
This is John and K.C. calling a long time listener.
Um, do you have a brother in Kansas City?
Because I'm driving here and there is a red Chevy pickup with personalized license plates.
Like to say, pot father on it.
And the dude driving could be your brother.
He looks just like you and blonde hair.
That's kind of scary.
So are you actually just pretending to be over in England?
And you're actually here in the middle of America, uh, podcasting.
Hmm, conspiracies around.
Thanks a lot, man.
Let me show you how to talk about it.
Dude, dude, dude, get a picture already.
You got to get a picture of this.
This is unbelievable.
It's very possible that there's some guy getting late in Kansas City.
And, you know, identity theft is lame when you're getting late for it.
And the original identity doesn't.
That just totally sucks.
Get me a picture.
Kansas City, let's work on this together.
Hey, this is Ron from zip-71101 podcast.
So I'm glad that you are listening to Trucker Tom.
Trucker Tom is a great guy and you'll enjoy his podcast every single day.
Not only that, have you seen Finding America?
His new HD high definition video podcast.
If not, you need to get on board.
It's a great podcast and you'll enjoy every single minute on it.
And while you're at it, come on over to zip-71101.com and take a listen.
See you there.
Hey, Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel.
Hope you're well.
We've got two rhythm games on the show this week.
We've got Parapama, the rapper on the PSP versus Elite Beat Agents on the DS.
We've also got a great feature on the God of War game for the PSP.
And we're given away Final Fantasy Fables, Choker Boatails for the DS.
Check it out at gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
Right on Matt, I like that show.
He's doing a video version too, which is going to be pretty cool.
Whole new type of format.
Very, very interesting.
Early in the week, I got a call from me.
It was last week, got a call from Guy and New Zealand who countered me by saying that
Australians are ugly and they sleep with their family members and with sheep.
And I parade and said, but no, I've only seen cute Australians.
Wow, I'll leave it up to those boys and girls down under to respond.
Hey big fellow, I feel Walker calling in from Australia.
I just wanted to take the opportunity to respond to the Kiwi who was on the DSC yesterday.
Let me just say this.
No, I haven't got a mallet.
No, I'm not ugly.
The maybe not as good looking as the big headfag.
Looking at my wife, she's gorgeous.
I couldn't want more.
Three good looking sons, not a mallet to be seen.
Mate, we're just typical Australians.
Not ugly, no mallets, just normal.
An idea saying most Kiwi's are just the same.
I've been thinking about your Kiwi caller and I reckon he's the guy he's been
causing with a trouble in the sheep paddock next door.
So Kiwi, believe those sheep alone, get down to a good Aussie beach or up into the mountains
into the snow and get it with some real good looking Australians.
You might just get a surprise.
Hey, have a great day.
Blue pill, but turning red, oh good, folder.
All right, man.
Yeah, there's always been a bit of an animosity between the Australians and the New Zealanders.
That's why he's calling him a Kiwi.
I love the, the reminding me of the pink Floyd song, though.
I was like, hey Kiwi, leave those sheep alone.
Damn, damn, did him.
I can just hear the recorders clicking on all over New Zealand as we speak.
Yeah, so I'm in trouble.
Come on on, man.
And prolific programmer.
Hi, I am prolific programmer.
Yeah, two things.
First off, one to express me condolences for Yan Polet sauce.
I mean, Yan, you're, you're like, you make the show more worth listening to.
Now, as would be every Friday with your, it tests nine joy playing along.
Second thing, Adam regarding the channels,
editor, your new cheddar feature.
I can't seem to figure out how to activate it on my channels.
That's all.
Cheers.
Oh, I prolific programmer in reverse order there, my friend.
If you have existing channels, then you have to do perform some kind of edit for it to kick in.
So click on, you know, go to one of your existing channels.
Move something around, move it back.
That's how you activate it.
Just have to make one edit, essentially.
There is no save button just with the minute you start editing it does it.
And then, you know, I've received such an outpouring of love and good thinking and
nice thoughts for a Yan Polet producer of the hit test for the daily source code.
He and his wife witnessed a real family tragedy.
They lost a, they lost a unborn baby.
And most comments that come in, people say,
well, actually, here, listen to this one and this is very, very common.
I've received a lot of these and I don't want to do a whole like, you know,
Yan, Yan thing.
But I do, well, listen to the comment.
Adam, I'm so sorry for Yan and his wife.
You recognize long and hard over when you can tell people about something like that.
And when you go public with the idea that you might be having a trial,
and I can only imagine how hard it must have been for Yan to finally come to the conclusion
that, wow, it's not gonna be safe now, I can tell people and then to have something like this happen.
I know that this is probably not gonna make the podcast, and you know what it probably should,
but I know that Yan is a friend of yours and you probably take form in the same way that I would
take for close friends, so I just want to take them home to say, I'm sorry for you,
and then for Yan and for everyone who's touched by this, and I hope everyone is well.
Thanks a lot, it's Bernie and I'll talk to you soon.
Oh, man, it's beautiful, thank you.
And, well, you know my theory about these things.
The good and the bad, it's documented in our memories throughout our lives,
and it usually happens through something that we call the soundtrack to our lives.
And I think that this next song is going to be embedded into this moment
and in my soundtrack forever. Jersey Todd sent this one, he says, Adam,
don't know if you want to check the song out, it's very sad, it involves one of my favorites,
Kevin Birdick who lost an infant daughter as well.
So again, thank everyone for all that outpouring of love, and let's make this a part of the
soundtrack to our lives in memory of Yan and Victorings' daughter.
Here in my eyes, in baby, sometimes it feels like I'm drowning.
The sea hasn't got me and I can't breathe.
I feel so helpless.
She's so pure and so lovely, she's floating on my me,
to cut for this world, she's sleeping peacefully,
let's wait, she's dreaming on me, to cut for this world.
And somewhere, somewhere, the angel flies softly, missing her mother and I can't feel.
She's watching over and somewhere, a spirit is tossing and turning, waiting at one
to bring patiently, will we return?
She's so pure and so lovely, she's floating on my me,
to cut for this world, she's sleeping peacefully, she's dreaming on me,
to cut for this world, and the heavens and our fathers will look over home tonight,
and the hills are throughout her, so I'll keep in our warm with light, that's right, that's right.
You're so pure and so lovely, you're floating on my me, to cut for this world,
you're sleeping peacefully, let's wait, she's dreaming on me, to cut for this world.
For ever embedded in the soundtrack to our lives, Kevin Burtick, too good for this world.
You know, I have some other stuff I was going to play for you, but I think we should just leave it
at that, leave the last tones of Kevin Burtick roaming throughout your mind, because this is what
good friend of mine, Tony Khan, who does a WGBH morning stories and has been involved in this
movement from early on, would call humanity. Here we are, Jersey Todd, a guy, I don't know him,
I've never met him, I've never met John Palette in person, either. Listen to all these people connecting,
people who clearly are connecting at a very deep and very spiritual level with each other
through technology and through art, that we're creating ourselves without any other help or intervention
from any other organization or governmental body. It's a beautiful thing, if I never make a freaking
dime with this stuff, ever again, it won't make a difference because this, this is truly what it's
about, when you can touch someone through media. I'll try and do another one for you tomorrow.
I am flying tomorrow morning, taking the lovely lady Patricia to the Netherlands, so it will be
a late one, but at least I'm home, and I'm not in the city. DannySourceco.com, Adam at podshow.com,
kiss somebody today, will ya?