Check out some of the world's best music video.
Animation at short films from the Manchester International Festival
and brought to you by Sony PlayStation at M-I-F-D-I-C-O-D-C-O-O.
Delta Sierra Charlie, six, five, four.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic, it's metal curry.
You hoped you'd last but still you'd never known.
Tell me that you think you knew it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Now you feel you need to know it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You don't know what it is.
Tell me how I need to know it.
I might have thought you'd do the things I say.
You're still outside freezing for this anyway.
You'll feel you'll never know it.
Tell me how I need to know it.
You're still outside freezing for this anyway.
Tell me that you think you knew it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Now you feel you need to know it.
You don't know what it is.
Tell me how I need to know it.
Still I know I need to know it.
Tell me that you think you knew it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Now you feel you need to know it.
You don't know what it is.
Tell me how I need to know it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Fire eggs, a lot of things are using that work.
It's over.
Which is pretty much sums it up for the the curry coast vacation.
And kind of the way I was feeling just before getting ready to do this show, which is coming to you from the the Magnum.
If you don't know what a Magnum is.
I suggest you go to Google and you check out Dodge Magnum.
It is the the only rental car that was available to us and the one that I picked up in Savio, New York, which we've used today.
To cruise over to the Roosevelt field mall, which is in Garden City, New York, about 30 foot, about a 40 minute drive from from Savio.
So we took the ferry 10 o'clock this morning.
I had the whole family.
I've got, of course, the lady Patricia and Christina and then my sister willow and her two darling kids.
Sabina and Mateo, Sabina 7 Mateo is a nine years old.
I have to tell you for two kids who have been pretty much stuck inside the beach house looking out at the waves crashing down upon the breakers because of just horrible horrible weather.
They have been absolutely delightful.
I mean, of course, you know, they've been playing scrabble and thank God for the Disney channel and high school musical too.
Boy, that's a real life saver.
So back to the good old days. Here I am sitting in the car in the parking lot.
I've got the window cracked just a little bit. So, you know, just for some basic air to come in.
I've got the car engine running.
I'm running on battery power. So hopefully, let me just check and see what what I've got left on the old via here one hour and 15 minutes. That should be okay if the time is correct.
I got to tell you, I was pretty down last night yesterday. I was just down in general. You know, of course, the weather wasn't helping.
And when the weather's crap, you know, you figure, well, I'll sit inside. I'll do a little bit of work or maybe I'll prep the show and I think everyone else was inside on the island and was surfing.
In fact, I timed it at 902 AM. That's when I presume everyone's up. The stores that are on the island are open for business and bandwidth goes down to a crunch.
Not just down to a crunch, you know, just to a little drip through a straw, but connections actually breaking. It makes Gmail renders Gmail pretty much useless.
Unless you use the HTML version, even that seems like a long URLs have a real problem in a low slash broken bandwidth environment.
And I was thinking, you know, I worked 12 hours a day, typically. I'm always trying to find a spot, you know, I need about three hours to do the show an hour worth of prep about 40 minutes to an hour worth of recording and then there's always show notes and uploads and all that stuff.
And I was like, man, I might as well not do the show at all. It's almost impossible for me to commit to it. And I was feeling really, really down about it. Just like, you know, crap. Why don't I just focus 100% all my energy, all my time on pod show.
And then when, you know, when things let up a little bit and we have enough people installed and can take over some duties for me, then I'll get back to the source code and I was really, really planning on shutting it down for a little while.
And then I listened to some of the comments that came in today and gosh, I really feel much better.
I had a money and see where I was listening from Camden and London. It's just coming up to one o'clock in the morning. I'm just outside work, lean it.
I'm really satisfied on a PhD student and I've just finished literally four years' worth of practical work like PhDs or where it becomes a lab again.
And I'm the nurse to you. You've been my constant lab buddy for the past years since I started podcasting.
And since you've been around the this time, I thought since you've been around with me with a daily source code that you should probably know that I finished my practical work.
Thanks very much for the show. I'll keep listening.
You know, so first of all, congratulations on finishing the PhD and, you know, you hear stuff like that and there's a whole bunch of other comments that came in and like, wow, there's a lot more going on.
There's a lot more of a relationship between me and you guys out there listening and it would be, it almost be like breaking up with your favorite girlfriend, you know.
So, thank you. That call, that particular call really made a difference it really did.
I just so you know, the setup. I've got my a via my Sony via running cast blaster, of course. I've got the the wireless microphone pair set up. I've got my headphones on.
You know, people are driving by here in the parking lot looking at me like, what is that fool doing?
Roosevelt Field Mall. Roosevelt Field Mall. Roosevelt Field actually, a very important aviation history. This is the, when it was still a field before they erected this humongoid structure.
It, a lot of famous flights were made here. Probably the most famous was Charles Limberg who took off from here to arrive in Paris, like 33 or 33 and a half hours later.
And yeah, it's kind of interesting to be sitting on, I guess, what formerly were the fields knowing that this was a place of such historic importance in an aviation history.
And I got just tons and tons of comments I want to get to. This is one that I'm very proud of. This is from Blake Morgan. Now, I played, by the way, had I known that the Blake was going to call in. I probably would have, would have downloaded maybe I'm amazed.
Maybe I'm amazed again, because it's such an awesome version of the Paul McCartney classic Blake called in and just really gave me some very exciting news, which is all a part of the pot safe music network and the platform and the revolution that we're all building together here. Listen to Blake.
Adam Curry, daily source code. This is Blake Morgan from New York, Colin in. So your spin of maybe I'm amazed on Tuesday has changed everything here with our release of this record.
And what we're doing at the label on a personal note, first of all, again, you're, I shot you an email about this, but you're, you're call out at the end of the, at the end of the song and something I will never forget. And it's going to be my press kit forever, but much more importantly, the reaction out in the actual world was unbelievable. We had such a humongous bump on iTunes that we're still trying to pick up the pieces.
Maybe I'm amazed has become the most successful download in engine company record history. It's the single most downloaded song of my career and briefly it topped iTunes on Tuesday after your show.
And what's more is that it's carried through for the remainder, you know, for the last couple days, if you go to iTunes and you go to my page, Blake Morgan on the page and you look at my top songs, you're going to see a gigantic bar across the screen.
For maybe I'm amazed and these tiny little, tiny little bars next to it for all the other songs, which is just put, you know, the massive amount of downloads that we've gotten for that song in comparison to everything else.
I did National Radio on Friday, National Syndicated Radio Show, the Lisa Bermback Show, she was terrific, I was on for half an hour and we got absolutely nothing close to the bump that we got from you spinning that song once on your show.
Anyone who thinks that podcasting is not beating out to restroom radio is insane because it absolutely is certainly in this case.
And what's more is that today on e-music, which is the second biggest music retailer in the world, five of the top 20 albums are albums from our record label.
My record that may be on May is on and four others, we have five albums in the top 20 and they have a catalog of 20,000 records.
So we are kicking ass and you have led the charge and really changed the nature of what this release is like.
So I'm here to say thank you and again, if anybody doesn't think that shows like yours and what you're doing and what PMN is doing is really the way of the future and make a different certain thing because it really is.
So thank you and so glad you dug the track and I hope to talk to you soon man.
Be well.
Alright, Blake Morgan, everybody.
They, wow, big difference when the mic cracks, huh?
Well, first of all, I'd like to take thanks for it, but I can't really, I mean, this is the work of thousands of people and of course, thousands of daily source code listeners who were tuned in, you know?
And I think that we are at several tipping points where it's some form of critical mass that's taking place where indeed it makes a lot more sense for you to start your own label to record your own stuff.
Do it at your house, do it on pro tools, get it out there, release it, get the CD on e-muse it or CD baby and put your tracks on iTunes and and then promote it.
There are many different avenues, podcasts, music network being one of them and all these independent shows.
It's phenomenal, it really, really is and I obviously couldn't be more proud of what has happened and encourage anyone who is thinking of doing something in music to check out the different options that are available.
I actually have asked Blake and he's a real busy guy, I've asked him if he could put together some kind of like a small video clip or something.
We're going to produce it, I've asked Mark Yoshimo to help out with that, you know, for him to put together maybe just like a three to five minute blurb that'll be on the podcast music network that shows people.
What steps you need to take to really do something independently, it's not just putting your music on the podcast music network obviously there's a lot more that goes along with that and there's a lot of things that you can do and a lot of them very cheaply if not for free.
So look for that very soon, God, I'm so happy about that and the next show I'm going to play the track again because it's just an awesome awesome version.
So one more day on fire island which besides the weather has been quite delightful.
The vibe is nice, all the people on the island are nice, it's you know it's just in general it's it's really really been nice and well there's some some history to it.
I think I've discussed most of it, but if not here's a here's another call about it.
Hey Adam it's burning, I'm listening to your chat about fire island and it is a beautiful place but a little bit about the unusual history behind it for a long time in the 70s and the 80s and I'm not sure whether it continued on into the 90s.
But fire island was considered to be a gay highway and all of the beaches were predominantly gay beaches so it was that kind of a place.
Doesn't mean it wasn't beautiful but it certainly does have an interesting history beyond the more ancient but the more recent is also of note.
I'm not sure how it is now I'd be curious to hear if you noted anything like that when you were there or whether that history is behind it.
I hope you had a good trip to New York, I'm sorry that I didn't get a chance to hook up with you but maybe the next time you're here, talk to you later.
I'll definitely be in New York again soon, you can count on that and for those of you who know of the TV program Little Britain.
There's this great sketch where there's this guy called David and he says I am the only gay in the village, well guess what we are the only non-gays in the village.
I don't know if it's considered a highway but I think the community there is pretty much 90% gay lesbian and whatever else you can think of in those categories and of course that doesn't make any difference to us.
Actually, if anything, it makes it really nice because everyone's just so friendly.
No one's worried about what people think about you, what you look like the dress code is completely casual, you can go into.
There are a couple of actually I think there's two nice restaurants and you can walk in there and you're in your trunks if you want in your swimming trunks.
The clothing appears to be pretty much optional on the beaches, although you definitely want to wear something with the weather the way it is.
But it's great and I have a feeling that it being a gay hideaway is probably been that way for a long time.
In case in point, we have proof that PW Fenden was here in 1972.
Come to podcasting.
Don't be alarmed or negro.
Two guys in a mic.
What's happening in the world? You all are not ready.
A little bit of sports, a little bit of entertainment, a little bit of comedy, a little bit of seriousness.
And you got two guys in a mic.
EFP and page two.
Senior writer, Elsie Granis and thanks for joining.
Hey, thanks guys for having me.
I think I was on the idea of that.
You know, friendship is a two-way street.
And just as you want with the fear of friendship friends, you want what's best for you.
Right.
That's true.
You know, but you're making a very, have a fit in my collar.
You're making a very intelligent and logical decision in a problem that's within the heart.
Two guys in a mic.
If you were driving under the influence, you need to snatch your hands off the road.
I don't want you running into me killing me or killing my family.
And that rant was brought to you by me.
I got to say one thing.
That's pretty what man loves the show.
Really cool show.
I'll definitely turn in again.
That's two guys in a mic.
Every Tuesday, eight o'clock Eastern on TalkShoot.com.
You know, I got to find out.
That sounded like a combination of Mark Yoshimuna and M.Coff
and Tony Price from Costas World.
I quite sure I definitely got to check that one out.
You know, of all the comments that come in,
and I screen every single one of them.
There's only one person that I will play unconditionally,
without even having listened to the comment as I have not done with this one.
It's just titled Korea.
It could only be from the one and only.
Comics trip.
How the Adam Kerry.
Here is your Polish friend, CSP.
Adam.
I have a question for your Uncle Dunn.
I remember a story about Grandmother,
that one Korean friend, Talk nuance.
She was taken to Japan by Japanese and violated.
My question.
Is it true that hatred towards Japanese steel is ripe
in both Korea's North and South?
You're all.
All right, CSB.
Well, as you know, I'm still working on how exactly we're going to capture Uncle Dunn's story telling.
This is a question I can ask in regardless,
so I'll be talking to him next week,
and I'll ask him.
I have no idea.
And of course, I think times have probably changed.
So it may not be that way anymore.
If you've been following Curry dot com,
you probably saw I posted,
well, from time to time,
we'll just post channels that people are making with our,
with cheddar, our channel editor,
which is now a feature that is available to every single,
account on potshot.com.
Oh, man, wait until you see the new dashboard
and the stuff that's coming,
which I don't know if we're going to have one big like switch.
I think we'll be rolling pieces out
bit by bit,
but some of them will be pretty drastic,
and I think we've leaked a lot of the,
a lot of the nagging bits of confusing interface, etc.
I found a great channel,
which I think actually it popped up.
How did I find that?
I might have found it through one of my ego filters
or like a filter for pod show or something.
For fantasy football,
which is a great,
a great channel to follow along with,
particularly now the football season
has just begun or about to begin.
And well, the guy who built the channel sent in a comment.
This is Mark,
and this is John,
from Pixkin Radio.
We put together a fantasy football channel on pod show.
That's right,
it's a collection of quality fantasy football podcasts,
along with our show,
a weekly injection of fantasy smack
to feed your addiction.
That's right,
so get on over to
Pixkin.potshow.com
to add the channel to your iTunes
or pod catcher in joy.
Yeah,
and there you go,
a promo for a channel.
It can't get much more nuttyer,
but I think it will,
and as we improve on the channel editor,
by the way,
an idea there is to,
to put a single episode,
like an intro or something at the,
at the front of the channel,
so whenever someone gets it for the first time,
or whenever they get it,
or whenever they refresh it,
basically,
they'll get your new intro to the channel.
There's a lot more that we can do
to help people package this,
and of course,
widgets on the other end,
so you can put it on your page,
anywhere you want to,
and your Facebook,
or your MySpace,
and I'm very,
very excited about that,
and really happy to see that this thing
is gaining traction,
because it's,
well,
it's what I had hoped for,
and it's really changing the way
that people are using RSS,
and without even knowing that they're using RSS,
and mashing stuff together,
coming up with,
with entertainment.
It really is.
You don't even have to,
create a show to,
to entertain,
just put together a channel of great stuff.
It's a fantastic way for other people
to find programming,
and when we start putting our connections together,
you'll see that it's really awesome
when you,
when you find a channel,
see who else is subscribed to that channel,
what other shows they have,
a really reminiscent of the old Napster.
Remember when you could go into someone's hard drive,
and look at all those songs they had,
after finding one song,
you could just say,
oh, let me see what else this guy,
or gal has,
that's the kind of,
the kind of social network that,
that we've envisioned,
and it really,
really is starting to come true.
All right,
let me see,
I got so much stuff to get through,
let's play this one real quick.
Right,
my name is TQ White.
I think that regarding the eye player issue,
you got it exactly wrong.
The fact that it's a peer-to-peer application,
makes the net neutrality consequences,
even worse.
All right, let me just set this up for a second.
I was talking about the BBC eye player,
when you actually install it,
it installs peer-to-peer software,
which you cannot turn off,
called Kentucky.
So essentially,
your machine,
whenever it's connected to the network,
whether you like it or not,
is a part of the infrastructure
that the BBC is put in place,
so they don't have to pay for bandwidth.
And I don't really have that much of a problem with it,
but,
well,
listen to the rest of the comment,
and I'll tell you why I think peer-to-peer is a virus,
and why it is a problem,
and why it has nothing to do with net neutrality,
rather with that PR,
bad marketing,
and the infrastructure.
Here's what's going on.
People pay for their bandwidth,
to their home computer.
They are supposed to be allowed to use that bandwidth
for whatever the X they want.
If they choose to use it for a peer-to-peer application,
so be it.
That's what they want to do.
In my estimation,
the net neutrality concept says
that we do not want the faceless bureaucrats
in the internet service provider organizations
to be deciding how we use our network bandwidth
that we pay for.
Okay, I just got to stop you there for a second.
Okay, so here's the problem.
The problem is, of course,
that the ISPs,
the people who deliver internet to your home,
never, ever in a million years,
never thought that this would happen.
They would just think, in fact,
it's called ADSL, a synchronous digital subscriber line
because you get just a little bit of upstream
and much more downstream
because they're thinking,
well, people are going to consume.
No one ever thought about people producing
and serving stuff and sending stuff up the pipe,
and they also never really figured
that you might be consuming 24-7.
Like, okay, I'll click on a page, the page comes in.
And of course,
there's a lot of shared resources on these networks,
and the entire internet is based on overselling
the pipes that they have available.
So there's a lot less bandwidth
than they're selling,
because they never expected
for these types of protocols to be put into place.
So, of course, if they had said this 10 years ago,
or maybe, yeah, about 10 years ago
when broadband started to proliferate
and say, well, you can't do this, you can't do that.
It would have been a very different story,
but they never did,
and they can't back out of that now.
But when it comes to the resources of the network,
if everyone is using their network connection that way,
then it'll bring the entire network down,
or at least that segment.
That's just a physical fact I would say.
So, it has nothing to do with net neutrality.
It only has to do with net neutrality.
It only has to do with the fact that they cannot sustain their network.
So, I think we're going to be looking
at an upgrade there for the ISPs,
and of course, as a whole backstory to that,
that the telco has got all this money,
and they should have been spending it
on building out their infrastructure,
which they probably didn't.
They probably spent it on a whole bunch of hogwash marketing,
and which is a shame,
because, you know, as I said on curie.com,
my blog, you know,
I think the broadband in the States
is really pretty lame compared to,
certainly compared to the experiences I've had in Europe,
whiteness the mesh network on Fire Island.
And again, that's just the oversaturation of the network.
So, it's not about net neutrality, it's about lying.
It's about lying that they have this fantastic network,
and all this bandwidth that you can consume,
and they really don't have it.
They've oversold you.
So, I'm down with you on that.
Unfortunately, I just don't buy the net neutrality part.
All they're trying to do is trying to,
basically make their network usable for everybody,
and if you've got a whole bunch of peer-to-peer applications running,
running continuously, that's a problem for them.
So, it's a different fight, okay?
It's not about them determining what content you can,
or you can't see.
And by the way, a lot of the peer-to-peer stuff,
of course, it's illegal.
We'll just say that the BBC stuff is not illegal,
but that's really what the problem boils down to.
I don't think it's about net neutrality.
Let's see what else you have to say in this comment.
The idea that they want the BBC to pay for this bandwidth
is doubly silly, because the BBC isn't doing it.
I suppose that you could imagine,
you could say that the peer-to-peer applications
are sort of a virus to the extent that
an application that gets into someone else's head,
that they want to use that causes them to behave in a way
that is beneficial to the BBC,
is a valid way to look at it.
However, what you've got here is people that are paying for bandwidth
that are using it the way they want to,
and the internet service provider is saying,
hey, well, you happen to be benefiting the BBC,
so they gotta pay.
In fact, I believe that that's wrong.
Hope you're having a good day.
I'd like your vacation.
Nice podcast.
Good luck with your company.
Bye-bye.
I think I appreciate it.
So I believe me.
I'm definitely against the man.
It's just there's a lot of confusion about what net neutrality
is really supposedly about or is supposed to be about.
And I just don't think this is the issue.
This is about them.
Just not having the resources to,
you know, they've sold you a bag of goods, essentially.
So I'd call it false advertising before I call it a net neutrality issue.
Let's roll another promo here.
Hey, you.
Do me a favor.
Go over to your radio, flip it on,
and tell me what you hear.
The same old crap, right?
But what did you expect?
Wait a minute.
Let's take the test right now.
Okay.
Actually, that wasn't too bad.
I'd get a little bit of chocolate cognate, no body.
So let's scan the dial here.
Nothing.
What?
It was real.
Trying to find the speakers.
Okay, that's boring.
What's this?
Z100 boring.
boring.
Okay.
Yeah, you're right, same old crap.
That's where podcasting comes in.
Look, there's hundreds of thousands of podcasts out there,
and thousands of music podcasts as well.
I'm but one of them.
What do you think I'm doing this promo?
I'm Potcia Radio.
I feature one artist per show.
You're going to hear some music.
You're going to hear the background of the band.
You're going to find out where you can buy their cities
and where you can see them live.
So, after you listen to all the other podcasts,
give me a try.
My name's Brent,
and you can find me over at PotciaRadio.com.
That ground music provided by the band,
46 Bliss.
I love it when people use podcasts,
music and promos,
and credit them in the promo,
which actually melds right into this next question.
Yeah, this is Chris and Philadelphia.
You may not know,
but I'm a digital artist.
I'm working on some video stuff.
I've always been visual person making art in Photoshop.
It's very quiet.
There's no audio.
And now I get up in video.
I need some music in there.
I have a question about the licensing for Pod State music.
If I call my art a show and produce it
and report it as such on the Pod State music network,
can I make a video that includes a soundtrack
that is Pod State?
Is that something I can do just download
from the Pod State music network?
Or do I have to work out something
individually with the artists
which I'm sure would be not too hard either
because it's on the piano.
It's a quick question.
Hopefully you can answer on a show or something like this.
All right, ma'am.
So the short answer is yes.
Of course, that's a valid use of Pod State music.
There's a little bit of a longer answer to it.
I need to know a bit more about what you're doing.
But yeah, you're certainly allowed to do that.
Of course, you do have to credit the artist
in that piece of work and report it back
to the network.
Please, everybody continue to report your plays
back to the network.
It's very, very important for the artists
who are making their art available.
So yeah, it's what we call, I think,
a derivative work, just call it a mashup.
Now, how you use it is where you're probably
your safest bet is to contact the artist.
For instance, if you were to sell these
and duplicate these, there could be some issues there.
So it's always a safe bet just to contact the artist
if you want to do something like something of that nature.
But the whole point is you should be able to use
music for a show regardless of what it is.
If it's a video show or if it's pictures
that you've done would like Ken's burns effect
or if it's in enhanced podcasts,
it's all kind of multiple sides of the same coin.
So should not be a problem, but it's always nice
to reach out to the artist and let them know
what you're doing with it.
And who knows, maybe there's more you can do with that artist.
That's how great connections are made.
It's a really up-point-cost,
it's like a custom on technique,
but it's not scared.
It's a weird point,
I like a point,
net-sniz-tek-gest-reck-cost.
No, you should know it.
Do you see 654?
I should have played that one at the beginning of the show,
Gustav.
I'd have a 10-email thread with Gustav.
He's from Sweden,
and he sent me a message saying,
hey man, I want to do a show.
What software are you using?
I put it into cast blaster,
and then he said, oh, this is fantastic.
I'll let you know what I've my show up and running.
And I said, I sent me a promo.
He said, in Swedish, I said, well, yeah, of course.
Why not?
I didn't understand one word of it,
but yeah, absolutely.
Now, from Sweden to home with the Beatles.
Hello, Adam.
It's a call on my beautiful England long time list
that's from the days when you came in from Belgium,
and moved to Gilford, fabulous show.
Love it, listen to it all the time at the essay.
Just thought that it'd be something maybe
of interest to you.
I was on the scope of a show website,
and he demonstrated a new application
to me called the VOD, the EODIA.com,
which allows you to do a live broadcast,
a live video broadcast on your laptop,
which then archives as well.
Which I thought will be great for you.
You know, will be great for us as listeners.
So we're able to see you, perhaps,
through a part of the show.
You can schedule it so we can all watch it a certain time,
and then we can watch the archive, if we miss it.
If you go to www.VODIA.com,
you'll give it to say,
well, it's all about.
I've used it on my blog,
which is the virtual travelcast.com.
Just thought it'd be good,
and I would really like to see you doing something like that.
Anyway, thanks for the show.
I really enjoyed the folder.
I can't imagine what a sponge it does to be honest with you.
Sorry.
Yeah, man, great.
Yeah.
No, if only I had time to figure all that stuff out
and set that up.
One day, one day, we'll get that on some kind of schedule.
Something else I was going to say,
and then I felt my iPhone vibrate in my pocket,
someone's trying to get a hold of me.
God knows what that's all about.
See, I was talking about, no, I don't remember.
It's completely gone.
I'll tell you what.
I've got about 17, not about.
I have exactly 17 minutes of battery power left,
so I can play one more song, say goodbye,
and then if I run inside into the mall next to the Apple store,
where there's a fantastic leather couch,
just by the way, big up, big props to Apple
for having a humongous bandwidth available on Open Wi-Fi.
Here at Roosevelt Field Mall,
really, really appreciate that's Devo.
That's fantastic.
That's the way it should be, man.
I really, really love that.
So then I'll be able to upload.
Well, then it's back to fire on one more night.
We got some sun predicted for tomorrow
and tomorrow evening we fly back to the UK.
So I'm going to leave you with a band from just around the corner,
more or less, from Connecticut,
they're called Echoing August.
I think you'll like this.
It's got a couple of good plays on the pot,
it's a music network.
I'm looking at the pot blazing here.
It's titled, The Song From Yesterday,
on Your Journey.
What should I say to Chuck?
They had a source coming.
I dealt this year.
And you know that I'll be there.
I want to go there.
I'm as lucky as being there.
I want to know that if you feel the same.
And you know that I'll be there.
But looking back on what I said before now,
I'll take my chances.
It's not my problem at all.
It's my pride fighting for it.
No, no, no.
It's just a beautiful day before.
You did not know what I'm about.
Still isn't your head no doubt.
Can't believe that I have still around.
Where you come and like time and kiss on the back of the floor.
Like tons and tons with it before.
And you know that I'll be there.
But looking back on what I said before now,
I'll take my chances.
It's not my problem at all.
It's just my pride fighting for it.
You did not know what I'm about.
Still isn't your head no doubt.
Can't believe that I have still around.
But looking back on what I said before now,
I'll take my chances.
It's not my problem at all.
It's my pride fighting for it.
No, no, no.
It's just a beautiful day before.
You did not know what I'm about.
Still isn't your head no doubt.
Can't believe that I have still around.
You did not know what I'm about.
Still isn't your head no doubt.
Well from the timer here on cast blaster, I
thought that song was going to last about a minute and a half longer.
Apparently it's the longest fade out in history,
but just about perfect, to hit our 40 minute mark for this daily source code episode number
604.
With some luck, y'know I might record one on the
plane home.
We've got time tomorrow, I'll see what
Of course Friday over the weekend next week is going to be absolutely chocolate block in London with with meetings
But I guess I'm just going to have to resort back to a little bit of the older format
And just record wherever I can and do whatever I can bringing you the true meaning of source code
Just the crap that's running around in my brain
So
Appreciate you listening. I appreciate you taking the time to subscribe check out
PotShow dot com daily source code dot com for all the show notes at today's episode
And if you got anything to say just drop me an email add them at pot show dot com
We'll be talking very soon everybody
Take care now. Bye-bye another pot show podcast. Stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest
Subdupt daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pot show and limelight
Are