The $60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass, then the next generation radio content
in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
On Jestig, it's Adam Curry.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels still think they can govern
what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses and make big
media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content comes the daily source code
with Adam Curry.
Delta, share it Charlie, five, nine or one.
Me from reality.
I'm losing ground and I'm feeling fast.
I see the sound of a trouble fast.
I never wanted this to be.
But no this isn't right.
But this isn't right.
This song, and here those screams ain't just a film, I take your hand, you seem to understand
I wish I knew what I was running into, I felt so fast.
I know this wouldn't last though.
I'm losing ground and I'm feeling fast.
I see the sound of a trouble fast.
I never wanted this to be.
But no this isn't right.
But this isn't right.
I'm losing ground and I'm feeling fast.
I see the sound of a trouble fast.
I never wanted this to be.
I know this isn't right.
But this isn't right.
But this isn't right for me.
This isn't right for me.
Come and round, I need a better life.
This is the life for me.
It's completely pot safe.
And what that means, well, hopefully we'll be exploring that in today's show.
It is daily source code episode 591 coming to you from the curry manner in the
affluent suburb of Suri known as Gulford west side of the G-town be represented.
It's good to be back home.
Man, let me tell ya.
It's good.
It's really, really good.
I didn't sleep a wink on the plane back from San Francisco.
I don't know what it was.
Actually, I do know what it was.
It was a combination of just as not being tired.
And the fact that it still was despite the the subvant recording schedule which took place
a little bit earlier in the evening than the normal.
I just didn't get to bed on time.
What can I say?
By the time that the flight arrived was only like an hour after I normally would have gone
gone to bed.
So it just didn't work.
And some weird people on the plane just exuding a weird vibe.
Oh, one of them being Joan Rivers, well known in the United States and in the United
Kingdom, of course.
In fact, I think she furthered her career for many years in Britain before taking over
tonight's show a couple times for Johnny Carson.
Then she became a huge household name in the States.
I've actually been on a couple of her talk shows in the in the MTV era, in the MTV
days.
And so she was she was kind of it was weird because she was city.
I wasn't like a 10k.
My seat is usually 12k or 11k or 10k.
I like to be on the right hand side right across from the massage center in the
Virginia upper class, which is so that means I'm not looking at other people.
Other people aren't looking at me.
The only person I can be looking at is the person who's actually getting a treatment.
Which is nice because I can observe them.
And so this is like a little island.
And when we were aborting the plane and I was on pretty early and I was chill and
reading a book.
Joan Rivers is just circling around.
You know, like she was almost like on a confessional just walking.
And at first I was like, who's that man?
That's that someone is having some problems walking.
Oh, it's because she's old.
Oh, my God.
It's Joan Rivers.
And the face was just amazing.
And I couldn't help but stay.
And I was kind of like peering over my glasses pretending to read my book.
Now I've been on her show.
So I think she recognized me.
She didn't say anything.
And it wasn't that moment where I could say, hey, Joan.
But boy, oh boy, pretty frightening.
And love the woman to death.
She's in her 70s.
I'm not quite sure how old she is.
But the face lift is just an amazing piece of work.
And she got a massage later.
And I could see the girl.
Massaging her very softly is nothing.
Like, you know how my grandmother when she was.
She passed away when she was 98 years old.
Unbelievable.
Lifetime.
And my grandfather as well.
Both of them passed very shortly.
Very closely each other.
And but, you know, I remember my grandmother's back in her 90s.
And it looked just like Joan Rivers back.
It was, it was just surprising.
You know, we're all going to get old.
And we're all going to look fucked up into crap.
But it'll be the first one, of course.
But, um, man.
It was just nothing like the representation on television.
I hadn't seen her in person in a long, long time.
Anyway.
So, no sleep.
No rest for the week.
I did chill a little bit on the.
It was so beautiful when I came home.
It was just spectacular weather.
Very much like what I left in San Francisco.
Only not as hot, which is nice.
And today is another beautiful day.
I've been looking at it that since I don't have to do, um,
serious stuff in the morning on a time basis.
I've actually gotten some life back this week.
I'm going to do some flying in the mornings.
I'm, uh, right after I dropped Christina off at school.
I'm going to go over to, uh, to the airfield.
I'm going to grab the Delta Sierra.
And I'm just going to, you know, do a couple of circuits.
Maybe I'll go down a goodwood.
I just need to fly and I need to fly by myself and the weather is so perfect for it.
So, and I'll do us.
I'm sure, uh, let me get through tomorrow first.
Because, you know, it's always little, uh, tense, you know, uh, intense,
uh, flying again after a couple of weeks and, and flying with myself.
And so let me just get my chops back and make sure everything's okay.
And then I'll record a show.
Well, uh, either flying a goodwood or doing some touching goes and, uh,
we'll, we'll see if I can multitask.
I'm stretch it at our night.
Hey, today will be a savant-free Monday.
Um, reason for it is, of course, uh, uh, just didn't really have time to come up with a topic.
Think of a, uh, a savant to approach.
So, today we will be talking about something which warns, uh, the help of many a savant.
Some of whom I may know, but you may know some and, uh, we might even have to get some government officials involved.
It's going to be, uh, yeah, it's going to be quite a big conversation.
But the savants, it's definitely something that's catching on.
I met a man when I was traveling and we saw him tonight.
Talking about nothing and everything till we saw the sunlight.
It only takes one minute to say hello, then you're on your way.
It's not you, then who?
If not now, then who?
If not anyone who's gonna be a friend.
Hey, Adam is Jason Jarrett.
I'm just listening to the DSC on 590.
Make the show just going from strength to strength.
It's a great show.
Have a great week.
Cheers, Mike.
Yeah, Jason.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, a lot of good response to the food bar Friday.
So, uh, maybe we'll, uh, you know, I want to be careful not to get set in any certain format.
It's, uh, it's dangerous, but I'd say nine out of ten people really love the savant segment.
So, uh, I want to do more of that.
Maybe I'll incorporate it more into, you know, in a flow and not have something at the set time in the show.
I do want to get more people on the show and I love talking to people, uh, live.
I love doing it unedited, trying to keep it short, trying to move the conversation along,
keep it relevant.
It's difficult.
I have to be honest.
It's, it's not easy to do, uh, but I'm enjoying it immensely.
And the amount of people who are, um, uh, sending me emails and saying, look, I can be
the savant of this or the savant of that.
And check this one out.
If somebody's, Sultan of savants, I humbly come before you to offer my services as an energy
savant.
As atomic rod atoms, I have worked hard to refine my craft.
And I'd like to share my art with DSC listeners.
I run a tiny company that is developing the ability to build emission-free,
atomic engines safe enough and clean enough to be surrounded by people.
We want to put them in a basement, so large buildings, install them on commercial ships,
supply them to developing nations, and even build them in the backyards of certain
affluent people.
As you might imagine, I spent a lot of time trying to understand the competition,
and the obstacles that are innovative company will face as we expand.
I'm sure that a man, as worldly as you, can come up with dozens of interest in questions.
You might be surprised and possibly entertained by the answers.
I know it would have a better chance of getting this played.
If I now insulted you, or cussed, or did something amusing?
Instead, I will simply sign off with folder.
No, an atomic rod.
Not at all, man. Not insult. Are you kidding me?
No, I want to know more about this. You know, we were in Los Angeles on Friday,
Ron and I went for, I think, would it be a final meeting before we close a deal
with the pretty interesting organization, which I'll be able to tell you about.
Hopefully, this week, or certainly next week,
shouldn't take too long to close everything up.
It's a very interesting partnership we're entering into.
So, when we're on the road, we really get a time to really just chat and shoot the
shit and when you're on an airplane, you've got the time.
You know, hanging out at, I don't just remember to say this about something about our trip back.
And we had a really good conversation about alternative energy,
and being, it started actually with our thoughts about
the U.S. pulling out of Iraq and George Bush and dependent on oil.
And I think that I'm going to have to invite Mr. Bloom as a sabond Tom,
because it's great. Whenever we have, we can get pretty heated and heated conversations.
We don't necessarily agree with each other on topics.
But this was a good one.
So, I'm definitely going to bring him on.
And one of the things I said was, hey, you know, this atomic rod
atoms, he's got these, you know, he has a company building nukes for your back yard,
nuclear reactors, and I'm like, I totally would be, I'll be all over that.
I'd love to try that out. And of course, Ron immediately says, oh, yeah,
yeah, you'll be glowing green.
You know, and I probably all stereotypical remarks about atomic energy about
a danger and the waste and all that.
So, we'll have to have atomic rod on as well.
But today, it is completely savant free.
Anyway, what I wanted to say is, so it was just a one day up and back trip.
We took, I don't know, the United Shuttle or whatever it is.
And on the way back, so we were a little bit early.
We had a 330 flight.
We were at the airport around 120.
And we wanted to see if we'd get on the two o'clock shuttle.
And because the automatic checking kiosk said,
well, you could get on the three o'clock shuttle,
but you know, you have to print out your tickets and go to the gate if you
want to get an earlier shuttle.
So, we printed out our boarding passes.
And there was a huge line for the two o'clock flight.
And it was like, I don't know, it must have been 50 or 75 school kids on some kind of
excursion or convention they were going to.
And so we're waiting in this line and it's taken a really long time.
We're kind of debating, you know, should we get so we do even try and wait in this line,
should we just get some of the eat and shoot the shit about stuff.
And I see over to the right.
I said, hey, look man, it's ice cube.
You know, the wrapper ice cube.
And he was kind of over in the corner with his,
I guess his body guard or his guy is a minor.
And so I'm looking at the situation right.
And I'm like, we're desperately trying to get on this flight to get back earlier.
There's set 50 to 75 school kids.
And there's ice cube.
And I said, Ron, I think we should step out of this line.
I don't think we should try and get on this flight.
And he says, why?
I said, dude, think about it.
This is always the flight that crashes.
It has 75 school kids and ice cube.
And if this thing crashes, we won't even mention in the fucking article.
So we went home on the 330.
Yeah, hi, y'all.
I'm going to call on you on this thing here.
And I hope I got the right number.
I'm listening over there on that show.
Now, I used to listen on that show.
I told him that serious thing there.
And all of a sudden, it's just just proof.
Now, I don't know what right to come with that.
But I tried to y'all in on my hand radio.
And I can't eat y'all on that night.
So I hope I got to know my number here.
And this dude has signs.
And what I was wanting to know is, that's here and all this stuff on the daily source
and I don't know about how come you want to have so many servants on your show.
Things like that's going to be a hard thing for you to come by is to find so many people
who's wanting to, you know, just do what you want and say, you know,
don't say what's wrong with the dude and all, but that's what I want to call.
The reason I call is, I have a problem.
Sometime when I'm listening to the show and I got to show loaded up on my iPod
and I'm listening to it, it seems like it's coming in kind of softly.
Anyway, I don't know if that makes much sense or if it's because I need to
get a new something or other.
But if I need to get a new something or other, I hope you give me a call because I
could probably help you be a servant in that regard anyway.
I sure do listen to them shows and I shall do appreciate them.
And if you won't play this, you've got my permission to do it, I guess.
But what I want to say is, how come when I'm listening to that show and
talking about servants is, is it sounds kind of funny?
I don't know.
And it seems like you want to talk a lot on there about toilet paper and things
and scratching and folding and all that.
Yeah.
I don't get it.
I don't understand.
But y'all keep up the good work there and I'm going to listen for you over their own
series.
I hope y'all come back on there because I listen to that and I let my
water listen to that and we sing y'all there.
Y'all keep listening to that as you know.
And it's dirt hard for us.
I talk to you sometimes.
Well, there you have it.
That was the serious satellite radio listener, I guess.
That's the first response I've received from any.
That's so fucking sad.
Please don't tell me that we were doing that show and no one was listening.
That would be, that would just be so disappointing.
There's no numbers.
There's no arbitron.
There's no rating.
There's no surveys to know who's listening to what.
But that is the first response I got.
I'm not quite sure that our redneck savant was was real.
Hey Adam.
Eric's mother here.
Oh boy, you remember I had that little conversation with Eric and
and as a girlfriend both in the Jersey boys cast.
Mm-hmm.
Oh boy, we're always proposing all kinds of things of a sexual nature.
Well, here's Eric Bergen's mom.
Oh, no, and as Allison Lee, the host of craft cast.
Not scrap cast.
No, yeah, I screwed that up.
I'm sorry about that.
Craft cast.
Scrap cast is cool too though.
Nothing wrong with scrap cast.
Actually enjoy scrap cast.
It's on your podjo network.
But on the host of craft cast.
Got it.
So, sorry I missed you and San Francisco.
I was hoping to be there when Eric did that interview with you.
I'm looking forward to hearing that on Green Room Radio.
And yes, aren't they adorable?
Little love birds out there.
They sure are here.
And they show up Jersey boys.
And it was so much fun getting to hear them on your show.
And I have one other, I have a suggestion at them.
Please, please, please.
Can you put a channel on podjo network for the crafter?
Could be under an art category?
It's a huge category out there.
And it'd be great to, you know, take advantage of that.
So, that'd be really fabulous.
Appreciate it.
So, I look forward to maybe I'll run into an LA when everyone's out there.
Yes, that show is going to Los Angeles.
Fair exciting.
Big opening in there on May.
And, um, and that's it.
I'm forward to talking to you again soon.
Take care.
Bye.
Thanks, fellas.
Well, so here's, uh, here's something interesting about your request.
Now, first of all, you know, that we're cranking up this help podjo
suckless campaign.
And I believe the beginning of the month.
So, or the first week, so that's this week and next week.
Uh, we're coming up with a pretty exciting opportunity for you to really help us suck less.
Um, and in a little more structured manner than all of the fantastic emails and PDF files,
as well, people are creating entire presentations of how we can be better.
I can't tell you how much I appreciate it.
Most of it, of course, focuses on the play button, the XML buttons.
I mean, all that stuff.
We think we can take this a couple steps further.
You know, first of all, it's not like we're unaware of stuff that's confusing, not right,
illogical, et cetera, et cetera.
This program is brought to you by TythonLPM.
Check out AngieB's unwinded on wine.potjo.com.
Now what you can do, dear Allison, and this is one of the things that's manual right now,
we're going to turn this into a more of an automatic feature.
You can create your own channel.
You may know this already, but give it a try, um, by going into your, uh, into your collection,
and any, uh, podshow, any podcast, in fact, that you can find anywhere, you know,
just search for it throughout the network, you can add that to your channel.
So why don't you build a craft crafting channel, whatever you want to call it,
and then we can promote that to the program guide,
and then you will, in fact, you will effectively be maintaining that channel.
And part of the upgrade that we're going to be doing, the next release will be, uh,
these channels will be propping, you know, we'll have that on channel pages.
You may have seen the new channel module.
If you haven't, you need to check this out.
It's really an awesome way to manage, uh, your shows that you listen to, um,
you can, uh, you can also manage the order that there are all kinds of stuff that, uh,
that is already good and stuff that is even better still coming.
But do that, Allison, let me know about it because then we can promote that into a program guide,
and we can, make that a, uh, channel, and it will be, you know, like something that
will be promoted throughout the network, but you can continue to maintain it.
So if you feel a show should be in that channel, or if you feel a show no longer belongs
in the channel, you'll be the one that's controlling it.
So, um, please, please help us out.
Okay, so you don't need to be sending in any more emails.
I think we pretty much got it.
We have an entire survey that consists of, uh, I don't know how many questions it is.
Um, it's a lot, actually.
And if you, uh, participate in the panel, this is going to be a gigantic survey,
not only will you help pod show suckless, but you'll also win points with which you can get free stuff.
I don't think this guy was pick up a Ferrari doing that.
So stay tuned, you'll hear about it on the show.
And we're here and says hi, Adam.
I've been listening with much amusement to your headphone issues.
And after you're description of, uh, what you now go through to avoid the headphone
earlobe problem.
I think it's time to pass on details of the ones I use.
I myself have fairly big ears and hates.
I hadn't even considered that.
And hate smaller headphones that press on my ears.
But a year ago, friend turned me onto the Senheiser HD 555 model.
I strongly recommend you give them a try.
They're open headphones.
They leak a bit of noise and don't block out all outside noise.
But the airpiece is large enough to fit my entire ear inside.
As an angled speaker, so my ear barely touches anything once they're on.
And the padding has a very nice velvety texture.
Very familiar with these Senheiser headphones.
Um, again, here's the problem.
Um, I need to have a closed off system because I use compression on my microphone.
Now, what does that mean?
It is intended to pull up softer, uh, noise and level it out with louder noise,
which, of course, it limits down a bit.
So if I were to have an open headphone like such, you see,
I'm only just opening my headphone a little bit, just the tiniest bit
and you already hear it starts to feed back.
So, um, I will try a Patricia has a set of AKGs, the 271s,
which I've just huge, um, uh, what do you call them?
Uh, earpieces.
So they would fit probably quite comfortably.
But the really the problem is it fits over the ear,
but then it's right underneath the earlobe,
which is where, you know, it's basically rubbing.
And that's what causes the irritation,
bacteria gets in there.
Of course, these headphones.
And now I'm also cleaning my headphones.
I should do, you know, you get like a hygiene kit.
I have that from, uh, from the aircraft,
including the aircraft headphones, all that stuff.
It's really important.
So I am kind of looking for the ultimate headphones.
And here's another, uh, another example.
Hi Adam, it's AG here again about your headphone problem.
I think what's happening is that, uh, if you're using headphones
for a long period, this can cause a lot of discomfort
and a guy like you ought to have the best headphones in the world.
So I would suggest you take a look at greater labs headphones
at golf, a Romeo, Alpha, Delta, Oscar.
I've used them now for several months,
and I just wouldn't go back.
Normally with headphones to increase the base response
and the possibility also the loudness.
You need to clamp them to your head by pressing your hands
against them with greater labs.
If you do that, you get a totally opposite result.
They were best when the equalizer is turned off.
They're not great to look at, but boy, do they perform better
than any other headphones I've used?
Hope that helps.
Alright man, thank you.
And I did check out great old labs that looked at the headset.
I'm not going to have to find a place where I can try them out
because again, they are not closed headphones
so they don't fit over the ear.
They are large, and they do have really big padding
so and there's very directional speakers in the headphones.
And they kind of look like, these things look like the roles
of the voice of headphones.
So besides the fact that they'll probably have a fantastic sound,
which is I don't really care about the sound.
It doesn't have to sound all that good.
It's important, but you know what I'm saying.
That's just my reference.
As long as it sounds good for you,
but it really has to close off that sound
so we don't get the feedback.
So I'll see if I can find a place in London.
I'm going on Friday to Big Smoke.
Because I guess who's going to meet me at two o'clock
at the UK crash pad or the shortage office?
Oh, yes.
Comics trip blogger's going to be there.
We're finally going to meet in person.
Hey Adam, it's Mark.
I just wanted to comment real quickly on the whole Alec Baldwin thing.
Now, I don't condone this type of behavior to a child.
But in the case of Alec Baldwin,
I do understand a little bit where it's coming from
because he, like any of us, is a product of his environment.
And that environment happens to be the entertainment industry
where this type of discourse happens all the time
ranging from topics such as why didn't my car pick me up on time
to why is there no vanilla pudding at the craft services table?
And I'm not even kidding about this.
So you have somebody like Alec Baldwin who's just coming off
a reasonably hit show 30 rock,
which has already been renewed for the fall.
So he knows he has a job that starts back up sometime in June.
And during his hiatus, he's shooting a movie.
So he has very limited time to do that.
And the movie, of course, I'm sure they've scheduled
around his availability.
But that means they're probably shooting really long days.
And his ability to actually go and pick up a phone
and call his family, well, that's got to be scheduled
into his day.
And I'm probably way ahead at the time.
So it's got to be very frustrating when you have something
a very long, you know, 12, 16 hour day on the set.
And you have a small window of opportunity
to actually talk to somebody that you love
and they're not there.
People that with the standard behavior of any pre-teen girl
and Alec's acrimonious relationship
with the girl's kuku bird mother, Kim Bassinger
and the pressure of shooting a movie.
Well, you know, I think you have your external influences
right there.
So in my humble opinion, you know,
pointing a finger at Alec Baldwin for this type of behavior
is very much like pointing a finger at American tourists
in Europe for acting like, well, Americans or pointing the finger
at somebody from Arkansas when they come over to your house
at F-Sex with your livestock.
But that's beside the point.
In my experience, most actors are babies.
And oftentimes, you have to shrug off their
aberrant behavior as diminished capacity.
And while I'm no Alec Baldwin apologist by any means,
though what he did was wrong,
I think whoever leaked this voicemail to the press
did something even more wrong and even more hurtful
to that little girl in the long run.
But there's Hollywood for you.
And if you like this kind of childish Hollywood behavior,
you can go pick up a copy of my book
where's my fucking latte.
And other stories about being an assistant in Hollywood
comes out May 15th available now on Amazon for pre-order.
Thanks Adam, I'll get you later.
You're such a sleaze mark.
I can't believe you really have been going there with that comment.
I'm like, okay, Mark's got an opinion.
And all it was is just a wind up to promote your freaking book.
Which, by the way, is a pretty good book
because I did read it on the plane going out the San Francisco.
Yeah, what's your basically saying
what Robin and Susanne said?
A lot of stuff is going on Alec's life,
and he wasn't completely focused.
You know, kids are kids, man.
They do shitty stupid stuff.
They really do.
Hey, I got a voicemail from my daughter.
I got a play for you.
I'll do that tomorrow.
Okay.
Because right now, I want to take a few minutes away.
Actually, something else.
This is,
so I was getting ready to leave on Saturday.
I always take the Saturday flight and I arrive on Sunday.
That's kind of the way it works with international time travel.
And I listened to a lot of podcast.
You know, if people wonder how come I never go out to dinner,
how come I never show up at clubs, at premieres,
at all these swanky things,
it's, well, not only do I no longer get invited,
but it's also because I'm,
I'm doing my job.
I'm listening to stuff.
I'm trying to feel how our network sounds.
I want to see what other people are doing.
What's the vibe?
What's the zeitgeist?
And one of the shows I listen to is show girls.
Now, this is a very interesting project.
It, it kind of started organically.
I mean, my mind will just get the show girls page here.
Hold on a second.
Let me, it's,
I was at some shirts showgirls.punchow.com.
That's, well, make sure I don't miss,
miss represented who's on the show.
I think it came together at,
the podcast new media expo either last year,
the year before.
It was, it's been building.
And essentially, it's a combination of,
a pod show affiliated female podcasters
and Frank McMahon,
who, of course,
produces room-a-girls uncut.
And here we go.
Each episode of Cali Lewis,
from Geet Brief TV,
share from Rock and Roll TV,
KFC, from the pod check podcast.
So I don't think it's actually on the network anymore.
Angie B, from the chill cast,
soccer girl from soccer girl incorporated
and Carla and Karen from room-a-girls,
along with Franklin McMahon,
and they bring insights into everything from world events,
entertainment technology, as well as behind the scenes.
Okay.
It's a fun show because you hear,
it's kind of like,
in a way it's like the view.
Only it's all done through Skype,
so it's a little tougher to
instigate a real conversation amongst the participants.
But Frank has a really good job of kind of,
it's more like McLaughlin group.
There you go, Frank.
Frank really manages the conversation.
It's really interesting because women
often have a different perspective on things from men,
who are in joy listening to it immensely.
So Saturday, I'm listening to the most recent episode,
episode number six.
And then listen to what I hear.
Yeah, the pod show has a current limit.
I'm hoping they're going to be upgraded this week,
and they have it.
Right now, just happened today.
Yeah, they have a limit on.
So now that we're doing HD,
and Apple TV and stuff,
the shows are getting bigger.
Yeah.
That's many people here.
We'll be affected by it.
In fact, we should all.
We should all complain about it over there, huh?
What are you saying?
There's a limit on something?
Well, it's true.
Yeah.
I think it's 200 megabyte,
which is, I mean, if you're doing MP3s in audio,
and smaller like 5, 10-minute videos,
it's fine.
But once you get into like higher res and Apple TV,
format and longer shows,
you upload a pod show.
It uploads,
but it doesn't take.
It doesn't actually go the distance.
Yeah, wow.
It could do is give you an error message
or warn you beforehand.
It could totally stay like, you know,
no files over 200 MB.
You know, they'll be easy,
but no, just says nothing.
Hey, let's all complain.
Yeah.
It's working on it.
It's all complain.
Let's all complain.
It's like two minutes.
It's like, let's all complain.
Let's not complain.
You know, I'm all for, you know,
it's amazing that the listeners
are more productive,
proactive,
and inspiring than these women
when it comes to helping pod show suck less.
You know,
first of all,
an upload limit,
which was chosen at random,
many, many moons ago,
200 MB was indeed quite an amazing amount
per episode availability
for upload and storage space
before there was any HD or Apple TV.
And it's quite easy for us to up that limit.
I don't believe any other service
allows you to upload that much.
And there's a couple of reasons for it.
The main one being you don't want to,
you know, hand out like a gigabyte
because that's exactly what people,
or even 500 megs,
people can store an entire movie there.
But that's just one minor problem.
Also, it's not completely free.
You know, if you do go ahead,
buy a 50 gig,
buy a 100 gig hard drive.
So after X amount of episodes,
your hard drive will be full.
You can calculate the price.
It costs actual money,
but it's certainly willing to consider it.
In fact, I've already asked for the
allotment to be up.
My general feeling is let's make it 500 megabytes.
But what just really earned me,
you know,
let's all complain.
Let's complain.
Why don't you be productive?
It's not complaining.
Like we're evil.
And oh,
you could have at least given that some,
is that Angie B?
It's unbelievable, Angie.
Ah.
Okay, hold on.
I'm just getting worked up here
because the real anger is about to come.
Okay.
Address is quoted from a bucket.
I was doing some web surfing with weekend.
I saw a story that just scared the hell out of me,
and I thought I should give you a call about it.
It's a story that was,
and it was,
and it was in daily chaos in a couple of other places
about the I,
and their royalty collection system.
How they're collecting royalties now.
With a compressor,
can say,
compulsory license,
which means that they connect,
like life is now for sounds that are even given,
given from,
are they even good permission to have their music played royalties free,
that are collecting music,
and then the artists are asked to register with the I,
to get their money.
But they're just holding this money,
and the I,
is trying to collect it on anything,
on any kind of streamed music,
so we don't have a choice.
They sound like the story could be,
or it is about like this whole system,
makes it sound,
makes you tell us we can't ever have toxic music and that scares the hell out of
maybe can I'm sure that does for a lot of podcasters use the podzic music that work music
does we know that those are some already given their permission to allow us to play the music
I don't mean to sit here you're thought to bother and I thought just bring us to your
attention and if we can start a conversation about it it does set it we should be calling
our our Congressional representative is because it's the GAMPS can see what the RAA is doing
if all the smoke they're collecting from these artists who brought you in their permission
they don't want their royalty collected so I'm like some of getting screwed here if I
some of the co-incularism so I'm potentially I'm thicker yeah go excuse me Corey thank you so
much and I received several emails about this and you know my previous conversation with
Doc Serals about web radio and the copyright royalty boards legal win I believe which
goes into effect on the 15th of May which I understood to be a different form of pricing
for licensed music and you know my stance on that it's like okay these guys own their music
if they want to jack up the rates for other people to use it in novel ways such as web radio
so be it you know that's the it's applying demand so they're going to diminish their the demand
for this stuff and because of the because the prices just too high so and I'm okay with that you know
it's a bummer and I wish that I could play all kinds of all these some I have been able to get
away with because I know the owners of all the copyright but most things that I'd like to play
now and if I've played it then I've totally broken the law and I'm quite aware of it but what was
pointed out so two things first of all I always thought it was daily cost but didn't make so much
sense now so the daily chaos but it spelled Delta Alpha India Lima Yankee Kilo Oscar Sierra
really delved into this this new rate hike and found something very interesting it appears that
sound exchange which is it's members are several large labels and one or two large independent
labels who are members of the RIA have received a statutory and compulsory license or that they are
they are allowed to enforce a statutory statutory compulsory license which means
and let me just quote something from the article here let's see this two quotes I should give you
the recent US copyright office ruling regarding web casting designated sound exchange to
collect and distribute to all nonmembers as well as its members the library of Congress issued
is this decision with rates in terms to govern the compulsory license for webcasters internet
only radio and simulcasters retransmissions so this is from the sound exchange FAQs now the
sound recording copyright owners and that means anyone who has created interestingly enough
it doesn't necessarily have to be music but if you've recorded a sound recording
then you are a so called SRCO so I'm actually also an SRC and that's really interesting hold on to
that thought for a second so the sound recording copyright owners are subject to a compulsory
license for the use of their music sound exchange was established to administer the collection
and distribution of royalties from such compulsory license taken by non interactive streaming
services that you satellite cable or internet methods of distribution so there's a whole bunch of
big huge pitfalls in this and the first being what is internet radio and what exactly is a
non interactive streaming service now from an experiential and from a technical standpoint
the difference between streaming audio and downloading it there's really not a lot of
difference in fact there's all kinds of little gotchas in these are laws of articles of law
about the difference between streaming that does or does not temporarily maintain you
is not temporarily maintained on your computer which with the progressive download is arguably
exactly the same so the point that Cory was making and others are saying hey you know if this is
a compulsory license it means that regardless of what type of if you're not even distributed
if you don't even have a record deal if you just make a song you put a creative
commons license on it or if you use the podcast music network license it is a license by the way
it even states as such so when you sign up as a podcast or producer you are agreeing to the
license when you sign up as an artist or as a label and you put songs up there you are agreeing
to a license it is an actual legal document it's a license it's not just some kind of
really nearly thing it was well thought out cost a lot of money hit lawyers fees to get it exactly
right and also working with the community to do that to hone it to make it even better that would
technically mean that if you created a web radio let's so let's just call the stream for now
of Ponsa music or music license under a different license such as the creative commons
that you would still as a webcaster you would still be liable for fees and as I read it with
and you know and I do understand what a statutory license is it means essentially no one has to
contact you only have to contact anyone just by the fact you're doing it means you pretty much agree
to do it so that that could be very gnarly now again this is not because I don't
think people should be able to make money off of their art but we have a license in place
seems to be working very well there are alternative ways of making money with your music
through concerts and merchandise and yes even just selling it directly a DRM free so the the
danger here is that this type of statutory and compulsory license could pretty easily be applied to
podcast and it's just one easy step away so that is fucked up and that's definitely not okay
so I'm going to need to find some savants to talk about this and they will have to be in legal
profession I'm going to get Brian Longest who did the original drafts of the podcast
music license and who is a lawyer he is also a director of operations he's a copyright lawyer
patent lawyer and some other kind of lawyer he's a fucking lawyer I'm going to have to ask him to
delve into this because I did find while looking so it's the US copyright office that makes this law
and and says okay this is what statutory means and this is what compulsory means and this is how it
works now I just want to say as a brief side note there is a bill that has been introduced to stop
this particular hike in fees for webcasters for streaming radio and I will put a link to that
in the show notes and I think it's good that they're intervening and if anything trying to slow
down this may 15th deadline but they're not talking about the compulsory nature of the license
they're only talking about the the fee structure so you know it's not really applicable to what I'm
talking about right now this is this is a very dangerous place that we're in I think because
and let me just what is the word I'm looking for waiver here we go so now I'm looking at the
at a copyright law see I'm not a lawyer I'll put a link to this as well title 17 chapter 92
one whatever the hell it is transfer and waiver the rights conferred by subsection A that's where
discusses the compulsory license may not be transferred but those rights may be waived if the author
expressly agrees to such waiver in a written instrument signed by the author such instrument shall
specifically identify the work and uses of that work to which the waiver applies and the waiver
shall apply only to the work and uses so defined in the case of a joint work prepared by two more
authors a waiver of rights under this paragraph made by one such author waves such rights for all authors
so if I read this properly and this is what I need some help on this is where I'm going to get the
savants to work and maybe jersey taught I know it taught I I know you only do like ambulance
chasing work but you could at least have a look at the articles because you're much better at reading
that stuff than I am it appears to me that you may be able to put a waiver in place and in essence
the creative commons or the positive music license would be exactly that now I don't know if
that means we have to send off all these waivers to sound exchange so that they can know that
anything played by these artists is exempt that will have to look into now I do think it is
interesting and that's what I just stumbled on a couple of minutes ago they're talking about
sound recording so in essence that would also mean that if someone used the daily source code
because I sang on it because I sang on it right so that just constitute this entire thing is
one big hip hop song wrap with a little bit of a chorus in the middle then I could also start to
collect fees and probably you know if we don't get any further I could probably edit the
audit the shit out of them because you're even if you're a non member you're allowed to audit
and say okay how many times is my shit played we could really follow them up so before calling
for a complete jihad on this I want to get some savants involved if you're a lawyer if you
understand this if you have access to a copyright lawyer please I'm also calling out to the electronic
frontier foundation where you guys in this and and to creative commons I think that they should
be all over this as well so before we start reaching out to congressman and and and government
let's get our story straight because I don't want it to be just about the fees I want it to be
specifically about this compulsory license so let's be let's be really really specific about what we're
looking at here so that'll do it for today but I do want to keep the vibe alive and keep you in
some good hope and good spirits so a song will typically do that you know what I'm saying
natives of the new dawn one of my favorites from PMN
no matter how shitty how proud just look outside it's gonna be a good day
I'm going to talk about the bad thing on my friend all the fact that we are here
let's make today a good day yeah wake up and some derives and shy just another day in this
life of mine and take a deep breath my lungs still took a past he's got to be a good day
wow the has to be stretched out my arms I failed out my worries you've been aided no end
with the possibilities these are mine it feels my bloodline never so becomes cold as I swing
from the fire my concern with time I finally feel fine days as it should be of my own design
there's no one on clock and you know when I'll rest sleep and dream mine to candy and rhythms are
all that I need and I enjoy the bad day and I'm on truth to be because you can't have a good day unless
you believe every day good and bad will be around so let's focus on listen to the positive sound
right I don't want to talk about the bad thing on my friend all the fact that we are here
then be next to day I'll go out
I don't want to talk about the bad thing on my friend all the fact that we are here
day yeah yeah
did there some offensive and on shadows ratchet our wrist advise ever in the room
full of compensation concept in the monetatization that we'll be playing back in the mind
of all the people in their faces in this moment of time somewhere we'remer's smiles all this
popularity with the misery someone finds tomorrow while others become history no where to
wind in the mic he fought the world with our
One of the stars, one of the sun, the lights are dark
Yeah, we've become a city, we can be this hard
And so learn about respect between the close, and the pharmacy
I lean for him, the season of the harvester
The soul of the seats, and I leave where the heart is now
Everything, good, you've got to pull me around
So that's what we saw, and this is not the five minutes
Well, noit, no, no, so come by breakfast
Comin' my friends, come all the same
We're here, we're here
Smart
Over the day
No no no no
Lord another thought
Round the mad
Oh my friend
Hell the fact that we are here
That made us again
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah DJ like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, kinda yeah, yeah, got and kinda, yeah folk how Yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, there
You can find that song through the link in the show notes at theedicstorescode.com
Natives of the new dawn, it's talking about it a good day.
You know how I've been talking about the soundtrack of our lives for the past a couple
shows.
I always suddenly remember that I played this song when my mom was really ill.
Just took me back for a minute there.
But let's think about the good days.
And we'll meet here tomorrow for another one of them.
DailySourceco.com, Adam and podshow.com, take care of yourselves.
See you tomorrow.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering podshow and limelight.