Attention on units, attention on units, be on a lookout for a white Caucasian male,
6-foot-five with a blonde, well-done hair, goes by the name Adam Curry with aliases of
pod father and big-haired bag, last seen at 57th in Broadway at a vegetable stand mumbling
something about taking a bite out of the big apple. Most recently heard on the VSC 564, subject
is armed, but not necessarily dangerous. Over.
Here we go, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry,
Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry
, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry like Madgeurt, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry , Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry, Adam Curry,
No, that ain't the way that they're
The time for soul should end to mention
Yes, and girl, pay close attention
Hey, hey, say, say you can let your head down
You ain't done nothing bad enough to feel so guilty
You're just a part of it, I won't run and rush
This crazy life will live and it's all apart and growing
You ain't never gonna praise them
No, but you don't have to write what they think
You don't need them
Hey, hey, say, say you can let your head down
You ain't done nothing bad enough to feel so guilty
You're just a part of it, I won't run and rush
This crazy life will live and it's all apart and growing
Crazy life will live and it's all apart and growing
Yeah, Laura Clav, hey, hey sister kicking off
Daily source code five six four coming to you from the curry manner once again
In G town west side, it is the affluent suburb of Surinone's Guilford
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's good to be back home, it's I feel I feel
Oh, it's the word I'm looking for, I confused, no, not confused
Disoriented, there you go
I am completely disoriented having flown to different parts of the world in the last last couple of days
Come back, oh besides one other thing that always disoriented me
When the sound isn't right, so I don't know how it happened
I think today's our lovely housekeeper
She was probably up here cleaning in Adams attic and low and behold
She unplugged the mixer and you know what happens when she unplugged the mixer exactly
The sound becomes completely messed up so I'm I'm starting trying to configure it as we speak
Just to make it sound a little bit clearer in your buds because I know you got those buds jammed in deep
All right start of a new week. It's it's Monday. Let me just tell you how things wound up on Friday
I told you it was going to be food barred and boy was it ever
Got to the airport more or less on time time. I had never flown out of a JFK the new terminal
I flown in the new terminal of JFK and but I also never flown virgin out
So I saw the I witnessed the virgin clubhouse quite nice at JFK. I have to say
So we got on the plane you know about half hour late
So that was 930 and we stayed on the plane for about two hours and then oh, it's time to you know the runaways now clear
Now we can go take off and we have another another hour of de-icing
Of course, I'm very happy we de-ice but crap. I was like three hours. I did find out something pretty unique though
Because I had elected since it's a very short flight like five hours and 45 minutes and you're flying through the night
So I really wanted to get some sleep to see if I could get onto the right timetable upon arrival in the UK
They have a sleeper section which is basically the upper deck you have a whole bunch of was it premium economy
Then the illustrious curtain you always wonder what going on behind the curtain. Well, that's where they have about 10 seats
And what they do is we have to take off to just shut it down, right? It's closed. There's no no food service, no no beverage service
I guess unless you ask for it or go get it. It's just everyone's supposed to be sleeping
And I'm sitting in this chair and in this well chair in the seat and I'm thinking like you know
I think the seat is bigger and so the flight attendant comes over whatever the supervisor
They always you know because I'm on the VIP list
They always come over and they have a little chat and you know, do you need to need any anything
So yeah, can you answer this question for me?
I think this seat is bigger up here than the one I've been sitting in for the past year downstairs
He says no, no, it's all the same service. I don't know, man
It's like I sit in these seats and I notice it immediately
And indeed it turns out that the upper deck the seats are a couple inches longer because of the angle of configuration
They're all kind of at a what are they like a 45 degree
degree
So yeah, like at a 45 degree angle
Okay, I just thought you'd want to know in case you're flying virgin upper class and you want to have a larger seat
It made a difference for me. It really did while sleeping or attempting to sleep it worked
So back Saturday morning later than expected everyone happy to see me. I'm happy to see everybody else
We're having a good time
I'm kind of in and out of consciousness as usual and
Sunday morning around 11 o'clock the lady Patricia had to go because she was attending a fashion show
Oh, it's Couture in Amsterdam
So she's out and I've been playing Mr. Mom got Christina off the school today everything perfectly. You know
I still got to make up the bed and all that stuff that she comes back and immediately you know
She bounces quarters on the bed to see if I made it the bed properly. You know that by now, right?
So anyway
She'll owe us an appearance
For sure she'll owe us an appearance this week
Hey Adam, this is Logan from South West Florida
It's like man, I heard myself on an intro of your show
And it's just like blew me away, man
And I gotta tell you, I used to save you up and do you all one week
But now I do every day
And enjoy the show
And I like what you're doing
Do me every day
Yeah, that's what I want you to do listeners
Do me every single day if you can
Eric Bergen, our friend from Jersey Boys
Who plays one of the lead roles of Bob Gaudio
Is doing something pretty exciting tonight, which we'll only pertain to those of you in the US
But check this out
Hey Adam, it's your favorite Jersey Boy here, Eric Bergen, live from San Francisco
Well, almost live
Yes, that's me the one with the crazy mother
This and you rate that our show so much
That hopefully there are daily source code listeners out there who want to see the show
Well, I'm here to tell you that tonight they can
Well, not the full show, but at least four minutes of it
Tonight we are honored to be performing on the tonight show with Jay Leno
That's tonight Monday, March 19th, 2007
In the US, the tonight show is broadcast on NBC at 11.35 pm
And we are going to be on towards the end of the show
As for people in the rest of the world who want to watch
I'm not sure where when or if it is where you are
But I'm sure in just a matter of days
If not hours, it will be on YouTube
And check out my website, Ericbergen.com
That's E-R-I-C-H-B-E-R-G-E-N.com
Where it will definitely be on later this week
So make sure to tune in tonight as we perform
A medley of great music by Frankie Valley in the four seasons
One of the songs is my eyes adorging
A favorite of yours Adam
Oh, and by the way, how we know which one is me
Well, I'm the tall one
The winner
Yeah, the winner
So tune in tonight to watch Jersey Boys on the tonight show on NBC
All right, Ericbergen on the tonight show
Tonight awesome, dude
Yeah, you can watch it on the...
There's some, but was it a more for or maybe it's no
Maybe it's MSNBC, you can watch it over here
I'll definitely be watching, dude
I was talking to Steve Leads at Sirius
I realized that Steve Leads is the guy who brought me to the United States
And in the mid-80s to work at MTV
And he's been in the radio and record business
I think for most of his adult life
I realized we've been working together for like 20 years now
And so he's over at Sirius
He does talent and industry relations
I'm such a fool
I told you that the Rockwell Hall of Fame was on last week
While while we were in New York
We were in the W Hotel right behind the Waldorf Astoria
Where the dinner, the induction dinner is always held
If I had known that I would have called Leads
And he would have hooked me up with a ticket
They used to cost 1,000 bucks a piece
You could buy table for 10 grand for 10 people
And I'm like, Steve, you know what have been awesome
And we could have gone
It says, yeah, you know what the prices are now
Well, I don't know, 1500s, how $3,000
How Rockwell is that, huh?
Oh man
Ah, let me see
Roy, I want to remind you about the new show
Angie Bees doing with the main sponsor, Tyler and all
PM
It's called Unwind and it's kind of along the lines
of her chill cast
Only really
This is
It's much more targeted
I think towards putting you to sleep
And I tell you when I listen to Angie
And her dulce of tones
Oh man
That doesn't put me to sleep
It puts me into a
Creative Dreamlike state actually
Of course, Tyler and all PM
Sponsoring the show
And I told Patricia about that
She said, oh, I really want to try those
I don't know if they have them in the UK
It's Tyler and all PM
I know they're marked blue
So you don't take it at the wrong time
During the day
But apparently
This is like some kind of a miracle thing
For women
Who also apparently seem to have more aches and pains
Than men or at least so they claim
And so if they want to go to sleep
The aches and pains disappear
Tyler and all PM seems to be the thing that works best
I don't know if you ever tried it
Let me know
Let's see
Spending the globe
There you go
Spend a while since we've heard from our friend
From Ecuador, Paul always on the line
Hey Adam, how are you?
It's Pablo from Ecuador again
I hope my last message didn't get to you
But I was going to let you know that
I thought to some friends that they have a band
Their names
Sick
And now they are
Out members of
But safe music
So
Just
If you want
Just hear a little bit of it
And tell me if you like it
Bye
Alright, Pablo
My man
In Ecuador
Dude
Thank you so much
First of all for spreading the love
Getting the word out
And getting some
Equatorian music on the podcast
Music network
I found them SIQ
Sick
Let me see
From Ecuador
Influences tool
Ninage nails
Slip knot system of down
Radiohead corn
Okay, we kind of know we're going to
Or get into
Sick is a part of the rock culture
An Ecuador
I'm just reading directly from the bio here
With a new musical style
This independent band formed by
Agni D
Angotar
Locals
Moises on drums
And 212
On bass
Why didn't they call
Their kids such weird names in Ecuador
Three times they had a number
One hit single in Ecuador in the last year
Alright, chosen
Best rock band of the year
And best alternative
And now on the pod safe music network
Alright, I'm gay
Check out
Watermark
Music
By my mind
Still in the future
The spread in the field
In the world we can't take
You're beautiful, alright
Born in Tennessee
Anyway, we're here
But don't miss a thing
And don't miss a thing
God, there's no time, some memories will fade
My head is unchanged, meaning yes, as we'll remain
So keep it alive
I love you, boy, I adore this
It makes this way
I love you, baby
I love you, boy, I adore this
It makes this way
I love you, baby
I love you, boy, I adore this
It makes this way
I love you, yeah, I love you, yeah, I love you
I love you, baby
I love you, boy, I adore this way
I love you, boy, I adore this
It makes this way
I was thinking of doing a little cowbell but couldn't quite find the right rhythm to make
it work.
Sick, watermark from Ecuador, thanks to Pablo for sending that in.
This is what I love so much about what we're doing with podcasting, independent media.
An independent reception device is because if you don't like the song, you just skip
ahead.
It's not a wonderful, it's so much better than the alternative, if you're listening
to the radio, you just can't skip ahead.
In fact, all of my natural broadcasts or instincts are listening to that song going like,
oh man, there's a lot of people who are going to fucking hate this song and I'm going
to lose them.
I'm not going to lose them.
They're just going to fast forward.
That's fantastic.
I definitely have to work on the sound of the microphone.
It sounds like shit.
Yesterday, I worked a little bit on my pet project, I've been doing an audio book.
I'm not going to tell you what it is.
Oops, hold on a second.
I'm maintaining contact with Lady Patricia through SMS text messaging.
She says that she tried a new hotel last night in Amsterdam and it's one of these like
botic hotels where they take an existing residence and they convert it into, I don't
know, like a 10 or 12 room hotel.
It's overlooking the park and she says it was fantastic and I should definitely try it out
next time I go.
If I ever get to go there again, I mean, cry.
I don't even know where my aircraft is.
I think it's an Antwerp being getting its annual checkup, which has to happen every
year.
I don't know.
I got to go to Holland, man.
I got business to do.
I got my bank managers.
I got to take out to dinner.
I got to get my haircut and Rotterdam.
I got a real business to be taken care of.
Oh, you know, was it Friday or Thursday or Wednesday?
Well, sometimes last week, I got this really angry piece of feedback.
I'll just play it so you can remember again.
No fuck.
Quia.
It's been a while.
It was something in this piece of feedback, which was very funny, but I didn't understand.
And now it was a guy if you saw much joy.
Yeah, check it out.
You won't.
Yeah, I'm a winker.
I don't get angry anymore.
I don't know.
I'm freshly out.
I rehab.
It was in a reference to Trinity, I think.
I do.
But I ain't going to fucking do.
I've been saving a few up.
Any of they are.
Number one.
I don't give a flying fuck what your ass is called, because we all know, and ain't really
your ass.
The brains you'll react to my son is your Mrs.
That's right.
Jet soft to Holland on a Monday morning.
It does a better dance in, better duck in, better dive in, thrit some
beads, and gets a bit of a bun from the rest of the leaves.
And then flies back home on a Friday night to Patricia's home to tear.
Yes.
Number two.
I don't need another fucking domain name.
All right, son.
In fact, the only time I want to wear the words go daddy is when me house boy
one is naked, laying across the dining table.
It still throws me up.
I don't take fucking sugar.
All right.
Four.
Trinity.
Three Trinity, not three Trinity, who gives a flying fuck.
You can grab in its tank.
You can shit on its seats for all I care.
You can piss in the washable.
I've only got one suggestion about Trinity's son, Swan Vesta.
So that was the part that I just couldn't figure it out.
What the hell is Swan Vesta?
And luckily, luckily someone is out there ready to help me.
Hi Adam, it's Parkie from this weekend London podcast.
Just ringing in after listening to Friday's show.
Just thought you might like to know.
Swan Vesta is a brand of match over here.
And your cooler was suggesting that you burned Trinity.
So it's a little harsh.
But there you go.
Anyway, just have a lovely curry in a few points against.
And I'm on my way home.
So thank you very much to today.
Goodbye.
Yeah, as usual, a few points against.
I got to tell you, man, you brits.
I love you dearly, but boy, do you drink?
I guess they Christina had two friends over.
You know, Christina's working now at the boutique.
She works out in that Saturday afternoon from two to six.
I guess she likes figuring out or finding out what it's like to have a boss.
She actually has a quite a good boss, which is nice, good, good first experience.
So two of her friends were over last night.
I don't know, I can move her like seven o'clock in the state for a couple hours.
And both of them, they had their own drink with them.
And they're like drinking beer, which is, I'm cool, you know.
It's like, they're 16 and one of them was 17 and so yeah, that's fine with me.
But they had like five or six bottles of beer each.
And they weren't, you know, didn't even seem to affect them.
And after they left, I said to Christina, I said, dude, you know, what's up with that?
She said, oh, I know dad, it's crazy.
They like to drink so much.
And she was drinking Coke, you know.
Christina doesn't really drink.
She just, she'll have a freezer, one freezer, which will nurse throughout the entire evening
at a party.
And I said, you know, these girls, they seem to be headed nowhere.
And she said, oh, yeah, well, you know, they're both A star students.
I don't understand.
It's in your DNA somehow.
All right, it's one Vesta being matches.
Now we're not going to burn Trinity.
Trinity's going to be burning it up.
I got to tell you.
First of all, let me, is an email that came into the free Trinity group from Timothy.
I was a, it's just Timothy Pilgrim, yeah, there you go.
Kind of interesting, dear biodiesel supporter, we hope St. Patrick's day didn't take
all of your energy because today is also national, or today is national biodiesel day.
National biodiesel day takes place on March 18th, the date of Rudolph diesels birthday.
The biodiesel industry chose his birthday to honor him for his foresight and recognizing
the valuable role of vegetable oil based fuel in the late 19th century.
Diesel's ran early versions of his engine on peanut oil and paved the path for today's biodiesel.
That's interesting.
I did not know that yesterday was biodiesel national biodiesel day, national biodiesel day would
be just for the US.
Let's call it international biodiesel day.
Also, of note 62% of US consumers are willing to pay more per gallon for biodiesel
than regular fuel, more than four and five consumers continues to support a tax incentive
that would make biodiesel cost approximately the same as regular diesel and while only
3% of consumers surveyed on a diesel vehicle today.
61% say they would consider buying a diesel car because of the benefits of biodiesel.
So again, let's not go to the green side of this.
That's not what this is about, but it's the whole concept of doing something independently.
You've got a car, you've grown up knowing with the knowledge that you have to go to the
man to get your go juice.
Well, no more.
Any diesel engine can take biodiesel and I recommend 100% biodiesel and it is very cool.
When you go to the biofuelo basis, which is where Trinity gets gasped up in San Francisco,
it's just somebody's garage with a couple of big containers of oil, vegetable oil, pre and
post-processed and an older fashioned pump, it does have the, you know, the, what
they call it, the spinners with the numbers on it.
So it's not electronic, you know, you hear ding, ding, ding, ding and you see the numbers
actually change in real time flipping over and you'll see in front of this garage, you'll
see, you know, easily on a Saturday afternoon, five to ten really nice high and diesel
automobiles lined up waiting to get in and it's because people would rather pay, you know,
someone in the garage money than then big oil, I guess.
So we're sending Trinity across the USA and we were in New York also pitching some advertisers
to sponsor the trip and as we were pitching it all of a sudden, it started to come out really
nice and I think I've found, I think I've found the mission for Trinity and the way it came out
was it's about independence because it's true that it's, and when you're talking to brand
advertisers and you know, stuff like that's, you know, that's what brands like to associate themselves
with. So it's about independence. It's a little bit about technology and it's all about relationships
and when it came out like that, it really hit me. I said, this is fantastic. This is exactly
what the promotion should be about. So when you have Doug Pilgrim and his son and they're going
to be driving across the USA in Trinity and we have the two girls, one in Boston, one in Maine.
These are the relationships that I hope to have come out in the podcast that they create together
as they use Trinity as a catalyst, a catalyst in a vehicle for friendship and independence
from the man. What we have here is a failure to comply.
And now up in the empty sea radio, it's hard to pass it.
The thing that's too big, we need too many way. There's another way and we can breathe back.
Go along, jump in light, follow everybody, find do it like you want to let's all light.
Be a bit Cavalier, even try to win a fear better when you fail, when you fail, something's right.
Have the rock on.
This new boy's back to see. Do you know?
Todd just gave me the mug.
I need you up.
Who got jump ball?
Here's up.
There's a nice new back to the radio, don't matter.
Hey Adam and Sean from Dallas.
This was a DSC for Fubar and I heard you were talking about
my comment, all that bullshit with the lawsuit.
You know, this is so interesting. I think I said this on Friday as well, but
when it comes to copyrights, I'll just remind you, when Potio made a very stupid
oversight, stupid mistake. And some people, it was so stupid. Some people think we actually did it intentionally.
And we launched our first version of the site and the internal codes to all RSS feeds were linked
to the RSS feed button, which of course was dumb because it should be the original feed, which it is.
And we're immediately accused of hijacking stealing and taking profits out of mouths of babies.
When it comes to copyrights of the big boys, let's just call them mainstream media. Let's say
Viacom is an example. Then all of a sudden, it's like bullshit and these guys are making
enough money already and it really shows a lack of understanding what goes into creating
what you see on television. Make no mistake. This is expensive shit. And part of that, of course,
is because of the infrastructure set up, the way things are done, the tools that are used,
the amount of people that buy agreement are involved in the process, and also what people are
paid by agreement in the process. Also what they're paid for derivatives and copies and
syndication rights. And this has been set in stone for many, many years. And one episode of
lost. I remember Dave Winner posting on his weblog, you know, how can you know, saying that why don't
we all just buy lost through iTunes and they won't have to broadcast that anymore and we'll pay for it.
I'm like, dude, it's $5 million per episode is what it costs. $5 million. That's really expensive shit.
So anyway, so I do take offense to that, you know, stealing of copyright, copyrighted material is stealing
a matter of who you steal it from. I'm also against fake Gucci bags and fake sunglasses,
and I hate that. I really, you know, I know lots of women who buy these things. And my wife is
bought sunglasses on the streets of New York. And I said, you know, go ahead, you know,
and one day someone's going to rip your shit off and you're going to be really pissed because,
you know, that's how it works. And if it were the other way around, you'd be pissed right now.
Oh, yeah. I'm so against it. Anyway, let's listen to the rest of the, the question slash comment.
As YouTube and a little note story, I mean, I guess it was kind of big, but a couple days before that
parks, you can see the peanut Google for the names of some users that uploaded some stuff
from his production house. Let me just say one thing, Mark Cuban owns the Dallas Mavericks
basketball team, which he bought partially with the proceeds from his sale of broadcast.com to Yahoo
at the height of the dot com bubble made out like a bandit. I think was like three or four billion
dollars. That's so much money. And he's doing a lot of things. He'll be bought as basketball team.
He has an HD high definition movie production company and doesn't he also own the HD channel.
I think he does. So he's he's working a whole different angle of the changes in media.
Basically, I just wanted to comment on what a fucking hypocrite Mark Cuban is because if he's
the peanut in these things and he's going to sue Google over it, I'm pretty sure that he made his
money by stealing other people's content and rebroadcasting it over the internet.
I think if I'm wrong, but I'm pretty sure Mark Cuban is a huge fucking hypocrite. So just wanted
to get to take on that, still a mask, then go mask. And I am definitely 100% scruncher piece.
Well, I can tell you a scruncher, my friend, because you have some hidden anger there,
trifolding it might sue you your soul. I think the, you know, broadcast.com didn't have much
really going forward in assets. I think the only thing it really had was the agreements. I think
they did have the licenses from mainstream media. I don't think it was a very profitable
project because of the expense of the licenses, but I think that's really what he did have.
So I could be wrong on that. I'm not sure, but let's just say I'm quite confident that I think
that was the only thing that broadcast.com really had short-up was all the online rights and licenses.
And at the time, there were probably much, much easier to get under certain regulations.
So I don't think he's a hypocrite. I think human is just trying to figure out where the world is
going. I thought I read his blog, blogmaveric.com. I always read it with interest to see what
angle, what his take is on the latest developments. And when it comes to, you know, when it comes
to copyright infringement or theft, you know, I understand why he's all over this. So yeah,
I think what he's trying to do is trying to prove the Google cannot hide behind the
safe harbor of the DMCA, the digital millennium copyright act. And he's stirring the shit up.
That's for sure. And I saw a recent post, which I thought was pretty interesting. Where
he claims that you can't hide behind safe harbor if you know that there is infringement going on.
And he had a very interesting post. He said, why don't we subpoena the Google searches of
Eric Schmidt. Eric Schmidt is the CEO of Google. And let's see if he did any searches for like,
you know, the daily show or any of any other properties. Because if he did, then in theory,
he would have known. And therefore, would not be able to hide behind the safe harbor of the
digital millennium copyright act. I mean, this is really interesting times we live in. And
particularly interesting for us in independent media because, you know, what value does Google have
if, if you can't advertise on it, because of infringement or if there's so much infringement,
it just becomes useless as a business tool. That's going to be very interesting to watch.
And I think his other premise is that he believes that, and there are more voices going up
about this that Google is basically building their business on stealing copyright from others.
Now, the book industry certainly believes that I think the record industry has has given up on that.
The movie industry, well, we're about to see certainly the television industry is of that opinion.
And there was big article in the Financial Times today about Google and about it being down
12% since the beginning of the year. And I don't know, it's price to earnings ratio is now
all out of whack and who knows. I guess the investors are finding it that it's taking too long
for Google to get to what they call Google 2.0, which would be, I guess brand advertising or, you know,
the next wave of money that is out there when it comes to advertising. And we've talked about this.
It's going to be much harder to get brand advertisers on board when you can't really predict
what the future content is going to be on each placement.
Alrighty, let me see. One more promo that I had in the wings here.
This is Samable, Samage from autobluggreen.com. The past year, autoblug green has been bringing
readers driving impressions, interviews, and all the news about what's going on with alternative
fuels, hybrids, electric cars, and more. Now, Sebastian Blanco and I have taken the next step
and launched the autobluggreen podcast. On the first show, Sebastian, I review the green car
introductions from the recent Geneva Motor Show. And I have an in-depth interview with Martin Everhard,
the CEO of Tesla Motors, builder of the amazing Tesla Roadster electric sports car.
Come on over to autobluggreen.com to subscribe. You can also find us in iTunes just search for
autobluggreen and stick around for fresh news all day every day.
Guys, it's autobluggreen.com.
I got to tell you that Tesla, that's an amazing machine. I went to the launch of that in Los Angeles
in an airport in a hanger, a aircraft hanger. It goes zero to 60 in like four seconds. It's unbelievable.
It just pressed as accelerator down. It's like a golf cart, a golf cart, bad out of hell.
Experience is awesome. And I see postings around the internet saying that I'm against
what is it that, I don't know, just basically saying that I'm evil as usual, promoting this,
people actually writing that I'm promoting this alternative view on global warming from the channel
form movie. Hey, all I'm doing is pointing it out. Okay, I just go take a look at it,
make your own decision. I'm no scientist. I'm no ecologist. I do my bit to be green. I've always
done that. In kindergarten, we were collecting can. First grade. I'm sorry. We were collecting
cans to recycle. You know, it's culture. Of course, we're going to try and protect the planet.
But God, just because I point one thing out, people are all over my shit saying that I don't care
about the environment. It's unbelievable. This place we've gotten ourselves into.
Let's just evaluate everything based upon the evidence. I have seen a lot more news articles
about the movie, the great global warming swindle. And of course, you can find a link to that
in, uh, was it, uh, show notes from a week ago, channel 4 program. All right, got a wrap it up
short today with some music that, uh, well, once again, it's self-submitted.
Hey, Adam. It's Ray Anthony from RadioGuide.com. First, I want to thank you for playing the clip
of my interview with Potsafe Music Network artist Pete Hopkins, back in February.
Secondly, I would love for you to hear Amy Kooney. We recently spoke and I discovered that not only
is she an amazing talent, but she's had a fascinating life. She candidly told me about her
kidnapping in Central America, a few years back. Her appearances on TV's Gilmore girls,
among other things, and we sampled songs from her EP. Here's Amy Kooney talking a little bit
about her life as a missionary kid. And what I was 14, my dad, kind of out of the blue,
just decided to move her family to Honduras and do missionary work. He just up and sold the house
and, uh, yeah, you know, it's interesting. He just didn't feel like we were doing what we were
supposed to be doing. And he says, now, you know, every day, he got up and did the motions and
did there routine stuff, but he just didn't really feel like any of us were where we needed to be.
Now, she's not yet on the PMN, but I've got her permission to play this for you. This is Amy Kooney,
so help me God.
We were sitting side by side in the theatre, but the whole time we had eyes on each other,
I'm by with touching and squirming in our chairs. You whisper something funny and sweet
love things in my ear. So help me God, you don't you do that again. You might wake up,
enough we're taking a man, so help me God, don't you do that again. You just might be my
man, so help me God, don't you do that again. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, whoa yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Kara,
Go and do that again
In just my dream
But next, we'll keep it coming
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So let's go, let's go
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go, let's go
Some chocolate
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go, let's go
Let's go, look it
And there's also Adam at PartShow.com, and I'll be back tomorrow, with a lady Patricia, guaranteed.
Another PartShow podcast. Stick it in your ear.