Yo, what's up? It's your man Tony Costa from Costa's world.
Telling you to go check out the new Sony Pictures release.
This Christmas is Star's Chris Brown,
Mackay Fife for Regina King,
Lauren Lundin, Columbus Short, and it...
It just has an all-star cast.
You can exchange gifts.
You can exchange the socks.
You can exchange fruit cake.
But you cannot exchange family.
So make sure you check out this Christmas when it hits theaters,
November 21st, 2007, and a mouth.
In a world where women wear comfortable shoes
and technology has changed the way you get your entertainment.
This is the pod shown at work.
No big media.
No excuses. No BS.
Now, the share of Charlie six eight and nine are...
$16 billion worth of airframes.
$16 chart out of several hours a week.
Just as tangible as you think.
Oh yeah, it's January $13,000.
I'm in now the Georgia, he was looking for a so-or-steel.
He was in a bag because he fed the hat
The bag, because he was way behind, he was with him to make a deal.
When he came across his young man's son, on the field in plain and high,
and the devil jumped up on the haylist of support him until you walk.
I guess you didn't know when I'm a little player too.
And if you cared to take a dare, I'll make a bet with you.
Now you play pretty good, filial mugs, you give the devil a deal.
I've been a little in gold against your souls, to make out better to.
I've been a little in my name's Johnny, and it might be a sin.
But I'll take your bet, you're gonna regret, and I'll make a bet with everything.
Got to hear us, I'm a good boy, and play a fiddle hard.
Dolls hell is both loose and Jordan, the devil deals a card.
And if you knew, get this shot, it'll let it go.
But if you lose, it'll get your soul.
The music is a piece of beast that I'll start this show.
With fire, with respect, your tips, and your rugs, the devil.
And if you pull the whole across the street, but it made a evil hiss.
And the band of demons, you're a head of this madness, unlike this.
And the band of demons, you're a head of this madness, unlike this madness, unlike this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness
madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this madness, like this這一 world, like this madness, like this
The devil bowed his head because he knew that he'd been beat.
He laid that golden fiddle on the ground to join his feet.
The devil just come home back and be everyone to try again.
I don't know what you want, you son of a bitch, I'm the best and they were me and we played.
Yeah, we've like mashed potatoes.
The devil went down on Vinnie.
mashed up by auto-violet.
Charlie Daniel's been in Ram Jam.
What better way to start a new week on the Charlie?
With something mashed up so thick, it's like, you're right.
Ah, definitely a little, uh, little model there in the middle, but uh,
felt good and nonetheless, everybody how you doing?
Episode number 689 of the Daily Source code coming to you
from the curry manner.
I'm up here in the attic, skies, overcast, cloudy, rainy.
We had a shitty weekend, capital S.
Even though I had the whole weekend more or less often to ourselves,
the weather was just not fl- I mean, it was flyable.
If you want to fly to thousand feet in the rain,
which was not what the Lady Pea was looking forward to.
So we left the Delta's share of parks and just chilled out.
I had a- really a nice relaxing kind of a- one of those really dark
wintery weekends.
If you know what I mean, you know, where you just put on some smooth
music during the day, we've got a coal fireplace,
let that sucker up, had it blazing.
Actually, we got two of them had both of them blazing away.
Great television on this weekend.
Actually, I should go back to Friday night.
Oh, man.
So, you know, last week was totally nuts.
And I predicted this, this is going to be crazy before the, you know,
the end of the, between now and the end of the year, it's going to be nuts for me.
And this is mainly because we have a number of rather large deals that are on the table
that we're trying to get close before the holidays quite honestly.
Because otherwise, you know, it's, it's January and then it's mid-January
and then we all ramp up again and it's February and it's just that takes too long.
So that's our experience.
So we're pushing real hard.
And a couple of these deals.
And so Friday went out with the Super Agent Keith with the badge,
our deal maker extraordinaire, this guy.
I got to get him on the show because he was on his talk and see it.
Let me tell you.
So it was with Madeleine who's head cheese now at the, whatever that means at the,
at the Pod Show along the office.
And bad used to work in the 70s.
He worked for the deep purple organization.
And, you know, he's a deal maker lawyer finance guy,
but he's like 62, I think.
Maybe a little older than that.
He just had five weeks ago.
He had opened a hard surgery.
And he's a revelman.
He's a revolutionary.
And he was talking about how, you know,
they were always trying to find the right tax breaks for, for deeper pull.
And if they recorded the songs outside of the country,
they didn't have to pay taxes in the UK.
And then the, you know, the internal revenue service,
I came to them and said,
we have, but they're writing these songs here in the UK.
And they're about to get a multi-million dollar tax bill.
When they were able to say, no, that's not true.
Case in point.
Here's, I forget what the name of the album was.
Here's the song, Smoke on the Water, which you may or may not know,
was written after the casino in Montro, caught fire and up in the attic of this building.
The top floor is where Deep Purple had their studio.
And he said, look, there's the proof.
We wrote Smoke on the water when the frickin' casino was burning down.
They wrote them outside of the UK.
And they, and their argument was accepted and saved a million,
millions of pounds and taxes.
And he's full of shit like that.
So that was a good time head by all, as we drank away the night.
Oh, yeah.
I was home like a two o'clock.
That's, that's a late for me.
Anyway, as I said, nice easy afternoon.
Nice Saturday.
Of course, dancing with the stars,
or strictly come dancing was on, which Patricia and I followed.
There's also, I'm a celebrity get me out of here.
Also started up again.
And you know, I'm a sucker for these shows.
Scripted drama is what I'd call them.
Not reality.
Scripted drama.
And actually, there was an interesting article that I saw in the,
Let me see, was a BBC article.
There, yeah, the same team behind strictly come dancing.
The original dancing with the stars here in the UK.
Sitting up a new talent competition with choirs.
And you know, I've said this many times before.
If you really, really want to get a huge audience,
do something with either choirs in the, in Europe would be choirs in the US.
It would be with the cadences with drum lines and high school bands.
Because there's so many people who either participate,
our member of a club have participated or a married to someone who's in a choir.
I mean, it's just tons and tons of them.
I think it's going to be a huge hit.
You mark my words.
It'll be another unscripted drama.
But the best, the best television I saw all weekend,
without a doubt.
Without a doubt is banging with Butler.
This airs live throughout the week.
Well, of course, it's not live at air several times.
Throughout the weekend on the plus, if you go to the plus TV.com
at midnight Pacific, I think we actually do it at midnight all time zone.
So it's pretty much all Butler all the time.
He's doing his version of the head bangers ball.
And it really, it kicks ass.
It is so awesome.
And I think you can get the, each episode downloaded as well.
Banging with Butler.potcho.com.
I think that's the, I think that's the URL.
I'll put a link in the show notes.
You've got to see what Mike is doing.
It is absolutely fantastic.
I think he has, he is really honoring the,
the time on our tradition of the Saturday night head bangers ball.
It's great stuff.
Great videos.
And of course, he's allowed the drink of beer on the set,
which is even awesome.
Hey, Ed, and this is Mark.
I know you're tired.
But we need to hear everything about the Nokia N800 10.
That's such a great thing.
You know, my, my iPods have died on me.
And I need to get something new.
I hope you guys will open something out with Nokia.
So I got my channels on the Nokia.
Yeah.
Tell us.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad you asked because I'm pretty excited about this as well.
I think it's shipping this week in the Nokia N810.
Excuse me, which is their new internet tablet.
And, you know, I, of course, when I picked up my Mac,
by the way, I love it so much.
A God.
I'm one of the fortunate ones, I think.
No upgrade problems.
It's just rolling.
Love it.
Staying together.
Low noise.
Low heat.
Fast response.
Lots of things I love from the Unix world.
I just love it.
I easily could have picked up another iPhone.
Because they're on sale now in Europe as well in the UK.
But I didn't because I've been waiting.
First of all, I've learned my lesson.
I need a much more robust device.
I need something that can be dropped.
Can be thrown across a table.
The really does have all of the.
You know, accepted protocols work in, you know,
and I don't want to be tied down to.
To my laptop to be able to put stuff on it and take.
I mean, there's a lot of drawbacks.
Obviously, the way they present the browser is just phenomenally beautiful.
You know, so I think there I'm a believer in the three.
The three types of devices.
And you carry them at different times rarely all together.
And sometimes you do have them all with you at the same time.
So you have your laptop, which now without a doubt is my Mac.
I love it.
You know, I'm I'm taking it everywhere.
I go.
I'm taking it into the bathroom with me.
And which is okay because it can't actually physically fit through the hole in the toilet if I drop it.
Now, by the way, these Macs are pretty vulnerable too.
I've dropped a one or two in my day and they do wind up the power book.
It does wind up pretty much hose.
If you drop it from, you know, if you just drop it wrong.
Then, of course, there's the mobile phone, which needs to have some type of browser capability.
I've been running the opera mini browser on my Nokia E61 eye.
And you know, for just getting Google and by the way, thank you, Google.
You guys are awesome.
You know, now besides having Gmail from mobile,
there's the Google reader from mobile.
Now we have finally the Google notebook from mobile, which is you get to in the usual Google way.
It's Google.com slash notebook slash M fantastic.
Great job.
So, you know, really got everything I need right there.
And of course, the E61 eye synchronizes seamlessly with my Mac,
which it does through I call, which in turn seamlessly synchronizes with my Google calendar account.
I mean, all this stuff is really starting to fit together quite nicely.
And I'm not having to think about it anymore.
It's just kind of working.
Now, in between those two devices, there is room for something else.
And, you know, just as my laptop is not a phone,
and my phone is not a laptop, there's something in the middle.
And I believe it's this concept of the internet tablet.
And, you know, I've had great pleasure with the N800,
particularly since it got Skype, which is our company's main means of IAM.
So, that you can get all kinds of IAM programs on it,
but having Skype is a big plus.
And, of course, you can also make your regular Skype calls through it.
I'd place flash video.
In fact, you might have noticed if you have an N800,
or you can try with any browser, actually.
If you click on a show at poncho.com,
and it's a poncho program, so something you've uploaded.
Let's say it's video, because that's kind of the easiest way to detect it.
No matter what you uploaded in the dashboard, it's now playing in flash,
yet the big media files are still available for download.
So, that now also works on the N800, where you can pop up the dashboard,
and it'll play the show in flash, and it actually works.
It's really cool.
So, this new version, and I believe that the new OS,
which is a big part of it, you know, there's a new operating system,
like an upgrade, kind of like the new leopard, if you will,
for the N devices, it's slick.
And it's a lot faster.
The flash videos play much, you know, they play smoothly.
Let's put it that way.
Everything's more responsive.
The Zoom functions work much faster.
They've really optimized, because it's the same process
where I believe in this new device.
They've really optimized the speed with the OS,
and with the hardware.
Now, add onto that that they have added a slide out keyboard,
which is just phenomenally easy.
The whole idea of on-screen keyboards, yeah, it works.
But it just makes the device a little bit less usable
for the situations I think it's intended for.
So, I can literally now take this thing, slip in my backpack,
and I've got the internet with me.
Almost anything I would need.
If not, I'm sure there's a program out there.
I could download or, because it's all open source,
I can, you know, build myself,
or I could join some groups and see if I could motivate
some developers to build it.
So, it's a, it's a great device.
Don't actually have one in my hands yet.
I'm expecting it, you know, to get one soon enough,
and again, we're looking at, at getting all listeners
of the daily source code and other podshow programming
who will be in this, an 800 program.
We're looking at getting you promo codes,
so you can order them right online,
and get a nice discount.
I believe it's like 15% discount, discount to the market.
That's going to be awesome.
Stay tuned for that.
Just before I started an email from Alex Freeze in High Adam,
I would like to apologize.
When we met a couple months back,
you mentioned they proposed North American Union,
and I scoffed.
Well, a friend sent me a report on CNBC,
and this link as well.
I don't know what to say,
except that I'm deeply embarrassed for having
so casually discounted something that actually has legs.
Let's listen to this MSNBC report for just a second.
This is about the Amaro.
This will be very interesting if you weren't
a believer before that it's actually happening.
A new currency for the Canada, the United States,
and Mexico.
And this is an actual news report from CNBC
with Steve Previs VP of Jeffree's International Limited.
Check it out.
We're coming into a cyclical bottom for gold,
and it rises going into December, January,
so that might be the reverse of the dollar fall.
Apart from that,
I think one thing people who are dollar-based
need to focus on is the Amaro.
That's the one thing that nobody's talking about,
but I think it's going to have a big impact on
everybody's life in Canada,
the US and Mexico.
If you Google it, you'll find out all about it.
Well, you could tell us a little bit more right now.
You always hear about CNBC guys.
The Amaro is the supposedly currency
for the North American community,
which is being developed right now
in Canada, the US and Mexico,
to make a borderless community,
much like the EU,
and the dollar Canadian dollar US dollar
and the Mexican pays for replaced by the Amaro.
You really think that would get any leeway?
You may want to visit a couple websites
and see how far along it is.
The Canadians are pretty upset about it,
whereas the Americans apart from the Texans
are the only people who know anything about it.
The rest of the public's really sort of with their
headness and on this way.
Well, there you go.
Yeah, it's for real.
It's really common.
And that, of course, explains,
talked about this on Noah Genda
with John Devorek over the weekend.
Oh, that's what I did on Saturday.
That's right, Ron.
After grocery shopping with Lady P.
Did a quick, no agenda with John C. Devorek.
You can find it at NoahGenda.podshow.com.
We talked about that
and about how the Liberty dollar folks
who also make the Ron Paul dollar
were rated by federal agents
that took away all the money,
all the tender they had created,
as well as all the gold and silver to back it.
Well, gee, could that do you think be
because it was actually gaining traction
and they're worried that an alternate currency
outside of the old, let me think a mirror
might actually gain some traction
and become a defacto standard?
Yeah, I think so.
Of course, Ron Paul really has nothing to do with this.
And I would like to remind you that
we're at about eight and a half million dollars
of the twelve needed before the end of the year.
I think we can still easily make it.
I understand December 16th
is going to be the next Ron Paul money bomb
we're going to drop.
So you'll be here and more about this on this program.
I'm still a huge support of this guy
and door some holy.
It's funny when talking to John Devorek.
It's really interesting because it doesn't matter
what people say to him in any debate.
All he has to do is just, you know,
recite the constitution, apply the question
or the issue to the constitution.
You come up with an answer.
Don't even really need a guy.
You know, of course, we want a leader
and someone who will remind us and stand strong
and take us down the path that the founders intended.
At least that's what I believe.
You know, but he could easily be a robot.
That's that simple.
And it's not a lot of, you could do it.
You too could protect the constitution.
You too could be present.
It really could happen.
So let's support this guy.
I think he's already into double digits now in the polls,
which of course may be skewed in the polls
in the primary markets.
So keep an eye on this guy.
I'm certainly pushing for, I would love it.
If this guy became present, how fucking cool would that be?
I'm pretty sure I could at least get one night
in the Lincoln bedroom.
And of course, we might actually be free
and rid of all crap.
That would be pretty good deal, I say.
Yo, Adam.
Trucker Tom here.
Really busy lately.
And you haven't been putting out too many daily source codes.
And I understand that.
You know, for people that are in daily source,
source code withdrawal,
you might want to come and check my podcast out.
Talk to Tom.
Tom, you're like a, a price gouger, man.
It's like, I'm in crisis because I can't get a show out
and I use them.
So come listen to your show.
I love you.
I put out a daily podcast as every day.
As I possibly can.
Once in a while, I'll toss videos into the feed.
Maybe once or twice a week.
But the rest of the time, I try to put out an audio podcast.
Come over and check me out.
You may like what you hear.
You know, warn you.
You may end up in the connection fits.
Now, Adam, I can't bring myself to say fuck you, Adam Curry.
So I'll just end this with fuck you.
Socialism.
Yeah, everybody.
Good job.
Tom doing some awesome shit, man.
Particularly is HD stuff.
If you're looking for some HD content,
because you've got an HD television,
and you just bored with all the crap that's out there.
Check out Trucker Tom stuff.
I think you can get everything from Trucker Tom dot to podshow.com.
Federal judge ordered the White House to preserve copies of all of its email messages.
A move that the Bush administration lawyers had argued strongly against.
Yeah, why keep a record of anything?
The order came from Judge Henry H Kennedy Jr.
of the Federal District Court came in response to two lawsuits trying to determine
whether White House destroyed email messages in violation of federal law.
Two private groups in filed suit, citizens for responsibility,
and ethics in Washington, and the national security archive,
say that five million messages have disappeared.
Judge Kennedy's orders directed at maintaining back-up tapes
that contain copies of messages.
How old fashion is this?
Get a dot mac account, and just copy your email there.
You know, better what?
Why don't we just have the president use a Gmail account?
They'll never have to delete anything for space.
An easily searchable.
Now that would be a great program.
Hi, it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show.
We've got a fantastic review of Guitar Hero A3 Legends of Rock.
We've also got a review of Samus Aaron's latest adventure
Metroid Prime 3 Corruption on the Wii,
and you're coming copies of Football Manager 2008 for the PC.
That's all at gamesweasel.btpotshow.com.
Right, Matt.
Thank you.
I haven't seen the, I don't know if the video version of that is up yet.
That's awesome.
The video version of Gamesweasel just really, really rocks.
I'll check for you.
Let me see, do everything else that we should be talking about.
Oh, yeah, the Hulu Beta.
Just a quick follow-up on that.
You know, I still haven't received a beta access,
although I was kindly given one to go and check it out.
And I told you, it was really nothing special.
There are some people apparently who have a beta login.
And well, here's a report.
But I should say Hulu is NBC's answer to iTunes.
It took all of their shows off of iTunes,
and then they built this incredible video portal
that is just outrageously fantastically cool.
If you believe all the reports that came out a couple weeks ago,
and I found this report to be somewhat suspicious,
because well, quite honestly, no one I knew had a Hulu Beta login.
And it seemed like there was just too much positivity.
And I didn't read anything.
But any no bloggers were talking about it,
because they didn't have access.
So clearly, some things have.
The items are Tom calling from SoCal,
so I've got one area just listening to the D.A.R.
Who's my Friday?
Well, listen to you talk about the Hulu,
that Hulu site should take joke as far as I'm concerned.
I still haven't got a beta,
and even to try it out.
But I think it's a ridiculous site,
because they're only allowing positive post.
No negative post, any time I tried to post,
just say something, or even to mention,
iTunes and a positive veteran,
and they're argument with NBC,
and iTunes between the Apple iTunes saying,
it's just not working.
You can't post anything as long as it's negative about their site,
and just think it's a ridiculous,
well, have a good one, and fuck you out.
I'm very glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Big mistake, those guys are making.
Big mistake, because the content is,
of course, phenomenally good.
They produce fantastic stuff,
although I almost feel compelled to boycott it
since now, we're all painfully aware
that the writers receive zero money for this,
because NBC and other television and broadcast
and production companies call this type of online view,
and they call it promotional material.
It's not really someone being able to view a whole episode
of a series that eventually started with someone
writing down a story.
No, it's promotional activities.
So I should kind of boycott it regardless,
but the mistake is, you know,
you can build a community around these properties,
but that only works if you allow the community to flourish
and to talk freely, and if you start moderating,
it just doesn't work.
Of course, you eventually, you know,
the people who are working on boards and forums do blow up,
especially if they're open.
It's even worse if you have moderators
who can take things off and ban people,
and it just, you know, it usually results in,
in a downward spiral of flames.
But you can certainly get something going.
It's good for a while,
so I think that's a huge mistake on their part.
At this week, it would be pretty messed up.
By this evening, I'll know if I'm going to San Francisco tomorrow
for this week and probably some,
if not all of the next,
it's also very possible that I don't leave until the weekend.
Again, it's just all the stuff we're trying to wrap up
before the end of the year.
So, God knows what it went, I'll be back.
I really hope I'm back in two weeks time
because both Patricia and I have a fun weekend
for the 30th of November and 1st of December.
One is a special, like a show
that Patricia has been asked to maybe perform in with a big band,
so we're going to take a look at the show
and see if she likes it, see if something she wants to get into.
And then there's a huge reunion.
This must be 30 years now, I guess.
20, 20, no, 20, yeah, almost 30 year reunion
of decibel radio in Amsterdam.
That's the pirate radio station.
I really started at Amsterdam.
And so they have a frequency, 94.9 in Amsterdam.
They have a legal frequency.
It's still a pretty local to do.
It can pretty much reach Amsterdam.
And then there's some parts of South Holland,
as we call it, the southern part of Holland.
So more like the Rotterdam area, not the Limburg area.
I can reach there as well.
I think they have another frequency.
And so they're doing a big party.
And it's going to be all the old DJs.
And of course, Ed just everyone who work at the station.
And some artists, and hopefully I can make that
because that would be a shame if I couldn't
hang out with all the old boys and girls.
Because that's exactly what we've become.
Very old boys and girls.
Hey, Ed, I'm it's all you again from the German My Way Home podcast.
I'm just flying on this asshole calling in on DSC686
and complaining about your show.
This is the guy from fuckewatumcurry.com.
First of all, you're getting in money out of your business.
Ed, I'm feel ashamed.
Get your ass into the corner and feel ashamed.
Really?
And you're putting advertising on podcasts to get a payback.
Oh, my God, you're taking 30 seconds of his life time.
Well, please be the kind and take 30 seconds of your life time
and tell this asshole where the fast-forward button is on his player.
And as Peter Macquat, the little brother of the Potio Potcasser
from tips from the top floor, Chris Macquat once said in his podcast,
when a listener complained about, I don't know what it was.
What do you want?
Do you want your money back?
Yeah.
Listen to me, asshole.
This is free content.
If you don't like it, don't listen to it.
And don't take your time to make a show like fuckewatumcurry.com
and complain about a private done personal podcasting show,
like Adam does, but read it tutorial on the internet,
how the fast-forward button works.
Okay?
Adam fuckew and fuckew fuckew are imperative, Tom.
Yo, yo.
Yeah, right, man.
That's what that thing is for.
That little double arrow that heads toward the right points that way.
That is the fast-forward button.
If you're not liking it,
if you don't like the tunes, it's up to you.
That is true in directivity.
We stand alone on the edge of the forest,
wonder why this came to be,
running your pants to my head.
This leaves them loud,
they're like the jungle for forest,
but at least you see what you do in here.
The smell comes from there,
is none of this magic smell.
No, it's women, you're all in the air.
Chines are the place, the woman is dead.
You can make these problems disappear.
But you can't even out of me.
I wanted to get on it,
so we've got to be,
maybe give me a storm for free.
I can see your damn voice,
break your love,
that's what I like.
Break your love,
break your love,
that's what I like.
Break your love, yeah.
In terms of goals of sadness,
my love,
to maybe,
in terms of faster wolf,
the smell of the deceit of the bird.
I couldn't see you,
what's the looks you were after,
now you place me on your keyboard and shy.
I've never met you to your love,
but man, it's so brave,
and I know you never say no to me,
it's easy to see that you're crazy for this you look alive.
I don't care,
don't care,
Don't care,
I don't care,
Break your love, that's what we like
Break your love, get always looked so good
In a way, you love, it's a cover
Break your love, get gross to make it easy
Guys, just act so crazy
Math the time to seem so insane
Oh, get it, I'm home
Oh, get it, I'm behind
To let it all at tonight
Tonight, tonight, tonight
Boys, we'll be boys, we'll do nothing
Boys, we'll be boys, we'll get shot
And the boys will be boys, we'll shout
And sing, boys, we'll be boys
And the feel, sure
And the aim, boys and girls
They do nothingblind, boys
Born, win, 20
Girls, we'll be boys, we'll do nothing shiny
Like until somebody heard a little bit too much during the run, each more organ is called
Tyler Burns, as Abtown Boys regular from the Podsafe Music Network of course, a link
to that in the share notes of dailysourcecode.com.
Crossposts of decorate.com and other FIMES scam websites across the interwebs.
All right, so let's leave it at that for today, I'm sure lots more, nice, nice
fade out.
I'm sure lots more will come in throughout the course of the day, planning on doing a
show tomorrow, unless of course I have to scurry off to Heathrow Brighton early, but I'll
post something on the weblogger.com in case you didn't know.
So, keep your eye out at dailysourcecode.com and carry.com for information on how you can get
a Nokia N-810 at a fantastic price, and if you're looking for a great deal on a domain
name, the best ones on the net are available through using my codes, DSC1, DSC2, DSC3.
You can find those in the show notes as well, a link at the explain exactly which code
you need to use for which product you want to buy.
Hey, I'm Adam Curry, Adam at Podshow.com, and I'd like to remind you to live your life
with passion and please enjoy your freedom.
2021's at a theater near you.