This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Hey Adam, I think I know where the problem is
with thinking that the Trinity Project is a green project.
You said the car was baby poop color.
You ever fed a baby cream spinach?
Uh-huh!
Now all of the DSC-554.
In a world where TV networks, movie studios and record labels
still think they can govern what you see in here.
One man has the power to return control of entertainment to the masses
and make big media corporations wet their tiny little pants.
From Pod Show, home of the world's most dangerous new content
comes the daily source code with Adam Curry.
The world's most dangerous new content comes the daily source code.
Pete Hopkins, become from the pod safe music network like you didn't know that because you've heard it before on this show.
I love that song. Hey, everybody. How you doing? It is daily source code episode five five four coming to you.
Once again from the Curry condo and no cow, that is nor the California for those of you not a no tomorrow triple five.
That should be kind of interesting. Open. I get some openers for that. I just got back from I'm sorry.
I'm over modulating all over the place tonight. I just got back from from the city from the theater. I know less and I have quite a story to tell about my evening out an evening of culture for the pod boy.
Man, I'm I'm you know what I want I want I want to tell you exactly what I did and why I'm so excited and I just had a great night out and
And you definitely want to hear about this because it's one of those weird connections that only through pod casting is this all come about and it's it's just it's messing with my head.
But almost I can do I hear music somewhere.
Uh, that's kind of interesting.
Hmm.
I'm not quite sure where it's coming from. Did you hear that? I swear to God I could hear music running in the background.
Anyway, uh, sorry about that little distracted.
Here's uh, this is uh, this relates to my evening. This first comment. Check it out.
Hi Adam. It's Ralph. I forgot here. Uh, I haven't spoken to you in an quite a while on the where you have played one through message from me in the past.
I was really interested to listen to you know some of your recent episodes because obviously you're now playing
Non-pod safe music and I remember way because I've been listening to for ages way back
When you would you used to play quite a lot of non-pod safe music and then I vow that you never would do it again
So I'm really curious to know what you're thinking is behind playing a lot of these classic tunes. Yes, they're classic tunes and yes
I'm sure the you playing them will definitely help their sales. I kind of imagine we do otherwise it seems to me quite logical
But aren't you opening yourself up to a realistic friend of getting sued by somebody
for playing music that's said non-pod safe or is that something you thought of when you're prepared to take that chance?
Or do you actually want them to sue you? Do you get something that needs to to be fleshed out in the courts?
I'm just really curious to understand some of you thinking because I'm sure you must have thought long and hard about
Going back to playing non-pod safe music again after being quite in fatigue about not doing it any longer.
Sometime ago anyway, I love the show as I think I've made a mission before still remain a folder all the best. All right
So thank you very timely with that comment and obviously you've heard me play a couple of non-pod safe tunes over the past a few weeks
There's a new segment in the show
Another track from Adam's first gen iPod which can be a non-pod safe song
Let me start off by saying I am quite aware that I'm breaking
The rules or probably even more accurate to say I'm breaking the law
But of course I break the law in many
Hold on
There we go. Ah fucking noise get you can't hear half of what I'm doing
I know I'm breaking the law. I've broken the law while speeding
These aren't all comparable but I'm very aware what's right and what's wrong
But here's the problem and by the way you'll probably only hear me playing non-pod safe music
That is from my past and
I think just about every single time that I've played and just an awesome song
The reason why is because I can't help myself I it's
Music
All music that I know in from my entire career my life
It's a part of me. It's a part of my DNA and I have to say it's what I do
What I do is I
Always been someone who's shared music with others millions millions of others whether it was on the radio on MTV
And particularly on the radio I have to say I'm a disk jockey. I'm a disk jockey because I have all the launch well
I album sushi
A disk jockey is something it's it's an art form that has been dead for probably
I'm gonna say almost 20 years
Hmm maybe a little less, but it's really been dead for the past 10 and let me try and explain
All these music services that that are out there and there's a ton of music services and you know like iTunes
Where you can create mixes
There's a Napster which I like very much which I subscribe to there's the Yahoo music engine
There's
Rhapsody you name it it's out there and
And
The problem is
Is that there's what are these services have a million and a half songs in their entire catalog?
Which isn't not too bad, obviously, but discovery of songs
Is happening through machines and this is
Yeah, it's part of a way to help people discover new music
But it's definitely not the best or most effective way what we saw with the original Napster
Was oh my gosh, you know now we're really sharing songs people were ripping their CDs
Which they bought presumably and
They were putting the MP3s online and you could go in and I think that was one of the biggest features of Napster
Is you could go into someone's shared folder and see what else they had because if you'd like this
You know the music you were finding from this person which presumably you searched for in the first place
And you'd probably like the other things and you know that was really one of the first social media networks in my opinion
So that works extremely well when you as just a fan of music can tell your buddies your friends check this shit out
And do we have proof that that is true? Yes, multiple
Multiple examples how about my space just in general? I mean my space was a place where you you slapped up a player of your band's music
And it was embeddable genius by the way so that other people could then put your song on there my space page
Podcasting exactly the same now
I have to say that pod save music sprouted from a little different background
It was Ron blew in myself getting together and saying look here's this podcasting
And it's working very well with speech and it's very effective for that
But there's just something missing from the equation and
Ron's a musician. I'm a broadcaster. Sorry. I'm a disco jockey. I'll just say it
And
I desperately want to play songs in music and I want to share that with my buddies and Ron says well, I want to get paid and after a lot of research
We came up with the idea for the pod sake music license now part of the another reason
For getting this together is you know, I knew certainly the time when podcasting was just cranking up in its
Current incarnation of audio on the internet
I knew that if we were playing
Licensed music
Particularly at that juncture in time. I knew that there was a very high likelihood
That one of us probably me would it be singled out and that we would branded pirates and
That podcasting would really in the media's eye
Be seen as a bunch of pirate radio stations on the internet now we have far surpassed that point
We've gotten to the point where and this is the hypocrisy of it all and I love following the money
If you want to know what's happening you just got to look at the money
There are only four big record labels now
All the independence pretty much get it they understand that the way to move music the way to market it the way to package it is to let people
Share it with their friends and podcasters sometimes have a shitload of friends who listen very intensely to their shows
And
in podcasting we've proven time and time again that you do sell music if you if a song is played on a podcast
The hypocrisy of the four majors
Is that whenever they've got something to promote that benefits their agenda which means new current music
Because that's really all that they focus on when it comes to record sales the record sales divisions not the music licensing, but the record sales divisions
Um
They're very happy to say hey man go ahead go ahead and play it don't worry about it. You won't get in trouble. I'll make sure I'll get you covered
Yeah, so
You know, obviously they understand the value as well, but no one can quite get past the lawyers
Now the music that I from time to time will play and I and again I just can't help myself
I do because it's it's my art. It's my art form to let you know how I'm feeling as it relates to a story or maybe something that's going on in the world
Or maybe just the weather or whatever it is and I believe that it's a real way to communicate and
Being able to choose the music that I want to play for you regardless of what it is is is
Virtually Nirvana it is it is what I love to do
Now I realize that pure music shows very very hard to maintain an audience
In podcasting. That's why I only play one or two songs throughout the entire show also I got shit to say
And it also makes it that much more special you know
I focus a lot of attention on the songs that I play. It's not just really nearly
You know, I really think about this stuff and I get a shit load of submissions
So
I just can't help myself and I think it's really important that
Maybe I just take that role upon myself. I want to make sure that all this great music which is now sitting in huge archives
Digital archives not even in stores stores almost no longer exist we can go and buy this music
There's almost no way to discover all the great great songs that I grew up with and
And the people that I know I love sharing those stories and it's no different from from what's happening now
It's exactly the same. You know will we be talking about a Matthew evil and a slow and
Carmen Tyler will we talking about these people
Ten years now of course you will and podcasts. There's will have the same stories that I have now about
You know aerosmith and and Von Jovi and the Rolling Stones
And the kings even god. I'm dating myself. Okay
So it's important and it's important that people who
Listen to the daily source code get some kind of education
I mean I'm talking so much shit anyway. Let me give you an example here's an email that I received from Cassandra
Hey Adam with your newfound willingness to risk playing non-pod save music on occasion why not
Hit up yon the food bar Friday hit test
Well, yes, and I have had conversations with with representatives from all of the dig four labels about doing exactly that
Same thing came back they love it
Fantastic we're not gonna make any ways, but of course we're not gonna
Publicly allow and you say that will allow you to do that
Cassandra goes on saying I missed the hit test so much
That thing was my favorite part of the show back in the summer of 2005
I listened to the source code loud as hell on my stereo in my room while I played PC games and every time
There was a new hit test. It just got louder now
I don't actually know any of the music on the hit test
I was born in 1986 so I was a bit young for the 80s music, but I always loved to hear the hit test because it's just so incredibly
Awesome and fun every time and I learned something about music past
And a few times I went to go buy one of the songs and iTunes bingo there you go the circle
It's complete that is exactly what I'm talking about
I hope you understand what I'm saying now I'm not giving up my support for pod save music because it doesn't matter to me
It's music and I love it and I love playing new music
I think the only safe thing to do here is just stay away from the new stuff that
The record companies are trying to sell I get it I understand that and quite frankly you've got your own ecosystem for that
And I'm not interested really although there are some songs that I hear on the radio that I'd love to play to let me tell you
There's still some great music being made just this mainstream doesn't mean it's crap and I'm here to service you
Hey, you know what that's the ultimate answer. It's my job to service you to entertain you
And if that means going to jail so be it
Okay, now now that what happened this evening? Oh, man, well how much time do I have six minutes?
Okay, yeah, I can I can get it in for the people listening on serious satellite radio
Beginning of the month I received this comment. I'm just gonna replay it for you because
Well, it's it's the beginning of a very interesting story
Hi Adam it's Eric Bergen. You might remember my name. I'm the host of green room radio and arts and entertainment podcast and in fact
We were one of the first podcasts to feature a theme song by Jeff Smith
Anyway, here's why I'm sending in this audio comment
I was very involved in the podcasting world almost since the beginning in fact
That was one of your first listeners and I was a dedicated listener. I listened every single day
In August
I made the decision to stop listening
This was in about early to mid August and the decision came out of the fact that my other life which was that of an actor
Actually started picking up steam and I started getting work and I was in rehearsals all day and doing shows at night
And I just didn't have time for podcasting anymore. I haven't done an episode of my own podcasts since May
Don't worry we're coming back next week, but I just
I just need to know
I need a little update because I want to rejoin the daily source code listening experience
But I need to know what's going on. I can't just join the show and not know what's going on
Did you move it sounded like you moved houses? What's this free Trinity thing? I need if you could just give me or maybe one of your listeners
Could give me just a three minute update of
Everything I need to know that's been happening in the daily source code world since I guess mid August the last time I checked in
August the pod show website had just gone public
But I think that's that was really the biggest thing that was going on then so if you could just just let me know
Just catch me up on everything and I'm sorry to ask you I just I want to rejoin
But I can't just rejoin and not know what's going on. It's like trying to
Join
24 in the middle of the season. You don't know what the hell's going on
Also next time you're in San Francisco
I'm here for a while doing a little show called jersey boys playing at the current theater and and I know Adam that you sort of are a jersey boy because you you live there
Now
The show isn't about you the show is actually about Frankie Valley in the four seasons
But I'd love for you to come we're playing at the current theater right on Gary Street. It's right near pod show HQ
So why don't you come on down? I'll pay for your ticket. I promise
Okay, that's all just someone give me an update. Please
All right, so Eric sends that comment in and I have to say hilarity ensued because it was pretty funny and you know
There were some updates that came in which I'm not gonna play for you now, but it was good
So you know you you heard there that he
Was host of the green green room radio. It's green room radio. I think yeah green room radio podcast
And that he's an actor. Okay, so and remember this is
What is this this is a February fifth of February six something like that when this came in
Amazing because still find it and and so he's you know, he's working this show
Jersey boys so I actually hear about this show. You know, it's a big Broadway smash
It's about the life and times of Frankie Valley and the four seasons. I'm like okay, you know, this is great
So I was supposed to go last Tuesday as you know my trip was delayed. I still haven't been able to tell you why
But that's also forthcoming maybe by food bar for lucky and
And I completely forget about about the tickets so he sends me an email. He says, hey, I don't
I heard on the show that you know that you're delayed your your trip has been delayed
Shall I move it till next week? I'm like, oh fuck man. I'm so sorry really apologize. Thanks for for checking in with the yes
I'd love to so tickets were a one ticket was ready for me this evening at the current theater
Folgers with splendor. I love it. It's a fantastic combination
So I haven't been to the theater in in a while. It's nice theater by the way the current so
You know after a while not not not after work work never ends, but around seven I get picked up because I know it should be there
We'll call by seven thirty because pretty busy. I'm telling you pretty busy. It's sold out. I mean this this is like I'm okay
Wow, this is pretty interesting now because I had one ticket and and of course Eric. Thank you
You know there's a high likelihood that you're going to get put next to someone else who had one ticket and
I was there a nice new on time and the theater hadn't filled up yet and I sit down next to a gentleman who I think was
Probably in his late 80s and
You know, I say hi doing and I said, yeah, it looks like
We're the only guys with no dates here tonight and it was a beautiful guy
Who lost his wife a couple years ago
He lives on the embarked era. He comes to the theater and he loves the musicals because
All dialogue really goes too fast for him to process although I had no problem communicating with him
He said, you know, it's not a matter of not being able to hear. I just can't process it fast enough
But I love the songs
I love musicals because you know, I can go with the flow here. There you go music
I can go with the flow of the music whether I recognize it or not and it just makes me feel really happy
It was nice. You know, I had a nice chat with this guy
And he's like he said, hey, yeah, no date
So we get into stuff. We're just talking and he says so how come you're here? I said well
someone who's in in the play and in this musical got me a ticket
And says name is Eric and I pick up the play bill and
Yeah, we're just chatting away and I'm looking I'm actually going to the page now and what is the the title of the page?
Let me see, let me just get to it here. Hey folks on serious satellite radio. I'm so sorry
I can't get this story in within within within a lot of times
You can have to go to dailysourceco.com
Download the rest because it's really it's really worth it. And you'll hear some great music
So I see here's the here's the credits if you wills have it they call it the credits page
Jersey boys the story of Frankie Valley in the four seasons
Book by Marshall Brickman and Rick Ellis or at least music by Bob Godio more about that in a minute
lyrics by Bob crew with Eric Bergen Michael Ingersol Christopher Cale Jones and Devon May
Dude, he's not in this he's fucking starring in it so I'm like you know going through the play bill
And sure enough you've got the who's who's in the cast who's who in the cast listen to this
You've got a kick out of this Eric Bergen who plays Bob Godio now Bob Godio was the man who wrote
just an amazing amount of fantastic hits for Frankie Valley in the Ford not just for Frankie Valley in the four seasons
But for many other artists as well and it wasn't until he joined the four seasons that are really
kicked into gear in the combination Bob Godio and Frankie Valley that's really what the magic was
It still is actually I should say so Eric Bergen plays Bob Godio
Eric is a recent non graduate of the North Carolina School of the Arts
Eric is thrilled to finally be making his agent some money and to be part of the Jersey boys family
Other recent credits around the country include white Christmas the three musketeers and warrior
Eric is also the producer and host of green room radio an arts and entertainment podcast at
www.greenroomradio.com all the love and thanks to mom and dad whatever you guys did seems to have worked
Please visit Ericbergen.com for more info and that's E-E-E-R-I-C-H Bergen dot com so I'm like oh, okay
This is really quite amazing. Let me tell you
Not and and this is of course why I'm on this whole
Musical educational trip because by the way the audience was pretty old I mean definitely skewed old there was a lot of
You know people probably in their 50s
Who would and and 50s and 60s I would say who would definitely witness
Frankie Valley in the four seasons and by the way when you hear some of the songs if you you know
If you'll just take a moment and go to iTunes and listen to some of the previews or if you have some kind of music
Service just you know type in Frankie Valley in the or the four seasons Frankie Valley and that's V-A-L-L-I
And and you'll recognize these songs probably from the third or fourth version or the third or fourth time that it was a hit and cover versions
This story is indeed about
Frankie Valley and
And and and what's so nice about it of course the Frankie in the four seasons are from Jersey and
You know indeed. I'm from Jersey and
You what came across so well in in this piece is
What Jersey guys or Jersey boys are like?
famously Frankie Valley and Bob Gaudio
Sealed their professional relationship on a handshake and
They always agreed you know this is how we're gonna roll with it from from this day on and to this day indeed
They they still have you know a handshake agreement
It's such a Jersey boy thing the way they talked. I mean it came across so well
I completely connected it's also a very very physical
Peace of work
There's a catwalk so you really have two levels of the stage and every single actor is is moving pieces of set in and out
I mean the scene changes there's there must be a hundred of them and it goes so quick because the actors are actually
moving the set pieces in
The lighting is fantastic sound amazing
Absolutely amazing
The singing oh gosh. I got to tell you it was really it was just enjoyable
Let's see it's
Christopher Kale Jones who plays a Frankie Valley fantastic voice and I don't know how these guys do it
Because you know they're miked with theatrical mics which are kind of hidden on their head or in their hair
And it was pretty clear to me that the microphones that we're using on stage were just props and
It must be very hard to sing a song hold a microphone but not to really have the direct relationship between what's coming out of your mouth and the mic and fun of you
You know thing is stuck to your head basically
I just I don't know how they do that
Devon May who plays a Tommy DeVito who kind of founded the group
Great actor award winning actor. I might add just amazing performance and
And Michael Inger saw who plays Nick Massey just everyone in the cast was fantastic. There was another guy there
What's his name and all you know
In a couple of songs all of a sudden you'd you'd hear this incredible voice and I'm looking around like where's it coming from and this this guy would be on the stage again
And he was just ripping it up. It was so good
Um
Not anyway, so if you have it it's a pretty hot ticket so you may not you know you can probably see it in Vegas
You can see it on Broadway
It would be nice if you were able to see it in San Francisco. I'm sure this is the traveling show
So I don't know when or where they're going next
But it is a show that we'll teach you something because even I was saying oh crap
I forgot all about that song. I didn't or didn't even know that
That it was a frankie valley in the four seasons song. I mean
Even though I know every single one of the songs the memory is so limited so it's really important that
You know that we keep reminding ourselves of what what great songs have been created and as the story goes throughout the evening
All the songs
Come at it the exact moment and in the exact circumstances that the song was written
And at one point frankie valley separates from his wife and and she's a sweetheart
But you know, it's a show business, right? It got all messed up and that's when
Bob Goody writes this song for frankie valley and
Just hearing it on stage
It was uncanny man
It was so beautiful when you listened to the lyrics and know the backstory that
He was trying to make and show business and it wrecked his home life
And yet so far
Carried your books from school
Played maple in your marriage and he
He worked the great hour six when we came to me
Walk at home every day
Overbound a good bridge
And wait until we go into the near you
When our separate way
My
Forever lay the hand on your mind
Like the name of the way for me you couldn't see how I taught
So close, so close and yet so far
Beautiful city lights
Clung the ladder of the fortune and fame
Worked my fingers to the bone
Make my self-ename
For the icing to find
But no matter how the news on the one
Still I reminisce about the girl I miss
And the love I let behind
Mines a toy
But we'll never let a hand on your mind
And don't
Like the name of the way for me you couldn't see how I taught
So close, so close and yet so far
Mines a toy
But no matter how the news on the one
Still I reminisce about the girl I miss
Like the name of the way for me you couldn't see how I taught
So close, so close and yet so far
Mines a toy
Don't worry about the way for me you couldn't see
Like the name of the way for me you couldn't see how I taught
You know I have like promo as all kinds of stuff I wanted to play that I'm just going to leave that until tomorrow
Because I want to leave you with that music ringing in your ears so that you
Well, you just won't be able to help yourself but go and find out more about
The wonderful music of Frankie Valley in the four seasons and again
If you have a chance to go see this musical jersey boys and if at all possible with this
Cast in wherever they are you definitely should do it Eric burger you are
Eric burger God damn it I suck Eric burger you are a huge talent
Fuck podcasting man on stage is where you belong you've totally totally got it and I got to tell you this guy carries a large portion of this musical with narration and the timing
blown away dude completely blown away
All right
One more full day in
Northern California that'll be tomorrow. Oh, I'm gonna be on cranky geeks with that's John C. Devorex show cranky geeks.com
So I I don't know if they do that live or
And then put up the podcast, but I guess the podcast will be put up tomorrow. So give that
Check that out check it out
All right daily source code calm Adam at podshow.com. Thank you very much for listening
Talk to you tomorrow another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
The best in the brightest served up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivery podshow in line light