Oh, look, it's been about five minutes I've been on Twitter, let's see, uh, listening
to the DSC 592.
Now, let's watch a pop-up on Twitter vision.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Should I be counting shit?
Cuz I can get no sleep.
Wherever I go, you'll be.
So glad to tell me it's been a second.
Really, when I say, my head is waiting for me.
How did I get this way?
I'm falling, I'm falling as you may do.
I can get you out of my head.
I can get you out of my way.
You'll be.
Talk to me.
Fucking
I have to run my way and get to where you run, I see it get to
I'm in, now I just want you out of my shoes
Going down with me all my knees
She says life doesn't know that it's easy
I love it, yes, it's gonna be a long day
All I know might not be coming home today
She says life doesn't know that it's easy
I love it, yes, it's gonna be a long day
All I know might not be coming home today
I can't live without you, I can't live without you
Creative control, down on that
My head, free brothers from Melbourne, Australia
Podsafe, brand new on the Podsafe music network
I can't get you out of my head
Everybody, how you doing?
It is the daily source code at per person
Number 592 coming to you from the curry manner
in Guilford and Surrey in the United Kingdom.
I did it.
I did what I set out to do this morning.
Remember yesterday I said that if the weather was just as nice
as yesterday, I was going to go flying solo, I've done it.
Now, let me just say a couple of things.
First of all, the weather today, once again, beautiful.
The weather report had Cavoke, that's C-A-V-O-K,
Charlie Elf of Victor Oscar Kilo, which whenever you see that,
what does that actually stand for?
I think civil aviation, okay, something like that.
It basically Cavoke means it's perfectly fine to go flying.
Now, a small caveat, the wind's about 15 knots,
gusting to 25 knots, so that's about 30 miles an hour.
And it's coming from 090, so basically a cross-wind gusting cross-wind.
Now, when you're landing, and you have wind from the side,
you've got to kind of steer into the wind.
So basically, you're coming in sideways, and at the very,
well, not the very light, but almost at the last minute,
you're going to turn the aircraft onto the center line,
and you're going to basically land.
Of course, if it's gusting, it's a little more challenging
because it's not a consistent wind.
Now, I knew this was going to happen.
And pilots who were listening will know this feeling.
You know, you've got this, you're anxious.
I have the last 10 flights I've done.
I have not done solo that been with a safety pilot.
I've been pretty much from here to Rotterdam.
I haven't really done any a lot of solo flying.
So you're always like, OK, you know, there's now
there's no one to save my ass if I mess it up.
So right after I dropped Christina off at school,
went over to Echo Golf, Tango Fox Trot, Ferrox Airfield.
And the wind had picked up a little bit,
and he had to wheel out the aircraft, so I had my nice English breakfast.
By the way, I really understand the English breakfast.
The full English, I get it.
I love it.
And you need that when you're going to go flying.
Now you need to be really completely ready and revved up.
So you know, and for those of you who aren't pilots,
remember when you first had your driver's license,
and you got the car for the first time,
you're going to go out and drive around by yourself.
That kind of feeling is basically what it is.
And it was warm today, so it was like 22 degrees centigrade.
So needless to say, I had a very sweaty ass.
But it went fine, I did five or six circuits.
One or two had a little bounce there, but that's
to be expected with the gusting wind.
And of course, I'm much lighter than typical since it was just me,
in the front of the aircraft.
But it feels like it's a victory.
It really, really feels good.
Hey, special reminder to May is National Master Basin Month.
Hold on, there's a link for this.
Let me see, counter punch, where is it?
Here we go.
Oh, boy.
May is National Master Basin Month,
having been so declared by the erotically aware,
Jill of Gells, at good vibrations,
and the Godmother of Master Basin herself, Dr. Betty Dodson.
That's true, Dr. Betty Dodson is indeed the Godfather
of female Master Basin.
Why bother to have a National Master Basin Month?
Well, since just about everybody plays sexual soletarily,
sometimes, is virtually the nations
and the world's most preferred leisure past time.
I will leave this link on the show notes
so you can take a look at that at yourself.
But I do suggest, I do suggest that we all honor
this fantastic month of May.
Hey, and I'm Frank McMahon here, producer of
Bunch of Show's Rumor Girls, Meteor to Secrets,
and yes, show girls, just listen to DSC 8591.
You're talking about show girls.
And we were discussing the file size,
little in it, I'll take the blame.
I brought it up, I was actually discussing it.
And actually, I've been trying to get it raised for a while now,
and that because I'm, you know, megabyte hungry.
But, you know, we're doing a lot of video stuff
and, you know, really coming up against the limit,
just to put things in perspective.
The 200 megabyte limit was set around the age of 320
by 240 iPod video format.
You could actually do a pretty long show at that res.
Then the standard for iPod video,
jumped to 648 times 480.
Now with Apple TV, the res is up again.
This time 960 times 540 for white screen Apple TV format.
Again, this is only in the past year.
This has happened.
So you're seeing web video that's higher res
than iPod video that's much higher res
and now new devices like Apple TV.
So for example, we now do a new show called Rumor Girls HD,
which is a version of our show that plays in high res and stuff.
Now, the iPod version of a recent episode
is 69 megabytes.
That same exact show in Apple TV format is 170 megabytes.
Now, that's only for a show that's about five minutes long.
We've actually been compensating by limiting our shows
now to about six minutes, the video shows.
So any longer than that, we're over 200 megabytes easily
with the high res Apple TV format.
So hence why the larger size is better.
And as for the girls complaining,
well, they're pretty proactive girls,
and they get feisty.
So you've listened to the show.
So you know what I'm talking about.
And we've actually been ramping up show girls
a lot in the past several months with share, KFC,
and GB Kelly Lewis, soccer girl, and Karen and Carla.
And we're really getting into the group.
We're having a lot of fun.
So we hope your listeners will check it out.
Go to showgirls.pachow.com.
And Adam just wanted to wrap up and say,
Pachow has helped us tremendously.
Especially with room of girls in the past year.
I mean, the storage is really just the beginning for us.
I mean, you've helped in promotion and marketing.
And of course, sponsors.
You've allowed us to run this empire as a business.
So thanks for that.
And thanks for upping the limit.
We just want to be ready for the future.
So anyway, thanks Adam.
Take care.
And I really appreciate it.
Of course, we're not entirely perfect.
OK, so we'll be next Monday when listeners will be invited
to help Pachow suck less.
I just want to say one thing about the video upload.
What you will see in a forthcoming generation
of the Pachow network is automatic transcoding
from your uploaded files into flash.
So you'll have your feed with your original source material,
which would be MP4 or MP3.
And all the rest immediately is transcoded to flash.
And you'll have a module to put that on your show site.
So hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, we're listening.
We want to suck less.
Help us suck less.
Pachow needs you to help us suck less.
1, 2, 1, 6, 2, 1, 6, 3, 5, 7.
1, 1, 2, 1, 6, 5, 6, 3, 5, 7.
Hello, I'm Mrs. Chow.
Hello, DSC listeners.
I haven't been listening for a while.
I haven't been phoneian for longer.
But back, you're not in the big number.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's chars the drunk in London, or any of those
silver and his bag got leaked my notebook uh just like me I've got
moleskin sort of no pad notebook that is analog notebook I lost my digital
camera I lost my ipod and uh are are the bits and pieces I like it does
mean that I now without an ipod means I don't really get a chance to listen to the
VAT which is a real bugger I have to wait until I've got a bit more money and
I can replace the thing oh well how you guys will okay and it means on
oh Charles I feel completely shitty for you man that how it you feel so
violated when someone steals something from you don't you gosh that sucks I'll
tell you what email me an address my friend and I will send you the the red
ipod I got from Virgin Atlantic so at least you'll have something to listen
to the Charlie to and you know it's like you definitely deserve that because
you've been such a you know it's such a consistent fine drunken
Londoner
I got to move things along because we have a yet another savant from the
circle standing by to talk to us about a topic that's on everyone's mind has
been discussed in the blog blogosphere throughout the past week or two and this
all stemmed from a posting on a daily cause about the sound exchange license
for web radio for streaming radio and of course there's already controversy
or should I say controversy about the pronunciation of daily cause.
They had them don't play this oh we never mind you never do anyway listen just
point of note it's daily codes and it codes apparently is like this guy's
nickname out of democracy I think it's a guys real name so now it turns out
it hurts my codes so therefore I think it's still a team that's what Mark is
Marcos and daily codes daily codes is just the guy's name.
See ya.
The savant specials.
Okay it's time for our savant from our series of the circle of savants
by the Sultan of Sitzavans.
So I think I'm going to be able to get at least one savant in episode
there's a fast forward button on there for a reason.
And I hope to be able to talk to savant every single day.
So I'm on.
And by the way I want you to know that this format change doesn't mean that I don't
student want to make it pictures make it pictures.
I'm the southern of Sitzavans savants.
From the circle of savants now and as you know the people that we hired pod show
I hope there's savants comic strip blogger might disagree.
But certainly Brian longest who has been with us since the inception
conception of pod show.
Brian what the hell is your title?
You know I don't give a shit about titles.
What is the EVP of operations and stuff?
Yeah the operation of stuff.
Covered quite a bit.
Whatever fall through the cracks lands on my desk.
So Brian is very interesting guy because not only has he been CEO of his own company
at least one that I know of.
He holds a degree in law and a degree in computer science.
And what did you that's right correct.
Does it look from a real school Brian?
Cool yeah.
Actually from George Mason both law and undergraduate comes to computer science.
And I practice with the patent attorney as well.
Obviously just every day attorney.
Okay so patent.
So not a copyright attorney per se with a patent attorney which is.
Well here's a thing about law.
You know you in the US you pass the bar for each state.
And then you can practice any law you want other than patent law.
Then you have to take a specific exam to pass the patent bar exam.
So everyone can say yeah I'm a copyright attorney or trademark attorney etc.
But only those that pass a particular exam they're a patent attorney.
So I did focus on patent copyright trademark trade secret.
Mainly related to software internet and that sort of thing because I was my background.
So when you when you mentioned this to chicks get all hot bothered when you say you're a patent attorney.
Does that work?
Does it turn them on?
Oh of course.
Now I just want to point out why that was my selling good look.
Oh.
Potshow has not to my knowledge actually filed any patents.
Has it have we filed patents?
No we haven't yet.
We haven't yet.
It's considered evil Brian you're not supposed to file any patents.
That's wrong.
You can't do that.
No no you know why we want to do it because we want to make everything we're doing public.
So others can build upon it.
Right?
Make a better world.
That's the patent system.
Oh man you are such a lawyer.
Oh my god.
Oh wow.
Anyway.
Well we we didn't hire Brian necessarily for his talent in law.
Although it has come in very very handy in a lot of stuff certainly in the start-up phase.
It was fantastic to have your wealth and breadth of knowledge amongst us.
Now you work you operate.
What do you do Brian?
What do I do here at Potshow?
Yeah.
What do you do at Potshow?
Oh boy.
So we handle let's see.
In operations business operations if you will.
We handle that.
And you know anything that comes in legal lives and we've got many different.
Count different individuals will work with us depending upon it's copyright or
corporate or what it may be.
HR facilities the office office IT customer support and then network operations which is different.
And that's handling our campaign management and then to fail to come through and make
it sure we keep everyone happy and running.
And then everything else that comes in there working with talent relations etc.
So are you also responsible for like the coffee machine?
Yeah.
Ultimately actually ultimately I think it responsible for anything that goes wrong.
That's right.
Brian.
Exactly.
So this is the main right.
Yeah.
You never get invited to the parties.
No.
For the crap when someone peeps in the toilet.
Right.
Exactly.
All kidding aside Brian.
There are two people that I reached out to regarding this web radio sound exchange.
Statutory compulsory license.
One of them is the official musicologist of the Charlie Sir Jersey Todd.
He's a workers compensation attorney.
So he said that he would have to pass on it because he was absolutely no good.
He did however point out that you know that earlobe infection I got.
He said I could probably get about five grand.
Really?
He's going to find like one thousand other people like you and put it together.
I don't know.
I'm getting what it would have been showing the company or who do we sue them.
Yeah.
I don't know how to handle it.
I'll find out.
Don't worry.
I'll let you know.
Sounds like easy money to me.
Sounds like gasp.
Yeah.
So you studied the links that I sent you and of course you've been involved in internal conversations about this.
Tell me what's your take on it?
Well I think it's interesting.
Let me I'm a practice full time for quite a while.
So let me give you the background of just copyright law in general.
And then you can kind of see why they got to where they are right now and why they're having these issues.
You know, copyright law in August was around 76 when they said okay everyone who has a they will have a bundle of rights.
So your copyright have a bundle of rights things that you can do.
And then as time goes on like anything else is kind of throw stuff underneath there because they don't know where else to put it.
So then came in 1995 I believe it was a digital performance right.
And they essentially said well they're going to add a new right to this bundle of rights.
And if you want to look it up at 17 USC it's 106.
So I did a new right right number six.
So these bundle of rights that consisted of things like rights to play on the radio rights to cells.
Am I doing that?
Well sort of mainly it's a little broader than that.
Like friends and the right to reproduce the copyright work to what one.
One that everyone always talks about it created derivative work.
You always hear them talk about that distributed copies.
And so that's six the right that they added with specific to the digital audio transmission.
So that's in other words they're saying you copyright holder have the right to perform this.
And well not perform it.
But put it out you know digital audio transmission is what they do.
To allow someone else to feed it through a digital audio transmission I presume.
Well yeah so in other words you get to retain that right.
We're giving that to you the copyright.
And then that and then what comes along they say however.
This is what they call the you know the performance right.
They created a statutory license.
And they who is they Brian who is they who creates it when you say they created who's that.
Gee well it goes back to let's see it always works with white up bill and then.
So it's like U.S. laws like it's like federal law.
Yeah essentially I mean they put it into the code itself.
So that's when they say it's you know they put it into the statute.
And then essentially what's nice is that that's the way you want it.
You want the copyright holder to be able to do whatever they want.
But they said okay under the digital millennium copyright act that was in 98.
They came up with webcasting because no one knew what to do with that.
So they said well we created this new right.
Let's stick webcasting under there.
Okay okay okay hold on a second so that right initially okay I've read up on the material as well.
My friend and as you know I I practice law my spare time here in the county of a jury.
And so those rights that that right initially underneath it was satellite radio.
Cable music services I believe and was there a third one that I missed.
There was something else I'd have to look it out maybe subscribe was music subscription services under that.
Well that's where that's where it gets interesting.
For subscription and non subscription there's also interactive or non interactive.
So what the hell is that what the hell is interactive and non interactive.
I saw that.
Yeah interactive is just let's say you were to look online and say I want to hear that song now you click it and you start to hear that song.
They can sort of that interactive and then to define it they say well anything played within I believe it's over an hour of when it was actually.
Um requested.
If it's within that hour then it's interactive if it's not then it's the non interactive.
So if you put it if you publish a program guide and it says okay at at at at 815 tonight you'll be able to listen to the Beatles help.
It would be good to interact actually.
It's a little more of you actually.
Um requesting something like almost like playing a movie on part request.
Okay I got it.
So so what they decide to do would say well you know what the we're going to leave a right with you to copyright holder unless it's non interactive.
So then they apply the statutory licensing.
And essentially what they're I mean usually what you hear most people say and I'm sure you have colors they'll tell me I'm wrong but usually what they'll say is well why you want to do this.
You want to do this because there's a lot of copyright holders out there you can't find them.
So this business would never you know I'm really aware of webcast anything if they had to go out and individually find everybody unless they have particularly a pretty clear degree with that so that's where they came up with well.
Okay now we're going to collect create a uh copyright like a collection agency that's the sound.
Sound exchange.
Now let them let them figure it out let um the webcasters pay them and then let them figure out how to find all these people.
So kind of make this intermediary.
But that intermediary turns out to be the actual owners of all this copyright because in most cases it's the it's the the big record label.
So the kind of saying you guys who own it you go and collected that's correct.
Yeah sort of they're telling what they say is the sound exchange they say you can go collect it.
And it's it's pretty funny here here's an analogy because all I deal with is my my kids when I'm home.
The analogy is you know my my two little boys one of them says hey dad I want to go to one's toy.
So I take it and I give it to them.
But this analogy is where they they see that there's a house down the street and they can look in the window and they see the toy and they know the boy's name is Joe.
But they've never been to boy and they say dad go give me that toy.
Okay well I go in I break in I take the toy Joe the little kid doesn't know I took it and I give it to my kids and they say okay.
I said well you know shouldn't we let Joe know we've got it like well.
Let's put Joe's name on a list and pack it to the back of our house and if Joe ever comes by and happens to go over our fence and look at the back of our house.
We'll have put five cents in you know every time we take one of his toys if he looks them then we'll get five cents because he found the list.
So that's exactly what's our exchange done go to their site and you can find a list of all these artists that they're saying hey guys you need to come to us and collect your money.
They don't proactively go out and find these people and after three years they get to keep all the money.
Oh really if you haven't.
Yeah so basically it's really interesting the way they set it up.
I mean theoretically I think there might be you know on the right track honestly I don't have a solution myself.
So you know if you don't have your own solution usually you need to shut up.
But in this case I don't think they've done they've gone far enough.
So why the big record agency they're always record agency's always talked about because well they have a deal with the sound exchange.
They know they're doing this they pay attention and they go and ask for their money.
Well sound exchange is the is the record companies Brian sound exchange is Warner and Universal so you know they know exactly that it's their stuff that's being played.
They know how to find the owner because it's them.
Right in the in the little guy if you will you know the independent artists.
Well no one's looking out for them really this was supposed to be something that would help them.
And that's them who knows if it really is because unless you're going to go seek it out.
So here's what's what's become here's what is very interesting to me.
So I understand that if you create a so if you put us if you make a song you make an MP3 out of it you put it up on the internet.
And you license it under creative commons creative commons attribution let me do not.
Yeah creative commons attribution.
It is there by.
I believe that the copyright holder has said okay look as as long as people.
I mentioned my name or say with the song came from it's kind of okay to put it on your your your non interactive service.
At the same time it appears and this is what the reporting this is really the nucleus of the story of course it appears that sound exchange.
Will be able to.
Collect a fee based upon the number of people who heard that song on said web stream or web streams.
Right that that's exactly right and the reason that is is you know essentially you started out the copyright holder you made that song you put it up.
You've got the right all of them so you can go out on the side with the do it on so you say okay I'm going to use this creative commons or whichever one it is here's my license and here's what people can do.
Then government come along says well I know we gave you those rights but guess what we're going to take that one back real.
Here's an exception that's what the statutory license is it's an exception to that one particular right that you had right and then.
What's interesting is will then comes along these and they're a little difficult to figure out with these waivers where the copyright owner can.
Can wave and say well okay actually I want to give these people.
The ability to do this as long as I let everybody know.
So it's it's weird here all your right or just like I'm going to domain but we're taking that one back.
Wow we will give you this weird strange exception and a waiver if you can figure out how to find the people and get a waiver from them then maybe okay you won't have to end up paying sound exchange.
So that's where it becomes really interesting and that's what they don't point out.
Well they don't point it out but but it's interesting light.
No I'm sure it's not in flashing light so a couple to have learned something very interesting here first of all I've learned that.
And I have to presume that this actually was in place a long time ago I don't think this is new because the initially the reason why sound exchange is kind of popped to the top of the stack is because of the rate hike.
But but this actual the statutory license has been in there all along so presumably and there are maybe thousands or hundreds of thousands of SRCOs I think that's what it is sound recording copyright owners independent artists who have put their music out there that may have been played on a web stream.
Who can go and get money from sound exchange.
Yeah there's a huge list and then actually say that it doesn't cover everyone you know there are two things they're going to make the float on the money although I did see I think one of their quarters they collected about 14 million so we're not talking about a huge amount but you know the float on what's not collected could be pretty generous.
And I hope after three years people will just forget about it or you know one through years passes if they don't go get it or they get to keep it.
Really that's that's pretty disgusting. Okay, so so it's interesting that this this is never popped to the top before and I guess what you know the the next logical question is what if they.
And I guess that would be the government who then hands it off the sound exchange determine that other types of transmission.
Now also fall under this particular right.
Yeah, there's nothing there's nothing you say they couldn't I mean you know this is essentially Congress they can do it if they want.
Now it's up to the court to figure out and interpret what they wrote which is what always happens.
You know they put something in the law and then it's up to the court to figure out what do they really mean.
So we'll have to see how it goes from there but it's going to be fairly interesting.
They constantly have carve out since happening more and more as you can see I mean one active in 76 with a 95 with a 98.
I think they set up this copyright the royalty panel whatever they call it I think that was either late 90s early 2000 really.
So it's going to change constantly it's pretty interesting.
Okay, so so one things for sure if today I started a stream.
I put it my little windows media server and I started a stream and I played pod safe music all day long.
I could potentially be hit with the depending on how many people are listening to it.
I could be hit with a pretty big bill for again to depending on a successful I am.
For the music played on that on that radio that web radio stream.
Yeah, well it's interesting you see how successful so the carve out is commercial versus non commercial.
So there are some differences in fees if you're commercial.
Whether or not you don't plan to make any money off of it.
Okay.
So you can go in there and read it's like on to the 115 pages where they talk about how they came up with.
How they came up with this with a particular code and essentially they talk about how they're going to charge you the percentage of revenue or is it.
You know per usage fee a flat fee it gets on right so now of course the people for money.
Yeah, the proposal now is is that it's zero point to eight cents per per listen with a minimum of five hundred dollars per channel per year.
But essentially the question that I asked is the answer is yes if I did that I would have to pay for it as a webcaster.
Yeah, exactly and I don't know if this makes a lot of sense because online I think we've changed so much.
The idea and the standard is how do they come up with you rates what makes them decide and they usually say well let's assume.
We had someone who wanted to give up their right and wanted the license it and someone who wanted to buy it.
Oh willing seller willing buyer and then there's some other factors they put in the play and they come up with what they think the right is.
But really it's what the market's going to bear.
Who knows?
The law is going to dictate behavior.
If all of a sudden you put something in place and they want to make any money off of it everything goes away.
Right.
Which was my entire point.
Yeah, which was my entire point.
My entire point was hey if the RIA which indirectly sound exchanges they want to put these huge prices on it that's fine because it'll just go away because people can't afford to do it.
And in the same breath I said but you know that's why we have all these alternative licenses out there you can go to garage ban you can go to.
PMN you can go you can use creative commons and in that case the entire intent of the artist is to say hey it's okay you can play this I'm going to make my money on sales I believe in that or it's great promotion for me.
By the way radio doesn't have to pay this type of fee unless they're rebroadcasting.
They're they're signal through a stream a traditional radio does not have to pay this type of copy right from what I understand.
So the last question I have for you Brian in those 115 pages or whatever it was that you that you skimbed throughout me hello.
Brian.
Hello.
Okay that's fixed.
So the the final question was in those 115 pages that you skim through like everything else.
Yeah.
Did it.
Was there a very particular language about what exactly a song constitutes?
I mean let's say right now I have a show it's 30 minutes long and I sing.
Hey la hey la hey la hola that means it's a song with a lot of wrap around it.
Is that now a song? Is that a sound recording? Is that an official tune that I can charge for someone webcast that?
Interesting.
You know I'd have to think a little more about that.
Okay we clearly have more work to do Mr. Long.
I do know that I personally wouldn't pay for that one.
Oh man.
You don't listen to my show on a regular day.
You will now.
All right Brian. So what I'd like you to do over the course of the next week and I'm going to try and find the Lawrence Lasseg of Creative Commons.
I'm sure no one from EFF will ever call because that's only when it serves them do they call.
I'm going to I'd like you to look into the waiver thing and see you know that could be a great way to save you know web radio which I do believe in.
I think it's good and I don't particularly it's not particularly what I want to do but the idea of exposing artists to tons of people at an affordable rate which would in my mind will be zero.
That would be fantastic so if you have some time between.
How many kids do you have now nine?
Three.
Okay between the kids and then the other seventy kids at the office.
Could you look into that for me?
Absolutely.
Hey you know just a plug my own little page on pod show longest dot pod show you can see a video of my boys.
Okay.
When they were babies and they're raising their hand for chocolate popcorn and they're just little tiny guys that kind of funny.
All right cool longest dot pod show dot com.
Oh yeah we mean you don't go there every day.
You got me.
Okay.
Who's Jay indeed?
All right Brian.
Thanks a lot man.
I appreciate it and talk to you soon.
All right.
Anytime.
Thanks.
You're honored.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Please don't bang back yet.
Do see your job.
Hey.
I hired me done quit the day.
Yeah baby.
Jersey touch.
Jersey touch here.
You know what's our badminton jersey tie the official music,ologist.
But you know I had a debut is some some new music there because I've I guess I've got a new term here at the daily source code.
code. I am now your ultimate Savan. Yeah, that's right, baby. Any questions you got? Just
just come to Jersey. I'm sure I can figure out the answer for you. But listen, listen,
I have no idea why you dragged me into this copyright discussion. I mean, I don't do copyright
for a living. I mean, it's a very, very, very specific area of law with some very, very
smart people and some very talented people of which I am not one of. All right, but I will try
to give you a little bit of an answer here. I went over to sound exchange.com's website
and there was actually a very, very interesting fact on the whole thing. And basically what
it's telling artists is that if they join sound exchange, they can still negotiate a license with
a webcaster or a podcast or if they wanted to. What sound exchange prohibits artists from doing
is licensing their copyrights to another royalty collection agency. You know, some sort of monsters
to collect money for them. But it does very specifically say that artists can go out and
license their music, whether, you know, to podcasts, there's a webcasters or to any other kind
of statutory licensing. But it does kind of sort of indicate that the artist better go and notify
sound exchange of any direct licenses or statutory licenses or digital music service providers,
so they can make sure that they're getting paid. See, sound exchange makes it look very nice and
very simple that they're just in it for the best interest of the artist trying to get the artist
paid. Yeah, of course, they do want their cut of getting the artist paid. And then, you know,
that's just kind of very, very see-through. So I think maybe sort of kind of, this isn't really,
I'm not as scared as a podcast or playing podcast if music because the artist, you know,
is part of the podcast if music network goes out to the podcast if music network and says it's
okay to play my music. I think that that falls into that section of the fact, I actually feel
pretty good about saying that it does. But, you know, at the same time, I don't feel great about
selling music. I don't know. I'm going to have to defer to Brian Longest on something like that.
But, and like anything else, I don't think that this is something that's going to be answered in one
shot. I mean, I know that everybody out there wants to hear me say or another lawyer say, hey,
this is all okay. It's not all okay. I mean, there's a lot of bullshit lawsuits going around
out there either by the R.I.W.A. or by ASCAP or BMI. I mean, all of these guys are freaking out
because of what we're doing. And this is the backlash. This is the backlash of a bum
rush to the charts and things like that. You're going to see more and more shit like this.
And I can't come right out and say, hey, yeah, okay, fine. It's 100% cool. Because it's not going
to be 100% cool. This is all new technology. This is all new law. You have a lot of judges out there.
A lot of attorneys out there that don't even know where the fucking power button is for their computer.
And I think that what's going to ultimately happen is that a lot of these judges and a lot of these
attorneys are going to have to educate themselves because these lawsuits are coming. They're going to work
their way all the way up and ultimately somebody at the Supreme Court's going to have to make the call on this.
But until that time, this is the wild west. This is the kind of shit that they dealt with then.
I'm going to have to keep dealing with it. So no, I'm not going to say this is 100% cool. I mean,
this fact isn't a legal document. I could have been written by some kid who just wrote their website.
I have no fucking idea. But at the end of the day, I think that the positive music network and I
hold and any time that you have an artist saying it's fine for you to play my music, I think that
that's something right there that you can put in front of a jury and say, hey, the artist said it was cool.
All these people want as their, there's their cut. And, you know, hopefully that's going to be all right.
So this is Jersey Todd, the official, the official ultimate savant. I got to get my total right. The
ultimate savant. Hey, you know, you call me. I don't give myself a title. So I'm your ultimate savant and I'm
punching out. Talk to you later. There you have it. Not one but two legal opinions. What other podcast
gives you that? Huh? None.
The boys grow too fast. Let their toes focus. Don't play leg on all ghosts. Don't play leg.
Do I change my ways? Just for I feel it all. I feel it all. All I feel it all.
She is the delicate, you know, just so I could be with you because don't play leg on all ghosts.
They let go. I feel it all. I feel it all. All I feel it all. All how I would say my chance, I should
be with you because don't play leg on all ghosts. They let go. I feel it all. I feel it all.
I change my ways. Just for I feel it all. I feel it all. I feel it all. All I feel it all.
I was there six o'clock hanging by the open stuff because don't play leg on all ghosts. They let go.
I feel it all. I feel it all. All I feel it all.
I feel it all. All I feel it all. All I feel it all. All I feel it all.
I'm young, what can we do?
I've changed my ways, just for I thought it out
I've thought it all out, I've thought it all out
From the backwaters of Southport, but not Liverpool, but in the UK, it's the Daisy Riots
And girls don't play Lego, I don't know if that's necessarily true, but the song's pretty cool
Just wrapping up a couple of things, by the way, I hope you enjoyed the double shot of Savannah
Today, a little long, I have to admit, but man, it took five minutes just explaining who Brian was
Of course, Y'all know Jersey Todd is who I thought also, although he had a very similar analysis
It was a little more human for some reason
I thank you all for sending pictures of Joan Rivers after I saw her on my virgin flight back from San Francisco
Yes, everyone comments how amazing her face looks
It truly is, it's like plasticine, man, it's fucking outrageous
Mad pod, Jay Donley sent me a picture that he took over in New York
Let's see, here's an email from John Glasscock, confirming her age 74 years old
I tell him, if I look like that one, I'm 74, I'll be very happy
And Brittany Mason sent me an announcement about the reopening of Pod Show Island in Second Life
After the recent move of Pod Show Island next to the popular Soho Island this weekend
That's his upcoming weekend marks the grand reopening of Pod Show Island in Second Life
Pod Show Island mayors, shit, there's mayors, Agma, I'm not a mayor
Now hosting a weekend of epic proportions, a true marriage of first life and second life for an store
All avatars that appreciate great entertainment
I don't know what the fuck that means
But the Jeff Smith will be performing on Friday May 4th
Of course, we all know the Jeff Smith from his many, many, many, many songs
You can't even call them jingles
Saturday May 5th, Cinco de Mayo comes to Pod Show Island
The Pod Mafia will be hosting a party filled with fun and mayhem
At their club on Pod Show Island
Then wraps up Sunday evening with a monumental second life concert on Pod Show's garden stage
Crap man, I might actually have to go check it out
Holy moly, there's a lot going on, I haven't been in second life
Well, I pop in once in a while, but pretty much an ages
Whoa
Okay, that must be the signal it's time to go
Show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Adam at podshow.com
I'll talk to you tomorrow after hopefully more flying
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear