Hey Adam, it's Cupid, well, keep it 1-2-4-9, it's a little new in fact they're over 4,000
Cupid's and were unionized and he allies the problem, Valentine's Day is our day to shine
and get a lot of overtime but if you don't own Lady Patricia like you normally do or
dare I say it even more so, then it'll create this whole lovey-dovey atmosphere but
everyone in a Valentine's spirit let's try and work for us Cupid's so for the
love of the local 406 and working Cupid's everywhere keep it within reason on the
DSC 546 with a lovely lady Patricia hey lady peak you know like a man and
sometimes an Adam's all alone and he needs his love right there on the microphone so
here she is yes the lady Patricia the say to have some better than one and with this angel
from above there's nothing that they both can't do make you wildest dreams come true
so grab your ear bites and jam a man and let the fight you will show begin
it's Adam and Patricia yes Adam and Patricia Adam and the lady Patricia
yes I should have seen it coming should have been ready
Cupid hit me out of nowhere just when I thought I had everything
didn't recognize a feeling like a rush coming to me
yeah you were shouting like a dumb-up just like a girl from a baby your mystery
you said you took me back so fast and not a day go by go down low by my
I'm taking my time and thinking about it not a day go by I don't know why I'm in a big
I'm loving it and I'm thinking of I was having trouble breathing a gentleman took me
could have stopped myself shaking I knew I just met my friends and me
yeah you know just like a angel you know so bright that you've learned at me
you're the world girl in a million I never believed I would never see
tell you love to me and that was a change my life and now the day go by go down low by
I'm taking my time and thinking about it not a day go by I don't know why I'm in a big
I'm taking my time and thinking about it not a day go by
I don't know why I'm in a big I don't know why I'm in a big I don't know why I'm in a big
big I don't know why I'm in a big I don't know why I'm in a big I don't know why I'm in a big I don't know
happy Valentine's Day 2007 mainstream has Bryan Adams we've got cherry swayed
damn it not a day goes by I'm not thinking about you especially for you my love well
my lovely lady Patricia hey everybody it's daily source code 546 it is Valentine's Day and yes
she's here finally for the first time in two months almost well I've been
well no I've been jerking off all day yes no no no in fact no I have not I have not been jerking off all
day okay it's Valentine's Day yeah what no it's a daily source code joke off
hey baby happy Valentine's Day thank you for being my Valentine for 20 years yeah and I'm so sorry
that the doorbell hasn't wrong yet no or we didn't air it no no no no I'm absolutely sure
oh no and then what what do they do with it well they're supposed to deliver something they're supposed
to deliver something for you yeah and what if we don't up a door well I don't know but the child
is downstairs the teenager oh that doesn't mean anything that's true got a lot of a lot of
people calling in for Valentine's Day a lot of messages for me for you messages of love
yeah so how how's the new house how's the new house doing for me yeah how's it doing
for you downstairs there upstairs is fine as you can tell we're all happy here in the
in Adams attic yes getting there a couple more boxes I'm just gonna find a little more time
in between jerk off sessions I find some time to get the final boxes you're almost there
I'm actually very impressed really yeah oh thank you because I thought you're going to stay
here forever between the boxes well I'm still doing pretty good job there are some boxes here
yeah I know it's hard especially when you have to work also yeah it's busy I know so that's why
I was downstairs you know just making the house pretty and what it's strange when you have a
you don't like the noise game it's very strange it makes me feel good I'm glad I don't have a
noise gate in real life on my voice oh we know I was thinking of installing one on you
I used to stop me a user configurable noise game not the whole point is it's actually supposed to
drive you to project more and to talk more into the microphone okay because let's be honest you
have a real issue with and I figured this out you have an issue with talking into the microphone
and I know why because you're used to singing into the microphone and when you talk you like
you pull the mic away is it light? how much says why? yeah yeah because you know nobody wants to hear
me talk yeah oh man you have no idea people love you oh okay people love you here check this out
hey Adam has it going it's Jersey Todd a happy Valentine's Day listen I'm not calling in today
is a podcast host trying to plug my own show not even calling in today is a fan of the source code
no no no today I'm calling in as your loveologist hey ladies how you doing you have any good time
yeah me too ladies I'm here today to give you just a little advice is your man not satisfying
you the way you're used to is you looking all time all run down it's not the man that you used to
be in your first matter hush baby hush Jersey Todd's here for you baby what you need to do is just
slip your man some folders coffee and some splendor and tell him to wake his lazy ass up all right
oh and Adam hey I'm not having anything with the animation you know how it is the ladies just love
music college talk you know as Jersey is a lawyer in real life yeah I would like to have
a lawyer like that apparently he's available all all the ladies love yeah well he's got it
now he's got a kid well he's available he's got a kid he's available he's got a wife he's got a kid
but he's available now he's funny though days he's a I guess oh man are available
what is that supposed to mean I disagree with you well why are you saying that then he's available
he's got a kid he's got a wife but why did you ask why did you ask it you said oh I would
like a lawyer like that well because I have experience with lawyers with bit voices very bad voices
I once had one bad voices and big bills yeah I once had one and it was a very
important day that day because it was with my records company and I did actually
I never met him was I in your life when this took place no and that was the day that I saw
my lawyer for the first time and it was in court so I sat down and the guy starts to talk
and he was not very basic okay for get about it yeah we really like that and I thought okay
we're gonna lose this really yeah with that attitude you will yeah and we did oh no
voices are I think it's so important sorry and a nice talking voice does mean it doesn't always
need to be beautiful but there is a certain timbre or something that's in the voice oh yeah
that is well look at Barry White I heard that a couple years ago how important Barry White
was for a lot of lovers what are we gonna do I mean it's very bad it's very white just
live on or do it does a new Barry White stand up or people still use his his material of course
and he's and lots of kids I'm you know were are you said it made what during his
lots of kids were made I bet I bet I bet more kids wound up on the sheets
and a toilet paper then wound up being made during Barry White babies were made
and his beautiful music yeah so name voices are beautiful and when I speak it's not the voice
that I want here yeah it's fantastic man yeah my sister willow who lives in Italy
send something yesterday I'm just gonna find it to all of the all the women in the family
and and I saw you laughing about this as you were huddled over your email of course
I immediately forwarded a copy to my own email yeah it is the house keeping monthly
May 13th 1955 so only say it again 50 955 that's so that's where you were seven years old
so you were alive and it is the good wife's guide when these were the rules when I was alive
these were the rules see now that's why I am such a perfect well let me let me just read a
couple of these things actually willow underlined a couple of her favorites it's all these things
you should be doing went how to be a good wife here's one over the cooler months of the year
you should prepare and light a fire for him to unwind by your husband will feel he has
reached a haven of rest and order and it will give you a lift too after all catering for his comfort
will provide you with immense personal satisfaction yeah yeah and this is all they mean you know
when the man comes home absolutely well it's like it's not yeah when he comes home
is it all about when he comes home when he comes home and he had a very busy day this is what
you should do clear away the clutter make one last trip through the main part of the house just
before your husband arrives yeah gather up school books toys paper et cetera and run a dust cloth
over the tables do you do any of the shit huh yes I do it prepared the children for pair
the children with a little bit of herbs and time going to the room that's the only thing
that's take a few minutes to wash the children's hands and faces if they're small come
their hair and if necessary change their clothes they are little treasures and he would like to see
them playing the part minimize all noise at the time of his arrival eliminate all noise of the
washer dryer or vacuum try to encourage the children to be quiet as my favorite listen to him
listen to him you may have it doesn't important things to tell him but the moment of his arrival is
not the time now let him talk first remember his topics of conversation are more important than yours
oh he did the other way around really was it really like that yeah was it were your parents
yeah it was all about my my my dad he was the most important man or person in the house
but is this really bad I mean because of course everyone's laughing about this but
and I just say if if it were I think when someone is coming home from work from from a day of
work some of these things are okay I do the same for you I mean it's not like you know it's not like
it's a it's exclusively exclusive or anything yeah you know in the beginning it says be gay
oh really oh that's a very good idea yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah get yourself get another woman in the house
be waiting have have the kids playing their part yeah be a little gay and a little more interesting
for him exact his boring day may need a lift and one of your duties is to provide it that's right
by being a little bit gay pun so print this out for you would you like this yeah a hard
copy version of this isn't this funny this is so good but don't you remember those American
sitcoms father knows best yeah well and then you had mother knows best a little bit later
but father knows best it was all about dad yeah you know but these are in the days when you
it's a little white picket fence and dad wear hat and beep beep beep yeah I'm coming over work
and dad got the biggest stake you got the biggest stake you know you got the stake and you didn't
get anything don't ask him questions about his actions or question his judgment or integrity
remember he is the master of the house and as such will always exercise his will with fairness
and truthfulness you have no right to question him fuck man that's awesome well you know
it was a women's magazine but how boring is this for the man I don't know that gay part kind of
got me yeah going for a second there you know it must have been so boring there's women were so
boring I don't think so I think that you know that's that's really when when everything started
because you think those women were really just sitting at home and they weren't doing Tommy
the mailman you don't think so definitely oh yeah this is this is like a step for wives man
step for wife shit and the postman rang twice yeah he always rings twice yeah yeah you know you
get these sort of situations of course what a fantastic article exploding from horniness
oh look who's here
hello I'm Roger here did you get my car I want to let you know I made it all myself and
all the hands on the mind right for now Roger I did you see it coming yet I haven't seen it yet
no that's disgusting I have no idea what he did oh man oh my god I hope it's not pure
well it's Roger so you never know what he's going to do I haven't heard you know you don't
hear from the guy for like fucking weeks and all of a sudden he he pops in a message like
sort of some Valentine card with pubic hair there was post receipts yeah no I haven't had
actually none so let me just do a little check here so we're in the new new house which we're
calling the curry manner yeah I know you don't listen to the show but that's not official it's the
curry manner which I think fits it fits as a manner doesn't it yeah it isn't that it's a wide enough
it's wide enough yeah what are all the viewers point of you yeah are you sleeping well
I think I faced the right direction the right direction with my nose yes what the hell
is that well sometimes you you feel that you're you're in the wrong position the wrong you know
the wrong way you should lay a little bit different but it felt right right you have good
bench we yeah it's very important to me but the biggest thing is you were bothered by the mobile
antenna the cell phone mask near the near the cottage so and and you were convinced that it
gave you back pain yeah more pain and and arthritis pain actually so well I think you think it's
a bit better yeah that doesn't happen well you know it's only couple of weeks that we are here
okay all right yeah I think I'm gonna and you know it's it is a beautiful neighbor
yeah sure we took some walks and it's amazing yes it's so green and all the the forest across the
street I mean it's where do you find that the forest and the paparazzi's across the street oh yeah
yeah they found us yeah that was pretty fun yeah yeah we don't know how here's how here's how
this works so you know so some pictures show up in a magazine the phone rings it's always your parents
usually your mom or your sister that's what I hear on the phone right and the first question you
say is how are the pictures yeah are the pictures any good how do I look how does the house look
is it nice is it look yeah yeah yeah we haven't seen it yeah yeah yeah because that's the way I
read these yeah of course you don't you look at the headline and then you look at the pictures
yeah absolutely and then next next one yeah I don't care yeah but I think they follow to Christina
probably followed it from home from school again yeah because of this time we know who the photographer
was he's actually a nice guy yeah so I don't care so actually the photographer did a very good job
did a good job yeah and the one thing we haven't well we haven't talked at all
is we have instead of a conventional oven and and stove in the kitchen we have an aga
oh man and we were a little worried I was very worried actually because this aga is like a huge
enamel thing that has four ovens and two hot plates and it's continuously on and and people say
you know oh once you've cooked on an aga you don't want to cook on anything else ever again
I didn't even know what to do with it I know and I was like oh course you're going to be freaking out
this is not going to work if you're not going to understand this was there in the kitchen has a big
monster it is certain of a monster it's real English and real cozy because you know yeah you
you sit next to this yeah big red monster so I got to tell you the shit you're making on it is
amazing it is it's almost like everything tastes differently it is so good there's something about
the way it heats everything I don't know it tastes better it just tastes better then more even I think
and it's beautiful the ovens are always on so you just pop it in the oven right away and it's always
the right temperature I don't know how the oven does how does he know that you know I don't know
I don't know it's always even right temperature and it looks golden brown it's beautiful you
have a cake oven underneath you have the meat and all the the poultry is the one above that
then you have the plate warmer you have the I don't know food keep warmer every single time you
take something out of that aga I'm like wow and we just thought heat is heat right yeah oven is oven
fire is flame is flame yeah who gives you shit and it's just and it's not true it really there's
something very different about it and simmering on it it's beautiful and it doesn't smell no it does smell
there they go they're just sitting in there and so the only thing you smell is when you take it out you
think hmm what am I baking here it's amazing it's amazing and in fact let me just see
that is something that I'm sure chef Mark will come and you have I told you about chef Mark
you told me yeah he sent in something for Valentine's Day as well
hey Adam it's chef Mark here from the remarkable pallet podcast you know our culinary podcast
network shows are also sponsored by Folger's gourmet selections on this Valentine's Day why not
enjoy your favorite sumptuous chocolates paired with Folger's gourmet selections chocolate truffle flavor
it's creamy and smooth with an irresistible chocolate flavor in fact I paired it with some of our
friend John Louis Gahan's new spiced truffles for some clients the other night and they confessed
that it was the perfect ending to their romantic pre Valentine's dinner so if you'd like a free sample
of Folger's gourmet selections coffee while supplies last you can visit www.fulger's.com slash
pocho and you can also check out some of the recipes we featured using Folger's flavors
in the recipe section at www.gildedforic.com catch you later next time we're in New York
that's a great song I don't know who that is that's awesome next time we're in New York
why don't we have chef Mark cook us up a sexy dinner yeah yeah you'd like chef Mark he's cute
he sounds nice yeah he's very cute nice guy and I haven't tasted his cooking yet
no I haven't tasted it yeah yeah that's what I thought you're looking at like what
oh hey hey I haven't tasted no not yet no all right so what else is going on in your
well um you're on important life according to how's keeping monthlist you you may now speak
no do you know yeah I've told you that right that um because my parents were married in
probably no not not 55 when when did they get married I was born in I was born in 64 so they
got married around 62 or 63 there were a little bit too old to be hippies yeah but on the honeymoon
you you dad said you may speak no it was almost like that and my mom didn't tell me this until
a couple of years ago and it was really outrageous on the honey when they went to some golf resort
and so after the the wedding night which I'm trying to say I probably said to my mom how
was that and she probably said oh he passed out you know whatever okay he got up in the morning
he said okay I'm going to go off and play 18 holes of golf and he tossed newsweek magazine out
and he said underline anything you don't understand and I'll explain it to you when I get back
oh my god you believe that well they you know what you know what the future is going to bring
that's like the first day of wedding bliss that was a warning it's not amazing but and
but maybe it was just something from that time it was only a couple of years after this house
keeping monthly maybe that's just the way American marriages work back a day but in these days the
sixties we were actually quite liberating yeah yeah but you hold on a second I just got to
say goodbye to the serious stars one or two listeners you guys want to hear the rest of this
and thrall in conversation uh the sex part is uh later in the show yeah okay they're going
yeah so but you were younger you were 10 years younger they you know they were like getting married
and career and doing all kinds of stuff and you were you know you're younger you're 10 years younger
my dad and that's when we stopped wearing our bras and everything so I don't know where your mom was
doing but um my mom if she were here rest her soul she would say what bra you know that's what she
say yeah that's right yeah but I mean you know in the you know it's just saying actually but
yeah we did that's when the when the women just started to do whatever they wanted to do
so maybe that was the breaking point maybe maybe the old fashion I think my parents were probably
still in the old fashion side of the generation gap maybe that's still was going on but that's unbelievable
to me it really is unbelievable yeah because we had our our skirts real short you know and that's
when the power came yeah it's not amazing yeah we noticed that right away yeah like hey if you
show the boobies then men become stupid you take the bra yeah then you know short skirts and you
booties and you what booties yeah oh like a Nancy Sinatra type thing short short skirt booties
booties and boobies and I walk right all over you yeah booties and boobies I think it's a booties
and boobies it's a winning combination booties and boobies get yours now yeah I heard about
that story from your mom and I think it's just amazing that after that she thought oh I got a great
man that's a fantastic item that's John and Ali from Swingercast are you know the Swingercast
no do you know what Swingers are yeah okay it's fun and intimate conversations about real
swinging experiences you know on a recent show Adam you play to comment from a caller who was
asking you a very important question about how many subscribers listeners does it take to have
a successful podcast and you answered one well Ali and I think the answer is two while there are
a lot of fun and exciting things you can do with one listener it is much more rewarding to share your
podcast with two can you imagine the possibilities with even more Adam Ali and I believe it's
very important to engage your audience and have them participate you don't have to fully swap
ideas with them but it's important to create an exchange and intercourse with your listeners
a couple may want to participate on a podcast or they might just want to sit back and watch or listen
the important thing is to just get it up and put it out there so keep it up Adam and I think you're
right reality is pornographic oh boy I think that was an invitation yeah it looks she sent you
a naked picture hold on hello hello yeah that's a nice nice ripples uh huh well nipple we only
see one yeah but it is it really her well I think we need more pictures to determine this
I don't know if it's really you then take another naked picture with today's newspaper
can you imagine you you you swapping with somebody else you saw us no no no well he made
he may be very cute I don't know yeah but you know I can imagine because I'm very satisfied you know
with my husband I'm sorry what'd you say I didn't hear you I'm pretty satisfied
pretty no what happened to very what happened to very satisfied okay I'm very satisfied I can
imagine if I if I there would swing with another you know we then other couple I can imagine
saying sorry can I have mine bad excuse me I like mine better just like a lullipop you know
yeah yeah yeah I don't like the right like my right one mine better yeah mine was better yeah
but they said we could just watch oh man you're not up for anything you need to be gay when I
come home you need to be a little bit gay yeah that's because I've been at all you but that's
so unfair I you have 60 70 I know we wouldn't get to do this I wasn't I couldn't I didn't have
a dick when I in the 60s in the 70s I didn't know how to use it I didn't know if it worked and
in the 80s it was like you know we had 80s yeah you missed it we had 80s it was like you know that was
it no free love we went from one to another I mean doesn't matter you didn't even know it was in the bed
yeah yeah well you're like this um I this was a story on Reuters lore
kitchens what lore kitchens oh I think Laura is maybe from some Scandinavian place sent me this
link uh nearly one in three Britons think that if a woman jumps up and down washes or urinate
immediately after sex she can prevent pregnancy what yeah it's a survey uh string of revelations
in the survey carried out by the family planning association at the start of contraceptive awareness
week in the UK they reveal widespread confusion and misunderstanding about some of the basic facts
which is called and the FPS now called from proof sex and relationship education in schools
isn't that amazing that's amazing the survey showed that half the 500 people question did not
know that a woman's most fertile time is between 10 and 16 days before her period I should I didn't know
that um half of the 500 people so half of the people who took the survey did not know that a
woman's most fertile time so when you're most likely to get pregnant it's between 10 and 16
days before her next period I didn't know that well but the basically like so you're most
fertile in the middle yeah in the middle of it in the middle of that that really period that you
when you're not so gay yeah two weeks two weeks yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
once or 30 30% think if the woman jumps up and down washes or urinate immediately after sex
you prevent pregnancy well have you seen all the strollers and a teenager really she washed
she urinated yeah yeah she jumps up and down quite a bit god is not amazing yeah they need some
education here i really appears that it really appears that way doesn't it it's uh i'm amazed by
that statistic see and and then i'm very proud if i hear that Holland is very good at it
the teenagers in Holland know exactly is that true is that based on scientific evidence yes yes
even um little closer than like baby um i heard the Americans did the whole research and said
that the Dutch really teenagers and people were just better educated really yeah well i'm
I have to say in Holland it's like you know the human body is just another part of life and there's
you know you take off your top on the beach and uh no problem you could you could be mowing the
lawn and take off your top and and no one would really care well i mean yeah it depends on what you
look good yeah i mean it's it's not a big deal you're not gonna get shunned or rested and
there much more in touch with that i have to say that is that is true yeah i'm proud to say that
yeah yeah and i thank god i had uh european slash Dutch upbringing but i remember man we arrived in
in 1972 that was before i had penis and i'd remember the chef on ukel show yeah it was on
it's seven o'clock in the evening when television basically started because tv would start at seven
with the five will just grown and then at seven oh five he would come on once a week i appeared
in that show yeah naked chicks walking around studio was not me but no it was a good look in naked
chicks oh yeah we like and i can i i i was like we're sitting like holy crap look at this yeah
my parents were freaking out what is this my mom like what kind of country is it yeah and we're
very very conservative i know i must have been just what maybe that's why i'm such a satisfying
lover now later in life it's all those repressed you don't think so yeah i think you're very very
laid back and there's no laid back yeah you're very laid back and these sort of things you don't
make a problem out of it you know it's not possible it's not possible you're not supposed
you're not supposed well if there's you know if you're very busy in your busy with your work
don't you mean i don't care about it then sometimes you don't care about it i can go for months
without it you care you really care yeah oh yeah
hi item prolific programmer here i'm going to try something new here
previously i've called in my what's Christina calling no i thought Christina
probably yeah i heard something too Christina did you call us okay
not saying sorry back to prolific programmer yeah my my messages and decided tonight to record one
so let me know if this is easy to understand um i went to waste Patricia a happy Valentine's Day
and you and the rest of your family also let her know that we like her on the show and um also
went to the the bit on ui that i was talking about in the previous episode was regarding your request
to have the meal stored on a street or my proposal to put your Gmail on a street um let me
know again through the either the podcast or a comment on my blog or email here's
cheers that's the prolific programmer okay he's uh new friend of the show and i'm working on
i'm trying to get him to um communicate in a way that we can actually understand him yeah
we're getting there well you don't know what's going on of course what do you mean the guys
are fucking genius i know exactly what's going on the guide lives with his head and his keyboard
all day oh that's why yeah i'm absolutely he's he's writing up code and doing all kinds of amazing
things but i think he's one of your biggest fans oh yeah as you could hear yeah
a prolific programmer excellent man all right so what else baby i'm going to a San Francisco on
Sunday yeah i'm gonna go away from you don't say that because all the man will come to i didn't say
which Sunday don't say um all the men will come to it what are you going to do in all the
men show up here at your door sign in my way uh really all of them all of them um i guess
well check them out first yeah a little little scan um i have a new camera for it oh yeah i posted that
on the on the web long it is uh it smells a little bit dim well it's a convertible
it smells tempi maybe somebody has i think it's been in the garage and i do what i have to do
it's it's a bit um uh it smells like a camping site yeah yeah and and wet tent
it is basically it's wet tent it has a tent cover it has a tent cover it was it rained this morning
this is why i don't like convertibles because the roof always gives you problems well it is not
wet on the inside but if you if you feel it on the inside it is wet you know what i mean
it's not wet on my chair it doesn't drip or anything do you want me to fix the garage so you can
put it in the garage would you rather have that because it is kind of a shame yeah but it is kind
of a shame to keep this thing outside i mean i know it's easy and everything but you know the roof
like that it will should have a car port a car port yeah i got to build a car port
you have you ever build a car port that's one that's hence my surprise yeah i didn't say you
have to build no i don't think that's possible but it should have a little thing over it yeah
well you could basically just throw up a shot but actually it dries really fast at the moment
the sun shines or you know the wind blows it's dry but i wonder if if i just can spray it a little
bit so that it's not oh with some kind of water proof stuff they're probably probably want you
to go by the the dealer asking because it you do smell it in the inside like a wet wet dog wet dog
wet dog it's just thing i say wet dog you say wet cat yeah all right darling so i'm i'm a cross
now you say that i'm racing through the neighborhood uh yeah you would call that crossing
you're mode of mode of crossing your way around yeah absolutely it's fantastic yeah it's nice
the turbo is good isn't it's great and when i hear you drive away i can hear but also you know
the thing is that you think you're driving your best you are because i drove behind you well yeah
I drove behind you it accelerates very because the hard ways nothing it's a thinking toy
i was gone before you know and it's like it has like three cylinders and 85 horsepower something
nothing it's like a lawnmower engine but because you don't weigh anything barbie turbo it's a barbie turbo
absolutely yeah it's not pink but it's a barbie turbo and i have to say uh guys i'm looking
now of course they're looking at you yep yeah i noticed that you look fucking sunglasses
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh hey what is that hey hey hey hey hey what the fuck is that and does that
actually work the guys ever get laid by doing this what i thought yeah i mean they wouldn't be
doing if they didn't think it worked i've noticed that a couple of times and i thought why you're
doing that so they do that they they turn up the radio yeah yeah and then you know and then they
they drive by and they look at you like it's new school we should come up with something for women to say
you know it's like so um so maybe if a guy pulls up next you at the stop light and he's going
you know and trying to get your attention maybe you roll down the window yeah but maybe it's a
certain woman that that they want to attract i don't know well but doesn't it attract me
and i'm a music lover well i'd like to know is there any woman out there there's actually
turned on by a guy doing that yeah and it doesn't matter and turning down the window even
well no so i think what you should do if that happens is you should roll down your window
wait for him to roll down his window and turn off the sound and say hey asshole
something like that or maybe like hey when your dick is as big as your sound system once you
give me a call yeah and then peel out oh very nice believe me well what else are you going to
do yeah all you had was hey asshole yeah that's classy all right women if you're actually turned on
by that let me know uh that's very interesting to me and doesn't matter what kind of car he has
is it kind of like saying he because we all know cars or penis extenders now i was thinking actually
Robyn Redford he was sitting in his beautiful open rolls rolls you know when he was still
good looking was actually a couple of years ago that was like 20 years ago and he was still good looking
that he was telling the story and he said uh somebody said did they recognize you and you drive
you in uh in LA and he was rodeo drive he was driving was beautiful with a turtle top down
he was driving people was smiling at him and a couple of guys and girls you know drove
next to him at the top of the line and they said hey Robin Redford and that he thought of us
yeah young guys recognize me so he waved and smiled friendly and they said asshole
I'm going to play one more song for you baby before we shut down the show for today
Laura Lambert
This is true
So much got me getting out to you
Hell's not letting you
And once in no while I stay
I'm now who I am feeling this way
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah my wrong to love you
And I wrong for feeling the way
And I wrong for love for you
And all your men
And here's your wilder feeling
And all my men
And all your men
And everything that we're in
And what you need
I'm watching you while I'm staying
And I'm feeling this way
And hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Am I wrong to love you?
Am I wrong for feeling what I do?
And now, that's what it is.
Come on black girls.
Do it again.
Am I wrong for love in you?
What the hell was that?
Like set of their life.
What I do!
Yeah, I'm a good girl.
Am I wrong for loving you?
Am I wrong for loving you, baby?
No.
I don't want to be wrong.
I don't want to be right.
As right.
Because it feels so right.
Everyone's how puking.
I feel listening to this.
Yeah.
We really mean it.
I'm sorry.
I hate to say it, but I do.
I really do.
Yeah, it's still there to spark.
Definitely.
And tonight, I'll show you that the spark can make a flame.
God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, don't let Christina hear this.
She's over like, oh, woo.
Well, she's going out for Valentine's Day with a boy's friend in London.
What are you wearing?
I said, red underwear.
Oh.
Hey.
Yeah.
Kids don't understand.
Putting on my red G string.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
My string.
Yeah.
Show me.
Wait a minute.
Oh, okay.
There.
What's that?
Oh, yes.
There it is.
Very nice.
Mm-hmm.
And you have panties on too.
No.
Pandy house.
I was going to say it.
Look like it.
How was that?
Show me.
Open that up again.
No.
There was my toy because it's so dark.
Oh.
Shit, man.
Yeah.
You've got a nice color.
I have a very nice color.
Especially for Valentine.
Oh, yeah.
Nice color.
Okay.
So, um, yeah.
So, I'm going to have to tell San Francisco.
I can't, uh, I can't participate in all the daily meetings.
Because, uh, I've got to, uh, I've got a, I've got a duty.
A big duty.
Yeah.
I can't be up until 11 30 at night doing, uh, need to shit.
And then I gave you a very nice card.
Yes, you did.
It said, let's, let's get dirty tonight.
Let's get bad.
Let's get bad if I said dirty.
Bad.
Uh, I thought dirty.
Let's get bad.
I know you had little devil horns.
Yeah.
With a box of after eight chocolates.
And after.
So, let's get bad after eight.
That's what it was.
It was the mess.
I, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, baby.
Um, right.
Will you come on again soon?
Probably not until I get back from San Francisco.
Because, you know, it's, because tomorrow I'm going to London Friday.
It's going to be fucking hell.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
But Friday, I can come with you too.
I'm sorry.
You can come.
I have to go to the dentist again.
Yes.
It's the never ending story.
I know.
You've got a car in the driveway and a Ferrari in your mouth.
Yes.
Absolutely.
I can actually, uh, it's a nice car part and a nice car part.
Car part.
It can drive my barbeque to my mouth.
All right.
I think no one needs to know anything else about your mouth.
Cool.
Thanks for coming on the show, huh?
Yeah.
Just mouthing is big enough for the both of us.
You do do do do do.
All right.
I love you, baby.
I love you too.
Another partial podcast.
Stick it in your ear.