You're Tony, what are you doing?
Well, you're listening to the DSC 537.
Why you pushing that button, Tony?
Well, you'll Adam always plays a commercial and then he plays a goofy intro and then he
plays some music, so I'm fast forward and to I can get to Adam talk it.
You know, Tony, you can't fast forward to hear Adam talk and you're missing a good
ad.
There might be something in there you can use.
There might be an offer that you can use, like GoDaddy, you can host your own website.
Yeah, I was going to look and see if Tony puts you really dot com as available, maybe
I'll go to GoDaddy and register that one.
And besides, Tony, if you skip the goofy intro for DSC 537, you'd miss us.
Oh, I didn't think about that way.
Man, this whole time shift and things has got me crazy, I don't understand it.
So, Tony, no more fast forwarding to begin another show, Capiche?
Capiche.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Made out of town in a small cafe, she had the motion of the ocean out her hips this
way, she had everybody looking back and everybody took him back and anything, she wanted
all the guys on the day now.
She won.
I'm fine, folks, we'll keep losing her.
She's not.
Tough Tony, cuz she knows she got it and she got it and she got it and she got it.
Comments and tights and can't expect to make a man, but where we still I get everything
is okay, she got it and she got it and she got it and she got it and she got it and she got
and she got it and she got it and she got it and she got it and she got it and she got
he goes you down but when you meet up her.
She'll keep it and she reflects that she Porsche look and she got everything
And I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again
again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I will take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll take all this again, and I'll take all over again, and I'll
She got tricks and she got some treats, she's taking the ground on the meat, you knock it off your feet
She did everything about her for my head, I don't know if I'll make rules or melodies and sounds of music when she speaks now
She's done, consistent with the energy, and she put them in the wings when it's time to play
She's like a fun, it's not for wanting just a whiff or a mental makin' needs, get me sick
Wow!
You can find them feature today at the PodSafe Music Network, I don't know if they're at least the
That's on the UK version of PodSho.com, BT PodSho.com
Black Alicious Powers!
It's interesting!
I'm always cruising around the network seeing what we're promoting and wondering sometimes why we're promoting things
Wow!
The craft!
And I'm looking at Black Alicious, so I go over to the podcaster side of the PodSafe Music Network
And I see that these two tracks they have up there were uploaded in 2005, I'm like, why are we promoting this guys?
And the only thing I can ask, obviously, the only reason I can come up with is that it's Black History Month, perhaps?
Maybe Black Alicious Powers, Black History Month, something like that, I gotta find out why.
Because I'd much rather be promoting people who are putting up new stuff and are with the program, no I'm saying it's 2007.
Hey everybody!
Welcome to Daily Source Code, Delta Sierra Charity 537.
I will tell you right up front, I'm in a foul mood today.
It all started last night, David the Sky Guy, who turns out to be a fantastic guy.
He's an independent contractor, you know, Sky call.
It's not the guy, by the way, who said he couldn't find my house.
I guess they figured out that was not the right guy to be sending around to me.
Really nice guy.
Very well mannered, you know, new a lot.
I've lived in the States actually in Chicago and in...
What's he live?
Asbury Park, New Jersey.
Asbury Park in the UK, 10 or 11 years, just moved down from Leeds.
He's been in Guilford for about three or four weeks, has his own company.
And he really, really went all out.
And we had three boxes to be installed.
Big holes to be drilled in the walls.
You know, wiring that had to be worked out, you know, nicely and kind of hidden if at all possible.
And that was great.
And even better, I'd have to say, as he said, after we were on the phone with Sky HQ,
getting the cards sorted out, the satellite viewing cards more on that in just a second.
Because that's where my shagrin started.
He's like, hey man, can you mind if I ask you, what are you smoking?
I'm like, well, unfortunately it's like some fucking melted CDs that's being passed off
as what they call solid here in the UK.
I said, I know it.
It's like melted CDs.
I can tell.
It's not doing much.
But besides probably killing me and giving me severe diseases.
He says, oh, man, you know, would you like some home ground?
I'm like, okay, he's my man.
And yeah, so we drank a beer all the way in for a second.
And this is when it all happened.
So I have three cards and because the, you know, I don't want to get all the way into it,
because I'm just going to riled up again.
But because the first installer said he couldn't find my house.
He canceled the job.
My cards got canceled.
All these fucked up things happened.
And so I have three cards of which only one works.
And but here's the thing that really, really, really piss me off.
So they charged me 10 pounds to reactivate one, sending me out a new one for a secondary or
tertiary box because that card was damaged or whatever.
And what they done is they can, like, I'm watching for like 30 minutes.
And then all of a sudden, your card is not authorized.
So I go through the whole thing again.
Every single time they will forward you to someone else.
And you have to explain, you know, hi.
How can I help you?
What's your name?
What's your phone number?
What's your address?
What's your title?
Well, we're talking about fucking title.
Pod father, you asshole?
Oh, Mr. Yeah, Mr. Adam Curry.
That's it.
And, you know, so you go through that a couple times and you have to explain the whole situation again.
And all the notes on the account are now completely fucked up.
So I'm like, okay, you know, look, I have this card.
Here's the card number.
That card doesn't exist.
Well, no, it does because I have it in my hands.
I've had it for two years.
No, that card does not exist.
Where did you get that card?
And that's where I really get angry.
At the, when did you get that card?
Because I know, particularly, you know, the satellite viewing cards.
That's really the satellite television industry's version of DRM.
You know, and there's a huge black market in so-called gold cards.
So you can, you know, and these are just basically jacked in every month or periodically.
The satellite broadcasters will send down some kind of bullet through the line.
It'll blow up the card if you, if you haven't even a quote, illegal card.
So this card is probably now blown up as well.
But, you know, so they, I guess they removed it from their system.
But the accusation, the accusation will tone.
Where did you get this card?
Yeah, I like, you know, maybe speak to a supervisor.
That's where it gets really interesting.
Why?
Because, you know, I can yell at you.
You know, and you probably are just following the script.
And I'm happy to do that.
Or you can give me a supervisor.
And I can really give him a piece of my mind.
And then, you know, you get put on hold for ten minutes.
Well, there's no supervisor available.
Said, go look again.
You know, and then it's like, well, this, this is not warranted for a super, whatever.
You know, whatever.
Just like fuck you.
Fuck you.
Send me the fucking fuck you.
Well, that's what I thought.
I didn't actually say it because I know they can't help it.
But it's just the whole culture of that of sky as a company.
It's a bunch of dickheads.
Okay.
So we have one card that we now have to swap around and move throughout the house.
And I guess they're sending new cards.
The good news is I made a new friend with David this guy, man.
He's a very cool guy.
And what I'm going to have him do is actually help me build the entire media room.
So I'm, I've actually canceled the, the H.D.
Wide screen that I had on order.
Because I want to make sure I get all the right stuff.
And we want to get the game console set up.
The karaoke's got to be, the karaoke's got to be set up.
Everything.
You know, I want to, we, I want the whole, the whole,
the, we by the way with safe guards.
So, you know, my teenage daughter doesn't throw a controller through the screen.
Which is also the second part of why it's so exasperated and a bit in the film.
Move today.
You know, we have this, I got two girls in the house, man.
I got my wife and I have the neighbor.
And that's my daughter.
And then they're closed fit each other.
So there's always something about the clothes and Christina takes clothes without asking.
And then she, you know, she borrows this.
And then, oh, no, I left it at cat's house or just has it.
You know, and I'm just like, I get so, I'm like, dude, you know,
you don't have to do jack shit here.
You don't, you know, you don't have to, you know,
do you have teenagers?
Do you go through this?
It's like you're living here rent free.
You got internet.
You got a satellite television.
Your boyfriend is welcome to come by anytime and have
dinner and by the way, you know,
Patricia will be taking dinner out of the oven and the door
will bill will ring.
I mean, and Andy's a great guy.
You know, he, he works after school every single day for several hours
cleaning office buildings, I think.
So, and it's within like a 20 minute walk from our house.
It's fine.
You know, it's totally cool.
But I want a little bit of respect from the teenager as
really pissing me off.
And, you know, so I'm not quite sure how.
I'm going to deal with it, but just,
sometimes, you know, you love him to death,
but sometimes you just want to stick him up behind the wall
paper.
Adam, Bill from Virginia,
just driving into work,
listen to DSC 535,
and haven't listened to all things into about 12 minutes
and you're commenting on your sound issues,
so I was so forth.
Just as you're working through those problems,
also play attention to the levels between
your voiceover, so on and so forth.
And the voice nails,
the voice nails are much lower level,
you know, turn up your volume,
and then you come back on.
And of course, your ears get a little flowed out.
So, anyhow, if there's anything you can do
to balance that out in process,
that would be appreciated.
Thank you.
Yeah, I've received a couple of those.
I hope this is better now.
I've done some more configuration, some tweaking.
Is it possible?
I don't know how long do the tubes last
on a stereo valve processor?
Why am I hearing now?
Because I think the tubes are going.
And this thing has been almost on 24,
seven, when did I buy it?
Like two years ago, when we first moved here,
so it's almost been on 24, seven.
And I think, because once in a while,
it's like one of the channels,
it sounds like it's crackling,
and then you blow into the microphone,
then it clears up.
If anyone has any ideas on that,
and of course, then I'm going to have to go and have it serviced,
or so I've done a little bit of tweaking.
The big problem is,
there are so many different levels,
and yeah, you can pump it all through a limiter
and a compressor,
but that really starts to mush with the sound.
And since I'm working with Casplaster,
it's really only one channel,
so you can't have like a different channel
for just audio comments or for softer bass content.
So hopefully it's a little bit better now,
than I know,
there's lots of people that your drums are getting blown out,
turning up the audio comments,
so it should be better.
Let me know.
So this is now,
it's official, it's the curry manner.
It's sticking,
although Casey Murl did say,
how about the curry condom,
because it keeps you and your family members protected
from people like Roger Smalls and comic strip blogger.
Oh, yes.
You know, this is a brand new show
that joined the Pot Show podcast network bucket.
And today,
we have not won,
but two comments from the buckets.
And I think that sounds from Jen.
She picks up on a thread
that we've been talking about for a couple days now.
Hi, Adam.
This is Jen from Bucket.
And I was just giving you a comment
to weigh in on this posh people and patties.
And this is right up my alley.
So you know,
I just had to send you a comment.
I believe the question was,
are posh people potty pigs?
Really getting off on all the peas here.
Anyway,
I just wanted to let you know
that I definitely believe that
bad potty behavior is not limited to the rich.
Believe me.
I work in an enormous government building.
And the things that I see every day
would just turn your stomach.
You just wouldn't believe.
You just wouldn't believe that
any in on the seat,
drop in toilet paper on the floor.
All manner of horrible things.
Everything that that person saw in their posh bathroom,
I have seen it in spades in the bourgeois bathroom
that is in my building.
So I do not believe that posh people are potty pigs.
I believe that we all are people
have disgusting bathroom habits.
Anyway,
I talk about this kind of stuff every week
on our show bucket at bucket.ponshow.com.
So I just couldn't resist weighing in
all the time.
Thank you, my dear.
And welcome to the family.
I liked all the peas, by the way.
Our posh people potty pigs.
There you go.
Posh people potty pigs.
You know,
I think we're on to something here
that apparently,
and you know,
you go to anyone's house.
I guarantee the people who are pigs in your posh potty
or not.
They're bathrooms nice and clean.
What is it?
Why do people behave
that way?
It is unimaginable.
And is this something cultural
to the United States?
To the United Kingdom?
How about Asia?
You know,
you may think I'm obsessed with
with bathroom stuff,
but it is kind of interesting
that we do this.
Dan,
It can get really, really bad,
you know?
Hey, Adam Ruster,
from the Bruinsport podcast here.
I was just listening to the DSE536.
In hearing,
I was just listening to some of the situations
he encountered while
ginging out on weekends with his band
and some of the nasty situations he found
and some bathrooms.
Well, unfortunately,
it may be think a little bit too much of a situation
that we've actually been having in the workplace as well.
And,
well,
I better describe it and you can go from there.
And this is kind of relate to the posh
piggies in the potty,
I guess you can call it.
Now,
the building network in is a very nice building,
especially by a lot of businesses that dare,
I would say on the professional level,
my company is a data carrier.
There are other service-related
and new-and-service agencies in our building.
And every single floor has its own public shared bathroom
with all the businesses used together.
Well,
our bathroom on the second floor,
unfortunately,
tends to get visited a lot by
the fans of the shit.
That's right.
The fans of the shit are used
in a dubbed.
Essentially,
somebody who works at one of the companies on our floor
apparently has some problems aiming.
Now,
most men,
sometimes have problems aiming while standing up.
Well,
apparently the fans of the shitter has problems aiming
while sitting down.
On a good day,
he only gets shit on the top part of the toilet seat.
The bottom part.
On a bad day,
it's down the sides of the toilet.
It's on the tank of the toilet.
And if you're really lucky,
you get to walk into the stall where the shit is on the wall.
That's right.
And really bothers me,
and a lot of the guys that I work with,
because we're all professionals.
We're all adults.
We all like to take care of ourselves.
We all like to have this take care of themselves as well.
And to see this nastiness in the bathroom,
at least twice a week,
is disgusting.
And unfortunately,
at least a lot of sideways glances too.
I'm in the bathroom finishing up.
I'm washing my hands and there's another gentleman
from another business down the hall.
Kind of looking at me sideways.
And I feel like I have to defend myself.
Look at me.
I'm washing my hands.
Look at the stall.
I was just in.
It's clean.
I'm not the phantom shitter.
Somebody else is,
but it's not me.
And one of the really disgusting things to think of
is that some gentleman is walking in,
taking a seat,
and just letting it go everywhere.
And when you look at the mess that's left behind,
you have to think to yourself,
if this is the mess he's living in the bathroom,
is he cleaning himself up as well?
Or is he just letting that go too?
It's really tough situation.
The custodians in the building are really trying to figure out
what they can do to try and stop this perpetrator,
the poopy perpetrator, I guess you can call him.
Unfortunately until then,
he's just going to keep on shitting and after he's praying
that I don't have any clients coming for a visit
and using that stall that he knew just vacated
because if they do,
I've got to say,
the shit is really going to hit the fan at that point.
Take care, Adam.
Dude.
You know,
if that was happening in our building,
I would have frickin' stake out going on.
I would have people stake out watching everyone
who comes in and out of the men's room
and checking right after someone leaves.
You better believe it.
You got to bust this guy.
That is just the lowest of the...
It sounds like he's doing a hovering job there
and he's not doing a very good job of it.
But what is it?
What is it?
With the bathroom.
Public toilets.
Why can't we keep them clean?
It just doesn't make sense to me.
I'd love to hear from some Eastern cultures.
Hey, you guys down under in Australia.
At the help desk.
How's your bathroom?
Is it also...
P-pigged up by potty pigs?
It's just unbelievable to me.
Oh, we're on the political correctness tip.
Whitney Hoffman from the LD podcast sent me an email
said,
listening to your comments about the Netherlands reality show
featuring people with physical disabilities.
Both Jen from Bucket and you use the term handicapped several times.
I just want to let you know why the term disabled or disability
is usually preferred.
Oh, so here's the history lesson.
Oh, I should go...
Besides the podcasting, I'm an attorney
and if help businesses and clients with disability access
issues under the Americans with disabilities act
for slightly over eight years.
Okay.
No, I appreciate the fact that you're a lawyer.
Here's interesting.
The term handicapped.
And that's where some controversy about this comes in.
Comes from the fact that people with disabilities
were often seen begging on the street with,
quote,
cap in hand.
Hence handicapped.
Oh, that's interesting.
So there's lots of links about it.
Please don't get into the debate of whether it's an urban legend
or where that came from.
But okay, I will do my best if that's what you want.
No problem.
I wish people would give me the same respect.
Some of the names people have called me.
I've been a little bit worse than handicapped.
I'll tell you that.
But that makes sense.
Absolutely.
I got something really cool for you guys.
You'll find a link to it on
dailysourcecode.com in the show notes.
If you're a Mac user,
you're going to love this little widget.
Hey, Adam.
It's Scott from Top Dead Center
and Weekly Breeze and Corporate Cluster.
Just wanted to drop you a line.
I decided to go ahead and start making
Mac OS 10 dashboard widgets for any podcaster
that wants to have a podcast player
widget of their own for their podcast or
what they can do is put it on their website.
And they can let any of their listeners
download it and install it on their Mac.
And you just drag it in and it automatically
loads up their XML file, their feed.
And you can just press play.
And it plays their most recent podcast
or you can actually click on the drop down menu
and go and listen to any past episodes.
It's pretty cool.
And only cost 10 bucks.
How about that?
Go to top, dead, center, podcast.com.
That's my website.
And click on the button up at the top that says
podcast widget.
That's about it.
Thanks again.
Oh, I'm glad that you thought that the trailer
idea for Trinity was was pretty good.
You know, I'm one of those people that I get
I get one or two good ideas a year.
And well, you got one.
So I'll talk to you later, dude.
By the way, folder.
Yeah, of course.
I expected no less.
Yeah, I got news about the Trinity trailer
hitch coming up.
Of course, an update on free Trinity.
So this widget is very nice to look at.
And it's a very simplistic idea.
I think Dawn and Drew have one as well.
So now you can buy your own for 10 bucks.
And you can hand it out unlimitedly,
which I think is a tremendous deal.
Now, as I was looking at this thing,
I'm thinking to myself, well, this is kind of interesting
because, and by the way, I think that widgets do have a future.
I love confabulator.
And of course, Apple came out with the OSX OS 10 widgets.
And there's a version of widgets for Vista, I think,
and who knows.
I mean, there's all kinds of different widgets.
And developers love creating these things.
Because they deliver one very defined piece of functionality,
and it's fun.
And I don't like the dashboard necessarily on OS 10
because, you know, it basically puts a whole layer over the stuff
that I'm doing.
I want to be able to interact with stuff while it's right there,
and not while all the other widgets have to appear.
So that's neither here nor there, because it does work very well.
I'm thinking, this will be great for channels.
I had, you know, I have an on-the-go channel,
which I listen to, I listen to it on a number of devices,
because it's basically an RSS feed that is dynamically updated,
based upon a number of shows that I'm subscribed to.
So, one if we expose, and the engineers at pod show
are listening to the show, so take notes, guys.
Pull over to the side of the road,
and write this one down, because here's an idea, which I think is going to
really be fun, fun to play with.
If you're listening to serious stars 102, you don't get that fun.
Because my satellite window is closing, you can hear it kind of sliding down
and creaking his p-dubbs about to move on to the next show.
So, I'll talk to you guys tomorrow for Fubar Friday.
So, what if we expose an API, which is essentially an application programming interface,
a way for other programs to talk to the pod show platform,
that enabled you to supply a set of credentials,
so username and password, and then it would populate,
or it would basically send back an OPML file with all of the channels.
And each channel that you've created on pod show plus
is, of course, an RSS feed, so you can select from that.
So, by the way, you know, just talking about this widget,
that's a widget I would really love to have.
So, I could just acquire this widget,
and then say, okay, log me into my pod show account,
boom, it would show me all of my channels,
and then I can just say, okay, I want to listen to this channel,
and I just start to playing that channel.
And that would be a really, really cool widget to have.
So, you've heard it here.
I'm putting in my work order.
I really want to have this API exposed,
because I think a lot of people could do a lot of fun stuff with it.
Let's see.
You know, it's going to be a long show.
I'm going to skip a couple things here, but I cannot skip this.
That's gonna be a big summit.
I can't, man.
You thought the GA was a big deal.
You thought the devote was a big deal,
ah, ah.
I'm sorry.
The 8th of February 2007,
that's going to be the big summit.
I can't mandate it Tuesday.
And on Wednesday, next week there is no airplane from here, so I can only say today, Friday or Saturday next week.
If Thursday, 7th February is fine with you, then please let me know SAP and I will come,
but be 100% sure that you can.
Regarding video, of course surely you can do it and bring some gas.
I think he meant the 8th Thursday is the 8th, so 2 o'clock Thursday the 8th February, 2007.
Comикster Blogger and I are going to meet up, he is going to interview me.
I'm allowed to bring a long video camera, he wants me to bring along some girls.
Dude, I don't know what to say to that.
So this will be a very historic meeting, and I have to say anticipation is building him.
I'm getting quite excited about it.
I've been playing more and more with that Nokia and 800 that I was given.
And I got to tell you, I'm really, which says I'm getting motivated to do some stuff.
I installed the X-term application and low on behold, you start this up and then you've got a command line.
You've got a Linux command line and you've got a shell.
And I'm quite familiar with the Unix shell and I've done lots of shell scripting in my time.
And some of it, if I want to test a network, I'm always open up a terminal window.
I want to ping something, I want to trace route, but also I like using WGAT and stuff like that.
There's a lot of things you can do, it's very, very functional, not a great, not a great fantastic graphical user interface.
But that's why I like Gmail.
I like using keyboard commands, I think the mouse is in many cases a waste of time.
And I'm thinking about, you know, I saw that there was Python is available for the device.
I'm thinking, well, why wouldn't I install Python?
And of course, it's a real, real geeky thing to do.
But if I installed Python, then I could easily install a Python version of, I think there's still an iPodder or maybe there's a juice version.
But I know there's a Python pod catcher somewhere.
And because this little box is so good, it's finding open Wi-Fi networks.
And I know this because there is a little feed reader that's built into it.
And the thing's always updated, you know, it updates every 30 minutes and whether it's connecting through an open,
an open Wi-Fi access point or through Bluetooth to the GSM that's in my pocket, it's always updated.
And I think this would be pretty much the iPod I want to have.
You know, and by the way, it has a great phone jack and a speaker, a earphone jack and a speakers,
you know, the player is reasonably advanced.
Wouldn't it be fantastic to just be walking around and whenever something new pops up,
if it has a network available or to wait until the network is there, it's going to start downloading.
And you basically just have your stuff all the time.
I really think that this will be one of the first.
And there was the arcos, the arcos, arcos, arcos, arcos, whatever it was.
I don't know what the problem is with that because I thought that was also Linux based and it's no one's developing.
But this thing has a battery life, it's just not to be believed.
I mean, I use it the whole day long until basically until I go to bed at night,
I haven't taken my laptop downstairs once since we've been here, just been using the tablet because now that I've got it figured out,
you can use full Gmail, it can do everything except really any type of office documents,
which we don't use a lot of at Podge, I think we use a lot of Google docs.
And by the way, that doesn't work in the opera browser on Linux, unfortunately.
But you can always view something as HTML in Google Mail just to get the idea.
But I'm really excited about it.
If I had a little bit more time, I guarantee you I'd be working on this.
And also, it's got VNC, servers, and viewers, and one of these days when I have some time, I'll really get it into it.
I add them, it's you from Ferrox, glad to hear you're back in the UK and everything's okay.
Starting here outside the hangar, looking at the dust Sierra, looking very sad.
It's a beautiful sunny day today, and she's inside and all the lucky airplanes are outside.
Difficult to look at on me at the end of the hangar.
If you come down this way to fly, you've got the sincere going and things,
and you've got to come and have a look at this waiter.
There's now part just near your aircraft.
It is gorgeous.
What is it, a waiter, is that what he said?
I can't wait to, you know, Captain Dan called yesterday, I haven't spoken to him.
But I think I just need to go flying this weekend.
You know, usually I'm a guy that won't go flying unless I actually have to go somewhere,
or I've planned to go somewhere.
I don't really just fly around and do stuff.
But it's been, what, six weeks at least.
Maybe even longer since I've flown with that bad weather.
I've been away.
You just heard from you, the plane is really sad.
Yeah, and he's got senseo.
Although I heard some rumblings in the sales weasels office,
that someone else is going to come in and take advantage of the hype of senseo
and completely replace it with a different brand stay tuned.
About the Trinity thing, I used to have one of those.
And there's a tow hitch built in, really neat underneath.
They used to be, and you kind of, the tow ball is separate.
It's like a really, really beautifully made bracket.
Usually comes in a bag and it's in the accessories.
And you kind of click it in, but it's not obvious.
Oh, that's what that rattling is in the bag.
I've always, I thought it was tools.
Now I know, it's the tow hitch.
You know, I do recall having seen on Trinity's ass.
Some kind of attachment thingy.
It's kind of very vague.
But now that you say that, I think that you're right.
She may have a built in tow bar.
Now I just have to see if the actual bar.
You know, I rosey.
Rosie, now that you're fixing Trinity up,
and you're going to keep her running until we send her off on her on her trip.
Would you please take a look and call into the voicemail line?
Let me know if this is indeed true.
There was any kind of tow facility.
If you just look at the back of the car,
but it's quite often, I wouldn't be surprised
it wasn't a standard feature on Mercedes like that.
Also on the sky thing,
two, I've had terrible problems with sky,
with the sky plus boxes,
with unreliability of new ones made by Amstrad.
They're horrible.
And we've had two of them now.
And I have, I'm having to wait three weeks
for somebody to come and just change my box.
Anyway, let's see you at Fairhead soon.
I look off myself, bye.
Nice touch there, Hugh,
with the plane starting up in the back.
Thank you very much.
Since we've started the conversation,
we might as well get the theme song roll.
Because we're sending her across the USA and beyond.
It's time to free Trinity.
I feel her up there and watch her go.
Letting everybody know that this is going to be the better way.
And two, three, Trinity.
Trinity.
The quintessential luxury.
Let the bio diesel set your free.
Trinity.
Well, of course the email box has been filling up
the Google Groups.
The free Trinity.
Google Group has already gotten like 20 or 30 members.
So that's starting to fill up nice and quick.
Let's see.
I'm getting emails now.
We have a regional biodiesel.
Information link has been posted.
People are trying to figure out how to get Trinity over to Blighty.
And you know, there's always people who keep saying the same thing.
Which you really don't have to do is,
you know, why not enter Trinity in the Gumball run?
Which, of course, is a, you know, this is the, this has been kind of a trend.
Amongst posers for the past couple of years.
You see it all over the place.
You know, they get their Ferraris and they're souped up cars.
And then they drive through perhaps a piece of Eastern Europe or they drive across the US.
And they're all basically trying to replicate the fun of the movie Cannonball run.
But you know, it's like, come on.
Man, that was 70s.
We can't all be burnt Reynolds, you know.
It's like, no, no, no.
This is something completely different.
We want to show the world that you can drive anywhere you want to in any country, any continent, relying purely on biodiesel,
which is produced by the people, not by big oil.
What did I just see?
Shell announced they, uh, made $25 billion in profit in 2006.
And it was kind of a bad year.
Now, I don't want you to get angry at the man because the reason they have so much profit is, of course,
because the prices are reasonably high, but they need that profit for the next 50 years of obtaining oil from other earth.
You know, the refinery is going to be much more difficult.
The way they drill is going to be much deeper.
They're using new tactics like gas to liquid and filling up drilling holes with water to push the oil up.
I mean, you know, and these things, a project like that is like a billion dollars for one project easy.
So they need that money and they will be reinvesting it.
But, you know, it's basically the end isn't site.
We got to do something different. We got to change all this.
So that's why we want a free trinity.
Sender on her way and have her driven by podcasters enthusiast alike and stopping off at biodiesel, uh,
filling stations, uh, stopping off at podcasters homes, uh,
stopping off at, uh, places where we can get vegetable oil to create biodiesel.
And that's the whole idea behind the trailer hitch is to actually have a biodiesel processing unit towed behind
or so people can really get into it and see how easy it is.
Hey Adam, this is Adam calling from Toledo, Ohio.
Um, thinking about your free trinity moment.
If you decide to throw a trailer hitch on the trinity.
So you can tow it around your own, uh, biodiesel refinery.
Consider, um, consider stopping at mom, pop type restaurants and set a big change.
You know, kind of support the whole independent media independent from foreign oil independent from big
chains, you know, the whole American type thing.
Just like you said.
Thank you.
Bye.
Right arm.
I think that's a very good idea.
That will even accentuate it more.
And you know, we want people tracking trinity and driving along with her and their biodiesel
the powered vehicles, you know, let's really create something new and fresh.
Like an old fashion like Bird Reynolds movie.
Hey Adam, this is Josh and Nebraska.
And I just wanted to share some information for the free trinity.
Um, I'm a computer consultant and I have a customer that uses a GPS system.
Um, to track his entire fleet as they're traveling across the country.
And basically what this does is it, um, it gives him the ability to log into a website and see exactly where
his fleet is.
And any point in time he can log in and see one particular truck where it's at on a map.
And then it shows how fast they're going and what direction and all that good kind of stuff
too.
And also has the ability to text message that driver.
So if they had any changes and load pickups or anything like that, that's what they use
that for.
But the idea would be that, uh, any of us listeners could actually log in to a website or you could
add it to a website and see exactly where trinity was at any point in time how fast she was
going and all that neat stuff.
So I love the show.
Thanks for putting it out there and we'll keep listening here in Nebraska.
Alright, man.
Well, yes.
Please join the Google group.
It's free trinity.
So it's groups.google.com slash free trinity.
I think you have to capitalize the F and the T on that one.
Oh, no.
It's written as one word free trinity.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
This is exactly what I want.
And I want that.
And we can build this.
It's not that hard.
I mean, I can completely conceptualize it.
Uh, I know these systems exist.
And, you know, willing to put up the money to make it happen.
And, uh, yeah.
Just willing to put the money to make it happen.
I just wanted to happen.
So I want all this flowing back to a webpage where you can indeed not only track her progress,
but over each push pin, as an example of a friper map, you'd see a picture.
You can see a video.
You can hear a podcast.
You can see a video podcast.
Uh, trinity will be sending back her own pictures and GPS coordinates.
See how fast she ran.
All of that stuff.
Yes, it will be one completely integrated campaign.
Please, if you're interested in helping out join the Google Group.
Hey, Adam, this is Cory.
And this is Jen.
And we're from Bucket.
Hey, buddy.
We heard you talking about the free trinity thing.
And we wanted to say that you could time to come down this way toward
homage country here in Pennsylvania.
And I just want you to know that Bucket, uh, which is a pod show podcast,
we're headquartered right here in the heart of homage country.
Um, so we love relatively.
So we love to have you and trinity.
Take a stop by the area here.
And we be glad to guide you through the scenic farmlands of, uh,
Lancaster County down here.
Interest of saving the world and winning valuable prizes, of course.
Absolutely.
Um, now a couple of things real quick.
Uh, you remember we're talking about the different cultures of the homage.
One thing they don't really like is they don't like to be, uh,
photograph your video taped.
Uh, they have a thing in their, uh, in their religion.
Uh, that they don't like.
It's, uh, kind of a thing that they believe that cameras capture their soul.
And also they have a thing about being vain.
And that's why they don't have photos in their home.
And the whole technology thing too.
That's right.
So, but they do use some limited technology.
They do a lot.
Some of them do drive in car.
They ride in cars.
As long as they're as a non-armage driver.
They have like, homage taxi services that go around and pick up, uh,
uh, homage families and vans.
So it's, they do use cars.
They just don't drive them themselves.
Anyway, the point is we thought that we'd love to be involved in free trinity.
And if you did want to drive it through homage country and possibly try to look up,
and maybe have a chance to record some homage people.
I think Cory and I are the people for the job.
Yes, absolutely.
So definitely give us a ring at, uh, or give us an email,
book a podcast at gmail.com and let us know if you'd be interested.
Yeah, man.
We're waiting.
All right.
Well, kids, please join the list.
Sign up to the group.
How much people have homage taxi cabs?
That's totally something new for me.
Hi.
This is that one.
What I want to find out what to do for our environment.
I listen to sustainable business practices.
Oh, my gosh.
Shameless plug.
Hey, Adam.
It's Doug Pilgrim.
Oh, man.
What a week.
It's hard to believe that it was just a week ago that a little bit over a week ago,
that you were complaining about a broken down 23 year old station wagon.
And I had a windshield day dream.
And now, look at where we are.
I have to tell you this completely blows my mind that we're having a discussion from Australia
to Italy about renewable energy and biodiesel.
I mean, this is just gone beyond my wildest hopes and expectations.
I think this is absolutely fantastic.
You know, this, of course, is Doug Pilgrim, the guy who kind of started all off by offering to drive
Trinity from San Francisco to Boston with his son who's in that was at sea right now.
I believe.
So Doug is, of course, the OG of free Trinity.
This really just goes to show, you know, the power of one and the power of podcasting.
The ability for all of us to get that, to get a message out there.
And I can't wait to tell my son when he gets off the ship.
What's been going on?
He's been at sea for the last month with the mass maritime academy and he's been out of the
communication.
I can hear him now.
Dad, you know, what the F, have you started now?
So I think this has just been a phenomenal acceptance among everybody that's out there.
And, you know, it's just so important to have this discussion now.
Now, from a environmental standpoint, from an economic standpoint, from a political standpoint, from a moral standpoint.
And here in the US, we are addicted like crack addicts sucking on the petroleum pipe.
And, you know, quite frankly, something has to break.
You know, I'm sorry, Mr. President, but reducing our gasoline consumption by 20% in the next 10 years,
8, enough.
And, you know, it's going to take people to drive this.
It's going to take every one of us to make our own choice.
And, you know, force businesses to follow us in a new direction.
So I think by promoting something like this, it's just going to help move this whole discussion,
and the whole movement along that much quicker, which leads me to my next idea.
Now that we pretty much move Trinity out of your garage, what are we going to put back in her place?
You know, I'm sorry, but, you know, to stick a gas-guzzling jag into a garage there in San Francisco.
Yeah, hold on a second.
I never said I was going to stick a gas-guzzling jag in the garage in San Francisco.
In fact, yes, dear.
I can't hear you.
Hold on.
What's that?
Listen to you.
But it's weird, you're like standing behind me, and it's like, if you want to listen, come up here.
Yeah, it's weird.
It's like having someone talk and then you're behind them.
You can't join in because you broke the headphones, remember?
Yeah.
All right.
Can I continue?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
In fact, today we made a big decision, and Patricia got the new car, the smart roaster,
which comes what next week, Tuesday.
I don't like that.
And, you know, I mean, yeah, we drive the super V8, but rarely.
You know, it's like a tank of gas, it's probably last us a month.
Anyway, decided to do a little bit better on the CO2 emissions.
You know, there's a big difference between a 4.2 liter engine V8 and a 2.5 liter engine.
So scaling down the sizes of the car, I'll tell you more about it.
I'll probably post a picture here on the web log when she's in, but definitely looking
at something different.
Now, for San Francisco, never said I wanted a Jagu.
It was Patricia who wanted any car as long as it was a Jaguar.
Not me.
I'm an Audi guy.
Yeah, she loved Jagu.
All right.
So what's your suggestion then, Doug?
It's just not going to work.
I mean, to be kind of hypocritical at this point, don't you think?
And I think you'd be sending the wrong message.
And by the way, did British petroleum ever send you a thank you card for buying that Jaguar?
So instead, what I propose is putting a Tesla Roadster in that place.
Now, a Tesla Roadster is 100% electric sports car.
Zero to 60 and four seconds.
130 miles an hour screaming down the highway to Cedar and 250 miles between each charge.
I think this is a great idea.
And it has a base price of $92,000.
Oh, only $92,000.
What a steal.
So Doug, let me just tell you, I was at the launch of this car.
Ray Lane bought one.
He's one of our investors.
And remember that was the story where we flew down on his jet to Los Angeles.
And we had a horrible landing and Ray went flying through the cabin.
And when I was really happy about that,
because it doesn't mean that I'm the only shitty pilot.
Those things are amazing.
It's right. They go from zero to the 60 and like four seconds.
Amazingly fast.
But it's basically they're using the body of a lotus.
I don't know if you've ever seen a lotus.
Man, this is like, it's too small for me.
It's too small.
And besides, the waiting list is so long.
I don't think, and this was, she was at four, four months ago.
Only five months ago that Ray ordered his.
He still hasn't received his car.
So when he does, though,
Guess who has dibs on a couple of test drives.
You know, I'm going to finnake it out of his hand,
so I can drive it around San Francisco for a little while just to,
to do some research.
Call that a steal.
A steal for the pod father.
I mean, for the rock and roll star of pod casting,
you deserve to be driving around in a car like this.
So here's the next concept.
We're going to call this the free Adam project.
I love you, man.
I forget about that.
I don't need to be free.
I'm one of the freeest guys you'll know.
So if you want to participate, all you have to do is join the Google Group.
You can't play with me.
Groups.google.com.
Slash free.
Turn it on.
Play safe.
If you want nice and beautiful,
and you know the answer is
something that I do you with,
cause the question for sure is
what you got in here don't worry.
Everything here is free.
Still you take our apprehenses.
Everything comes in three.
So you make sure who's the last lap is.
And you play fun now.
Let you know first hand.
If you want to sit down,
you're not the way you stand.
You make what you play.
My pride won't block you.
But from up there,
not even you can't stop it.
If you could want to sit down,
all that time,
and nothing to break,
Play your sunshine, but there's not a cure
If I stay until I go blind and I'm trying to find some shade
It closed my eyes at night, but the world comes in a way
And there's no way, leaving side, everything is free
Do you take our applications, everything comes in free
So you make shoes, our last life is everything
It's free, so you take our applications, everything comes in free
I know, let you know, let you know
If you won't sit down, you'll have nothing to waste
Yeah, you might be right, but you still got nothing to spend
If you won't sit down, then you'll never understand
That thornly stand from the pod save music network
Of course say inspired by a dog's little promo there at the beginning
Excuse me
You don't walk away now, now you got to come up here and say it
Now you got to say it
So there's a, can you just grab that microphone and may sound like shit
I don't know, I haven't said it up for you yet
Wait, talk for a second baby, so I can, there you go
Just talking to that microphone, this is Lady Patricia
Yeah, Lady Patricia here
Talk more talking
Yes, Lady Patricia here, test test, do you hear me?
I'm trying to turn down your reverb or whatever it is
Talk some more?
Yeah, yep, okay, there we go, that's okay
You hear me
So what was this in a
No, my whole on a second, let me set it up
Professional pronounced decay
They're pronounced decay to
In a gossip magazine in fact the same one that stole our pictures
Yes
What did they publish?
What is in it this week?
We are very big on the cover
Said my, that's what my mom said
But we're very big undercover, what does that mean?
On the cover of the magazine
On the cover of the magazine with a big, big yellow thing over it
And it says
How do you say that when you want this resort?
Wanted
Talking to the mic because it's not set up right
You're wanted
Yeah
Because you are escaping
From everybody in Holland because
Because they're yes, I am because they're idiots
Of course I'm escaping
I think I've done a good job of escaping Holland
Yeah, because people need, I don't know, people get money from you
I don't know something like that
People get money, what does that mean?
Yeah
What does it say?
You don't know what it says, do you?
Oh my mom said
Yeah, your mom, by the way your mom is a complete authority
On relaying information
She read it for me
Yeah
And so what's the point?
What does it say?
What is the point of the car?
That's what I want to know
Oh yeah
And now you are absolutely not successful
I'm not successful right?
No, of course not
Yeah
You're sad
You're running away from everything
Today I'm very sad
Yes
I'm running away
And you are just starting a company
Just started a company in America
Yeah
And not successful yet
Of course not
That's why you drive in
Attunity
A very old car
Who just broke down?
Yeah, that's right
You told it yourself
Yeah
Yeah, so it's true
That's where you got it from
Yeah
And it's sad
Everything is sad
And so everybody is looking for you
Everybody is looking for you
Yeah
But what is the school that I've seen in English?
I don't know
It's someone who is looking for someone who thinks I owe the money
Yeah
So they talk into the fucking microphone
Or get off my show
I don't know what it is in English
Because I'm trying to tell you
But you keep talking away from the microphone
I'm fine
It's a credit
A creditor
Oh yeah
Is that what I mean?
Not to be confused with predator
No
A creditor
Yeah
So I owe someone money
Is that what we're saying?
Yeah
Well shit, I don't know
No
All these gossip magazines seem to find out
Where I live
Well I have to say
It's
Remember we
Were this guy
Months and months
You know we were talking about
Mark Fondalinder
Fadass Mark Fondalinder
Back
He is satisfying
He's friend
The other diva
Did they have a good picture of us?
There is a good picture
Yeah
It's not bad
Mom said
I said it was the picture mom
And she said no
No no
I said that's good
As long as the picture is okay
Oh my goodness
Yeah
It was quiet for long time
But then mommy has to do a somba
Which was too good
Did I not tell you that this is exactly what happens
Is the minute you show yourself
They start digging stuff up
And of course
It's easy to dig up stuff on me
Because there's all kinds of shit around
I'm fine
That's right
That's what I keep telling you
It's like
But they put your name next to mine
So you may want to dissociate yourself from me
I think we should
I think we should take it all the way
I think we should say that we're divorced
I'm living in San Francisco
And what happened is you took all the money
Yeah
You took all the money
That's why I just bought a new car
You just bought a new car
And I'm in San Francisco
In a broken down Mercedes 300
Turbo diesel station
Wow
I'm very sad
It's a fucking sad
Yeah
Now Mark finally in this very sad
As long as it doesn't take our pictures
No
Is there a picture of Trinity?
Not from the Trinity
What do they have just a picture of us?
Yeah
Oh wait
Maybe I can look at it online
What do you can
There's also you can see the cover
What's the
Do you know the website?
Now we can do
We can.nl
That's an out probably
Yeah
Everybody can see you
The weekend
Let me see
Looking up
Now we can does not it
What's weird?
Hold on
Uh
Big blood
We can't
Maybe
Oh here it is
Weekend
Dash online
Dot an L
Yeah
Let's see
Oh look at this
This is why he
Avoid Holland
Adam Curry on the run
Ha ha ha ha
Let me see
Adam Curry in Patricia Pi
Ha ha ha
Talk about their recent move
On their internet site
I didn't
No
I did
Is there something wrong with me saying that
Am I not allowed to see
Now of course you don't have any
Oh here it is
In the past week there was an advertisement
In a newspaper
Of a creditor that is looking to find
Adam Curry
Let's go
Who apparently has no
What do they call it?
Fusta
Vona for
Lifelots who has no
No no no no no
Established
Yes
No no established
Address
No we don't
Yes we are
Oh god
Maybe stop
They're going to
They're stepping around
Really
They're going to extra
Dite me to the Netherlands
And two trucks
Two trucks
Just for shipping around
Yeah such ideas
I wonder what it is though
Well if anyone needs to find me
They know where how to find me
That's so easy
But
But you know that the neighbors
The warned us
There were
You know people at her door
Looking for us
Our neighbor
Where we moved to
She said
I'm not going to tell you
Because I really screw that
You never know
Screw that
Yeah
But if they're really serious
You can always find it
You know what I think this is
I know what this is
Oh yes
Yes I do
Because I was asked about this
A year ago
Do you remember
Helikom
The first helicopter company
That I took lessons from
Okay
So here's what happened
So I flew with Helikom
For a god
I don't know
Two years maybe
I flew with them
Yeah
And each flight was easily
I mean it could have been
400 euros
A thousand euros
It depends on how far we would fly
And so I met
Wing Commander William
Yeah
After like two years
And then flew with him
For another two years
Perhaps flew with him
Yeah
And after
So I had had stop flying with Helikom
And a year and a half
After I stopped flying with him
They sent me a bill for
I think like three or four thousand euros
Saying that these were flights that I hadn't paid for
A year and a half
After
And by the way
They went through a bankruptcy
And they were in trouble
And they were looking for money
And so they sent me the invoice
And I said look
You're just sending me fucking invoice
Show me the logs
Show me all the books
Show me I really did these flights
Because I don't know
It's like a year and a half ago
I would have to go and defend myself
It's stupid invoice
If you show me
Then you never know
It's all about
Right
And so
They never showed you
No, of course they never showed it to me
I think they
I think they put a freeze on one of our bank accounts
For like 4,000 euros or whatever
And I'm like okay
I'll just let it sit there
I still get interest on the money
I don't need to spend the money
And so whenever they feel like
Proving that I actually made those flights
I think there was an advertisement from them
Yeah
I mean it's looking for you
That's like it's part of legal proceeding
So then they can you know
So they probably
They probably sued me
I don't know
I didn't receive any paperwork
So maybe they sued me
And maybe the judge said
They don't know where to send it
Yeah because he didn't show
So maybe they forced their way
Into the foreground or whatever
But it's not a big deal
Certainly not
Not worth the front cover
Not an hour world
Certainly not
Yeah
Certainly not the
Worth the front cover
Of the gossip
No but you know
If you need something
Talking
If you want to find something
Need something
To write something
Bad in your magazine
Anything
Anything is of course
Well I say
Come on
Come on over here
And get it
Come on over here and get it boys
Well
And just prove to me
Yeah
If that's what it is
I can't think of anything else
We have no business
No we have
I pay for one car
Yeah
I still pay
Lawyers and Accountants
Yeah
That shit goes on forever
I can't think of anything else
No but you know
As we call it
Even if it's not true
A storm and a glass of water
Yeah but they can ride anything
They want
Yeah that's true
As long as they don't place any pictures
I'm fine
Yeah
And luckily this building right
In a certain way then it's
There's nothing wrong about it
I'm on the run
You are
Go lock the door
I'm on the run
That's why you're going
Every two weeks
Of course I have to change my location
As I got to change my location
If they find me then they're going to get me
The booge man is out to get me
You know
They listen to your show
Get all the information
You know what I said less
You know when we did the show
Also with me
Then all the things we're saying
They're using it
Isn't that sad
Well
But it was very quiet
And I told you that if you do anything in the Netherlands
Then it's exciting
It's exciting
Yeah of course
You did a good dance
I did a very good job
That's fine
So basically it's your fault now
That my name was like
You know what I was saying
Self-aclaimed
Yeah so I just
Oh dude
I get all the time
Now I get the whole is like
The self-proclaimed podfather
I didn't call myself the podfather
Then I say self-proclaimed
Proclaimed
Okay, yeah
That's what it says too
Yeah
I never called myself
You know one day we really
One day we really will run away
When our daughters all grown up
And boy
Let me tell you
People can be really sad
They'll have nothing left
Nothing left a bit
You're mowing about
Yeah really
I'll be mowing
All right
Okay
This has been a show that is twice
The length of a normal show
So I got to stop
Yeah but you know this was
Breaking news
It's breaking news
Mark from the Linder
Oh fuck you
All right
Will you come on the show
Sometime in the next decade
Would you mind?
Yeah
I unpacked hundreds of 50 boxes
I'm done
Okay
All right then.
Adam and podshow.com
DailySourceCode.com
And
We'll see you tomorrow
For the food bar edition of the show
Bye baby
Bye
The other podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
The best of the brightest
Set up daily by the sharpest minds in content
Delivering podshow and limelight
Subdupt daily by the sharpest minds in content