It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's Adam Curry.
Let her drop.
Delta, see her turn.
Episode 6-07.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
It is late on Thursday evening.
I'm back at the manner.
Don't worry.
It's not another flying sound scene tour.
It's been a pretty busy 48 hours.
Maybe even a little bit longer.
And I'm really, really tired.
And tomorrow on the maximum music footballer Friday, I'll be happy to tell you all about it.
For today, though, we have a special S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-P-S-S-S-S-U-S-R-I-C-S-S-And-E-T-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-E-S-A-D-D-S-S-I-S-S-S-E-O-R Freeienst, CH
That really makes me feel good when I hear someone enjoy something like that, basically.
Not really an experiment because I've done these recordings before and the responses are exactly
perpendicular.
People say I don't, I'm not interested, hated listening to it and it was way too basic
and then the opposite because you really should be listening to an episode like this in
the car.
Because you're in the same type, this is totally, it's theater of the mind.
You don't need to close your eyes to be in the cockpit with me.
If you turn this up, your car is actually vibrating.
If you haven't listened to that in the car on the speakers and it does seem to work for
a lot of people with earbuds, but really trying to get it on a nice speaker system and
that by the way, completely uncompressed, un-tweet, non-filtered recording of exactly what
was going on in my ear, I will tell you, I just use this little love microphone, I stick
it into my ear and then put the headphones on so it's picking up the intercom, it's picking
up the radio.
The radio, by the way, there's something fucked with it, I've got a, I'm trying to get
that fix, it's not very clear, it's a little unintelligible and I'm just on the reception
side, I'm actually having some trouble hearing what people are saying and I went with
the cat and yoss and that's a story from another day, you flew me, you flew co-pilot
and safety pilot to Darmstadt, oh man, I can't so much shit to talk about.
Hi Adam, it's Will from Essex and the UK again, I'm getting a bit concerned, and I've
got to be honest, I haven't listened to all of your shows, but what's happened to Roger?
His Roger Smalls got, because I think I'm most of the TV to highlight, and I haven't
had the ring, I haven't had just me, and more importantly I haven't had a dodgy phone
microphone action and him doing his card and bit, I don't know, I'm going to be worried
about it and so I just wanted to keep you doing the chemical or you know, the text or any
amount, because I'm sure you got it's competitive, I'll just pop around to his house and
just take these, you know, in the right, dude, I feel really bad, I don't think I've
looked at Roger sight in such a long time, Roger Smalls.com, is it was it Roger Smalls
thought, I think it's that log, spot.com, Roger Smalls.com, that's interesting, leads to
OS X training.com, okay, we're not looking for that Roger, Smalls are blogs, okay, Monday, May
seven, so it's been a little while, it's got, oh, it's got another weird stuff, hmm, it seems
depressed, oh man, you're right, I don't know if I'm going to go to his house, but I think it
is a good idea to check up on him. Hey Adam, this is Dan, just wanted to say that's over
it, I'm going to put it into your PSC 606, your flight to the channel, great piece of that podcasting,
I've been listening to your show for a while, and that was a great piece of what you did there.
I work in an office, I guess you must have flown over the top of our gas platform, as I
think it was on route. Anyway, take care, really enjoy it, all the best, Roger Bye.
Hey man, if you're on the gas platform, get me the coordinates, get me the GPS coordinates,
because I don't know which one is yours, I'll fly over, and we'll set a time, and we'll like
to take pictures of each other, do something radical like that. The prize definitely goes to
Bell Flyer, who said Minimil, who said enjoyed the flight, what do you say? What was the
interest to you? Okay, here it comes, I thought I heard a bounce. This is only a fucking
pilot could hear this, because yes, upon landing, I bounced a little bit, keep that flare
going until you, until the stall warning, if you can, Cessna's will bounce above 80 knots, yeah,
I know, I came in a little too fast. I can't believe that someone actually heard that,
just with the audio, because I'm not saying anything, and you just have to listen to it, because
actually, revved up a little bit, but the bounce, I thought it came through ever so slightly, so
oh, I have a James's back on the line. Yeah, Adam, pretty, James, just listen to your little
films, so you're into a nice little bit of a difference. You mentioned it, Jeffrey and Jeff, I'm
guessing that's a helicopter, but I'm not a aviation person, but I gotta use to fly helicopter,
you don't, you don't, let's do enough, just a question, sorry, I'm not next, okay,
James, I gotta tell you, man, that I am so jazzed about what's gone down in the past couple of
weeks with how the flying's gone, but yeah, I miss it terribly, and now that the nice weather's
upon us, I'll definitely get some chopper flying in, and I don't know, if you guys like it,
I'll do another, I think that actually, as we move into the German market, and again,
please, after the weekend, we'll talk about that and what's going down, but we are definitely
coming to thank you, everybody, for sending me emails, with your great insights on the market.
Actually, I felt my German kind of start getting a little bit better, while I was there for a couple
days. Anyway, so I feel that, you know, there'll be plenty of opportunity, or maybe that the
only time will be able to do a show is when I'm flying, which is okay, because it gets pretty lonely.
And speaking of lonely, here is Mr. lonely himself. It's been a while and great to have him
back on the show.
On a second, I didn't receive any messages.
Why do we need to get to those? No, no, no, no, please, something went wrong. I didn't receive
any, I haven't received anything from you since I started asking for you to call me.
Crap, I hate that.
Shit, man. Would you try doing the the UK now or just send me an email if you called it?
I really, really hate this, so please, let's try and make that word better. Let's try and
suck less on that. Anyway, dude, what's with the show in the airplane? I'm on. What's
focus group that you listen to that said? Or your audience wants to hear you as a sound of your voice.
It doesn't matter what you're saying. It's a show. I listen to a show and I'll wait a minute.
Did I imply that at one time you didn't find the show? By the way, it was an episode of a show.
You didn't find that to be entertaining or a show. I was, I was definitely putting on a show.
I was multitasking and you probably know from your own experience, man, on good multitaskers.
Your voice, respect to audience, give me a show. You know, which raises my second point.
Is this show a hobby or a profession? Is this thing to me that this show has just been
getting in the way of your flying? Which I thought was your hobby and the show is your business.
Oh, dude. The flying is to get around to enable the business to happen more efficiently.
At life gets in the way in general. I'm confused by all this. So, hey, dude.
Um, what's the show? We don't just want to hear anything. What are the show in the topic?
You know, on Delta Sierra, Charlie, you know, let's get the show back on the road.
You know, what happened to Larry King? Hey, wait. Which brings my last point tomorrow's football.
Oh, whenever you're footballer. And I think the part-face network has to be a little bigger than
White rock and roll bands. Okay. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now, this, you got to listen to this. I'll just let it play. For some reason
nylon is, is, is, is confused. Well, he's definitely confused. Saying that, have you ever looked?
Have you gone to potter.com slash music? Have you ever looked at the categories?
Now, they're white rock. What is white rock music? Jesus.
This network has to be a little bigger than white rock and roll bands. Are there no jazz or
does out there? Are there no R&B artists in the pot safe? And as soon as you see the word jazz on our site,
there are R&B. Click on the link. I mean, maybe even there's some classical people.
Oh, classical, click on the link. Yeah, but let us expand this to, you know, beyond just the white rock
and roll bands, jazz. The audience in the world and then podcasting is bigger than that.
So I'm back. Say flying. Good thing we don't have to get a return trip. And that's what you
assume. That's her dick. Not a lot. Hey, nylon, nylon. Look at me. Look at me. Turn around.
Now, bend over, bend over. Stand over. This is from the pot safe music network.
You get me to know that. I just love people when we're naked. But you've had a buckle up baby, baby.
Because I won't make you scream. We can't tell lies. I'm so about the way I walk. I can't help
what's ever in the twinkle in your eyes. You've made the switch. If you want to get next to me,
I've got you wonderful stuff. So messin' with you, please. Yeah, I can't help but follow.
Has you stay with your drops and the breeze roll through my hair. Condition up on the cliff.
I've got you written and cold won't flash you. And I was smelling my perfume.
It was a roll like I'd you all stew it to all you need. Baby, we can see the poignant stuff together.
Dancing next to me. I've got to get my travel window. And you my eye just thought in the sweat.
Want to get between my body down the bed. Looking that low so I say,
have no. You almost want your legs when it turns to double. Close your eyes for a second.
But you're tongue on my neck. But you lost yourself. Try to take that for a second.
Step, step, step, step.
Mistimcially, step, step, step. I'm the kind of girl to make you hollow.
I'm out, you shouldn't be in the next to me. If you get better,
find your baby for your tongue runs out and run out. Mistimcially, step, step, step.
I'm a kind of girl to drop you and stay in the rain. You want to see who impress me.
You're better bringing up for the funnest champagne. Just what it is,
because you haven't figured it out yet. What draws you see me? You ever sent your first set to eyes on me.
You want to get to know me way better than the one that you went so ready.
You get the one you little feeling whenever I walk by. You try to take a deep breath
and then you let it stop. What do you think about me? You're not a good stop.
One takes to this baby and you'll never get enough. And I'm just trying to drag me to let you discover.
Hold on my seat, where's that you want to come from? But don't fall for your words. You only get one chance.
I got you, you're not in the touch. Me, so you ask me to dance.
So I want you to sing so mesmerize and sing so gentle. I forgot to fan the side and die.
But I forgot to think you could hold your roll. Then make you later on. I'm out, just take you home.
Home. Mistimcially, step, step, step. I'm the kind of girl to make you hollow. I'm out,
you shouldn't be in the next to me. If you get better, find your baby for your tongue runs out and run.
Mistimcially, step idea. I'm a kind of girl to rob you and save you and save me. You want to sing so mesmerize,
you better bring her for the funnish in pain. The parcel is washed for the scalp and that's make it the cla ankle if
I like the g vwh't but what I'm needing to know baby if that's something like you. I ever Hands to get my attention telling
not to know you ain't got a scheme just make all theRed colours baby and I pull make you scream. I've got to SUMN UF
I won't make you scream
I've got to so much nervous and I think it's sweet
But I don't need a minute or two left
Be back, I just hang in there and it's getting hot
But yeah, will you better make you move before I disappear
There's just so much about me
I'm so afraid, don't you?
I've got you so intrigued, I'm talking to seriously sexy
She's so damn fine, I hear you whisper to your friends
Will you better find your game before this party?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna drop the neck
Yeah, I'm gonna get out of the aisle
I'm feeling that's coming
Yeah, I'm gonna find your game before you throw runs out
Runs out, yeah
Mistakes, please take this extra time
I gotta drop to drop you in a chain
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna bring that for the fun of shit
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm gonna get out of the aisle
I'm feeling that's coming
Yeah, I'm gonna find your game before you throw runs out
From the very own Proxy music network
J-me mysteriously sexy and nylon seems to apparently matters to you
She's white
The savonth specials
Okay, it's a time for our savonth from our series of the circle of savonth
Dying the self-interference of savonth
So long
I think I'm gonna be able to get at least one savonth in episode
There's a fast forward button on there for a reason
And I hope to be able to talk to a savonth every single day
savonth
And by the way, I want you to know that this format change doesn't mean that
I don't still want to make it pictures make it pictures
By the salt and the sense of savonth savonth
So with me now
one of the biggest
Superstar savonth
In fact, he is the Mac Daddy of savonth
He is the true J-C of savonth
John C. Dvorak
Hey
The funny thing about that savonth thing is that I was once called the columnist savonth
By the Washington Post. I thought that I always thought that was amusing
And they were quite new at that moment
Did you tell us not so you didn't take it as an insult or compliment you just didn't
Well, the way I see it, I'm kind of like you mad
I mean, you know any you way the publicity by the pound
Yeah
Or the kilo depending on what I mean to that day
Well, yeah, well you're in Europe
So
I
Think the news is a starting to spread to quite well by now that
You've joined Pod Show as
I'm going to right here the Vice President of Managing Editor who will be producing a new breed of technology channel
You know, how could I resist?
Didn't you make all the title and everything up?
You guys made up the title
But this beside the point the fact of the matter is that I you know I decided I'm gonna actually turn
This experience into into a into a speech. I you know, I give these these speeches around the country
I keynotes and whatever
But you know
The funny thing about the whole podcasting scene is that it's just so mirrors
What's happened to newspapers and print with online publishing and I just
Can't not see it happening exactly the same way and for exactly the same reasons
For broadcasting it's just it's just the way the numbers work out
This is the future so I so I was really enthusiastic about
Jumping in on this one so
I've been looking around the web and a couple the there's basically two things that
Of course gets repeated and copied and linked to over and over with with something like this
And by the way John welcome. I think it's it's awesome that that you've made this decision of come on board
I'm already loving working with you
But I'll suck up some more later so the ones that the yeah, right the two things people want to know
Action my contract by the way. I have to suck up to you. Oh really and is that on Tuesdays and Thursdays because I do have that
No, actually, you know what it specifically says in section three five days a week. I only get two days off
in
2000 and four
25th of
October
You wrote in your column on PC magazine about how you just didn't see it happening with in fact
I love this list if podcasting such and this becomes popular and you describe what your experience was of course
This is early days then it's placed in the pecking order for all forms of fun entertainment would be as follows
I love this on top circuses night clubs
Movies sporting events cable TV network TV county fairs talk radio PBS
Whittling fingernail clipping and then podcasting
I'm a laugh riot. I had to say and I remember you writing that and and I probably thought at this at the time
Fucker, I
We'll show you
But you know the funny thing is it's like I did the same thing with blogging and
I mean actually wrote three or four columns and some of them same kind of like snide, you know, you know humorously
Positioned
Policy papers essentially and
You know the blogging thing of course I got into a couple years or a couple years ago in 2004 and I now
Actually think about it because I could have probably gotten into blogging around 1998 when like Leo the port over at ZDTV was
Was blogging already because he jumps on anything
that happens and
If I had done that I wouldn't you know, I'd probably be retired. It just like it was it was I
tend to do that people don't understand this quite
You know, completely my my normal fan base does because I know I'm always like experimenting with with my current thinking
Is that I like to
Look at a technology or an idea or something new like a trend like this and then I'll I'll
Try to try to see everything that's wrong with it and then expose what I think is wrong
And see what kind of pushback I get I you get different kinds of responses to some of these negative pieces that I do and I'm at natural
If you know I've taken
Vocational tests and I it turned out to be
People it comes up at the top of the list. I swear it's
Critic it's like that might
I'm not telling it's the truth. I've done this more and more and
Every time it comes up number one what you should do is become a critic
So anyway, so apparently I have like critical genes
So I'm very critical and that's why you should don't jump on things like you know the second that they happen
But what I do is I criticize it and I go into great details or I'll do something very snide like that
This you mentioned which was quite funny by the way
I do say so myself
But anyway, I'll get I'll get blowback on that and I'll start to reanalyze and reanalyze and then pretty soon
I get a clue now with the podcasting thing compared to the blogging
I kind of got a clue. I think a little faster on the whole thing it did it it didn't take the you know
What one two three four five it didn't take six or seven years for me to figure out that that
Content management software was a great thing because it allowed people to like bypass
You know complicated systems
But with the podcast and think because I'm so in tune with what's happening to newspapers
I just realize it just dawned on me talking to both you and Ron
The CEO of Potcho that that it's like exactly what's happening to newspapers is going to happen to broadcasts because
Just the cost you don't have to have an antenna you don't have to have a first class radio telephone guy running it
You don't have to have a big staff you don't have to have amplifiers. You don't have to you know
You have international poll. I mean it's unbelievable and it's just exactly the same mile away
What's happened to newspapers is that they have they're overhead
It's like they have to print the papers. They've got a buy ink. They've got a buy paper
They have a distribution issue which is by the way another thing that radio broadcasters don't or TV broadcasters
Don't need when you have the internet you don't need the distribution network. It's built into the system
So what I and it went at that dawn. I mean, so this is the end of you know
Conventional thinking I got I got I got a clue a little faster here
So I love these press releases. No, actually I fucking hate them because they never a press release
Never puts in hyperlinks to anything. They just mentioned all these great
Properties and all these fantastic things that we have and that you've done and and they never put a link
But anyway, did you actually say this in the let me just read your quote
Technology has given us this massive new distribution medium and yet our approaches producing technology content
has been in the same old predictable style comments devourack by working with pod shows new channel format
We can combine entail of entertainment and insight
Ron wrote this I can't believe entertainment and insight and take the concept of integrated programming to an entirely new level. Did you say that devourack?
I think I may have said each one of those words at some point in my life
Well essentially, okay, so what's interesting is that and the way people that what we saw on interrupt you
But people out there who listen to this show. I mean you have to I I can explain a few things
But the way they should know everyone should know and by the way when I do I'm going to be doing the tech five report on
On the pod show network, which will be a daily thing that people should subscribe to but and I'm going to
reveal some of these kinds of weirdness is that take place with the press release. A lot of the stuff is written
Not necessarily by the person that's quoted. I believe what I said there though is not contradictory to anything
I believe it's just not something I was specifically said at any given time. I just want you to know what I said
okay
In life technology is no longer in the back row seat. It is now taking center stage. I got to do the dramatic voice
Pod show tech which is the channel you'll be building or whatever it is John
Will reflect that change says Pod show president and co-founder Adam Curry John is the perfect anchor
Combining his legendary insight on camera personality and extensive roll of decks to keep to help keep us fresh the channel fresh informative entertaining and relevant
That's pretty good. That's pretty good sucking up isn't it that was a good quote. I got one of that so
We split you know, we actually we met a long time ago. What was it 15 years ago, maybe now? That's too long
Was a 93 I think
14 years ago
Cnet's formed yeah, it was 92 or 93 could have been 15 but I think it's 14 because you know, we were both on the original
Staff of the scene if the phenomenon which it was only it was a cable channel at the time
They didn't in fact I registered seen that dot com for them. Oh
Did you now yeah for haulsie and
Shellbee and in fact I hosted their email for I don't it must have been half a year or something like that
Yeah, you know that I don't think the I don't want to
Talk out of school here, but you know, I don't think the public generally realizes what a geeky nerd you really
Let me ask you a question John
You know, they made an offer to me at the time to
You know to move out to San Francisco and work for Cnet
Which would have been a very substantial
Change of life for me. Oh although I I really was tempted by it
There are a number of reasons why I wasn't going to leave and wasn't going to do it, but the deal they offered
Which was you know a reasonable money to do it. It was they are so still some risk
But there was like a whole shit load of options
Yeah, and I was just wondering if if the deal that you could you did launch with him you launched with the channel I believe and you were there for
God knows how long
And then you know, did you ever make any money off of that to those options? I mean was that a a good set up?
I was actually a I never took the there's a couple deals that were offered to me
And the deal I took was kind of a was unless I didn't want to really throw everything at those guys because I wasn't like a big fan necessarily of
See halls he had came up with his initial
schemes were to do a interactive TV play which was something it was dying and they kind of just stumble onto the internet
After the fact and it was and it wasn't until actually then I didn't actually refuse to do a deal with it
Right at the bat when you were still talking to him. I was done and then when they brought in Kevin Wendell
Oh right talk they talked to me into doing some workform and so I did some stuff there
But it never you know I got some options. I never but I didn't make the kind of I mean I if I had jumped in when Wendell came on
I would have done pretty well for myself
I did I made some money. Let's put it that way but I didn't make the kind of money that Richard Hart made
Who's the guy who took your place crack and Richard Hart is retired now and doesn't apparently doesn't do anything
Last time I saw him was in a theater
He was sitting there was a full beard
He didn't you couldn't recognize him
I mean I didn't I don't want to say look like a bomb
But that's funny. You look better. Let's put it that way. So I think you did well
But you know it was a pretty risky situation at the time they did great
I actually should I could have probably pushed myself into a really
Important job there and
Then I would be retired myself, but yeah, you know, I'm not like I'm starving to death. Let's face it now and
The other question that is just popping up everywhere
Is does this mean he'll no longer be on twit
Yeah, it's funny people like the you know the twit thing is
I don't know what these guys are like twit is like some sort of a weird phenomenon. It's a kind of a call
It's a cult showing with the huge following. No, I'm still doing twit. I mean twit consists for me
I mean I actually actually do some work here at Pocho. I got to like you know produce a page and do stuff
Oh, oh god damn page. Well, actually I have to say well, no, no, but I'm bringing some other people on board
So it's not going to be like I'm just sitting around doing nothing but with twit it's basically I you know pick up the the
Skype thing on a on a weekly basis. I've already done the work because it's what I do normally and I just sit there and shoot the crap with these
With the other guys who haven't even on the show. It's not like it's not like a job
So there's no reason for me not to keep doing it and well, it's it's a whole competitive thing
You know people believe that people don't know what to believe but not at zero sum yet
I mean I don't I don't understand that completely because I'll go although you
We're chiding me earlier. We had for people out there. We had a chat earlier about
Robert Skobel who works for a competitor and
I said I don't think he's ever gonna mention that I'm over here because I don't think this competitor who you if you notice
I'm not saying they're names, but I'll say it pot time tech. Yeah, they are I think they play zero sum which is the you know the game
We're saying well, you know if we say something about them they're gonna take our business away when in fact
We're not at the point
in this industry
for any
for years where
You know everything is accumulative in other words if I plug somebody they plug maybe it's not like it's not like for example at pot show
I'll be doing some news drops, but you know
Cali does news news kind of and Natalie does news kind of but it's not like any one of us is gonna take any business away from the other
Yeah, because you know and it's not gonna be that way with one company competing with another for maybe ten years
I mean at some point yes
That's gonna happen, but it's not happening now because there's distilled growing what are you gonna do that's gonna be different
John because that's kind of what our great press release says
Yeah, when you hear it you'll see what's different about it
It's gonna be a little it's gonna be a podcast, you know, I've been thinking about this by the way because it's like something you're
Want to know and uh, you know pod I mean just
Reading news is one thing, but having kind of a really just kind of an extreme pod
The pod
Community right now the podcast in community they don't
It's just it's a little more experimental than what you would get from
Standard radio because everything's been coming homogenized and and
Maybe ruin by some of these large corporations that have taken over major media and which is typical in the death throws
Yeah, that's right, but
You know the pod thing is so much
Weirder because you can I mean if you watch like Cali show for example
Geek brief you see
You know, it's it's a very unusual kind of thing that would never be on broadcast TV yet
Although that woman who did the rocket boom a man to condon went and actually went to to
Major media. She's like I think she's with ABC now and she does some some podding
Well, isn't she supposed to also be like a segment host for
For one of their cable properties. I don't know what don't they have a case? Yeah, it's something like I mean I've seen but hey
Well, she's got a bunch of jobs. She's supposed to be doing over there, but the fact of the matter is you know
These major media guys
I think are largely clueless about any of it and and so they they're gonna just ruin her the way I see it and
Should we go save her is it worth it?
Well, you know, I think that she would fit in
I mean she's and she's you know, there's a thing I have to say this and I just kind of embarrassing to do this because I
Written for you know
wide range of publishing the vehicles as it were and the thing is I used to do some of my best work
at a low pay
Regional distribution publication that was actually free called micro times and it wasn't because it was
You know finally tuned writing that was heavily edited and and made to be super slick
It's because nobody cared enough because they were getting me so cheap to say anything about what I was doing and so I would do very
Experimental stuff and it was some of it
It's actually holds up. I've reprinted a few things on the one not as much as I showed over at the devorect.org slash blog
Site but I'm going to eventually put some of this stuff up and I you know, I've had I did like
You know scripts. I put us phony scripts up and and strange poems and all kinds of weird stuff
They got a lot of play and I always find it the one of the most interesting experiences experiences I had once is that
You do experimental stuff that works and then people who are mainstream
They want you to do that for them and so the situation occurred
I was writing for PC computing which is of you know was a high-end
Prestigious publication at the time and I had sent them a piece
That was because they're always saying why don't you give us more stuff like you're doing over there
And so I sent them an experimental piece that was really an interesting
Kind of a strange dream sequence article and
They kicked it back which is
It happens once in a while everybody and it's now this is kind of weird. I don't know what we're gonna do
I don't know what can you do is give us a regular column so I get a game a regular thing
And so I gave that dirt that that other piece right to micro times which was the outlet
I was using and they went and told me we love it
Well, they they wouldn't say that because they just ran everything but they ran it and the kicker was is that the editor
For PC computing calls me up about the micro times piece and says why don't you give us stuff like that?
Typical so typical so do we get the micro time
Stuff for do we get the the the the PC CIO magazine stuff it depends
I'm gonna give you the micro time stuff
But we'll see what you whether you like it or not, but no you're gonna get some I mean
One of the things I'm gonna be doing over there besides my own material
I'm gonna do that five minute thing and then I'm gonna try to do some some longer pieces that run
On occasion, you know we're getting some other we're gonna get
I'd like to get people out there who are interested in doing tech
Analysis or they want to do podcast
You know, they should definitely check out the pod show sites and
Put up something or just get a hold of me or if somebody's doing and I'm actually looking at every
Tech podcast or listening though my guests mostly every tech podcast out there now and there's there's stuff already that that we can bring on
To to live and things up. There's a lot of good stuff. There's a lot of good stuff up. There's a lot of crummy stuff
You know, it's really like going through
Unsolicited manuscripts to find the good stuff, but but it's
There's a lot of stuff. It's amazing. Well, we got reacquainted after
I appeared on cranky geeks and I think we'd probably
Pingly each other back and forth once or twice over over the 15 years
Well, you got real you got here's what happened you got some happened with you some years ago
You got really rich and so then you just kind of kicked away everybody else
This happens to anybody makes a lot of money. They they step on everybody under him
Okay, I hope it hurt
I did out my ear is still swollen
Did you ever receive any offers from anyone to do something like this? I mean
I have to believe that there were
Certainly a pod tech or someone must have said you know, do you want a pod tech now no pod tech would never do
There there there I don't think they have the insight
I hate to tell you this Adam, but you know, you're actually in the forefront of this whole thing
not
Give it ask me to do stuff, but just in the whole pod scene
It's it's it's it's but generally scatterbrained right now
I think it's it's has not coalesced in any way shape or format set for about four companies
The other guys are like little mini networks like rev three and these other people who you know
Just produce a lot of little shows that are you know
Interesting and
It's this is I when I got on board with you guys I was thinking to myself this is I'm one of the few times where I'm early in
Because I think that this is the ten years from now
I think almost everything is gonna be done through this
Mechanism I mean you already seeing it the big networks are freaked out about it
They're looking for alternatives or IP TV you know I got kind of jacked up about IP TV
Which by the way, I think is one of the reasons like I jumped on board really fast because I'm all over that
You saw this and you and you've seen our IP TV interface, right?
Yeah a little bit
Wait man, I had a big you haven't seen the whole Chris hasn't given you the whole demo
You know, I haven't seen the whole thing because I'm really right now just completely preoccupied with audio
Okay, all right, which by the way I have to say I love I really when you when you when you when we first talking and
And you know, because you do cranky geeks, which you know, I think has great appeal as the type of program that it is
But I was really happy to hear that you would do audio and daily, which is a big deal. No audio audio is the right now
I don't see anything. I mean the video thing is cool. I agree and I think and I'm a big and like I said
I'm a huge fan of IP TV real IP TV where everything's distributed on the internet. You don't have you don't have antennas anymore
You know like there now there's a new thing called IP
B and or some interface or a internet protocol broadcast networks and isn't there a
A couple of companies are trying to pull together and consortium to build an open source and
Open standard IP TV
Spec or platform or something of this name a couple is a bunch of these things showing at mostly by the way
Here because the internet actually IP TVs already moving way. I mean they're it's on its way. I have a website
called IP TV daily, which is a scraper
And it I've been up for years and it's like essentially it's a huge database of news stories
And the thing about it is that the number I have
Try to put the scraper together for a number of specialist subjects because I need these for my own data for my own purposes
So I you know if I'm going to do it as a website and
The number of stories that come across on a daily basis
It's just astonishing about IP TV in general. You mean yeah, it's just a huge business that's gonna
When it hits it's gonna be a monster and it's gonna be interesting to see what works and you know
We were at see bit and it was all you know like Microsoft
The IP TV platform. I'm my wife is loud
The Microsoft IP TV platform and everyone kind of had the same thing and now in you know Motorola's gonna have one and and
Nokia's gonna have one everyone's gonna have their own version of what they call IP TV
You know Eric's already got one. I mean go to Sweden and this stuff's already in play it in yours Korea
It's just some of these guys these Johnny come late. These are coming on to the scene with trying to you know
Serpent what's already pretty much in play. I mean if you want to follow a company that's on top of all this look for
Menurve and networks. I mean that's the company that really is a dominant force if I was
And if I had any you know money, I didn't invest in them. Hey, John, are you if you don't mind me asking you are a Democrat or Republican
I don't like to say, but let me but let me tell you first I started off as a Democrat because I was a kid
Right in my parents were you know we're working middle class so then I became a Republican and then it because a Carter
It'd be honest about and the fact that I noticed over the years that all the Democrats kept trying to kill me
So then I became a Republican. I stayed a Republican and now I consider myself an independent because I think the Republicans have just
lost control of their own
ideology and so I'm I would consider myself a Republican independent libertarian
Okay, well luckily, I'm just a pothead that makes it much easier to explain. Oh, yeah, that's I can't do that anymore
Oh, you can really for health reasons
No, it's just it's not you know once you get over
Fuck you
Only 24 yeah, thanks
John, I'm really well, I've already had fun working with you. I'm really looking forward to
What's coming and working with you? I hope certainly that you when you will remain
Genetic self by being critical of our company and you know what we've already discussed a lot about the site
You know stuff that you know, I can't find anything wrong with the company
I love that you know the funny thing is is that you know the one of the other reasons that you know the company is cool
And people that don't realize how big this company actually is but you really have put together a lot of really cool guys
There's a lot of people there. They're all enthusiastic. They're all you know
Reminds me of like you went into magazines once in a while where it's a computer magazine
And there's like people running the magazine that don't like computing
I'm sorry to God and it's like what are you thinking
And because you know if you work for a week for example you have to know how to fly a plane
Yeah, that would be kind of a good idea
Yeah, because you don't want people writing about aviation and they don't even know how to fly a plane
So that they'd be a night that but you should be an enthusiast which is the cool thing
And that's what you should be with a computer magazine
But everybody at Pod Show is an enthusiast to an extreme and most of them have like I mean a lot of these guys
You're talking to them and it's like they got two or three or five
Podcasts that they do themselves on all kinds of weird stuff. It's a pretty pretty amazing group of guys
Yeah, I think well and most people would say is why do you know those people?
And by the way, I shouldn't say guys guys and girls. Oh, yes for sure for sure
I should even say gals, you know, okay
I mean, I live in the Berkeley area. What can I say? I can't have to be careful with my language. That's quite all right
I got I'm fried man. I'm sorry. I just really wanted to talk to you
Because you know the the press release came out and and and and if anyway, you know
I'd love to do some kind of show that is specifically
Hey, Han
I'm interviewing the sabonth there's sabons could you just close my door for a second?
Could you just close my door for a second, please?
Like she slammed it. I don't think she'll screw in
Nicely I thought
Fuck was I gonna say you're talking about your you're glad to see on board. Yeah, exactly. No, but I really am and and I hope you you know continue to
You know to be you and help us with all these other areas and I'd like to be a part of the technology
Potcho tech channel with some kind of show somehow
Hey, let's we should do some sort of some talk shows or something. I don't want to you and I just talk and just I don't know that would be like to it
I'm sorry. We can't do that
Actually wouldn't be like to it because the twit no it wouldn't be different because you're different than it would be
Twit and twot is what it would be. They'll be kind of fun. That's watch show the twatch
Okay
Oh
We what we need to what you need get some I don't know. We'll come up with something
I'm sure because there's you know because we have so much time on our hands
Well, of course the thing that I hate I hate this with the passion and you know Ron and I were in Germany and kind of had our
Our backstone and everyone and you're right everyone of course is extremely enthusiastic
But you know, so there's like nothing to go to so we have the news is out and you know
There's this press release which is about all we have which of course. It's great someone's thinking we're getting the pieces working together
But you know we haven't you know gotten the you know the the page up yet for a site
You want to tell them tell everyone just what what's gonna happen next and what time frame you think
Yeah, I think next week
We've got the page design. I've got the show kind of figured out
Next week we should start having a show on and unfortunately the U.S. we have a holiday on Monday
We have these holidays once in a while. It's a bank holiday in the UK as well interestingly
You know really what what what what is the holiday there? I don't know it's well
It's strange here, you know, they don't always tell you what the holiday is it's just a bank holiday by the way
And the UK and Canada is boxing day for years and years
I can't say why did they celebrate boxing in those countries for just to take a holiday for boxing?
I don't even have that any good boxers. You're kidding me, right, right? You don't really know that
For years. I was thinking they don't get any good boxers in these countries. Why are they celebrating boxing day?
I haven't so such a hard time believing that
And so I find out it's like boxing day for thinking box stuff. I'll be gonna take back
I mean what kind of a holiday is that oh, man
Anyway, yeah, no, that is the day after Christmas here
Right, yeah, so day you take your box stuff up and take it back believe me. So
Anyway, the so we're gonna have a we'll have the thing going. I want people to subscribe to it
It is it'd be perfect for the drive the daily drive to work. You'll get the tech news the with you know the
kind with snide comments
Probably I can just say hey
I live we got a new format
It's
What is angry guy?
Tech news snide comments
Yeah, well, there'll be more than that but the
It'll develop to because I'm not gonna you know, I'm gonna
I'm gonna develop the thing so it changes
It morphs into whatever people really want it to be but it's gonna be you know, it'll be it'll be valuable for anyone
In fact, I mean we have that the tag line is you know, probably the most important five minutes of your life
I like that. I do like that. It could be
The channel concept which I don't want to try even attempt to explain because it's like explaining Tvo and when you just use it
You get it
How are you what are you gonna do with that? I mean what would you know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna set up. I'm gonna set up a
Manish of them. I set up five channels. I've been exploring what to put in them
And the channel concept that Potcho which is another reason I thought it would be worthwhile
Working for you guys is really some note of genius in terms of commercializing
the usage of this technology for people who drive you know who use
MP3 players or or iPods or whatever and they like to do these RSS downloads with the audio attached
The idea with the channel is that you can take a
A series of shows and wrap them in one RSS feed
So the user can just click on that one thing and then they get this entire
Channel full of material and
Which could be you know two shows ten shows a hundred shows. I mean obviously you don't want that many but
You know, I'm thinking in terms of like ten or twenty maybe and what I want to do is I want to set up
Chancellor people who you know they're more a little more specializing just listening to the news
Most of these channels by the way will have my news cast because it seems silly not to
But I want to put together like a kind of a light channel of shows that people like to listen to that aren't really you know
They're they're the longer format shows like
Your show for example daily source code. Mm-hmm. It's a longer format now light show that people like to listen to it's very entertaining
You know it would be geek briefs would be in there probably she might actually get in a couple spots and and and some of these other shows some other vendors
That have useful shows that are long formats
There'd be a kind of just a pure new show that has nothing but just all the new shows stacked up there'd be the one
I'm having the most difficulty with is the IT channel, which is nothing but IT shows literally
Shows done by IT professionals for IT people. There's not going to be the most interesting of the group
But I can suspect that people that are in IT that have to commute to work will listen to this thing
Because that's you know, you want to know what the everyone's doing then I want to my favorite one
And now I do a gaming channel and then I would the one that I you know, I think that might some people might kind of get into
Is kind of the thorax favorites, which is which is not going to be just computer stuff. It's going to be what I think
You know, there's going to be some there might be a national geographic podcast or maybe
Local podcast okay and tucky and but you know, I'd be like my news of course and then may I might have John Madden's
Yeah, of course John Madden's
KCBA John Madden's got this great show. He does locally on the radio that they podcasted I think and I would put that in there for sure
Because it's really funny and people who don't like sports by the way
I won't like this channel because I'm kind of a sports nut as you discover when my phone accidentally called you
And I'm driving around when you're listening to that room guy was that what it was?
Jim Rome is the best yeah because yeah, you but phone me like three times today and hey, you know what it was I
Sitting on the other thing is bouncing around on the seat and it called you and then you caught me listening to Jim
Rome or one of the other sports talk. It's embarrassing
To the fact that I listen to this stuff
But I tell you the truth Jim Rome to me is one of the greatest broadcasters that we've seen in this country for decades
And for a lot of different reasons it's not just because he's he's very entertaining
He has a style that's very distinctive
He has a following. He doesn't you know, you don't seem at Hollywood parties
He just does his own thing. He's got his own little world around him and he does this so well
He's of course making millions of dollars, but
It's like really you know when I first turned my thought it was like, who what? Who is this maniac?
This is the weirdest shot I've ever heard because he's actually developed his own language. Is he but he's he's syndicated?
He's on one of those huge radio syndication systems. Okay
John John oh the premier
Radio network is that what it is. Yeah, one day we'll go get him
Hey, you know what he needs to be podcasting more because right now they have you could pick up some of his material
But he he charges and it's a it's an awkward situation. It's not the same
Yeah, he'd be ideal actually his show is this is just but anyways good drive time stuff for me
But although I'm gonna probably get that my card doesn't have that cool connection where you can
Jack in your iPod
Yeah, I had a new car. I got a new car. Well now you're working for pod show boy. We got we got a we got a lot three years
I'll be able to get a new car
On on layaway
All right, John man, that was a that was actually a longer chat that I intended but I really appreciated
I'm a talkative guy now, but that's groovy man, so we'll look forward some time next week and
You know anytime we can you know shoot the breeze on on my show
You could do this is a two-parter
Fuck that you know I don't like that
You know you're a dick
Seriously John it's gonna be a lot of fun for sure. All right, I hope to see you out here soon when you get out of
Really get out to the coast again. Yeah out of out of Germany and and like you do Germany is gonna love you by the way
Doc, yeah, I glass I glass couldn't talk that's a good yeah couldn't talk head walk
All right, John. I'll see you around the office and we'll talk later. I use okay. Thanks
There you go
John C
Devorac
So I hope most of the initial questions were answered
I think it's very interesting to see this response and
So it looks like
Next week everything's gonna start kicking off. All right. I just I have to go to bed. I'm sorry. I just I have no more
Happening to me a moody
Data source code dot com is where you can find uh, it was not a lot of links of course to the the song today. Oh
And if you
Thought that discussion between John and I was boring
But I didn't help you completely fall asleep. Try a tyrant opn
Who sponsored angb's unwind online dot patcho dot com
Adam at patcho dot com if you want to send it any comments and
I will be looking forward to talking to you tomorrow
Another maximum music football Friday
See you then