Welcome ladies and gentlemen to the DSC 5773, I'm your pilot Steve and please pay attention
to the flight attendants in the aisle at the head of the plane. Please notice that the seat
belt sign is on remain strapped in your seat until the light goes off. Look around you
and locate the nearest exit should there be an emergency. Remember not to fast forward through
any of the good parts and pay attention to all jingles. Smoking is not permitted in the plane
until after you hear the lighter clicks at the end of the show. If the plane should happen to
start to descend at a very rapid rate, please bend over, kiss your ass could buy and say it's
Fubar Friday. Thank you for flying the DSC 5773.
Hey this is Paul Durham from the Band Black Lab. In the aftermath of the enormous success of
bum rush the charts, the chairman and heads of NR of every major label called and offered me a
record deal. Come back to the fold they said we want to make you famous. Okay I said I'll do it.
I'll sell my soul for a third time. I'll give up creative control and any hope of a long-term
career as a musician. There's only one thing I ask. What they said will give you anything.
Chairman and heads of NR set your music free. Let hardcasters from around the world play the
songs you control. Let them remind us of great music we've forgotten about and turn us on to new
stuff that is actually good. So that we may go out and buy it for ourselves. Stop acting like
morons thinking that podcasting is somehow going to hurt sales. Stop strangling the golden goose
and let us all have eggs. No they shouted never are they screamed as each one of them in turn
slammed down the phone. So here I am back with the rest of you crouching in my fox hole as the
revolution rages around us. But I have one thing to say to you cigar chambers. I've got my microphone
and my guitar. I've got my computer and my internet connection. I'm coming for you and I'm out for blood.
Good you said the bad my way. I'm following this notion. It's making all things clear.
I find it found my place and you're not here. But you got the last love.
But you got the last love for this broken heart today.
Everything gets longer this way. We are only half of what we've made.
You're shallow west the ocean. It's empty as my field. I find it got too far in your
heart. But you got the last love. You got the last love. You got the last love for this broken heart today.
It always ends in the letter. It always leaves me dry. No time to love. No time to say goodbye.
But you got the last love. You got the last love for this broken heart today.
But you got the last love. You got the last love. You got the last love for this broken heart today.
Because nothing's quite as simple as you say.
Everybody how you doing. Welcome to Fubar Friday from a very wet afloan suburb of Surrey
known as Gilford. It's the west side of Gtown from the curry manner. It is your Delta Sierra
Charlie and indeed no lady Patricia. But not because she didn't agree to come on the show today.
Because I asked her actually not to come on. Next week as you know I'm traveling to San Francisco. I'm
actually traveling on Monday for a change. I got some stuff to do on Sunday. And on Saturday,
the lady P and I will create a show which will air on Monday. So if you if you're disappointed,
please bear with me because we've got a great show lined up for you.
This is story about a man. By the way, I was such a dick.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
That's fine, man.
Stuff.
RSS feed. Is that sound right? Yeah, on this, it said this very frequency, this very RSS feed. Hey, oh my goodness.
Got so much to talk about. No one, absolutely no one responded that I saw to my quest for a decision I had to make,
whether to buy a new digital transmitter receiver pair for viewing television in the kitchen or to do it
through a sling block, sling box. I just went out and I got one. Let me tell you, this was a very
interesting experience. I've been reading about the sling box, never really had any need for it. I didn't
know that it actually is marketed as a device to watch television inside your home in different
locations. I thought it was intended purely to stream outside your home, which it does do. I haven't tested
it actually, but it is configured and set up. And I think the router is all set up properly as well.
But it was pretty cool. I went to PC World here in Gilford. I pulled one off the rack and I was
looking to find out if it would connect wirelessly to anything within the home, which of course would be
absolutely perfect. I think the messaging on the outside of the box is not very clear. It definitely
did not say whether, it says, network requirements wired or wireless. I mean, not until you
actually open the box, do you figure out that you need to plug a hard wire into this thing that
goes into your router? I was already prepared for it because I got two of those power line
Ethernet adapters. You just plug into the wall and you plug one into your router and into the wall
and then the other one you can plug in anywhere in the house. That works really well. So I was
prepared for that. And I had those. I had a different use form if I wouldn't need them. But the whole
experience of opening the sling box, you know, you see the picture and it looks like this
kind of like a titanium dipped Hershey bar. You know, it looks really, really sexy and it has those
three like modules that are all placed in the egg carton fashion together and you just really feel
good about it and you open it up and it's like this really cheap plastic thing. Very disappointing
experience. They could learn a lot from Apple. It was no porn. It was like a downer, man. Like a
way downer when it comes to gadget porn. It doesn't matter because the device works as advertised
and it's fantastic. So I was able to throw out the extra TV from the kitchen, downloaded the
Mac software for Patricia's eye Mac, it works. It's amazing. It is so good. Now, the whole idea
of being able to get up from the living room and walk into the kitchen and not miss anything while
the show is, well, whatever is running is running. It gets a little bit obviscated by the fact that
there's a 8 to 10 second delay between what you're seeing live and what is actually being received
on the receiving computer inside the home. Well, that is, if you're going from living room to kitchen,
it's okay, but if you go to kitchen from from kitchen to living room, you're bound to miss
10 seconds of very valuable airtime. We'll get used to that and I can't wait to try it from San Francisco
see if I can access the box from outside the home network. In fact, I like it so much. I'm going
to get one for San Francisco, so I could watch TV here. It's absolutely phenomenal. Great piece
of technology. Very, very bad on the porn factor, but man, oh man, oh man. Let me see,
for our food bar Friday, I got something in from Virgin Atlantic. Oh, I love it when companies
do this. Dear Adam, Hollywood has the Oscars. Britain has the BAFTAs. Virgin Atlantic has heroes.
Hmm. Our heroes program is the reward and recognition scheme for outstanding
Virgin Atlantic team members and it's up to you to nominate them. I love doing this. When companies
do this, I always participate. I hate surveys. I don't participate in any feedback for, you know,
they, I think Virgin Atlantic has figured out how to make me feel good and then I'm a good customer.
They have not disappointed ever. So I'd like to, I'd like to give back, check this out.
The heroes program gives you a chance to single out the Virgin Atlantic team member who has gone
above and beyond the proverbial call of duty to make your journey with us absolutely fantastic.
After all, as a flank club goal member, you'll fly with us. You fly with us more than anyone,
so you know us better than everyone, blah, blah, blah. If your hero is chosen as a finalist,
they will be in, they will be in with a chance. Kind of being, which is that. If your hero is chosen
as a finalist, they will be in with a chance of winning £1,000 and could go on to win the superhero
award of £10,000. Plus, you and a guest will be invited to accompany them to the glittering
awards night in London this summer. Oh, yes. Okay. I think we should have like a secret word or something.
And on my next trip, my round trip. Excuse me, this has to be in by April 12. Yeah, no problem.
So the flight over and the flight back, we should have something that if any Virgin Atlantic
person says that word or does something in particular, um, that we've already pre-decided,
then they'll get my vote as a finalist for the Virgin Atlantic Heroes 2007. Okay. So post your
comments at the dailysourcecode.com because I'll need that for from Monday. All right. And then I'll
make sure the lady P and I talk about it on, uh, on Monday as well, which of course will be recorded
Saturday. Oh, boy, I'm getting confused already. Paul Rogolinski. Hey, Adam, you really should get paid
by Nokia. I just got my N800 yesterday. Mostly because you've pointed out so many times on your show,
looking forward to develop some apps, seems like a solid Debbie and platform. Mm-hmm.
Linux porn. Keep up the great work. And maybe you could mention Scott's ancestor,
Rush the Charts thing tomorrow on football. His deadline is April the first. Yeah, absolutely.
We had bum rush the charts, which was, well, you heard Paul Durham talk all about at the opening of the
show. And Scott Singler is really going to go into make quite a mark. I think he has a much better chart
to deal with the Amazon chart. I know he has so many people who are, uh, including his work that they're
going to go and buy this book, the minute it hits. And, uh, yeah, we got a problem over that.
Over the course of 19 weeks, one monster filled bloody audio book grew to terrifying audience of
30,000 listeners in the process. He became the number one literary show on iTunes and every other
podcast chart on April 1st. Scott Singler's thrilling horror novel, ancestor, closet wane the print.
On April Fool's Day, the of your copy of ancestor at amazon.com, or visit Scott Singler.net.
Or get your ass kicked by that guy with a ballsy voice.
American and Holland, and married to a Dutchie, too, is the subject of this email. Adam says,
Gina, hey, there. I recently added your podcast to my daily car commute from all me at a
to hoof door. She lives in the Netherlands. This is a new listener. I love talking about listeners
who don't have podcasts. Quick bit about me. I found your podcast since it's kind of neat. I'm an
American married to a Dutchie. I moved from Holland from my hobby two years ago. This June,
I was listening to one of my normal podcasts to it this week in tech. When you were a guest
or so ago, see how this works. You see how it works. She listened to a whole other show.
Didn't even know I existed or had forgotten about me. And then found my show. I love that.
He was funny because I was in my living room in almyra and hubby jumps in and says, hey,
that's Adam. He's Dutch. I didn't even realize you were the same dude. I knew from MTV.
So I said, no, he isn't Dutch and Google it to prove him. He told me stories about when you
lived here. You married a Dutchie also. You were fluent in Dutch, which is why he assumed
you were Dutch. So this is how I found your podcast. Now I listen daily. You're in my every morning
podcast list for my fun, two-hour drive to Hofdorf. Oh, yeah, traffic and Holland blows chunks.
PS, how the hell did you learn this language? Six months of private lessons. And it's still
freaking insanity to me. Thank God, I'm a web designer. Everything is English for me. Yeah,
well, my parents. At the time, I hated them for it. They threw me into Dutch school. Did I
ever tell you this story that we were when we moved in 72, we moved to the Netherlands? And the
three of us kids, myself, my two sisters went to the International School of Amsterdam, which at the
time was located in Osdorf. And we had a vacation, like a weeks vacation. And Sunday night they
they said, hey, kids come sitting in the kitchen here. We're going to talk for a second. Guess
what you guys are doing tomorrow. We had a whole week off so we're excited to say, what, what, what?
You're going to Dutch school. I spoke like three words of Dutch, two of which were fish and poop.
It was traumatizing. But in hindsight, and I don't think they did it because they couldn't
afford the International School anymore. That's why they did it. But in hindsight, fantastic. I'm
so happy. And I thanked them for that. Even if it maybe wasn't even intended. I'm very happy
that I had an international education. All right, blah, blah, keep up the fun podcast. Even
cooler when you mention Holland since I since I'm lost, I'm a lost American here. And it
makes me feel more at home. PPPs. Thanks for this for the fun and song in today's podcast. I bought
the album from under cover, keep, ah, take to. I bought the album from undercover hippie tonight,
not my normal style, but it's a fun sound. You know, Gina, I know a way, I know it'll make you feel
better. I really do. It's not that hard. It starts off with a naked picture. Adam and pochio.com.
They don't sell out 400 concerts a year.
They don't have the entire world in length of them. They are all independent, all about the music.
I heard it on a podcast. Oh, yes, it's true. I'm going to quit my day chat. Stop laughing. This is just
down my mind. Work. We are in the midst of massive heat.
Throughout this past week, we've been talking about a number of things. One of them is
regulars, regular callers, and the rest of the world. And of course, I've said many a
time that the rest of the world are the regular callers. 80% of the show is put together by
the audience. One of our regular callers, who always has something interesting, just no,
about half of what he has to say is interesting, is a Charles the Drunken Londoner,
which is kind of a misnomer at this point because it's been a while since Charles was
called in completely hammered. Adam, hi, it's Charles. Yeah, good on your James.
People that produce regularly and get played every now and again, we will appreciate the fact that
Adam, I don't want to say a sentence, but certainly picks and chooses just the best bits
that are interesting, it's true. His listeners and his audience, I appreciate that, as I'm sure
so does everyone. Programmer seems to be getting the message. So yeah, different James, I'm with you
on that one. I'd be able to show Adam is becoming a inventor of the jingle to jingle
all the all jingles from flower and the jett and the suggests to me, which are they are fabulous.
I did like that 911 and I have to say, no, I like you, I think you're great, do it, keep going,
you know, what's the word you use? Adam, Contrary and or Contrary views. They make for a much
more interesting show. That's a slightly different note, I just like to urge everyone to head on
over to PWB digital slots and listen to his latest podcast. It is a really good episode in my opinion
and it really helps us all to recognize what's really going on in the world and what's really
important. So, I think I'll have to everyone out there fixed soon. Bye.
Yo, Charles, big up to you, man. Yeah, I told you guys the listen to that show before I'd actually
listen to it because I know that PWB stuff is always quality, but of course it's about the
passing of his dad. Oh, man. Oh, ho, ho. He want to go on a podcast emotional rollercoaster ride
and then that is the show for you. You definitely have to listen to it. Let's see what's going on
with those 15, 15 soldiers in Iran, home on a second. I've got to keep my eye in this
comic strip blogger sent me a pretty, like I almost like, hey dude, we've got to use the power
of podcasting to stop this because a suitcase or a clairvoyant, I guess. Told him that if something
wasn't done about it, there would be nuclear war. And it looks like a second sailor has a
apologize to Iran. I guess that's what they're looking for, huh? Okay, apologize and move on already.
Sorry for the confusion. Oh, boy. Now, this could get ugly. That's for sure.
Hey, let me see. Yeah. So, just briefly back to what Charles is saying about
callers regular calls. I got to tell you, I love it when people are different because that's always
interesting to me. You know, the look at comic strip blogger who has been labeled by many as a
stalker, really called a stalker and all kinds of horrible things. And without a doubt, he has an
interesting way of communicating. But I think he's smart and nylon who are also sometimes
contrary, and yes, indeed, sometimes abrasive, he's got to be smart. I've got an email from someone
about nylon that the New Yorker living in London. Let me see, who is this email from Devon?
He had something here to say about, well, maybe it's the email is too long.
All right, but he doesn't like nylon. I love it. I love you guys. In fact, you know, if Howard
Stern is his hero of the stupid, then I am the sultan of the Savans my friends.
Here's another one of the Charlie Savans. He is a prolific programmer and as you know, I'm trying to get
a prolific programmer, a conquester blogger, and nylon all together on a conference call have not yet
heard back from nylon. CSB coming up at first indeed, the prolific programmer. I didn't
program her here from San Francisco for things. First off, it's me girlfriend birthday tomorrow.
I appreciate you wishing to have a birthday on Fubar Friday. Okay, prolific programmer. Happy birthday
to your girlfriend. And would you mind sending me a naked picture of her? Name is Keras low and she is
okay. Just send me a naked picture. On to Canada. Second, I also have a song for you to play for her.
I'm not quite sure of it. Oh, okay. Oh, I love playing songs. Okay. I didn't see a link in your email.
Let's go. Sneagly pod save. It's been on Friday dance party. It's on the Sunday. It's at the
year of HTTP. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Let me do it with you here. HTTP,
colon colon. Yeah, this is the prolific programmer. So I want to take his instructions
quite literally if you don't mind. Okay, next year. Hold on, second. Here we go.
Send. Send ID equals equals. Send 3015162. Second thing. Wait a minute. That was genius.
Genius. Oh, yes. I'm, oh, man. I'm going to go back and I can't do it. I'm going to go back.
I'm going to listen to that three more times. I'm going to type it in exactly prolific
program. I love you, man. You didn't send me a link to the song. No, no, no. You give me an
audio version of the link. Fantastic. I, uh, sure on the show, I think it's a lot better when
she's here because you play off each other, which is always nice. Yeah. My, uh, I think you,
I don't think I give in my, my bio at all. I am a British born Asian working in San Francisco
for a computer company. Hence, I call myself a programmer. For thing, get this here. There are a few
thoughts I have on this. Namely, discrimination is wrong. However, we all do it. And we do it to others.
Our reaction is different. Then when it's done to ones, we respect or love. Have a good day. Have a
weekend. Have a good weekend. Have a good day. Have a good weekend. Have a good day. Have a good weekend. Have a good
weekend. Cheers. I just had to be quiet for a second there. The satellite window slam shot right at the end.
Ah, you see what I mean? I love this. A prolific program of fantastic.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't know. It's Friday, man. I'm footballer. I really
tired. I don't know about you. But if you thought that was the only savant who was going to show
about how wrong you are my friend. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip.
Comic strip. Is this thing on? Is this thing on? Hello, Adam Kerry. Shouldn't we meet
up in the UK soon? Or is it not for you? Regarding me having session over a Skype with
prolific program and nylon, or surely my public Skype ID is the CSB. And I am available
after appointment at nine PM and 11 PM London time. Regarding paper post, I agree
with you. And as an example, I could mention Seth and Thief, who sold his company to AOL
and who attacks paper post constantly to get publicity. But at the same time, his bloggers
for years were being gripped. I think he's talking about Jason Calacanis. At the paper post thing
was just a little mention, please not to be turned to do a topic here. Go to the bloggers
rear if you want to talk about that. Guiding blogging code of conduct, just example, a blogging
code for Yahoo employees was signed also by certain retired Yahoo employees who defamed me
with lies and unchecked false accusations. Conclusion, everybody in blogosphere is a horror or a
covert core and hypocrisy is common. I'm happy that you see it too. Are we too
an anomaly in a sea of bullshit, an ocean of hypocrisy? Blogosphere? By the way,
Guid Patricia from Yam Yam, Apebam. Another one of our Charlie Savans, the infamous
comic strip blogger. Yeah. Yeah, of course. The things you're seeing online, which are only
going to get worse, which I hope we don't try and regulate. It's all a part of free speech and
it's going to get very, very ugly. And yes, I'm convinced that death and tears and sorrow and all
kinds of crap will occur. I will be the result of this open line of communication, this vast
open space where anything can be said, anything can be done. I've said it before. This is not
about laws. This is not about the government stepping in. This is not about a code of content. Well,
I have to say, code of conduct. It's an inkling of a piece of humanity. And I think that what has
to happen is we had, it has to get much, much worse than this before it can get any better. But
it will get better because I believe that that's the evolutionary way. Maybe more about that
in the final thought of the week. Adams has David Peterson. I just received my sample of
lively Colombian Folgers gourmet selections today as heard about on the Daily Source Code. That's
right. Folgers is sponsoring a number of programs across the Pod Show podcast network. And
you can, if you live in the US, get a free sample. When I heard you talk about it, I was curious
because my experience with the taste of Folgers has not been very positive. I woke up this morning
and decided to try the Folgers. It was the most bitter coffee I have ever tasted. Worst, the McDonald's
coffee. I couldn't taste much difference between the gourmet selections and the gourmet,
Supreme Dark Roast that I had previously tried. I couldn't finish one cup. I had to pour it out
and make a pot of my regular and freshly ground French roast coffee. Now you should tell me what
what brand that is. I know you can't control the quality of the coffee, but since you're pimping
the coffee, I figured you might want to know about my experience with it. I won't be purchasing any,
but I'm happy for you and podcasting in general that Pod Show has the sponsorship deal with them.
Love the show. I'm a folder, not a folder. Dave Peterson. Who has his own website at dipstick.com.
Damn. Wow, this is what an amazing piece of feedback from the man who has dipstick.com.
Dave, absolutely. I really appreciate the feedback. We don't get a lot of negative feedback from
the audience about any of the products mentioned here on the show, whether they're paid for or not.
But I have sent this on. It's always fun. It's Greg the Sales Weasel and I forward to the
note to him and I said, dude, I'll be talking about this on the show. Let's talk to fulgers.
You know, what do they do when someone says that they hate their coffee? They don't like the taste.
I mean, I believe, you know, maybe you're making it in a funky way. Or let's find out what this
regular freshly ground French roast coffee is. I'd really love to know. So thank you for that.
And I assure you, we will get back to you 100% for sure.
I get getting a lot of email, just to kind of wrap up the week here. A lot of email and a lot of
messages about the cost of SMS texting. Now, this all stems from the conversation about Twitter
being such a runaway success. And my belief that it is particularly a success in the United States,
because people are actually now understanding how cool SMS text messaging is. I have to say SMS
text messaging. Because otherwise, it's not clear what's going on in the state. Do you know that I
asked our producer of, well, Lisa Aaron to produce his textra. She produces a number of shows for
she's working on the plus or 24 hour live video channel. Oops. That's something I shouldn't have.
I, you know, she, she wanted me to review a show. And I said, well, just send me a, send me an SMS
text message. I even use the American vernacular that I thought would make help or understand.
And I didn't hear anything for like an hour. And then she called and said, have you seen it?
Yes, it was waiting for a text message from you. He says, well, I pinged you on Skype. It said,
no, no, no, through your phone. I don't know how to do that. And she is brilliantly smart.
It's just not cultural yet. So that's why I think Twitter is exploding in the U.S.
Anyway, so part of the downside of these SMS text messages and this plays into me walking around
with my singular one account in the U.S. and here in Europe and the cost of receiving phone calls,
the cost of data, which is really just outrageous. I pay about it. I think it's a two dollars
and a megabyte downloaded or use perhaps up and down while I'm roaming. I mean, that's, that's
atrocious. And I claim that that receiving text messages when you're in roaming mode across borders
cost money. I know it does because I've paid the bills.
I had them 20 films here just listening to your conversation about JSM roaming. And I've been in
industry for quite a while and I've never heard of anyone being charged or receiving SMS. The point
is with calls. You can choose where I'm not, you want to receive calls on your roaming. I'm
using the director of firing. And SMS is no way of stopping SMS is coming in easily. So you could get
hundreds of SMSes while you're roaming. There's no way of stopping them so you could get charged.
So it's basically no fair charge for them. So it's part of the most company doing charge for
receiving SMS while you're roaming abroad. Okay. There's an okay folder.
Oh, yes. Well, despite the fact that you're a fellow folder, I have to disagree with you. And I looked
it up on the singular business page at singular.com. And they have all kinds of packages. I went
through every single one of them and here's the best and cheapest and most cost-effective package.
There's no other packages that excludes this. International text messages. Send international
text messages from the US to friends, family co-workers around the world. There is no monthly
charge to send or received international text messages. It is just 20 cents to send a message
from the US to international destinations and just 15 cents to receive one.
With a singular media bundle or messaging package, receiving a text message will be applied
to your package allowance. It costs money. It costs money to receive. Wow. Is this also
if you're just in the states? From the US to send a message from the US to international cost 20 cents.
Is this cost you money just to receive it from international? Look, I'm telling you, it's a scam
and it's messed up, okay? And it costs money. It does. And if you're on prepay, oh man, you get totally ripped
off. You're out. I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out. You're out. Please don't
bang that gavel. You can try this cowbell out. Let's all give a nod to the hardest work in the
wrong year. It's Jersey, it's Iowa, it's Jersey, it's Iowa. Yo, what's up, Adam? It's Jersey, Todd.
The official musicologist of the Chacha. Boy, oh, boy, boy. If there have been some big things
going on at the PMN this week. But I've got somebody for you for Food War Friday. They're just
really, really stuck in my head. The woman's name is genocide. She's out of Texas. She is the
flower of the east as they put it on her website. And I don't know who did what to her, but this girl
is really, really pissed off. But it's a good thing that she took it out in the song. Check this out,
it's I've had enough by genocide on Food War Friday.
And her in your hands. Now what's left is what it is.
Don't accuse me of blame me. You're the one you lied to me. You're the one who used me. I won't
give you my sympathy. I'll let you drag me down with you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
I know you will never be true. I love you. I love you. I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
Sheala named girls you fought you. Now you fought me over you said it's me
you love the heart of you fought others. I want to drag me down with you I love
I know you will never be true