Yeah, everybody. It's the Daily Source Code. I'm Adam Curry and I'm trying out some new
software today for the, what the heck was called, the show. First of all, let me
dog into the studio here. Come on, Jess. Come on. Because the dog wants to go outside. So I had put out a request for
software that I could actually do these recordings with and plenty of suggestions. Nothing exactly what I wanted.
One, a couple for GarageBand, which I did like. I did try out. And you know, you really can't do the live mix and
starting stuff in.
in starting songs and maybe sound effects or audio bits.
If it's a timeline based recorder editor,
you really need just a couple of buttons
that you can assign to sound files.
You have to be able to hit them
and the output needs to be combined
with the microphone channel into an MP3 file.
What I did like about GarageBand though
was the great effects and the preset effects
that I could use on the microphone.
Really sound good as opposed to this crappy sound
that I have now.
And I'm gonna explain a second what I'm using.
Hold on a second.
Dogs back in, would like to leave.
explain. There's a, what I call the studio is a bar in one far end of the house and there's a
door open here that goes out into the back patio and into the grounds and Jesse, our biggest dog,
knows that that's a quick way out. All right, other suggestions were Audion,
which again, you know, you can, that'll let you record an MP3 mix down, a playlist of songs
mixed together, which you could talk over, which isn't quite what I'm looking for. Acoustica,
which is something that Dave posts on his site as a recommendation. Again, that's not what you're
looking for when we're doing this kind of stuff. That's a timeline based recorder and editor,
although great for pre-recording stuff and it's not really good for the live environment.
And then it hit me that really, there's so many different
Um
Um...
applications that I use for different real-for-sound.
I may use iTunes for one reason, perhaps for some of the digital signal processing features.
I may just use a quick time player and other instances.
I can create the mix on my speakers almost, because I have a program that will record
my voice.
Maybe what I'm looking for is just a very small application that will actually record
a mic in channel or line in channel, a microphone channel, and then anything else that's on
the speakers.
Anything.
There's got to be a way to hook into that somehow and the poor audio or whatever it
is on the Macintosh.
Anyway, I finally wound up using Studio 365 Live.
I'm going to put a screenshot of it on my web log at live.curry.com.
hum because that interface really shows what I'm talking about and it's really really
simple. There's a playlist window where you can put songs that will play in order or
that's where I just store the song of the day. There's two what they call cart machines
and you can load up an mp3 in that and hit a button that starts immediately and then
there's a mic channel that you click on or off and you can set your levels and that's
basically it. The downside here is that I'm also pooping out 64 kilobits a second of
whatever to live 365 server which they've already sent over 2 megabytes but it does
let you record a copy of the output that you're sending up to their server as an mp3
on your desktop. So that's how I'm doing it today and that's what gives me the opportunity
to play the song of the day which is something that's just perfect for a Sunday afternoon here
in Belgium. It's sunny and the temperature's nice.
cool maybe for the summer but it just kind of gives you this type of vibe. You just want
to hear a little bit of the small things.
I'm gonna bring your sides to rest my eyes and shade to bring. I'm gonna dream in space.
To each of you, go back, let's play. What did you do there? What did you feel there?
It's true, it's not the key is there. It's hard to but it's hard, it's hard to but it's hard
to but it's hard to but it's hard to but it's hard to but it's hard to but it's hard to but it's hard
I tell you what I do, I like to go there, I'll review you, you can miss out school, what's that?
Why go to learn the world of that world?
It's all too beautiful to be playing, but you know my mind, it's not enough for me to play slow about my mind.
They all corrupt, you're not the one which my center path is free.
It's all too beautiful, it's all too beautiful, it's all too beautiful, it's all too beautiful.
It's all too beautiful, it's all too beautiful, it's all too beautiful.
Well it's all too beautiful. It's your good part. Small faces. Look at this. Apparently,
the playlist is on repeat. Okay, so again, it's all about the interface in this case,
and a couple of other items in the news. I just want to talk about briefly. One is that
I woke up this morning and the Dutch teletext, which is kind of like a newspaper on your
TV. It's kind of like web pages. They all have a number and the signal is sent along
with the television signal and it's decoded. So you can actually just read text on your
television, hence the name teletext, that in Arumaita in Iraq, which is in the southwestern
region where the Dutch troops are stationed.
that last night one soldier was killed, four were seriously wounded.
And the Folkskrant, which is one of the larger newspapers here,
the very left wing, was the only one online with the story,
see around 8 o'clock this morning.
And for hours, and I haven't checked just recently now,
it's at three in the afternoon, you know, there was nothing on CNN.com
or AP or Reuters, there was just nothing about it.
And as a part of the coalition, you know, whether I agree with us being there or not,
that sucked, you know, it's like, hey, come on, aren't we a part of the whole global group here or what?
And it also really hit home because I've been to that camp where this happened.
So, and I do remember of all the trips we took, we all collectively actually felt that we were
most unsafe there and we actually did most of the walking there at the time and crossed
a platoon bridge. I believe that was all in out of my town. And yeah, it was kind of shocking.
It brings it all back. And what's going on in Texas? The sixth person this year to die from the
flesh-eating bacteria. This is, you know, this is worrisome. See, this guy was pretty young too.
I think I was like 52 years old. Let me see. Of course now I almost have no bandwidth left to
surf to stuff because I'm sending my signal up to a live 365. But,
Bye.
Okay, never mind that, but another case of this weird flesh-eating bacteria, apparently
this guy, he was, I think it was a 52 when he was a doctor.
He cut himself boating and it got infected, they had to amputate the knee, blow the knee,
and he died.
The bacteria ate him up.
I wouldn't mind knowing a little bit more about that and how to avoid it.
And finally I released the iPod or script today, released being a big word.
But I got so fed up with just having this, I lost my scripts and recompiled or compiled
them incorrectly so I couldn't get the real source back.
So I'd step back to a couple versions ago which I'd saved.
I've gotten much better at that now and I reconstruct what I had done and of course
the script came out even better and it's working really nicely.
I figured alright now is the time to get it out there.
People look at it so you can understand.
What is I've been talking about?
How I see a totally open market?
Because I'm on a Mac, I did it all on a Mac, it works on a Mac, but the iPod is also kind
of ours, right?
It's not that we let them use it now.
But just by connecting all these dots, I think it's really interesting where you fire
the script up and it does all the work for you.
All you have to know about as someone who has an iPod and a Mac is that you receive new
audio shows automatically, you didn't have to do anything, no downloading, no transferring,
just put your iPod in the dock and you're good to go.
And there's a million different things that I could have done better in the script and
it's not even really ready to run if you don't know what you're doing in Apple Script.
You have to change the folder basically where you want all the file stored.
Download with caution is a link to it on my on my web log and
Tomorrow it's back to work again two more weeks of doing the morning show up until August 31st, and then
That's it. I'll be a free man
And looking forward to it, but we also have a lot of great guests this this week and I'm sure I'll learn a lot as I
chat with them every morning from 6 to 9 a.m. And
I'll be talking to you guys
Probably right after each show every day. I was thinking maybe I'm recording him on my commute back to Belgium
Although doing all that with a laptop in the car is a
challenging again
Something to look at man, maybe I should I maybe I should do one of these while I'm flying home
All right
That's it for today. I'm going to leave you see how long I've been at this 13 minutes yet long enough
I want to get I actually wanted to play the FCC song
was it said Eric Idyllith?
think from Monty Python because I don't know if everyone's heard that or not.
But I'll just have to do that tomorrow.
So this was my source code for Sunday, August 15, 2004.
You can reach me at adam at curry.com and my web log address is live.kurry.com.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.