Well, good morning, everybody, and welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Thank you very much for taking the time to download this mp3 file, or if some of you
may have received it automatically overnight as an enclosure in your aggregator.
In that case, thanks for subscribing.
The first, what I'd like to do is explain exactly what this is, what the Daily Source
Code is going to be, and well, as the name already suggests, it's something that's
going to be daily.
And I'd like to elaborate a little bit on the name Daily Source Code and what inspired
me to do this, where that came from.
By the way, I'm recording this in my car.
I'm on the way from our home in Belgium to Breda in the Netherlands.
Pick up new pair of glasses and contact with...
Oops.
It's a very important carriage.
I think I'm going to have to take another route.
Anyway, the Daily Source Code.
Let me back up here for a second.
I'm in a very narrow country lane and there's a horse and drawn carriage coming my way.
So you know what?
I'm going to just step over here and while I'm talking to you guys, I'll just wait for
this guy to pass.
When I was on vacation just recently in Sorrento, Italy, a couple of great things happened.
First of all, as if by magic, my wireless microphone, which I had lost for a few months,
I had the receiver apart but I just couldn't find the microphone part.
It was left over from our reality show that we taped over a year ago and I bought a couple
of really professional wireless mic kits.
It cost about $2,000 each.
So this is great, has great range and has a great sound.
It's just fantastic.
Professional stuff.
So I found that in a suitcase that had been lurking there apparently for a couple of months
I thought, well, alright, now I can finally start doing some audio blogging again.
But also, I'd loaded up my iPod.
You may or may not know that I have created a couple of scripts that
parse some RSS feeds with enclosures and automatically downloads
the MP3 files and adds them to my iTunes library and to my iPod.
I'm subscribed to the IT conversations feed.
And so I loaded that up.
Wave to this guy here. Sure, buddy. Happy to do it.
I loaded it up.
And on there was a couple of conferences or a couple of sessions
from the open source developers conference, I believe.
And I forgot who the speaker was.
Of course, I'll be sure to find out and link to him.
I was talking about what source code really is.
Is source code the actual script that runs that makes your computer
do something or the machine code that sits underneath all that?
Or is the source code perhaps?
actually the written explanation, the English explanation, not just funky English that a computer can interpret,
that explains what a program is supposed to do.
And I kind of subscribe to that idea that maybe even an RFC or just a functional description of,
okay, here's what I want this computer program to do, here's how it should behave.
That is the actual source code, it's the thought behind what eventually gets written in computer code or scripting language.
So if you think about a radio program or an audio program like this, you could, coincidentally, it's also called a program, right?
I guess you could say that this is the source code to me.
It's Adam's source code.
And every single day, a bit of me is filtered through to the web, and I write about what I'm thinking, what I've been reading.
You know, the links that I choose, the sites that I choose to link to, all that comes from a certain mindset on the website.
on any given day or moment, and that's what I call the source code.
So I figured if I have a web log and I've got all these links and stories, it might
be of some interest to some people to listen to the source code where all the ideas come
from.
The narrative that's running around in my head that I can't possibly write down.
other inspiration has been Dave Weiner, who started doing his morning coffee notes in
audio a while ago, and he did almost a daily version during the blogging of the Democratic
National Convention. And I'm addicted to it. I just love listening to his source code, basically.
And his latest coffee notes, which he actually pleaded people to listen to, he made a very
good point, which he and I have discussed before, and I think I've written about it
on the web as well, is that we're coming to a head between bloggers and journalists.
And it's all really about, on a second, in Belgium here we stop at the, we stop for
pedestrians. Sure, man.
recollect my thoughts here for a second.
I didn't want to hit anybody.
This is kind of tough.
Hold on, let me just spark up.
About a half hour drive-out.
I'm trying to make this 15 minutes
So at any rate
The big
Revelation really of the promise of the web which they've says I think correctly is not necessarily web logs
It's the fact that when you write something you can link to the source
so
If you interpreted something that someone wrote in a certain way and you have an opinion about it
You can write that and then kind of the unwritten rule is you link to the source and then people can
Form their own opinion and agree or disagree with you
that's one of the beauties of the web and
It doesn't work that way in traditional journalism because there is just no way to link in a radio show or
Television show or certainly not in a print publication. Well, I guess you could print a URL
But it's not quite the same it doesn't give your readers the same immediate access to check out the source
And I was listening to that and I was thinking, you know, wow, that's so true.
interview so many times, particularly in the Netherlands where my wife and I are very well
known and are written about all the time in, unfortunately, usually just a tabloid magazine.
Sometimes there's a serious article, but it really doesn't matter who's writing it or who
did the interview or what credentials the journalist comes with. Once you read it in print, it's never
100% what you intended or the way you said it and it often has, it's often opinionated by the
journalist, the writer, which is obviously okay, but there's no link to the source. The sources,
in that case, would be the conversation that we had for the interview, which could be anywhere
from half hour on the phone to, oh, I've had interviews, for instance, the big Playboy magazine
interview that takes two days, including a photo session. And that's still down to X number of words
that the journalist has allotted and the space that is available for the story.
It's a deer.
Thanks for watching!
So as I was thinking about that, there was something that I wanted to write about, which
I will, but again, this is just my daily source code, so I'm kind of distilling through the
thoughts right now.
I found something that was really useful.
I got so sick and tired of people just writing crap about us and wrong information and just
you know, they couldn't even get my age right most of the time.
Which usually was to my advantage.
I remember there was a, at a certain point, there was a big thing and someone wrote about
some supposed tax inquiry that was going on into my business affairs.
That was on the front page of several newspapers, another newspapers, you know, pick up the
story and it was on the news wires and all the actual errors would just pass from one
to the next, like the kids' game of telephone.
In fact, they usually got a little bit worse as one publication copied another.
And there was another large daily.
the newspaper that said, well, we really want to interview you and your wife about what's
going on and what's happening. I said, you know, that's fine. Are you guys going to
record the interview? It was for the newspaper. So a lot of, I'd say eight out of ten journalists
record their interviews on usually still on a cassette player, portable cassette player.
Some good little funky and have a new fast, new fangled gadgets like maybe a mini-disk,
but very few MP3 recorders out there. Really just more memo recording devices. And I said,
well, yeah, of course we're going to say, well, you know what, I'm going to record
our interview as well. And I'm going to reserve the right to publish that. And that was something
new. They agreed to it, which I think was absolutely the right thing to do. But they
were definitely a little bit freaked out about this new concept. But I mean, when you think
about it, hey, you know, you're recording me, what gives you the right to be the only one?
I mean, I should be able to record our conversation.
to. And I figured that that way if they start printing all kinds of factual, incorrect bits,
or maybe even if they just interpreted it incorrectly, I would be able to point to the
source, the source code of that interview and say, here you go. These guys clearly misunderstood
me or they took this out of context. And I have to add something that also happens is
I may have explained it poorly. I may have not communicated something that in a certain
way and that just came out wrong. That happens probably most frequently. One second buddy,
you want to move in here? Wow, doing this in the car really makes me a very nice and
courteous road user. Okay, this is the big trash truck. All right, Val. When the article
came out, by the way, and most generally, well, not most, but many journalists will give you
read the story before it's printed and change anything. And said, you know, they did ask
a couple follow up questions over the phone later. And the article was good. And I don't
believe there was, I mean, you can't really change any article sound the way you want
it to sound. But when it comes to the facts, these guys are really on their toes. They
had recorded themselves and it was two guys did the interview. And it came out very well.
And I think that part of that was because they knew that they really had to be on their
toes and get it right because I would publish the source code. I never actually did publish
the source code. I still have it. I felt that, you know, that just wasn't necessary. And
in fact, just the idea that I could worked. So when you think about it that way, which
is a great way that journalists and their sources can work together to make better to
better results. Something that everyone who is ever interviewed might want to consider
doing. So I just flipped that around and said, well, hold on a second.
I've got source code.
The source code is what's running around in my head.
And it's what I'm reading and what I'm linking to and what my thoughts are.
And I should make that available.
The only thing that's going to cost is what just bandwidth.
I mean, I have so much time to record stuff.
I mean, the car a lot.
But it's really no effort.
And of course, I'm going to...
And it gives me another opportunity to write a couple of nifty scripts that automates the
whole bit and does the ID3 tags and posts it to the right place and adds it to my RSS
feed as an enclosure.
So all of that, of course, is the fun part for me is a fledgling developer and program
or maybe I should say a scriptor.
But again, you get all the source code for me if you're interested in it and you don't
have to listen to it at all.
You won't really lose it.
So another reason that I'm doing this and I do plan on it being daily is that I like doing
audio or radio.
I've been doing a morning radio program.
for almost a full year as of August 31st. I've done it for a full year for
Radio Veronica in the Netherlands who asked me about a year ago this this time
if I could fill in for a month because their new morning guy could get of his
contract at a competing radio station and I can't even when they ask me
damn you know a month of getting up at 3.30 in the morning to do a show from 6 to 9
I don't know if I last three days the month went okay and I really got into it
and I was enjoying it and a morning show is it's kind of like this you know
you're talking to people you're helping them wake up and talking about topical
stuff it's just what's going on in the world what's going on in the
community which is the country of the Netherlands and I guess the community
is a global community so you can talk about all kinds of stuff and we had a
great time on that show I mean we took the ratings up sky-high actually in just
a couple of months by
taking the entire show on the road for a week and broadcast live from Camp Smitty and Asamawa, Iraq,
where the Dutch Marines were stationed.
And it was just a blast, you know.
And really it's just talking and playing a little bit of music.
So that ends.
Oh, well, so the morning guy for a number of personal reasons couldn't make it to the station,
and they kept saying, well, oh, the station management kept asking me to extend by another week
or another month.
I said, well, you know what, why don't we just say we'll do this for a whole year,
so I can actually build something and create something.
And that's my traffic alert. Check this out.
Very in navel, direct restoque es tar fesperz.
Travo glan zam rifin a tarpo d'imitin van ai dresou van vediam.
D'imitin van ai d'imitin van ai d'imitin.
Okay, that's a traffic report cut and it happens automatically on radio.
So we did it for a full year and that's winding down two more weeks.
So a little bit over.
Yeah, a little over two weeks and then I'll be a free man for September 1st and Patricia
and I and our daughter Christina who's coming 14 in just a week and a half. We decided that
we want to change. Part of it for health reasons. Trish was diagnosed with heart disease earlier
this year. Not as horrible perhaps as it sounds, but easy for me to say I guess. But it's not like
she has massive heart failure heart disease but she has to pay attention to her life and
what she's doing and is on medication and has to keep a very healthy lifestyle. And we want to
change to really get into that and so we've decided that we're going to move and we're going to move
out of the the Benalux and we've picked the United Kingdom. So we've put our our both houses up for
sale the one in Amsterdam which I affectionately call the
that's actually been on the market for about two and a half, almost three years now.
The market is completely dead in most of Europe, I guess, and certainly for big luxury
houses.
There's just, ah, there's no buyers really, unless of course you're willing to lower
your price, there's always a buyer for something if they're bottom-feeding.
We have the Castle in Belgium, which you've now put on the market.
I've already had a lot of interest for that, of course it was also really the set, if you
will, for our reality show.
So a lot of people are familiar with it and we're pretty hopeful that that'll move relatively
quickly.
Price to sell, as they say, great house for entertaining everybody.
And then we're off and then we're going to go to the UK.
We're not, well, we know the general area where we want to be, which will be south of
London, but within a reasonable car or train ride into the city.
And I
a totally open agenda. There's nothing that I have to do. Well, first I want to remember
what it's like to sleep in. You know, not have to set the alarm clock for 3.30 in the
morning. But just by saying we're going to make this change, already things have happened.
I'm getting all kinds of new, fresh, creative ideas. In addition, I've been asked to write
a book. All kinds of things are just coming together. So I'm really looking forward to
that in a way. It feels like I'm getting my freedom back. The one thing I do want to
try to do is to do these daily source code, audio, blog posts. And I guess it would be
since they're in English and to have an excellent advantage as a time difference goes. I'm going
to try and have these up by, I guess, 7 a.m. New York time. So if you're driving to work
and you have your download or automatically downloading the
The MP3's from the RSS feed.
You'll have something to listen to on your morning commute.
That probably really won't be possible until the first of September when I'm not doing
the morning show.
I just can't see getting, you know, being done on the morning show at night in the
morning, my time.
I'm usually not home before to, you know, only give me a very small window before,
well, actually that would already be too late.
That would be 8 a.m. New York time.
So these will probably be up around 9 or 10 a.m.
for the couple of weeks, first couple of weeks.
It also gives me a chance to figure out what I want to do with them.
One of the thoughts I had for instance was to do a song of the day.
Just get you going with one song that I think either fits in with the mood of the day
or the news of the day or the state of the world or state of affairs.
So I'm looking forward to that.
And again, it'll be what's going on in my mind.
What am I thinking about?
And by that time, I probably posted five to eight entries on my web blog.
And this will be the source code for that, what I was thinking about.
Which is pretty much on par for what I've posted today.
So that's the general idea.
Um...
As you can tell, there's a lot of talk of RSS and enclosures and MP3s in this first daily source code.
You may or may not have read that I've been programming a little bit, been working in user talk,
which is scripting language that comes with Frontier and Radio User Land,
and also been doing some work in Apple Script,
which allows you to script your Macintosh to do things automatically.
And a little bit of Python, although I haven't delved into that as much as I want to.
But I'm really working on a system that'll make this a little bit simpler when it comes to downloading stuff under your iPod.
I have a kind of a beta version running now, and I'm subscribed to a big file.
One is the IT conversations, which is great because almost every day there's a new interview or panel or session coming up.
down the pipe and it's right there my iPod in the morning on my hour-long commute to
the radio station. I just listen, you know, I didn't have to do anything, I didn't have
to click or wait, just pick up the iPod in the morning, throw the headphones on, the earphones
in and there's something there. Also, of course Dave's morning coffee notes is in there and
something called blog, was it audio digger or blog digger? I'd have to look that up, which
is an RSS 2.0 feed with audio enclosures. It comes from blog decks and it's just stuff
that it's scraped off of the web and there's about 5 to 10 new MP3s on that as well. It's
always very surprising, all kinds of wacky stuff that just kind of shows up. Total serendipity,
if you will. I have no idea what's going to show up. A lot of it's crap, someone's very,
very interesting. So I'll start pointing to that as well. So the script that I've created,
doesn't work the way it should yet and I already lost that source code by
accidentally compiling it in AppleScript and not knowing that you lose your source code.
But I'm going to start working on that again in in the also after September 1st
so that you know you don't have to really think about oh how am I going to do this
what do I need with the news aggregator how do I get
the mp3s from point A to point B now it should just be something as simple as
start this program up and you subscribe to your RSS feeds and it kind of does the rest
it just drops everything on your iPod and playlists and it even has a
little notification system so you know when something is new has been updated.
So I'm now just passing over the border into the Netherlands from Belgium. Thank you for accompanying me on the trip and
Tomorrow, I'll be back with another daily source code. Thanks for listening and see you tomorrow. Bye