It's the source code and it is Tuesday August 24th 2004 coming to you from Curry Castle
in Belgium which well this may be the last week it's actually called Curry Castle but
I have more news about that later and then apology right up front yesterday I signed
off on the show by saying we'll see you tomorrow on Wednesday in the middle of
the week hump day yeah right I guess I was extremely tired so tomorrow of course
will be Wednesday today was another well very busy day Patricia and I were
interviewed by Rina Ulamans who does a show here called Pulse which is I'm
trying to think when you compare it to well and it's they do a profile of us
and they do a profile of the guest every single week and so they're starting up
the first new
show of the new series September 4th and we're going to be in it. So he was there at the radio
show in the morning. The camera crew was there at quarter to six as I arrived at the studio.
And well, I can't wait to see how I actually look at that time in the morning.
Let's see just a brief rundown of stuff that's been going on. Oh, I see that Joe Ito obviously
caught the source code maybe a day or a couple days after I published it. I don't know if you
remember I mentioned that he had a video of the rocket car of death. The death-defying stunt that
I performed for ABC's Circus of the Stars looks like he doesn't have the video anymore and he's
actually put the word out to see if anyone still has it. I wish I wish I could find a copy of that.
It's one of my favorite quick times. I don't really have a theme for today's show other than
or just a couple of loose thoughts that I put together. One thing that I've that I noticed in the
I'm gonna open up a soda here.
Ahh... have a coconut smile.
Thanks for watching. I'll see you in the next video. Bye!
One thing I noticed with the development work that I've been doing, and I've had glasses
since I was 18 or 19.
I probably should have had them for a couple of years prior to that, but just never really
knew.
Currently negative to 7, 2.75, negative 2.0.
And I did through the radio station.
There's a big chain store of eyeglassware and contact lenses.
And they needed someone to do a promo for them that was going to last a week.
And I said, what the hell?
Why don't you give me a year's supply of contact lenses?
Because I've been wearing contact lenses for, oh man, the past 15 years probably.
And so they said, well, you know what?
We're so happy that you're going to do that for us.
We're going to give you the contact lenses.
We've got these new plasma-ized, whatever, extended wear.
We're going to give you a new pair of regular glasses and a pair of sunglasses as well, which
will be sunglasses cut to my street.
strength. And so, you know, we really went through, I normally have no patience for that.
I had the ugliest pair of glasses up until now in just a reserve pair, you know, from
bottom in 1972 that are about to come back into fashion. So it really took our time
and picked up some nice frames and really looked at the color of the glass for the sunglasses
and went through all the motions. So I've been wearing my new glasses. I haven't been
wearing the contact lenses for a couple weeks now. And what I've really noticed, because
I did put in some lenses the other day, is it makes a difference. Glasses just work better.
The technology of contact still hasn't made it as far as I'm concerned. Particularly
driving, I notice a big difference. And really, we've gone through all the motions of getting
just the right type of lenses for my eye and curvature and whatever. There's just no comparison.
And particularly when it comes to developing and doing stuff on the computer, the clarity
on the screen. It's also big big
different. And I wonder if anyone else had experienced that the difference between looking
at a screen and working and even driving with contact lenses or glasses. To me, big difference.
On the development front, you probably seen on my web blog, I've posted a list of the current
iPod or scripts that are starting to be a part of the iPod platform, which we seem to be somehow
cobbling together. I've been running David's Get Enclosures Pearl script. I've installed it as a
Cron script. I had to tweak out some stuff because it was looking for the feeds file and couldn't find
it the way I'd set up the Cron job. So fix that. And it's happily running twice a day. I set it up
for 3 a.m. So that's just before I get up. And so, you know, if anything needs to be downloaded,
be ready for me before I leave it for 30. And then it runs at 6 o'clock because I always, you know,
check after dinner.
And it's working great.
And it's giving me some ideas about how I can continue to update the Apple version of
the iPod or Apple script.
And let's see, got a piece of mail that I wanted to share with you.
Oh yeah, this is from Gordon, from Gordon.
And Gordon says he's been listening to the source code.
And he did send me an email earlier about the size of the audio files.
Of course, now that I've got a new recording system set up,
which I think the quality is way far superior to the Mac.
And the mic isn't crapping out.
And it's really a nice sound to it.
As he was complaining that he has to download the source code on a regular modem link,
and it takes an hour and 45 minutes.
And he says, well, he only finished just before I left my drive to work.
And he really would like me to down sample to my usual 64 kilobit sample rate instead of 160.
But I did want to talk about that for a second because I think this is exactly the point.
If we can set up these scripts like iPod or to run at night.
and just be reliable about it and just make sure that it happens.
It shouldn't matter if it takes an hour and 45 minutes
or five hours and 45 minutes as long as you sleep long enough
and have it set up to run when you're asleep.
I think that's the beauty of it.
And the way it shouldn't work,
and which is exactly why I like the Get Enclosures Pearl script,
is that you hit a button and wait for it to come in.
This has to be running automatically on your machine,
you have to forget about it.
That's why I like Pearl script and shell scripts
and Python scripts is because you don't have to launch
an application.
It's not sitting there in your face saying,
hi, I'm running, I don't want to forget about it.
I want another application, namely iTunes,
to pop up and say, hey, I got some new stuff.
Good morning, I'm ready for your drive.
So a little bit of pushback on that,
their dog now on the other hand.
Doug says that he's written,
he removed three lines of code
has rewritten Dave Sloshers getting closure.
and it works on Linux now.
So I hope he publishes that, looking forward to it.
Of course, I'll link to that, so we have yet another platform coming on board.
And what we need now, of course, is we need Windows.
And I have no idea how to do it.
I'm lost.
And of course, I can operate Windows.
I have a Windows machine here, but I have no idea if there's an equivalent to Apple script.
I think there's something called Windows Scripting Host or something like that.
Maybe we can use that, but then we still have our devices problem.
Sure, there's lots of iPods out there and lots of iTunes floating around.
But can we write for all different MP3 playing devices?
Or maybe we should write for iTunes and have, and hopefully iTunes will start syncing up with all these devices.
We really need to get to the point where people like Gordon don't have to think about how long it's downloading.
It takes 10 minutes or it takes several hours.
We'll get to that point.
We're going to get to the point where it's going to be video and there's all other kinds
of issues we have to look at.
But same thing, it's just going to take time to download.
And that's this time shifting, this magical bandwidth that we create while we're sleeping.
We use time that we wouldn't use otherwise than sleeping.
And so let's put that time to some good use.
So that's from the old email bag that of what is not span that comes in.
I told you, I don't know if I mentioned that we went to Christina's school, her new school,
I think I did about the Antwerp International School.
And we were looking at the list of stuff she has to have, what pens and pencils and agenda.
And of course you can buy that in the campus bookstore.
But they also require that each kid has a 128 megabyte USB plug-in drive.
And one of those keychain things you put in your pocket.
and they actually sell them on campus.
And this is a part of how the schooling system works here now
with the international school.
You take your work home on your USB portable drive.
I just blew me away.
I thought that was extremely cool.
So to wind up today, I want to play a song of the day
and it's an appropriate one,
because I think that we have sold the house.
We've gotten down to the final 50,000 on the price.
So that's just a matter of whose dick is bigger.
Of course it would be mine.
And with a little bit of luck, I'll have news
that we are going to start our move and get everything in motion
very, very soon.
And Patricia and I were just talking about it.
And of course we've walked through.
We have about 20 acres worth of land here and gardens.
And we are definitely going to miss this place, that's for sure.
And we've moved several times before and we like it and we like moving to new challenges and new things.
but we never quite had a nature resort like house like this one. If I could pick it up
and move it to the UK, I would in a heartbeat. So this is a song that I think anyone who's
ever moved and we probably all have it one point or another. You probably feel a bit
like this song describes.
I like the fire. You place the flowers in the vase that you bore today.
Steering at the fire, the flowers, flowers, my eyes. They go to the stars all night long.
Only for me.
To me now, you rest you have just my lips, everything. Such a cold, serious, cold, windows are illuminated by me.
Such a cold, serious, cold,
only for you.
A house is a very, very, very fine house with two cats in the yard.
I used to be so hot, how everything is easy to solve you.
Nooo
Yeah
Ah
House
It's a very very very very nice
Smithdoo cats in the yard
I used to be so hard
Now everything is easy cause of you
Oh
I'll light the fire
While you place the flowers in the vase
that you're born today.
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
the internet grade that you can download those songs and share them with friends and then get sued.
It's about a quarter to ten here in time for me to hit the hay because I still got to get up
the rest of the week at 3.30. So that's it. I will be back here tomorrow and let's see,
I don't have a very busy afternoon so hopefully be able to update a little more stuff on the
web blog. The writing of course you do have to take a little bit more time for that for a web
blog post I find and you get to put some emotion in there as well. So thanks for tuning in if you're
subscribing. Thank you very much for subscribing. You can reach me at adam at purry.com, see you
r-r-y or live l-i-v-e dot purry dot com and we'll be back tomorrow with another source code. See you then.
Bye.
♪♪♪
Oh, yes, it's gone.
Oh, no.
Thanks for watching!
you