Thanks for watching!
Bye.
Mmm.
♪♪♪♪
Adam Curry. Got a short source code for you today. Of course it's hectic here as always.
A church has a meeting she went to, so I got to take care of dinner. The animals haven't
been fed yet. And when I say animals, I mean animals, right? We've got goats and chickens
and swans and ducks and horses. Yeah, menagerie. And my mic is still really crappy. My question,
it's somehow the software is not able to handle something with this microphone because
it's only really the mic that craps out. The rest works fine. And the mic works fine on
other applications. So what can I say? Still looking for a great interface on something
to record my mp3s to if anyone has any ideas. Really could use it. Someone's got to make
it. Let's see what's going on. Today I met with the head honchos at the radio station.
As you know, I'm stopping for the first of September with the morning show. They really
want me to keep me involved with the station. And we came up with a plan with like a talk show.
format that also involves me and my guests flying into helicopter and continuing our
conversation, which I'm excited about because that's something you could do for radio, you
could do with television. And of course, I'll be able to blog a lot of that as I go along.
So I'll keep you updated as that moves. We're going to sleep on the idea for a couple of
days. Kind of freaky news about Blair Witch Project, about the cinematographer. Of course,
now I forgot to jot down his name. Hold on a second. He was the cinematographer of Blair
Witch Project, was filming for a new movie, doing aerial shots from an, I think it was
a single-engine airplane. And the plane went down. Four people on board, three, including
the pilot got out, but the guy didn't. And he went down 70 feet, divers, they recovered
him. He just never got out of the plane. I'll get you his name in a second. I linked to
it on my web log, which forces slow to load as I'm using this Studio 365 live.
application to record and simultaneously pushing out all these bits onto the internet that
no one's going to listen to. Got a great new show from IT conversations on my iPod through the
iPod or script. Two people I know, one I know better, Halley Comet. Halley Su. Known from Halley's
comment.com. I've met her at BloggerCon, the first BloggerCon and Joey Ito. And Halley apparently
is doing a series of shows where she's interviewing people and Joey is the first interview subject.
Joey I met very briefly at BloggerCon. And the format of the show is nice. It's kind of like
a trip down memory lane, which is cool because I recognize a lot of things that the Joey
witnessed and went through, etc. in the early days, really pre-internet, well pre-web certainly.
And I'd love to hear more. I'd love to hear more people talk about
the history. There's a couple people I think that have some great stories. I think it's
interesting and it's fun to listen to. Damn, this microphone is really crapping out. This
is not very good. Neil Fredricks, that's his name. 35 years old. Single engine Cessna.
So as I was listening to this show, and I'll talk more about the iPod or in a second,
Of course.
Chrissy!
Shut up!
Ah, hold on.
Dog.
Lumber dearly, but she's a Maltese. I'm supposed to live until about 12. She's 15 and she's deaf and she's blind
So actually me yelling at her hat makes no sense. Come here. Come on babe.
She can, yeah, she can recognize shape. Hello, baby. Hello, come here. Come here. Come here. It's okay. Yeah
Shit
Oh, go baby. Oh, oh you miss your mommy. See Patricia's off to work. It's kind of hectic today
She went to a meeting in Rotterdam about 45 minutes drive each way and so I'm
Taking care of the
Right and we all have to feed be fed. We all need to see we got the ducks the ponies the swans the chickens the goats all of them need food
Okay, let's see now. Hopefully that recorded as I walked away
I'll only know after I listen back to the recording.
one. So back to Halley in doing Joe Ito. In this particular interview, there was a piece
where he tells a story that he told me when I met him at Blodecon and for the 10 minutes
we spoke, he told me this story. And there's a little more to it than he mentions in the
interview, but I just want you to listen to it. So once again from IT Conversations, I've
linked to it on my blog. It's at itconversations.com. It's Joe Ito being interviewed by Halley
Su. The internet was eventually going to completely change the way that the media business worked.
Right. And that's when I shifted years away. So in the early 90s I moved a little bit from
just traditional media and music to computer graphics and virtual reality. And I was working
with my brother-in-law Scott Fisher then. But when I saw this Mac PPP and I saw packets
which networks are actually really working on a Macintosh, I decided that this is a client
to really shift and that I would have a lot more freedom in the internet because I had
felt so much better.
What do you call it?
Lack of freedom in physical media.
They're constrained.
And I started preaching this conversion thing sort of in the early 90s.
I was showing the Chairman of NHK, the Adam Curry's page where he had these videos and
stuff like that.
And this is sort of back when we, I think it was when we were using Go for an FTP and.
Okay.
So the video Joey is referring to is actually me in the circus of the stars on ABC television,
during the death defying rocket car of death, where I was up like 60 feet in the air in
a roller coaster car.
I roll down the track ends at the bottom, which launches me through an angry wall of fire.
And then I finally land on a bunch of mattresses and there's Hulk Hogan to welcome.
It was very bizarre.
And it was a clip that we cut to Rocket Man by Elton John for I think that was something
we broadcast on MTV.
I made a quick time out of it.
And I've got to tell you, I've lost the tape.
the original tape of that stunt and I really really really loved that video. I told Chris
and I told you it's impossible. Hold on. I told Joe you do this and he promised that he would send me
that he would send me a link or somewhere that I could get a hold of that video of that quick time
that original quick time because he says he still has it.
So, Joey, if you are listening, if you heard this, still waiting for the video, but quick
iPod or update.
So I've released beta 03, which now you don't have to do anything, no configuration.
It has four feeds currently in there, including IT conversations as default.
You can edit that script if you want.
Just by opening it up in the script editor, which you find in your Apple skip folder,
in your applications folder on Mac OS X, you can add URLs to that.
But you don't have to do anything else just to fire it up and it'll run and create an
iPod or folder on your desktop.
That's why all your content is put in.
It creates a playlist for each new channel in iTunes and puts all the new shows or content
or whatever it is in there.
And then if you stick your iPod in your dock, press though, it's automatically updated
with everything new for you in the morning.
Beautiful thing.
In fact, it makes me wanna sing.
To sing a lot.
It's good hokey.
Play something, uh...
You know, kind of a habit.
I don't know, uh, this is from, uh, I think it's 1963.
Foundation.
What do you think of me? Bye!
You will never see you
But I can't even die
You know what I'm gonna say
Tell me I'm gonna die
Don't break my heart
I'll be over at 10
♪ You can't stop, baby, can't smoke ♪
♪ You need, you let me down, baby ♪
I'll make you happy, happy home
A baby's life don't wait until you leave
♪ What do you do to me? ♪
♪ I'm gonna go back to my bar ♪
♪ No that I have brought this to you ♪
♪ To build me a... ♪
♪ Gotta come, don't make me fall ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You were the time I could be the ball you were done ♪
♪ And we would just let you go ♪
I
♪ I'm inside a car and I'm inside a car ♪
All right, foundations build me up buttercup and well, I'm gonna wrap it up for now.
Once again, I apologize about the quality of the microphone. I'm gonna work on that because this is beyond
unacceptable. So gotta fix that. So anyway, have yourself a great day or evening depending on where you
Are. Roll credits and great show everybody. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Bye.