Hi everybody, it is the source code for Friday, August 27th, 2004.
Good afternoon or good morning or good evening, wherever you are, wherever you're listening
to this, either you clicked on the link on the website or you might be subscribing to
it through RSS.
Thank you very much for subscribing.
I've been thinking a lot about what we need to do with this show in particular
because I'm even getting pretty bored of talking about myself.
And then last night it hit me as I was trying to get to sleep around, I had to go to bed
early, only two more days, Monday and Tuesday, the last two days of the morning show.
And I was thinking that really what maybe at this audio blog or audio show can be about,
maybe it can just be really for users and developers to bring them together.
I mean, I'm...
100% a user on all sides of the broadcast equation.
I really like receiving stuff and I like making stuff,
sending it out as well.
And I think that so far we've been pretty successful at
bringing together a number of developers to work on the
iPod platform and get stuff working.
And these may not even be developers per se.
These could be just users who have a little more
knowledge and experience at making the computers do things
that they want them to do.
So I'm going to see if at all we can make this a
platform of its own for users and developers.
And if you have a comment, obviously you can leave a
comment on the web blog or send me an email
adamantcurry.com.
But maybe if you have something to contribute, you can
create your own audio blog post.
Send me a URL point to it and I'll pick it up.
And then maybe we can share some of your ideas or
questions or stuff that you're looking for or things that we
need to make our computers do and how we can connect them all together through the internet.
And I made a very important discovery yesterday, although the application wiretap for Mac OS
10 had been pointed out to me a couple of times by people in my quest for getting the right
audio software to record these with.
The interface really, I had downloaded it, I think the interface just confused me so
much. I didn't realize that it does exactly what I wanted to do, namely record all the
audio that would normally come out of my speaker. I want that recorded digitally just by listening
to the core audio bits or whatever it is. And that's exactly what wiretap does. I didn't
think it did because when I looked at the preferences file and I think it's selected by default,
it says save files to and then you give it a place to save to and then it says
you can add prefix if you want, which can be the aim. And so when I clicked on the application
name it seemed only to want to save files.
save files with the application name that was at the front that was recording.
So I figured well it only records one application at a time.
And then yesterday while I was doing the source code, Cindy Camilleri came online on iChat
and since she doesn't come online when usually when I am because we are in different, she's
in New York and I'm in obviously in Belgium.
And I always have iChat saying you know, Skipper is here which is her nickname, Skipper.
And I heard the iChat alert that she was online while I was recording and I didn't think that
you'd hear it.
But then I listened back to the yesterday show, yep sure enough it was there.
So I started experimenting and indeed it records everything.
So instead of a mixing console now in front of me, I basically have all my applications
open that I normally use to play bits of audio or use in an audio show like this.
I have three quick time windows open.
the Rachmaninoff remix which is, well, by default now become the tune for source code.
I have a song of the day all queued up and also I have iTunes standing by in case I think
of something I need to search and iTunes is great for that, just typing your search
and immediately you get your results.
Okay, before I go on to with more about what source code could be and a little update
on iPodder, here's something that came in through my own iPodder, at least I'm using
the get enclosure.pearl script and this came in from, what was this, blog digger
and this is from their their media RSS file and apparently some German guy has
written a book called blogs and his name is Don Alfonso and here is an audio
show that was out there on the internet somewhere and I just want to play a
little bit of it because it's kind of cool to hear Germans talk about web logs.
15.40, you can hear the exact same thing in Germany.
These texts are only available on the Internet.
The book is a special logbook for the reader.
It shows a new world and often also a radical point of view.
The book is about blogs.
The title of the book is also published in the beginning of September in the book of Schwarzkopf and Schwarzkopf.
A book published by Don Alfonso and Kai...
What's the name again?
Don Alfonso?
Kai-Pal.
Exactly.
The book is about blogs.
16 webloggers write about text and form on the Internet and why they take over the Internet.
I love it.
Okay, so if you read German there's a book called Blogs.
Blogs is out now in Germany.
Okay, so about the source code, I'd like to see this turn into some form of a platform
where users and developers can talk about how we can work together and make our collective lives better.
I know one thing for sure that all of the...
users I know, if they are using shareware and they use it consistently or if there's a registration
fee.
Most everyone always says the same thing, hey, I want to pay my dues and make sure people
get paid.
So I think there is a market there.
It's probably on a per user basis, small license fees, but there's a lot of software to be
made and if we can aggregate the ideas when it comes to per topic, obviously, then
maybe we can get some economies of scale going like has happened with iPodder.
So the history real quick, I created this script, an Apple script that takes a list of
RSS feeds with MP3 enclosures, downloads those and contrary to popular belief, by the way,
it does check to see if the file has already been downloaded.
It doesn't download again unless the file has been removed because I use the curl
minus F switch.
It downloads them and then it transfers them to your iTunes, which if you have a
iPod automatically syncs up to your iPod and in iTunes it actually creates a playlist which
is equal or equivalent to the name of the channel that or the RSS feed that you're downloading.
It takes all that information from the RSS feed.
So a couple different versions showed up.
We have a Pearl version which I'm actually using myself now and there is now a Windows
version and apparently there's nothing extra to install, no bits that you need.
So I'm going to just download the script and it's good to go.
It's made by Peter Overbeke and I'm pretty sure he's Dutch.
I haven't met him other than online.
I've linked to him today on my web blog.
It's opportunities.nl slash wordpress and he even sent me a ping about it because he's
up to, he's done like three versions now and it's really ready to be tested.
So please give Peter's script a test because if we can get this working for Windows, and
by the way it works with the iTunes, the Windows version of iTunes.
If we can get this working, then this concept of an iPod platform, meaning all mp3 devices,
that can download stuff without you doing anything and just have shows ready for you, I think
we're just on the verge of a huge potential being unleashed here.
So again, if you could, and I've linked to it on my web blog, check out the iPodder
for Windows and let's say get some feedback on how it's doing and if it's working and if it's
performing. And then of course, the next step, which is needed for both platforms, both for
Windows and the Mac, and for Linux and anything else that we can find that people have this desire,
is getting the shows, the mp3s from iTunes to non-ipod mp3 players. And I have a feeling
that's going to be a little bit more challenging. So just about at the end for today, yes, that was
really long time.
them. As I said, I'm trying to keep these around 15 minutes, which is, you know, just believing
in Andy Warhol's vision.
Today, 14 years ago, Patricia turned to me and said, we need to get this child up. And
we knew that we were going to have a C-section way ahead of time because Christina was a
breach. And we went to the hospital and Dr. Ladosi was there and Dr. Sony, the wife
Sony with an eye at the hospital, St. Barnabas in New Jersey. And they said, okay,
you know, we're gonna have this kid today. And it was around seven o'clock and it was
a really great vibe in the operating room. And as the doctor literally picked
Christina up out of Patricia, it was just an amazing sight. On the radio, it
was Light FM was on and the Beatles in my life started to play. And it was
something that we will never, ever forget. Now, of course, it would be easy for me
to play.
the Beatles right now and we'd all have an emotional moment.
But since my daughter, Christina, turns 14 today, I figure I'd honor her since she does
share the bar slash recording studio slash computer room with me.
I'd honor her by playing the brand new song by her favorite band.
And of course, I need to remind you that you do have to vote for them for the viewers'
choice for the upcoming MTV Video Music Awards, which I believe are next Wednesday.
They're all time favorite and I've met these guys.
They are great, broke, bunch of musicians, very, very talented.
Is Good Charlotte.
Check out their new one, Predictable.
I'm still I don't know why
I'm not switchin'
I knew it all along
You're so predictable
I knew something would go wrong
It's all a way back
So you don't have to call
I'll say anything at all
You're so predictable
So take your red tip
It's your broken promises
And all the time you stole
Because I am done with this
I can give it away, give it away
I'm doing everything I should've
And now I'm making a change
I'm living to death
I'm giving back what you gave it
I don't need anything
I knew it all along
You're so predictable
I did something with you
I'm in the middle of a fight
I see you now, I have to go
I say anything at all
So free to bow
I'm in the middle of a fight
Everyone needs every time I travel
I'm so broken, I'm so cold
I'm so hurt inside, I'm so scared
I'm afraid of, I don't even know
The story's been running out of here
I'm searching for a way
I'm dreaming you won't come back
I want you in my story
I'm ready to come and fight
I knew it all along, you're so pretty to phone I knew something would go wrong, and I'm fine
You don't have to call, I'll say anything at all, so pretty to phone
Good Charlotte, predictable.
And believe me, I am just cherishing for as long as possible the fact that my daughter
and I actually like a lot of the same music.
So that's their new one.
And be on the lookout for the CD.
Right.
Okay, that's it for the source code for today.
Just within my 15 minute time limit weekend coming up.
And then two more shows Monday and Tuesday, got a big party.
And then my new life starts.
And I can get to, well, the one thing I want to start doing is having the source code up
and available every morning before, preferably before 8 o'clock East Coast time in the United
States.
All right, well, have yourselves a great weekend.
Hopefully you'll check out the shows this Saturday and Sunday.
If not, talk to you on Monday and have a good one.
Bye-bye.
The power of your intelligence.