Hi everybody and welcome to today's source code. That's Jesse, my dog, saying hi as well.
On a second. Well, I got to start off with a gripe right off the top. I've spent hours
today trying to find software that will do what I wanted to do to record these shows.
I'm sorry, go ahead.
And it wasn't easy searching the web today because we had not one but two different families
come to check out the house, see if they want to buy it.
Which, you know, it's kind of crazy. Anyway, so I mean, I've been looking around and there's
plenty of software if you want to stream stuff live to a shout-cast server or live 365.
But nothing, excuse me, that actually includes the ability to mix more than one of those
to MP3s together and to also have a microphone channel, at least not for Macintosh. So if
anyone has any ideas, love to hear about them. Let's see. Well, yeah, because one of the main
reasons actually that want to have that type of a setup is, you know, for stuff like a
song of the day. I've done some experimenting with keep holding the mic up to the speaker,
but it sucks. Yeah, if I'm going to put songs on, then might as well sound good, or at least
halfway decent. One to just stop briefly and think for a second about Julia Child, who
passed away yesterday, age 91, which I, it's a nice age actually, I guess, if, you know,
but she's one of these people that's been around for just, you know, forever for generations.
I remember as a kid living in Kensington, Maryland, Julia Child came to cook at the local,
I think it was the high school.
and you can hire pleasant view high or something like that.
And, yes, she cooked up a big, big batch of spaghetti and meatballs and families.
I could, you know, for a couple dollars ahead go eat there.
And I remember distinctly the food was really good, although a bit lukewarm by the time
we got ours.
I remember my parents were like a little bit tense.
They were a little bit tense about the service, which of course was done by high school kids.
So people who came in after us were served before us.
Anyway, but it was good.
I do remember that.
And I actually found a Julia child quote and she had a lot of really good ones through
the blog digger enclosure feed.
Check this out.
Now, hold on a second.
See, this is why I need good software to do this for me.
Okay, here's that quote again.
Just boil it in a big pot of scone
See other things I sometimes caught my eye was a Paris Hilton
Her dogs gone missing her her was a pet chihuahua
I gotta say I really like the Paris Hilton reality show the one she does with Nicole Ritchie
Even though it's not officially being broadcast in Europe yet. I don't know maybe it's gonna start in September
I've I've seen the entire first season and I'm up to almost up to speed on the second season
because of the bit torrent feeds and able to
Download an episode well maybe two or three days after it's been aired
and I'm using
This great program called nucleus. I've linked to it before
it's basically it's a little Python application script and
I have it sitting on the
server at my data center and it has keywords and it can only it's it's pretty
rudimentary but so it can only read one RSS feed and it looks for keywords which
are just basic search terms so I've got in their simple life growing up Gody
which is a new show that I just started just started watching. Hi Christina.
That's my daughter Christina.
He's going to use the other computer, so I'll just walk outside to talk for a second to
you guys.
So back to the keywords.
It's really great because it just sits there, it parses through this big RSS file that comes
in and it's updated very regularly.
The TV torrents.
And when it catches one of those keywords, it downloads it.
So of course I'm also getting some serendipitous content.
Not everything that has the keywords simple and life in the title is Paris Hilton's reality
show.
And then once it's in there, I get notified and then at my convenience I just download,
batch download, all the new files which is a pretty fast link.
And that way it saves me a lot of hassle and the aggregation is 24 hours.
So basically it's the last yard.
It's on my server just not at the house yet.
And what I really like about Nucleus is that it doesn't leave your torrent files open.
So it just sucks it in and of course while it's downloading a file and it doesn't one
at a time which also helps on flooding the pipes.
It is uploading but once it's done it's done and then it goes on to the next torrent.
Because last night I downloaded a torrent here which is a 250 meg torrent file and this morning
when I woke up I had pushed out over 750 megs and like you know that was more than I thought
I had to offer it and not that I would mind about the cost or anything but I literally
can't buy more upstream than with from my ISP here in Belgium.
Well, I'm just gonna take a look at my notes for a second.
Right.
So that's one final thing.
Last night, watched the Olympics, the opening ceremony,
which was prime time here in Europe.
And I thought that the Greek did a pretty good job.
Their opening show wasn't as made for TV
as it was, for instance, in Los Angeles or Sydney.
But the show definitely was good.
And water is always hard to do on television
to make it look really spectacular.
What I thought was, well, first of all, there was DJ Chiesto,
who was our pride and joy in the Netherlands.
He was spinning all the dance music
during the presentation of all of the athletes
from all the countries as they walk around the track
and then collected into the center.
That was so very cool seeing him.
He's been voted top DJ of the world
for the, I think, the past three years, consecutively.
What caught my eye is that the number of video cameras
cameras and digital still cameras but the athletes who were being presented the crowd
carried with them was like wow that I'd love to see some of that footage or some of those
pictures and you know we have all the bits we could connect them all together. I'm presuming
that they have some kind of internet access in the in what is it in the Olympic Village
but maybe they even have Wi-Fi I don't know but it should be just as simple as plugging
your camera into your laptop and basically saying broadcast this. And I think there's
two sides to that equation and I'm trying to fix the first side just working on it in
audio to make the iPod more than just something that you sync to iTunes. I want your iPod
to be a receiver in a way where you put it in its cradle to charge and it loads it up
with new audio from the web.
and that's it.
And it should be seamless.
You don't have to think about it and it should let you know.
And it should, you know, that it's done that and it put it
into a perfect playlist.
And I've been hacking around with that, which is pretty easy,
well, relatively easy on the Mac because it's already
kind of meant to work together.
So I'm going to continue working on that and release the script
or code or whatever you want to call it and who knows,
maybe folks will make it work for Windows.
And then, of course, is the other side to the equation,
which is how do you make it simple for people to broadcast that?
Is it as simple as maybe creating an on the go playlist
on your iPod?
And when you put it back into its charging stand,
it looks at that playlist and turns it into an RSS 2.0 feed
with enclosures.
And maybe the enclosures are torrent files.
I don't know.
Well, I guess I don't have to know because this is source code, right? This is just stuff running through my brain
I was a little more discombobulated than I wanted.
Ahh...
No, that's about it.
I'm gonna walk out one more time.
It's weird.
Can't sit in the in the bar with Christina my daughter and talk to you like this cuz she'd probably burst out laughing
If you heard me talking to myself, so that's it
For today's edition
If you do have any ideas about the software
That that I need you know that has a mic channel
Please drop me line Adam at curry calm
Or you know leave a comment anywhere on my web log live
Curie calm l i v e dot curry calm
Well, I guess it should have said the beginning. This was source code for Saturday August 14th 2004 and
We'll talk to you again tomorrow
Bye