Delta Shera Charlie 867 holy crap am I really doing this
this is Batman's adventure. I'm dying. 21st century of radio's dice here. The outline from no justice for God's sake. It's occurring.
I'm going to have to stop for the big ones.
♪ I am alone ♪
♪ The magic is no matter ♪
♪ By the world ♪
♪ See you in the world ♪
I am fucking you.
Oh, it's bleeding.
Thanks for watching!
♪♪♪
It's time for the ice and snow from the midnight.
So green...
This is great!
Hey, this is your...
Oh my god!
♪ Your gift over control ♪
♪ ♪
I'm gonna get out of the water!
♪♪
November 27th!
2013!
♪♪
Thanks for tuning in!
I think I should have scored a try.
and the other than just a full full of excellent music provided to me by DJ Power Boy.
I feel good about it.
I'll probably get a tell you what's going on right after this.
Loves that alone in a buggy march
Totally much alive except for her heart
My pride up in a love special
She totally confused all the pussing
Others that she's up, she's up, she's in my head
She's not! She's not!
She might be a zim!
♪ ♪
♪ Left in love for brain ♪
♪ And the watching God has stolen rotten and insane ♪
♪ Small things don't say that brides good land ♪
♪ Is my fastest ♪
♪ But she's not, but she's not ♪
♪ But she's in my hand ♪
♪ I know ♪
She's gone! She's gone! She might be dead!
What?
♪♪♪♪
I don't know.
B.......
Bye bye.
I'm not leaving it, shove an unslipped autocast then try more than you, I'm just there to wait in between the jeans, I'm free of the lads of silence baby.
She's in my hair.
She's not!
She might be dead!
Brethren, it's up United States of America!
Oh, she's so lonely!
TAPM as I said on Wednesday night just did all the show prep for no agenda for the show tomorrow
Which of course is our annual Thanksgiving extravaganza, and I'm just looking through this folder of
Tracks for the pre-stream like man. This is almost like this is perfect for a daily source code
So I figured out just kind of grab them and you know one thing led to another
I'm listening to these tracks and I had purchased a
bottle to take to my friends tomorrow where I'll be joining up with them after
After the show for some Thanksgiving dinner
They've promised me
Cowboys and tranny so looking forward to that and then and the guy at the liquor store gave me a bottle of Glen live at
This is aged 15 years. You know what but like one of those airplane bottles only it's a little bigger
Let me see don't have any lights on here. I mean give you an idea of what the quantity is
Of course, I've got these brand new lenses so I can't see crap
Bye!
I was just saying there is a this is pretty bad. I can't actually read
how what the content of the bottle is. Oh man. Anyway, I've already consumed it as
you know I'm quite a lightweight so that kind of helped me over the over kind
of the the hump to do the show.
I saw a time you you what did I know you don't
a deep breath but you have changed I'm the answer to you
It's like a...
I cannot hear your voices soothing, but the way that I play, if I can use it.
I've learned the case
I'm looking through you
I need to tell you what I need to do without dreaming, right?
The last year I've been up there for a beer in all the night
You're singing at me, the flame all the way
You were a black me, but not today
I'm a black me, but not today
I'm looking for you
♪♪♪♪
♪ Tell me what I did you like ♪
♪ Is the spirit all the night ♪
I can swim you
What did you go?
I saw time you
You
You don't look different but you have changed
I'm against you
I'm just looking at the DSC dot to curry dot com and it says David source code 866 was the last one that I did on August 28 2012 although it actually says
episode 865 on the player I wonder if it was 865 866 let me listen here what can I fucking hear it
I'm not doing this streaming tonight because I can't don't have access to the stream it's a little different without live audience but we'll still give it a try
I'm sure you'll enjoy the podcast edition most people do.
Charlie, my favorite mistake must have been Lance. I'm a little favorite of mine. I'm a good one.
I'm sorry
Don't let your boss was born, and you don't give me a bug
I made up that we sleep in
A dead block when you creep in the woods
Silly-a-lilly as I must go
♪♪
I'm gonna die.
I'm so sorry for me, and what you're doing to your domain, I'm in full of all you skin.
I'm so sorry for you, and what you're doing to your domain.
I make a bad dream, like a beast of silly, I make a bad dream.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
Even I never have stayed here.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I'm gonna die ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm not a good one ♪
♪ Oh, I need a hug ♪
♪ I need a hug ♪
♪ We're all up, we're up ♪
♪ I'm like you, but I ♪
of music radio live here on the Charlie
that you might like and a long time
when the computer necessarily do everything
kind of make it a mix.
I've got to listen to this at night.
I can only listen to this show at like 11 o'clock at night.
I've got all the lights out in the house.
I'm here in the studio.
I don't think I've never done a Charlie in this new studio,
which is very cool because I've got the stand up desk.
The energy is going to be way different than last time we did it,
which was the lunar edition, if you recall.
Wow, it's been that long since I've been on this weekend Tech, too.
♪ Only tonight so long ago, but I was not so strong ♪
So back with the nose.
See each other in every dream
I ain't like you, no matter
You look like you mean
Yeah
Come on, come on, girl
You said the smile
You don't have to help me
And let's get out of all
But try to understand
♪ And talk ♪
♪ I'm still ♪
♪ In the night we sang in the moon, played inside the moon ♪
♪ Let the spell lights go, ever ♪
♪ Just on the light, past and forth ♪
♪ Try and relax, go, on, before it ♪
♪ Growing up in the moon ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Just on the light, baby, and my girl ♪
♪ Should be at home, but try to understand ♪
♪ Try, try ♪
He's a magic man mama
Ahh!
♪♪
I'm gonna be a little bit more like a kid.
♪ I'm so hungry ♪
♫ This year! ♫
♪ I'm not here to find my house with me ♪
♪ To take a minute and I'll hold you ♪
♪ Oh, we can't get in with you ♪
Oh
Oh, no.
Oh, you're the best.
♪♪♪
♪♪♪♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Mmm.
Me too.
♪♪♪
Oh no, that's not what I said.
Oh my god.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
♪♪♪
Yeah.
Bye!
♪♪
is
I'm so sorry.
♪ You are a small girl ♪
♪ I'm trying to stand around the stand ♪
♪ I'm trying to try to understand ♪
♪ These imagines are cheap ♪
Oh oh oh oh Zarmin!
I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, and I'm waiting for you to follow me.
I told you what it takes to reach the highest.
You'd never find a thing like that simple
My father's been so many times before
My shyest words you know
No one ever gots to leave the temple
I'm free. I'm free.
And please.
♪ The mountains of reality ♪
♪ ♪
Free!
♪♪♪♪
♪ And I'm waiting ♪
♪ To find me ♪
Oh man, I almost want to make some beat in a cyst.
I love you.
I'm actually dancing to the house.
I am completely free.
Completely free of any corporate restraints.
To bring you a collection of music
with a bunch of flathers between.
For free.
Call the Deathly Source Code.
Very happy to bring it to you.
And I'm not quite sure when I'm gonna release this.
I guess I'll do it for the weekend.
Maybe everyone, the opportunity to most recent know agenda first,
which actually is also part of the inspiration for doing the show.
So we were talking about, well, Bitcoin.
And even though I do not recognize it as a currency and I have my doubts,
I made a deal with a lot of the producers of their show.
I said, listen, why not just do a daily source code and keep that going.
And people donate Bitcoin to keep that show rolling.
And I won't sell it until what I say until it hits 10,000.
I'd set the exact parameters, but it's already over $1,000 today.
So it was like 1,083 last time I checked.
So I wouldn't be publishing a Bitcoin address along with the show notes for this,
You can find it dsc.curry.com
Bye bye.
Go ahead send me some middle Bitcoin to whatever and then by the time that thing
heads 10,000 I'll be a hundred million air and I'll take all of you out for
hookers and blowing bacon
♪♪♪
Listen to this, it's from James Brown record. It's instrumental. And wait, it's a dance on the delzea!
♪♪
I'm going to try and beat the song for sure.
♪♪♪
♪
It's gonna be really weird tomorrow morning playing the same tracks the note didn't prestream.
And of course it is all those pre streams that kind of slowly got me back in the mood.
So much research going on like today getting now Miss Mickey is there working on Los Angeles
coming back into love Saturday.
So I've been of course in the studio.
You know, in the office really researching everything gone so deep on so much that I just needed some relaxation
Damn!
So anyway, so if you do donate to some pieces of bits
Then know that we will all be going to Vegas and well, but at that point I'll even go over to hire this guy
As we enjoy our hope for some blow
Miss the Saturday dance
Her day crowded the floor
Couldn't bear it without you
Don't get around much anymore
Thought I'd visit the club
Got as far as the dog
They have asked you about you
Don't get around much and involved.
Thanks for watching!
Well, darling, I guess that my mind's more at ease.
But nevertheless, why star of memories been invited on the east.
Might have gone but what for?
Awfully different without you.
Don't get around much anymore.
Been invited on the east.
I might have gone but what for?
Oh, sweet damn friend, where the house is? I had a little bit of a vision. I'm gonna get her up!
♪ I'm not so long ♪
I know the guy I met him.
You know it's a party.
We do it in an old school.
Anybody?
Old school, Vegas.
And a disco, twerking crap.
All the drinking scotch and hanging out.
And girls all look pretty and dressed up,
including you girls who become alone.
And basses tree.
Here's a street where all the boys
and the butth folks live down the New Orleans
And the land of life.
No, how nice it seems and not so much a billy means no no no no no no no you're dear to me
Yes, reed
Give me yes reed get you seen baby I can lose
Those good old business
Blue
Oh
♪♪♪
Me!
♪♪♪♪
♪♪♪
Mmmm.
♪♪♪♪
♪ ♪
Bye bye.
♪
No, no, no, nice to see it. Just a much real amazing.
Hey, I'll see the moon and the moon is pale!
And it looks like they're taking some cat to jail
No, it's the moon is pale, the Sun is...
and then the Sun is gone, and the steam-water coming, and they're splashing, and then they're going...
Whoa whoa!
I bawl the moon and the moon shining!
Oh, it's all smooth.
you tell me.
Oh, steepy down, down...
♪ Folks, I'm an idiot ♪
I'm so familiar to him there.
So I'm thinking that maybe we should only make a minor feel.
all the time.
long way things are going with our internet freedoms for a quote unquote
unlicensed music program like this to just go out and kind of an RSS speed of
you store them
fashion should be a huge problem. And what are we going to do? This is going to be playing
music. I'd love to know what you guys think about it. Of course, this is a very interesting
episode because I have no chat room, there's no live stream happening. It's a little weird
because I don't think I've ever done... I mean, it's doing radio and you're doing it in the live
format that I do it, but then without an actual audience is... it's very unfamiliar territory, so...
get this weird feeling about talking to no one, but yes, yet I am talking to you.
It's concerning.
in the coming episodes of this rekindled Charlie you'll be needing it.
you are really wise, there's no good scenes. One life for yourself and one life.
You drift through the years, and the life seems tamed.
♪ So I can dream of years ♪
♪ And I'll visit tonight ♪
♪ I'm just a little girl ♪
♪ Is a stranger ♪
♪ Who'd better be one ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
This dream is for you
So pay the price
Make one million come true
You won't live twice
And love is a stranger
♪ You look back and you are ♪
Don't think of the danger
This dream is for you
So pay the price
Make one dream come true
You only live
It's your home.
♪ We're happy ♪
♪ We have layers ♪
♪ Some say that we have pawns ♪
♪ But we've been making money since the day that we were born ♪
♪ Got some slow dance ♪
We fought.
We got stuff out of there in the face!
I have to let it walk as we know that...
♪♪♪♪
The exact fly you're brand-new. Oh, but those are Christmas. I'm giving it up for Lance.
So thin of cover beaters to keep the pain we not enjoy the man
♪ I'm gonna fade away ♪
Yeah.
♪♪♪
Go! Yeah!
And the hell it's...
♪♪♪
♪ Girl, you, you, thank you ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ I'm gonna be you ♪
Thanks for watching!
♪ I love you ♪
♪ To be alone ♪
♪ I can't find it ♪
this record not just this song but this entire record the Robby Williams the
it was really genius and at the time I was living in Amsterdam and would be
taking Christina to school and I had a little smart back in the day which is
now when was this this must have been 2002 2000 yeah 2002 2003 and having a
smart in Amsterdam is very very handy it's exactly what you want but it had
an awesome sound system and we'd be blasting this record it wasn't there was
a couple other cities I think somewhere I might have the actual like CDs from
that car which of course I've no idea what happened to it after all the money
went away some things you just kind of lose track of it really don't remember
what happened to that that's a smart car I hope I sold it a couple other cool
tracks that coming up for you actually I'm gonna play this from a YouTube video
which was just released. Tom Kiefer from Cinderella. I hung out with him multiple times.
It's kind of in the Jersey scene back in the, oh man, that must have been really late 80s,
maybe early 90s. So he has a solo record out and I think it's either on Jack Ponty's
record label or his music publishing or I don't know, he might have produced it because I know
Tom Kiefer through Jack Ponty who you got to Google him if you want to talk about Jack. He's
one of a kind. Anyway, so I saw a posting from Jack that Tom has this new album out and I definitely
wanted to play this track. So it's straight from YouTube so you have to take the quality for what it is.
Thanks for watching!
song.
♪ Hey, you too, baby ♪
explain.
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ You just got to say ♪
♪♪♪
I'm still so close with you, that you good.
♪ And I feel as you taste all the time ♪
♪ Just a few little rules ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ I'm gonna be ♪
I'm afraid of you.
♪ You just want to be a star ♪
♪♪♪♪
♪ Baby ♪
Bye!
♪♪
♪ In the mud ♪
♪ A pretty girl ♪
♪ To have the last leg ♪
♪ Oh my God, I'm gonna go ♪
♪ In our hearts ♪
Women are God's greatest gift to our world. Truly beautiful inside and out system.
song. So much that way life goes.
uploaded to YouTube
the video too.
Stealing on a corner, wow.
Ting on a pretty girl's.
You're right.
And it's one of those videos where I just keep
expecting to see Jack Ponty pop up somewhere in
the crowd.
That would be something for him kind of like a John
Collodner, John Collodner thing.
Very, very cool. Awesome.
Hey, that's the kind of stuff I'd like to do a little
bit more of here on the
Robbie up for a brahming.
Give me some new stuff to listen to once in a while.
That's just an ancient kid.
Hey,
and hello.
Mr. Greer, Mr. Greer.
Are you happy we're doing another Charlie?
You might be.
Danny Shores code 867
to your service.
Shh, you're not gonna get it.
Thanks for watching!
I'm in the town, it's in the car, and sometimes it's in the back, sometimes it makes me happy, and sometimes it makes me sad.
Don't you do this all the way, you feel it like a child,
Hey!
Ladies, sit down!
You make me smile
Sit down!
Come!
You're talking about what I'm doing
I don't even understand why
You're talking about me
And you're cheating like a child
♪♪♪♪
Hey, I'll sleep with you. I'm sick of you. I'm gonna have to grab you.
I know you're not real, man, because I'm loaded, okay?
I've had some experience in that area.
Yours is bull anyway.
Blistering awesome heavy metal
In a little bit of pressure, it's only sitting alive. In a little bit of pressure, it's only over here.
I'm gonna go!
Bye!
♪♪
And I sinned and LOUD LOUD LOUD.
What the...preathy shit?
And if I wanna dance or take my clothes off...
Or both.
Somehow I missed it when this really was...
I think that was probably mid 90s when I was focused on
making money.
Ahhh!
How fun is we are when we're young?
How little do we truly understand the ways of the world?
How about this?
in control.
I'm going to go.
Oh. Yeah. Oh. Good morning ladies and gentlemen. What's in the fucking girl? She's your captain with no name speaking and I'm here. Don't go away.
I'm gonna get you a job!
Oh my gosh.
♪♪♪♪
Oh
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
It's in a scoondah, a little bit.
You will watch the fight you!
The straight A, then cover.
the chapter and everyone that...
Nothing! Drop!
, Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
I'm just dead a bit.
Hey, she got a single lick on his head.
I said, nigga, you crazy.
I don't know.
The woman in the world ain't a freak
time make what I can get away so what's the possible thing on the internet cuz it's somebody
Corsa.
Courtset.
belongs.
♪♪♪
I need another piece of yo ear
I wanna hip you all to the reason I'm known as a playa
The year cuz I met this girl named pussy
I've been in this girl
I'm a 50, 3, 6, then a weepy I look good
Driving a huddle, a full double, this side high
My kids went down, I said motherfucker I know your reputation
And I must stand it, show you how I feel
You're lonely and you won't turn me on
for a laugh, and make it a little bit of a movie. But it's gonna be hell. Keep my-
Can I tell you what I'm taking at you already now?
You need a mother
That's a country
Music Chime
Take care!
And the more this motherfucker is,
Ladies, make a Mac like to know,
You are worth an all-way wheel.
Close the country.
You really?
What?
The one?
Oh
I'm not sure.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Who's the last you ♪
Thanks for watching!
Oh
, it's a sound.
Chain chain chain chain chair
Ch-ch-ch-ch chain chain chain chain chain chain
chain speed
yhew
tangy
j deal
through the octave
tangy
tang
oh
Oh Oh?
Why you just need me now?
I wanna rule you man
I wanna rule you for me
More than lost
I don't want you to leave, in shame
Oh
Satan
♪ Take me ♪
♪ Take the ♪
♪ Get me a movie ♪
♪
robot
oops
byeeee
what did you remember in your life?
half worked out
mile worked out
Donald Trump
Where are you going
Friends
That was so good.
Good being Thanksgiving 2013 and all, almost.
I just want to say, in this context of this program with the Daily Source Code here with
the chuckleheads, I'm really thankful for the fact that there's...
♪ Blue, yay, and lots of fun ♪
If you don't watch, I'll instantly do you.
Do you?
you
It's time to go!
you see that my behavior is I see a ghost kind of singing unless it's a summer I have the tendency of getting there and things that go so much is kept cause they're proud do you need a miracle?
♪ The dream of dying, maybe why I'm even here ♪
♪ The double vision ♪
♪ But you know very well I want to go on ♪
♪ But you fucking tell the bad I am walking on ♪
♪ It gives to all our souls ♪
Either anyone out there, cuz they're FUCKING hard
Oh, that's
Sure I art
Shouldn'ta been ze'a da
You never
Listen for a set
Palme
Crin Ya
Fo La
Oh
♪♪♪♪
the
tell you man this is this is this people get up in the morning and this
people get up in the morning and go make really
good really
fun pop records and i got to say that's adam laveen
uh... was maroon five uh... and for that of course uh... cream but
uh... i i don't watch a lot of television that i watch a lot of course i
watch it in the news programs i watch c-span
uh... by watch p b s you know there's lots of television on but that really
sit down watch something for entertainment purposes one of the few
programs i'll watch is the voice
uh... because that to me and and by the way we uh... always record the show
so we can shuttle through not just the commercials or sometimes i'll actually
stop and watch the commercial
if it's entertaining
but so we don't have to win the game element is so uninteresting
you know the uh... the judges
Yeah, usually I'm not interested in hearing what they have to say, but it's a great pop music show.
There's no shit on it, which is what I like.
So it's all though, you know, cutting the songs down to 90 seconds and stuff.
You know, that's very frustrating to me.
But as a music program in prime time, I forget the contest element.
It's good.
It's cool.
And it's Adam Lee Levine guy.
I think I really didn't like him the first time around the first season or whatever it was or the second or I don't know, or third.
But I think he either gave up the Vivance or the changes dosage because he was a little amped out the first, first one or two seasons.
And so now he seems, you know, I don't know.
I have, I kind of like him.
Is something about him that that I find endearing, although he does weird things like he'll do a hug, but with his elbows out, not really hugging somebody and that's that's wrong.
So this of course leads me into the opportunity to play this song which I saw at ACL live.
Austin City limits this past year first time that Miss Mickey and I went.
I really like this. We basically saw one band play all the way through their set.
And it was electric six.
Thanks for watching!
♪♪♪
You're there on the TV screen. It's a mass producer.
I mean not just the vocals and the lyrics but the guitar solo is like a murderous like
someone really pissed at Adam will mean a little drum the BN.
Wow.
Come on music.
♪♪♪♪
♪ It's the dream for me ♪
♪ Send me to the house when you talk to me ♪
♪ Right at the time, I'm coming home ♪
I should...
The battle we are doing.
We know what you're set to set.
We've got to take a break.
We know what you're doing.
We're not your killer.
We've got to take a break.
We're not our killer.
♪ I'm gonna go back and go back ♪
Morning!
I've never grown, the blood would, and the desert would hold and rat sat violent.
♪ They're saying ♪
♪ A shit ♪
♪ And time has come ♪
I'm not gonna stop that.
So fast.
Hey, I want to see you there.
Thanks for watching!
Shh, I think we gots when our tis burnin'
♪♪♪♪
While we're scabbing, I'm gonna lose a fucking talk, ain't it? Cause you're not a fool, don't you?
It's time to stand.
Thanks for watching!
♪ I hate the way it's gonna be ♪
♪ Good job, bless you all ♪
Peace!
♪ I'm not this violent ♪
Kind of dig the stuff after what typically after about three years
That's where you can really start to play songs over again
Now back in the 70s
This was like when I was a kid. This was you know, you're like, wow, you have heard of those guys. That's kind of cool. Yeah
And you would just talk about them in kind of FM album oriented rock kind of way the Alan Parsons project
You could even say, hey man, you heard the latest from the project?
And those in the know,
this would be all over now.
Thanks for watching.
I'll see you tomorrow night at you!
Oh
We have to get the
Bye!
Oh yeah, wow, sir, I have to go home!
You have to Disagree
I was too
What Can I be with?
injunction
♪♪♪
No wonder I took myWhy
It's a long ago
I'm gonna go the next time.
♪ Stickers on, loves her style ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Oh
Wouldn't wanna be like you Alan Farsen's projects on the daily source code which I think
is probably the first time we've ever played a Sarsen project on the source code.
♪ This is a good one ♪
♪ Look what's in drag, man, big waters pass ♪
Thanks for watching!
gonna play one more song for you and by then we'll done almost an hour and a half
not bad for a minor reboot right I really got to get to getting up early to
do the show even though we
So show notes, I'll have my big turn QR code, whatever, money for you.
Did we do more of these shows pretty soon, okay?
There was a boy, a fellow, a man sitting almost in his light. He's a loaded world, and sometimes he's a...
Oh, I must be fine, cause my arms don't be taint
Come and give me by the river sand
I say, oh, says it's loose, you don't consider it shaint time
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh.
Where is it?
Then move on to the baby and high to pay per Hmmmultiple cars
Can't keep away from theits
And I remember when u dont know
♪ I've prayed those all of it's been chai ♪
♪ He's been looking for something new ♪
♪ I said it once before but it bears my pretzied ♪
What you need to do right now is go to Google and Google Jostone and look at the images while
you're listening to the song.
I'm so happy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Aaaah! Aaaah!
I'm gonna...
I fell in love with a bump I fell in love with my internal clothes from blue light He's in love with her
It's gone, son, please, feelings can't be so misleading He turns us as a you are
All must be back as my heart's in me, coming kid, we've never been a sight Sarah says she know me still but she's lying to me
Aaah, Aaah, Aaah, Aaah, Aaah, Aaah.
♪ Scamping a benefit to do ♪ ♪ Let's bring no soul of its fate, say ♪ ♪ Here's a look at the something new ♪
♫ Ah, ah, ah ♫
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Thank you so much.
You make this show worth doing.
Alright, juggleheads, talk to you soon.
DSC.Kurry.com.
Adios, Mofos.