Delta Sierra Charlie 860, the SNFU Saturday edition for February 5th, 2011.
Between the innocence of an engineer and the dignity of a janitor,
we find a lovable monster called a disc jockey.
This jockey is coming a certain size as weights and colors,
but all DJs have the same creed to bluff unknowingly as many commercials as possible in an eight-hour
script.
This jockey is our found everywhere.
Under turn tables, swinging from typewriters, climbing a disowned effects rack,
or jumping to attention at the approach of a program director.
Their relatives love them, sponsors can't stand them, engineers ignore them,
but the listeners protect them.
When you want to concentrate, a DJ is an inconsiderate but some intruding jangle of noise.
A clown, when you want some music, he plays something fast,
and when you're in the mood for something heavy, bright and sparkling,
he always gives you a slow, serious, sticky, sweet bound.
A disc jockey is a composite.
He has the voice of a horse, the courage of a cast-per-milk post,
the imagination of an insect, the shyness of a politician, the lungs of a barter,
and all the energy he can get from Dr. Moon-Pinkles' little bipamantil.
He likes bat-mail, a day off, girls, comic books, his wife, his family, doll, fishing, girls,
comic books, phone calls, compliments, girls, comic books, and occasional kind
word with a light panel in the head. Girls, talent seeks, girls, compliments,
recognition, girls, comic books, time-off, girls, and comic books.
He's not much for working an expert day, words of more than free syllables, and certain musical units,
and nobody gets so much fun out of trees and dogs and time signals as he does.
A DJ is a lovable, wacky, real, cool character.
You can lock him out of your workshop, but you can't turn him off your neighbor's ready.
You can get him out of your study, but you can't get him off the airway,
so you might just as well give up. He's here to stay in many forms,
tall and short, thin and fat, neat and sloppy, beautiful, dulce tones and squeaky squealing.
Bonser dance is standing alive and half dead, good and bad.
But when the day is over and you get home with only the shattered pieces of your hopes and
dreams remaining after the day is puzzled. He can lend them all like you with those six magic words.
Music on this program was recorded.
Music on this episode was recorded.
Music on this programavan was recorded.
Music on this program was recorded.
They say the water is sharing work, and all they've been drunk all the time
Sheriff Jackson, we're not the back, and now he's done us, all dressed in blue
Tracing blue
Not a man, but a driver, where you are, there's a woman on the hill in a mud room
With a shotgun for the form, and a raise a pack for in the pack of a check-ups for a pack
I don't think I can hear you, I don't think I can hear you
Travelling for me, oh, I'm afraid you'll be for a certain condition, a status quo
Not a man, but a driver, where you are, there's a woman on the hill in a mud room
With a shotgun for the fall
There's a black plastic bag
Like a little bit of a surprise
CROVED to kick off
They have a source code
860 is a snap boost out of me
How you doing in the morning everybody
Adam Curry your DJ
Rollin' about for you
The fifth of February
And we've got tons to talk about today
Because I needed to do the show to talk to my friends
It's all I've joined in and no oneеловjoins.net
Noajoins change.com
Peanut luck time Friends since we rock and roll
Really all pass and Rock in no
They all pass and Soccer does GO
Really give better saknake
Can me give back, now do me uk wol
It's been a long time and a long time and a long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long
long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long longer long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long long
You
Go
....
...
Tell me
But you know, they let it all come to me
They let it all come to me
It's been a long time, a long time, a long time, a long time
In the morning, it's been a long time, a long time, yeah
you
yeah
in the long time
in the moment
in the only moment
in the only time
yeah
how about some bloody today
you're more than in the morning
being more touching
We rockin' wooled on the Charlie as we be my live at noagendastream.com
Happy to be your DJ on Moody, the name is Adam also known as the afman
It's Miss Mickey actually who spurred me on to do a show today
She said you know I'm gettin' all kinds of tweets for people say maybe he's gonna make some pancakes
Because the guy needs to do another show
And considering I had a minor deflation of energy earlier this week, it's not a bad idea
We'll be talkin' about that in a lot more in the next couple hours
We party together here on the GSG
You do it on me yeah, yeah
Happy to be your DJ on Moody, the name is Adam
It's Miss Mickey, the name is Adam
Happy to be your DJ on Moody
I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that
, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, did not hear of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've heard of that, I've never heard of that, never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've ever heard of that, I've never heard of that, I've never heard of that, that, I've ever heard had that,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,突,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, best of all, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah I. Yeah, yeah
Great to see commester vlogger in the chat if you're new to the Charlie and I can imagine
after 860 episodes there's still some people who've never heard of the program the way
we do it these days which is a far cry from the early days is with the chat room everyone
comes in live we hang out we drop tracks in the dropbox and we talk a little bit of
bold crap and commester vlogger did the pass on an entry which I'll be playing
free later which of course is another one of his excellent analyses of the
European Union my friends each burns while we're more concerned about the
Super Bowl yes I had a mind about the depression earlier this week more on
that in a bit
a
You know what I mean?
But the world of actress watches
It's the world
I got it
So what's the way?
The life is short
And the hours always
So what?
The world?
I can read the drugs
And read it by the way
With a song
I'll die
And I'll hide the world
And you will anger
But the world of actress watches
It's the world
The world is made of
So what I mean?
I'll become the living
Pythas
Everything is Applause
Ignoreable
From I'll always And Display
The world.......
If the fireworks
And you will walk
And you have more
And the world of actress watches
What about the death tonight?
ament
It's time, life's over, life's over, life's over
Life's over, life's over, life's over
Life's over, life's over
Life's over, vida's over, life's over
The rest of the scene is nothing,
It's nothing, it's nothing, it's nothing.
The whole world will break into this world,
It's dust and the whole reality.
And the time will come alive.
The time will come alive.
Sisters of Mercy, we're just a top to the hands.
I'm over a house on the Temple of All,
but your daddy's door is going episode 86.
Zero, the snapper side of it, which means we will not be making
your ears bleed all the time.
We gotta bring it down a little bit in time,
I have to say,
the way I've been feeling recently looking at the news.
What's happening with slaves worldwide?
I kind of feel like I'm living at the corner of
dude and catastrophe.
How about you?
Who got by the pool again?
It's the play of the pool again.
What the whiffin' pool again?
But on the grill that stinks,
kind of like burnt fur,
and rare to drink,
but an undertone of the acorn
and leather that's laid on,
thick like Liz Clayborn,
step over with thick trepidation,
lift up the top off the meat cooking station.
To discover my home and tie,
that's it, oh my god,
what brim facade,
to give me with them up,
waitfulness, I have too many sellers,
and they always crisp,
unless I rise up in the morning with my squirrel,
the sister from the world,
and sister does I get this instant,
and you're nothing again,
it's pretty mature,
if only we had the teamwork concur,
spoken with the tongs,
do won't wake up,
put them on the lawn,
raise a basket,
a steak up,
and they say,
no kind of miles are leaving,
got to get the high degree on,
toss on them on the pool,
got all but they all used up,
I'm a little sizable link,
nothing left to try,
phone and crystal,
my heart is pistol,
I mean it could break like crystal,
ain't never learned to whistle,
don't break,
it's cadaver up,
what's a matter with your mind?
he ain't a long cliff,
he's been knuckle heads since old times,
dig out the bat and helm and then the bat,
we're all about to have a funeral,
and that's that,
we'll do it after breakfast,
we'll do it after proper,
we'll drop all his ashes out the air,
we'll cop,
they're rusting in the dirt,
he's all spreading out blossoms,
and it's gonna flip up,
but the beef freaking awesome,
we're all living inside the same,
wasting my time,
to prove,
we're all living inside the same,
bout a guy,
we're我们 2 dead,
classroom,
six bomb rips lay the w closed gonna
the hell I bet saint around your再見,
one to wedms tell us that,
these dudes ain't?
II don't send a meant stole,
now I want to say a lil giving me something,
but a bit of laying card,
so the rest I call,
you get frustrated of aggression,
they're like the eagle got to do,
they'll passed out on the barbeque,
charging on the brand for most of my images,
while I can turn around,
the life it's great with a less than envy.
With the less than it, jelly, traffic and black toss
Mac, and psychedelics in that little ass
Man, the his and drunk, doing it
No one with the right thing to do was
But a showing it, hidden soon, pretty probable
Plears are all the bullheads
The duty that's hot, oh, oh, not just in death
But in after that, like the bat
Out the HG double, hurt a cool slack
But in mound, in the case of this road
It's like when he got killed, out on it's loaded
Or in back, when he got shamed in the joint
And the cause we need to wonder if it's easy
To the point, to my shepherd, the tending of his life's ending
Up that he's chilling at friendlies
And gonna be back in the neighborhood shortly
Discussing how awesome it is to be
Fortly reporting the slant that he just got on with
Listener, drink to his risks, hurt
Going to ghost in your sister
To the bucket kicks to when he asked me
And this one wasn't like I'm asking
So yes, we're depressed, but not dressed
We leave it in the corner of doing catastrophe
Where I'm living inside the same
Where's the mudtime, I'm not to prove it
You know, it may not help a lot
If you want to support the artist that are playing at a daily source code
I believe no agenda entertainment.com is updating the track
Listening in real time
Of course, if you're in the chat room, you can vote on the tracks
Good old Gungus, stupid track of stuff the way Dungu does
You know, Dungu, he's the guy that tracks all of our
Everything in the chat room, no agenda stream.com, no agenda chat.net
Stand by, we'll be breaking things down just a minute
I'm a loser
And I'm not what I appear to be
I've all a love, I have one, or have lost
There is one love I should never have crossed
She was a girl and a million, my friend
I should have known she would win in the end
I'm a loser
And I love someone who needs to meet
And I'm not what I appear to be
All the way left and I act like a clown
Then eat this mask, I am wearing a crown
Matty is all falling like rain from the sky
Is it for her or myself that I cry
I'm a loser
And I love someone who needs to meet
And I'm not what I appear to be
What have I done to deserve such a bait?
I realize I have left it too late
And so it's true, pride comes before a fall
I'm telling you so that you won't lose
I'm a loser
And I love someone who needs to meet
And I'm not what I appear to be
For those lesser known tracks from the Beatles
Which you can probably find on iTunes
For free here no agenda stream.com
I'm a loser on your daily source code episode 860
It is the Snapfoo Saturday edition
In the morning to everybody who is listening
And in the morning to everyone in the chat room of course
And I have to say it was weird this week
As of course I've had CNN on for most of the time
Trying to pop back and forth between that and C-SPAN
As you know John C to work and I
Watch C-SPAN so you don't have to
Which is harder than it sounds actually sometimes
And a suddenly from a metal level I got this oh my god look at what's happening
Because obviously what's going on in Egypt is real
And people are really pissed off and they're really coming out
And of course we know that anything we're seeing here in the media is slanted
Twisted
It's the Ministry of Truth so and I don't read Egyptian or Arabic for that matter
Or whatever language may be blogged or Facebook
No one is actually pointed out a Facebook page to me that shows the true voice of the people
There's all kinds of
Shills who are running around there so we really don't exactly know what's going on on the ground
One thing for sure it's not Anderson Cooper Vanderbilt bringing you the truth
That just doesn't feel right and too bad that Christian Ampour has been co-opted by ABC and CNN
Maybe she just felt like retiring didn't want to do the real stuff anymore
Used to be a big fan of what she did
But at a metal level I was looking at all this stuff and like you know
We really don't deserve any better. We let ourselves be treated like slaves and when you are treated like a slave and you and
Respond like one then you need some global elites who are going to move you around and point you in the direction that is necessary
And this became really depressing to me because I'm like you know
If we were really truly left to our own means to be human beings
With all the love and and beauty that we have in in ourselves inherently the world would be a very different place
I'm convinced of it, but no because we allow this to happen
Because we allow ourselves to be moved and manipulated and
Steered in every direction and we accept it we both Hika they say and get monation east
Bend over here it comes again because we let all that happen
We deserve to be moved and and
Control by the elites and
I was thinking what part do I want to play in that moving forward in the future?
I'm gonna turn 47 this year. What am I gonna do? How are we gonna do it? Can we do stuff with
No agenda can we really make a dent?
Well, maybe a little bit does it start one person at a time
Can we do things with the music we play can we start to
Bring our own mind control back into the equation?
I'm really not feeling too good about the direction this has had it for three four years now
I've been saying that this shit is gonna happen and now it's here. I'm getting scared
I've been saying that this shit is gonna happen and now it's here.
I miss the steps in which I need to take
I realize we'll be free from this violence in the rage
You might as well pass it through
Now break it through
And now break it through
And we can see
Now we're falling
We can see
That's right, slaves, make sure your cheapest firmly implanted
Make sure you're here in the voices in your head
We're all in K.O.T.
You can save
No, it's true
Here was on the Charlie
Gotta say there was another thing that kind of bothered me
I was spent the day yesterday with a charity
The Mickey and I do work for
And their largest donor by far
Who was a medical venture capitalist of in San Francisco
He actually told them
That he saw the future of the United States
It's a very bleak future
And he's actually going to New Zealand
To look at a house to buy for his escape
I know this guy and I'm like, wow, really?
That's his plan?
I thought Australia was the place to be
Maybe we need less people and more sheep
Could be the plan for me
That's where all zombies
And the other hand is the only child we know slowly
Take care
And the violence
Concepts, violence
We are, we must take care
Many you see, it's not me
It's not my family
But it's your letter
It's your letter
It's not my family
I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here
I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am there, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, I am here, here, I am here, here, here, here, I am here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here
We must be worth it again, it's the same oldie
There's 9, 16, in your head, in your head
There's still fire with their tanks, and their bombs
And their bombs, and their guns in your head
There's still fire with their tanks, and their guns in your head
There's still fire with their guns in your head
There's a revolution happening
There's still fire with their guns
There's still fire with their guns in your head
There's still fire