Delta Sierra Charlie 833 Happy Birthday Mom.
We're 16 months and 7 minutes and showing 5 rounds of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We're not in the city.
Created in the evening of life.
I know it's just a dream doctor.
Fantastic.
It's a matter of courage.
It's from our planet.
It's great time.
I know I know I gotta tell you now for one.
I know it's nothing but a hell of a hell of a death.
You just take it for one baby.
You can't stop breathing out of my heart
Hold up me, I'm going to see you
And I'll die for you, I'll die for you
But what I really want to know
I don't mind
And I've got to know
I've got to know my heart
We've always got this we were dreaming of good
We must think of each and we are ways
And through this bread it's back to world
We've got to know it's going to be wild
We've got to know it
And we can't wait to know about it
We've got to know it's going to be wild
And remember that love we've got the better we know
I've got to know it's going to be wild
Got to know
Say hello to my little friend
And go, I'm going to get in search for you
I've got to know it's going to be wild
I don't think there is a better way to kick off a footballer Friday than Monday
It is episode 833 of the Daily Source Code
Footballer Friday edition, hello everybody
How you doing? It's definitely quitting time
We've got some tunes that we got to rock and roll together
And a lot to talk about
Lay down that word
I can't give you what you want
But you got to come home to me
I've got to know it's going to be wild
I've got to know it's going to become wild
When I get throughué I'll need you gotta come running back before, oh
Those are rockin-one and up and down, ruckus, d sig
All these talking about your skills, do a Swiss roll-in
If you play little thing lemme laugh to cannot cause, ah, ah, ah, ah, damn
This it's rounded
More, more tears, no
Yeah
That's all
I'm out of the dozen, and I know I'm working too little
A little beam limit left, you can't know cause a mama, I'm show all the hannin' at it
Just around me, yeah
So all the hannin' down, oh yeah
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Now this is the way to kick off a weekend
Oh, oh yeah, oh yeah
Then the black clothes, more of Chris Robinson, the lead singer, so skinny, he had to run around the shower just to get wet
I hope you are looking forward to a break week at I am, it's been an unbelievable week for me
Sure to be talking about that, I'm just from our Friday, this is the Danny source code
And it is also a weird day for me, it is my mom's birthday, of course she passed away over three years ago
So I'm sure she's proud of me, you could see me right now with my beard
and my scruffy clothes should be like, oh my god
This is the way you became
You don't want to be a girl like that, maybe this could be the first time
This is the first time
Oh, oh, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Then the black clothes, more of Chris Robinson, the lead singer, so skinny, he passed away over three years ago
I'm hoping Jeff puts it up for sale, I think that's what he should do with it
I think he should put it on iTunes and make everybody go buy it
Because the guy's done so much for the Noah gender show
He laid this on me, and it's kind of a precursor to an album I think he's working on
Jeff's a guy who's been around podcasting for a number of years
He's done a whole bunch of jingles for this show
It really builds a little cottage industry out of it
But also it's had a tough time recently with his piano bar in Nashville
Mainly because of the flooding, so business is down
So when this comes out, I want you all to go and buy it
When his album comes out, you definitely have to go buy that
But when you hear this song, particularly if you are a fan of the show that takes place in the morning
You're going to trip out
It is the in the morning song, Jeff Smith on the Charlie
Jeff Smith on the Charlie
Jeff Smith on the Channel
From up on the hilltop
As the world occurs past bad
It's time
Same old history
Switching off the TV
Soon in and out watching the sky
It's a little bit cracked
But I didn't must kill it
Did you ride a kill in the mouth?
I've been doing how, here in the morning
I'm all doing how, here in the morning
It's nothing that old it is here in the morning
It's time to kill the morning
It's time to do it now, here in the morning
I want to do it now, here in the morning
It's nothing that old it is here in the morning
It's time to do it now, here in the morning
I want to do it now, here in the morning
It's nothing that old it is here in the morning
It's time to do it now, here in the morning
It's nothing too old
It's not here, not here
I can't tell if you're British or English бounds
I sure just met on the Charlie brand new
The Bean S alguns with her Noah alive in the morning
I, Jeff, I love your math
I really, really do
A Kit's ass
How many guys for give you your theme song is a gift?
Not many
This is Daily Source Code A 3-3
This is for survive edition with funky인 Copmt Duna
Oh, cool and add a ball, and I'm looking for some action
But like Big Jagger said, I can't get no satisfaction
The girls are all around
But none of them want to get with me
But they're at depression, I'm looking deaf
Yo, what's up, what have you all seen
The girl who's all jacking
At the other end, get a ball
Have a trick with some no name, just want to know that I'm a star
Someone got up the stove, dove
To the other side of the cantina
I asked the guy, why are you so fly?
He's never funky, comb it'd be enough
This brother told me a secret
On how to get more chicks
Put a little Medina here, your glass
And the girls are all real quick
It's better than any alcohol
Or have a dcac
A couple of sips with this love, both of it
Still long, long, long
So I gave some to my dog
When he began to beg
And then he looked his bowl
And he looked at me into the wild thing
Oh, my leg it
He scratched it bite me
Before he was much, much meaner
But now all the food is run
They're my house for the funky, comb it'd be enough
You know what I'm saying
I got a little big dog and my neighborhood
A break of them, I'm a dog
I got spurs with his feet
And Alex from his clothes
He won't leave my dog alone with that Medina girl
I wouldn't have to do this girl
He said, hi, my name is Sina
I thought she would be good to go
Or the little funky, old Medina
He said, I'd like a drink, I'll set a home
Okay, I'll go get it
And then a couple of sips with this girl
Listen to who they see with me
So I took my crib
And everything went well as planned
I thought she got a dress with a big old man
Sina was a man
So I threw a mouth, I don't throw the wrap
When the Oscar mile went up
You must be sure that's the girl
It's pure for the funky, combed Medina
You know
You know plans with a man
There's the 80s and I'll go with the lady
I'm a man
Break it down
You got a subwoofer
Now's the time to turn it up
I'm a man
Break it down
Look for a little affection
I took a shot, I took a test
You know, I'm the love
Be all you guess, boldest
And you know, they picked a winner
I took my date to the opening for Medina
I asked them dinner
She had a food drink, something and so on
What I'll be getting
She said she started talking about plans for a wedding
Still waiting, I love not so fast
The healthy Sina
That's why I fell, you don't play around
What the funky, combed Medina
You know what I was saying
Yeah Medina's a monster girl
The date is a masterpiece
I don't know Medina
The part of the airways is landed, and he's sounding good to me
This is the daily source cut
With Adam Curry
Oh yeah, you thought Tonlo was interested in the choice
I don't know
Remember the video for this one?
Flying up in the helicopter
Two problems with a baby
I think there was number one for weeks
Couldn't get it off the charts in the 80s
Eat the lover
ese lover
You'll get ahold on you
Believe in
Nigh your love
Before you know it, you'll beON YOUR MEAST
She's an easy lover
You'll take your heart that you won't be in
She's not the one
I know I love her, and I'm just trying to make you see
She's the kind of girl you dream of
Dream of keeping hold up
Better forget it
You'll never get it
You'll wear your mask and leave you
Leave you when it's safe you
Better forget it
Oh, you'll regret it
No, you'll never change it
So leave it, leave it
Get up, quick, cross the end
Leave it, you'll only wear it
You'll never know
She's the kind of girl you dream of
You'll get a hold on you, believe it
Like no other before you know it
You'll be on your knees
She's the kind of girl you dream of
She'll take your heart, but you won't be there
She's like no other
And I'm just trying to make you see
She's the kind of girl you dream of
You'll never change it
You'll never get it
She's the kind of girl you dream of
Oh, you'll regret it
I know it's trying to change it
Just leave it, leave it
You'll not be only one and see it
Then leave it, don't you only wear it
You'll never know
You'll never get it
She's the kind of girl you dream of
You'll never be there
She's like no other
She's the kind of girl you dream of
And I'm just trying to make you see
And I'm just trying to get it
She's the kind of kind of girl you dreamed
And I'm just trying to put
The last time I had the
You're your two heads taller and you've got hair. I hate you along there with the filibalee easy lover filibalee
Of course from earth when in fire another awesome awesome performer
Oh, it's a little note to self. I got to play reasons from earth when in fire
You know where all of a sudden he's like oh filibalee he's things so beautiful don't you agree. Oh, yes
Hey, wow, it's been quite a week for me. I spent the first three days in San Francisco
which is always
It's great to be
In the office with the the guys and gals although it's
Relatively tough to keep the no agenda show prep going
Of course, I'm leaving my laptop at home these days. I'm going 100% iPad and it's really working out
Although
little interesting experience I had I finally released my iPhone app called the big app show and
I highly appreciate not only all the promotion that everyone's done by retweeting and
Pointing pointing the show out to people
But also the trouble shooting as it seemed that we had some encoding issues and it therefore broke on older generation iPhones and
And iPod touches
And so here's you can only imagine in my hotel room
The thing is out. It's propagating through the the iTunes app stores worldwide and I'm getting like 15% of people saying hey man this thing don't work
Like what what after all after a month of rejection from the apple police
This is impossible
So
Once I once my buddy Rob Corver in the Netherlands figured out what it was
He he said well you got to re-encode the clips this way and by the way
I'm still working on a new encoding compression settings and schemes and Nick Mac at the office has helped me out with that
Because I think we can get it even better, but of course the videos have to work over Wi-Fi and 3G
Otherwise you have to label your app as a Wi-Fi only and I really didn't want to do that and
So I wound up
Accessing my laptop through the iPad
Through log me in
Log me in dot com is where you can it's kind of like a VNC type thing and they have an app for the iPad
It was not the easiest
Setting up compression settings and and compressing them all with the iPad, but it did work
Proving that even in a dire emergency
I still don't actually need a laptop in my possession when I'm on the road
So I'm very very excited about
About the feedback I think everyone now understands what I've been trying to accomplish with with the app
I did it right up at curry dot com if you want to see if you want to take a look at that
Actually I'll put a link in the show notes for that a daily source code dot com
I think that you know why I think I basically said it in my am I blog post
There's a hole in the whole discovery mechanism of apps that is big enough to drive a Mac truck through
And no one is able to really do
Screencast properly to demo their stuff and you know it takes a dumb guy like me who thinks very simply
To come up on the way to do that and just the response has been great and for the apps are featured
People like whoa wait a minute. What is this someone featured my app and it's working
It's helping people get more distribution for their apps which is exactly
Kind of what you do in radio so it makes so much sense to me and right after the show after I
Do my three by three workout, which I'm still on the program by the way
Room for three months for the three some has promised and I will collect in there will be cameras
Then I'm gonna cut a couple more shows so suggestions are always welcome
The thing I really want to do is show some really cool games, but I am such a non-gamer that I have no idea
What to show so if you got any cool ideas for
Games on the iPhone that I can show off in the next big app show I would love to hear from you
Drop me an email at a Maccurry dot com or add them at levio dot com
Parties we get ready for the weekend
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la le la la la la la la a la la la la la la la la la la l la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la sa la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la a la la la la
Oh, they, they sing, they play in our song
Rocks are gonna have a freemame workout
But you're gonna leave me fish with most of them
Take a man, take a fight!
Freddy, do you know what you need to be thinking about?
Freddy, do you know what you need to think about?
Freddy, do you know what you're thinking about?
Freddy, do you know what you mean about?
Freddy, will you stay with me for a while?
Freddy, do you know what you're thinking about?
Freddy, do you know what you need to be thinking about?
Freddy, watch out for two?
Freddy, Are you kidding me?
Freddy, do you know what you think about?
Freddy, Do you know what you need to think about?
Freddy, do you know what you need to think about?
Freddy, I know what you need to think about.
Freddy, Do you know what you need to think about?
It's like a roll, who'd you go off a try to eat three, three,
and put my pride in.
It's not through the winter first, so go away.
It was a night at the old town hall.
It was a good mother-child because they were waiting to death.
It's not through the winter first.
It's two years of old r69.
It's not through the winter nights.
I've been lighter, dear to all my life.
With love, love My love, love, love,
Love, love, they keep up the ring.
I've been a future, dear to you.
I ain't lost a breath, everything ain't pasted.
We've fallen in the grass and closed behind the bar
And I hear it's got to bring you like a fire alarm
I'm just a little drunk on out, it's crazy
There's someone who's saying, you are like a...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
She wrote that act, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I won't know what I'm talking about
When you're nothing really knocks me out
I'll get higher the time of your all-out to you
The most we're going to do is to you
Rock heroes who take you out
When you're nothing like you
It's been these measures
This is what's just about the point where I want to be cruising down Ventura Highway.
In a convertible with this song, jamming out Rick Derring to rock and roll, who's secured off the Charlie 833 football Friday edition.
As you know, a lot of the show was built up and produced from the people who listen to it.
If you are listening to this on the podcast, we usually do the football Friday live.
Some are around noon, get my nation westtime on Fridays, and I'm so sorry I haven't had time to do any other shows.
But on the other hand, I really love just grabbing a whole bunch of songs from iTunes, throw them in, throw them in, throw them in, throw them in, throw them in,
throw them in, oh, I'm stuck. And just jamming out with a whole bunch of buddies in the chat room. Hey, where's Bobby eating by the way?
I mean, today's the exact other day where I feel like we need a porn star to join us.
Anyway, so we've got some comic strip blogger coming up.
I'm sure he'll give us an interesting take on the European Union.
And right now, before it takes off on a two week holiday, it is Ray on the Charlie.
It's been a very busy week, but I'm finally facing two weeks off.
So, my vacation is starting with a beautiful sunny Pentecostal weekend, and I really could use a song that fits perfectly with this mood.
The soundtrack to my life.
First of all, I'm totally awake and I am not afraid.
This week, the Netherlands got a serious warning from El Qaeda.
Within two weeks, the world championship soccer will be played in South Africa.
And to hit up the event, the Iraqi government has released a video of a suspected Islamic extremist of El Qaeda.
The man claimed, during his arrest, that there are plans for attacks on the world cup.
On the same day, the Dutch National soccer team went to a training camp in Austria.
There was a serious warning of possible terrorist actions.
El Qaeda fighter El Qaeda would have considered to commit an attack on the Dutch National team and their fans.
The guy has been detained in Iraq.
He also gets such a weird feeling, are they messing with our fear again?
No way, man, we are going to kick some ass over there.
I mean, we got a rough elephant apart.
This leads to the Ryan Babel in Clash and Undal Arts.
All big, international soccer players.
We are not afraid of anything.
But first, we got to deal next week with the Euroficient Songcome past, and the Norwegian capital has long.
I mean, talking about big names, aren't?
The Netherlands is going to send sneak up a lovely Dutch girl.
You all probably understand for this song, at least we need a typical Dutch sound.
Something like a Herry Gurdie.
And then we add a little bit of brain control.
I mean, this refrain man really got snuggled in your head.
So I'm going to play just a little fragment.
It's still in this fragment.
This is so embarrassing.
I mean, we can't be sending anything like this.
We've got some better artists in the Netherlands.
Brexit.
Just a beat up tempo song with a international sound and a rough, tough rock chain.
Let me tell me how to get to Jerusalem because I have kind of lost my way.
So will you help me get the rat class as I can tomorrow might be too late.
I know I'm not sure.
I haven't changed it to myself.
I have.
You all think I know I'm a show.
I need some artists because they're me out as hell.
Just a smile.
You have me for what I've been to the Netherlands.
Oh well, we're going to keep Belgium 10 boys.
And then they give the same points back.
Actually, it's just one.
It's something each other's boss contest.
Why am I even bothering you with this stuff?
That really.
So I have them.
Congratulations, which you're first iPhone app.
Well done.
Thank you.
I don't have an iPhone, so I can't follow your new creative artwork.
But I'm certain you're going to be the man again.
So to wrap it up, two weeks ago, there was a request at the no agenda chat about
a new soundtrack to your life episodes.
Right.
So let's combine that with a perfect song to kick off a sunny weekend in Kitmo Nation
Lowlands.
And it's a song you like at him because of the great memories on a time when 45s were just
the day's version of ads.
Oh, he's been new all the time.
He's from 24 years ago when it was a beautiful sunny spring in the Netherlands.
In 1986, there were the brothers.
What a full belief.
Thank you for the morning.
My fellow technical head.
She came from somewhere back in a long ago.
She said, remember, fool comes.
She tried hard to recreate and forget yet to recreate.
That's in her life.
She missed us all smart.
For his nostalgia table.
Never come in there but you wanted to save.
Only to realize.
It never really was.
You see, we had a place in his life.
He had a man half the dice.
As he rises to her apology.
Everybody else puts you in the dark.
He's got you right going.
But he can't see.
The wise man has to go back.
To be the way.
I see.
To be.
Just by the way.
Nothing at all.
Keep shining in the sun.
Why don't you give me a lot of gold?
Where he can still believe there's a place in life.
Someday, someday.
She will return.
She had a place in his life.
He loved her man half the dice.
As he rises to her apology.
Everybody else puts you in the dark.
He's got you right going.
But he can't see.
To be the way.
All right, Ray.
You totally made up for that Eurovision track you played.
The chair went wild.
My ears are bleeding out of my rectum.
As a Eurovision song cast contest.
So focused yet.
You can't not help watching.
I used to love watching it on the BBC.
He would always have the most sarcastic commentary.
But he stopped doing it.
Someone in Brussels got all pissed off and were angry.
Actually, we're on the topic of Europe.
We might as well welcome our old friend back for a moment here.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip.
Hello, I have a personal agenda.
You know, John and I got a kick out of you saying that every single time.
But you also had a digital agenda.
It's a five year plan when all your citizens should have brought plans by 2013 and later,
even with about 100 megabits per second.
Yeah, I was reading about this.
There was two stories that came in about the European Union.
But in owners of the United States of Europe, one is they want to harmonize all women's
dress sizes, which I find highly entertaining.
And the other one is that everyone should have broadband approved by your government, of course.
Well, we all know what that's good for.
So you see Adam, that you stands for faster pawn down.
So you must be good.
Right, yeah.
Yo.
I'm in my pain with this thing.
Thank you, CSB.
I can stop driving 120 now.
Killing me softly with this song.
Killing me softly.
Slow down.
And get into the room.
I say set the crews that are about.
It was 73.
It's one of the jam kicks in on the food cheese.
It really is nice.
With his song.
Yeah.
This is my cleft reference.
It's where I think about this little face in the head.
Why am I on this road, hang on my girl now?
One time, one time.
Hey, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
You got the lyrics.
I heard he sang her good song.
I heard he had a style
And so I came to see him
And it seemed for a while
And there he was this young one
Straying to do my ass
From in my pain with his finger
Singing my life with his words
Feeling me softly with this song
Telling my heart with his words
I fell off lost with fever
It never stopped around
I felt he found my letter
He's what I know
I pray that he's worth happiness
But he just kept riding a horse
From in my pain with his finger
Singing my life with his words
Feeling me softly with his song
Telling my heart with his words
Feeling me softly with this song
Feeling me softly with his song
Feeling me softly myś
Feel me softly with his song
Because of course the language of music is so universal.
We lost a great one, I think it was Friday or Saturday, I found out that Ronnie James
Deo had passed.
Now I had just seen him at the Golden Gods Awards in Los Angeles a couple weeks ago.
And of course, I didn't really have a personal relationship with Ronnie, but you know,
I interviewed him a couple times and had bangers ball and I think I've been to a
one or two show.
Maybe one show.
And it's really, really sad, I mean, the first thing I thought was like, I got a call
Rudy.
Rudy Sarzo, not my buddy, he was playing bass for Deo.
And he was a distraught man, it was unbelievable, he was just like, yes, it's so messed up
because he had just gone through six weeks of intense, really intense chemo and radiation,
which is just completely F. And he didn't make it, which, you know, he had a tour plan,
they had a new album plan, he had just set up a new record company, he was, you know,
and there's a lot of infrastructure and a lot of people around the guy like Ronnie James
Deo, crew, band members, you know, office people and it's just, it's really, it's so,
so sad.
That's all it is.
And he's really sad.
And musically, he will be incredibly missed, but it'll always be Ronnie James Deo,
our rainbow in the dark.
When there's a lightning, you know it always brings me down, call to free and I'll
see that it's me, it was the last thing you've ever found, I cry for you, I've been
dancing in the night, it was cold, lost my head to the sky over the night, no sign of the
morning party, you've been left on your own, like a rainbow in the dark, a rainbow in the
dark.
Do your demons, do they have a lot to go, when you're trying to be hiding inside, is it so
fun that you know, you're just a picture, you're in the image constantly, we were late,
you were going, you were lost without a rise, there's no sign of the morning party,
you've been left on your own, like a rainbow in the dark, just a rainbow in the dark, yeah,
I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I
cry for you, I cry for you, I cry, cry for you, I cry for you, I cry for you, I cry, I cry with you, I cry for you, I cry for you, go away, now, let me be back my heart that takes me to believing in you,
Call it free, and I see that the street
Who's in the house, who's in the door
Who's in the magic
I feel it proud to be here
But it's here, and you're here
Calling you away, stuck out
Just the cycle of learning for me
There's no sign of the day
Lupin, let's know you're home
You're a rainbow
You're a rainbow in the dark
Yeah, yeah
Just the rainbow in the dark
You'll sign of the night
Rest in peace, Ronnie James Dio
Rainbow in the dark
Oh man, I will miss that guy
That's the crap that happens when you get older
You see all these people who you've been working with
And have hung out with and have loved their art
Just slowly fading away
Screw that man
Hey, happy anniversary, just a transition for a second
Happy anniversary Marcus Couch
Five years of the scene scene
I was just cruising through my email
Saw that he sent in a couple of tracks
Recommendations for the footballer Friday
Well, sight unseen as usual
Because you can always trust Marcus Couch
To come up with a good
K9, that's when I fuck things up again
I'm not a fool, I'm not a fool
The only happy well after this is not so easy
I should be your only sad
When I'm in the middle of the street
Only everything that makes me trust your hands
I know everything you do
That's when I fuck things up again
That's when I'm in the middle of the street
I'm not a fool, I'm not a fool
That's when I fuck things up again
Happy anniversary Marcus Couch
Five years of the scene scene scene scene
I'm not a fool, I'm not a fool
That's when I fuck things up again
That's when I'm in the middle of the street
I'm not a fool, I'm not a fool
I'm a fool, I'm not a fool
sapphire, that's when I'm in the middle of the street
I know it's the thing's all
It's just that you think it's the last round
What things are the chance?
Oh, I'm Marcus, you didn't have to disappoint
Yes, you did
Yes
Kage 9, that's when I fucked things up again
Completely right on target for the full bar Friday
It's the beginning of Daddy's Tour Scode Episode 3, 3, 3, May 21, 2010
Let me guide you through the tracks and the soundtrack of your life
Member Jay Ferguson, Thunder Island
It's not here's a little light
The moment you're with me
Think in the sun with your hair I'm done
Can you hear me now coming in there and coming
Come across the bay
We see someone steak
We laugh it in the hi-tit
Chase a blow
Out of thunder
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you guys, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I love a close until the storm passed and we fell down laughing in the wet grass
What the body's drying in the sunshine sweet sunshine
So shine light, light, light, light, light, light, light, light
In the sun with your dress I'm done
Now I'll be by the way and I'll be naked to little the deeper
I'll remember the night in the cool sand, make it look
I don't find the right hand
See this beauty in the red sky
Hey
Night in the fresh everything
I need you
All that I want is oh
And guys, so very bad influence on me.
I still got the housekeepers running around and like, FTW.
We always got the guy who was strange, but he's sitting there with a two-day beard growth
in the sweatpants with a grungy t-shirt on.
Of course, Miss Mickey's nowhere to be found today.
That's why I can kind of look the way I want to look.
Oh man, I am so loving the sound that I've got coming out of the rack that these songs,
this type of song sounds good again.
Requested by Paul Boyer, it's a good security song.
TSA?
Fuck you.
Donald Fagan on the Charlie.
Security Joan, listen to the lyrics, I think you're like this.
I guess I'm in it America, the files don't make my life.
I had to get to get to see the team, and it was still where I saw him.
The song is standing in my carry on like, it's off the X-ray machine.
It's been a change of faith in heaven, I still used to step behind the screen,
and when I felt someone to bother me, to know that I felt so clean,
now you won't find my name on your little table.
If I look at you in the mirror, I'll just keep my shoes myself on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, we are
No more love, love, love forever
Thank you for joining me
You nåt much such thing?
I'm thinking we, uh, yeah, I just want to keep in this vibe for a minute and I look
super quest.
If you're in the chat room, let me know what you want to hear, I'll see if I can find
that an iTunes.
Jam it in, I'm just charming.
I'm thinking we're in the chat room, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just
I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm just charming, I'm justRIS White White
But those of you wondering why it sounds like Steely Dan, that's because of course Donald
Fagan was the driving force and I would say was he not the lead singer of Steely Dan
makes so much sense.
Doesn't it?
Okay, so I've opened up the chat room to do a couple of requests and I'm already seeing
things roll by that I think are excellent choices, so let me try this one out for size
home on the second and it's just got to load up oh this is a cool idea I don't know
I just kind of got in the vibe and like yeah let's just place some songs man let's share
some music together thank you for the 10cc requests iTunes fulfilled my search holy crap
have I not put this in a long time one of the very first music videos the dread like holiday
the brown and the state of fright I saw for faces one man the brother from the gutter
they look me up and down the depth and turn to each other
I say I don't like cricket though hello I love it though I don't like cricket though
I don't like cricket though I don't like cricket though I don't like cricket though
I don't like cricket though I don't like cricket though
I don't like cricket though