Delta Sierra Charlie 839 of the Snapfoo Saturday Edition.
With 16 months to set,
we've been showing five nights of time.
The 21st century of radio stars here.
You know, we lost.
Can't hear me now, live.
I know a gender-stricken driver.
Fantastic.
It's fellow curry.
Woo!
I just thought of you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, keep out
What the hell is this?
I thought of you getting a tip out
Touch me
I've never heard of you
It's nothing
Don't talk to yourself
I'll tell you
Can't tell you
What the hell is this?
Oh, the costal, the costal, the ticket, the ticket, the ticket
In the morning
Oh my god, there is no one's going to be there
It's just a nice
Oh, so bad
All in love
Cause you're the ones
How will we be afraid of
No, no
I ain't going. Come on
Screw it
Hubsanous
That's not a war
But handout
Put them up on your story
The stance you get
That's not a war
Is that what you get
Hubsanous
I'm always hurt
Here, fuck it
You're not a war
My old
I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I
I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way, I'm on my way,
The more everybody's coming to you, coming overcasts, once you say partially overcasts,
Southern California, that would be the people's Republic, this is the Daily Source Code episode
eight thirty nine on Saturday, the 10th of July 2010, snap with Saturdays and other night,
like the full bar Friday, so don't make your ears bleed immediately. We take a little bit of time,
kind of ease into it, and boy, I've had quite a week. It was the longest shortest week I've ever witnessed.
First, we had the fourth and fifth July celebrations. Don't you know that I was in messages?
I've had my chance to make it happen, but in the end, I wanted to play, but I ain't back in my life.
No, I've got to have the people who said keep playing a battle rocket roll, keep doing what you've been told.
Oh, say your money up when you get old, got to be, tell your better rock and move.
So I picked up and I made it up to blue, y'all, when my world was a baby, you saw.
In one through with fucking news, yeah, saying it and playing the job.
Johnny was making a big turn, and this thing was throwing this way, hey,
but we ain't back in my life. No, I've got to have the people who said keep playing a battle rocket roll,
keep doing what you've been told. We say your money up when you get old, got to be, tell your better rock and move.
Oh, say your money up when you get old, got to be, tell your better rock and move.
Oh, say your money up when you get old, got to be, tell your money up when you get old, got to be, tell your better rock and move.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Hell yeah.
Keep on playing.
I will obey.
Johnny, have your winter.
You gotta keep on playing that rock and roll.
I can't roll.
Oh, man, you guys seen his so many good tunes for me to play today.
I am just ready to roll them all out one after another.
And nice cool breeze wouften up to the hilltop, watch tower, crack pot,
command center is way the rock and roll for you.
Yeah.
You gotta kind of get into the mood.
You know, I'm not quite sure exactly what the vibe is going to be today.
We're going to go back and forth just a little bit.
But I got some bits for you.
And some music that will educate you.
And it's also good for your soul.
And we got some shit to talk about.
Oh, sure.
Make a plans for Nigel X.
Do you see how the Charlie?
We're only making plans for Nigel.
We only won what's best for him.
Nigel just needs that helping him.
I think young Nigel says he's happy.
He must be happy.
He must be happy in his world.
We're only making plans for Nigel.
Nigel just needs that nice form.
And he likes to speak.
He loves to be spoken to.
His happy name is one.
We're only making plans, but I knew
We only won what's best for him
I knew just needs this outfit I knew
And if your night just says he's happy, he must be happy
He must be happy, he must be happy in his world
We only won what's best for him
We're only making plans, but I knew
And Nigel's one lucky bastard, Annie
Next to you see making plans for Nigel on the Charlie's Snaps
From Saturday, Adhesion, for July 10th, 2010
We've got some good news, there is now an official official official
DSC iPhone app that will give you access to all of the episodes
As well as the stream, so you can find that in the show notes that is sourcecode.com
And of course when that goes to the Apple store, the app store now and find it if you so wish
Oh man, what a week it's been pretty crazy
Mickey celebrated her 40th birthday
We had a nice little party, a celebration here on Thursday
With an interesting mix of people
I was like 50, 60 people here
I really didn't realize we had so many friends in Los Angeles
And we had TV stars, movie stars, porn stars, food stars
Yeah, people who are way into food
We had artists, we had musicians, it was really awesome
It was good, I think I'm still a little bit hung over though
I just got it
I got an ease into it all, that's what the Snaps who Saturdays are all about
So we go back and forth and of course a bit later on I will attempt to make your ears bleed
As we roll out the harder stuff
The Snaps who Saturdays the Charlie A39er with the Eagles
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I'm a little different, you know, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, just Tuarez wasn't A passing piece, yeah, yeah!, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
When I need it now
Ooh, you and the ginger garlic
Come on, a hand choose where I'm going to stand
You get your baby one who is nice
I wanna be your star
Who hurt you?
Who wanna be your star?
Who wanna be my star?
Who can feel you?
Who wanna be your star?
I can't feel how I'm just white
I wanna stand in love
Who is both of my heart
Who can feel you?
Who wanna be your star?
Who wanna be your crazy crazy crazy
Who wanna be my star?
Who can feel you?
They actually have forgotten mention
They'll make it in her intensive acting course today
And she had a whole bunch of her acting buddies over
For the party as well
Oh my god
Just like a bunch of hot little actresses running around
Then every single time she introduced me to wonder
Like, Hey, wanna get in the hot tub?
She's become kind of running joke
But I think I might actually pull it off
One of these days
all the girls might come over and hang out.
Mickey knows how to throw a party, man.
She's like, hey, I invited a whole bunch of good-looking girls.
Ha ha ha.
Yay.
Totally loved that.
That was good.
He was good.
And so by the way, those of you on the stream,
screaming for a mismicky, she's just not here today.
Which means that I can sit here in my unshaveness
with my t-shirt on and do my thing.
Which is sharing all the awesome tunes with you guys on the Charlie.
Episode 839
Isn't it the way these sad girls?
Let's forget all that and give me the number if you can't find it.
So I can't call just to tell them I'm finding to show.
How to become the float.
I learned to take it well.
I'll never wish my words would just convince myself
that it just wasn't real.
But that's not the way it feels.
I've already gone.
Go could you help me please this call?
I can't read the number that you just gave me.
There's something in my eyes.
You know it happens every time.
So think about the love that I thought would save me.
What isn't that the way these sad girls?
Let's forget all that and give me the number if you can't find it.
So I can't call just to tell them I'm finding to show.
Over call the float.
I've learned to take it well.
I'll never wish my words would just convince myself that it just wasn't real.
But that's not the way it feels.
No, no, no, no.
That's not the way it feels.
I'll never read all.
Let's forget about this call.
No one there.
I really wanted to talk to.
Thank you for your time.
How you been so much more than kind.
You keep the time.
Isn't that the way these sad girls?
Well, let's forget all that and give me the number if you can't find it.
So I can't call just to tell them I'm finding to show.
Over call the float.
I've learned to take it well.
I'll never wish my words would just convince myself that it just wasn't real.
But that's not the way it feels.
Oh, yeah, I haven't heard this song and so long.
Jim Krochi, another guy that I miss.
They're good.
This that he brought to the world.
Operator on the daily source code.
The snafu set are the additions.
We kind of roll into it all and wake up nice and slow.
I have, uh, I got some love man the other day.
I got some massive massive love and I want to give it right back in the mail.
On Thursday afternoon, couldn't have come at a better time.
Of course, we had the party going on and the mailman rings the bell.
He's got two packages for me.
One from my good friend, Mr. oil, who I believe is in the chat room.
Now, it's no agenda chat.com and from Charles known as CQ and they both sent me
massive quantities of old hole burn rolling tobacco.
Got me some, uh, risla ultra long king size slim rolling papers.
You know, this will be good for at least another six weeks.
I cannot tell you how much that touches me.
It really does. I mean, it's, you know, it's, it's obviously it's not about the money, uh,
and neither of these guys will take any, uh, reimbursement for, uh, for sending this to me.
But it's the, you know, the trouble.
So, I want to go through the trouble to, to buy packs of tobacco, which are just unavailable here
in the United States and send them to me because they know how, how happy it makes me.
It really does. I am so incredibly happy and thankful. I really, really appreciate it.
And, uh, I love you guys. That's the best kind of value for value you could have given me.
I'm telling you better than any type of donation. I love you.
I know if you know what I mean.
The loss of me is to talk on a cereal box, really, which I, uh,
is a smile on a dough. I'm not aware of too many things.
I know what I know of, didn't know what I mean to do.
Yeah, show me the share of what, before I give to you.
What I am is what I am you, what you are, what, what I am is what I am you, what you are,
Oh, how to wear, you many things, I know what I know if you know what I mean.
The loss of me is to talk on a cereal box, really, which I,
like before, I'm not aware of too many things. I know I love you, I am me.
To do yet.
Show me the shallow water before I teach you to do.
What I have is what I have you, what you want.
How I live, how I live, how I live, how I live, how I say I see I say oh you, yeah.
Why are you so many things looking this beautiful, you're not going to know that I read, write, write.
Yeah, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
She'll meet the shell of one before our empty city She'll meet the shell of one before our empty city
Show me in the shallow water, be bucketed to deep
Water, don't let me get to deep
Don't let me get to deep
I remember the first time I heard that song on the radio
I was driving into New York City from the garden state from New Jersey
It's like, holy crap
I love this
The sound, the Edybrokelle's voice, it's the whole thing, just really fit together nicely.
Edybrokelle, the new bohemians on the snafu setter edition of the Charlie episode A39er,
we've got a full chat room where the party, of course, really takes place.
Let's turn it up a little bit past 10, shall we?
Maybe, by the time we get to mid-Song, we'll turn it up to 11.
I got to tell you the story about this song, too, we've never heard of it before.
How it came about?
Well, the Charlie smoked on the water.
Why doesn't Calvehwood work in this second?
Well, we didn't have much time, but things have happened a lot more, but I have the best ways around.
The song, stupid, we're the player.
Turn the face to the ground.
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly.
Let's turn it down again and win the house.
It's not the world of all sound.
I've come to call the party dinner now.
Oh, it gives out the ground.
When it all comes over, we had a flat and another player.
The Swiss town was coming out.
It seemed to be a bit busy waiting to be Black.
ball-down, we did it.
No!
You
Don't
Throw
Do
All right, whenever you get hit a little bit of cowbell, the sun just comes out and starts
shining, love and smoke on the water, deep purple on the Charlie, hey there was one of
Mickey's actors friends, we were talking about cowbell at the party and he did the perfect
James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, Bruce Dickinson imitation from
the Saturday Night Live Skid and I think I actually literally pissed my pants, it was so
incredibly awesome, oh yes, nothing like a little bit of cowbell to get you going in the
morning, okay, let's see if we can look at it and split with this one, thanks for all
the suggestions you guys sent in and really really helped with the preparation, it's
killing joke, love like blood, on the snap of Saturday Charlie,
what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does
it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it
know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not
James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson
what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does
it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not
James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson
what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not
what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson
what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know
not James Dickinson, what does it know, not
James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson
what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson
Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson, what does it know, not James Dickinson
I do not follow the world cup as you know, but I believe Germany and Uruguay are playing right now battling out for third and fourth place boy, that must suck major balls when you're not allowed to win and you have to play for third and fourth place
of course we'll talk more about that tomorrow in the morning on the Norwegian to show as we know that the fix is in
to be too small size that's better after all to close to climb a quintet to a screw sazine
let's see the spends and out of the van a line in the outside far and raise the rice
life's too short there's not marijuana one size fits all to close to climb the track
so what's the problem? let's go as quick to pay me now pay for the lead life's too short
so what's the problem?
you must obey me
what's the problem?
it's the start of this event way back in 2008 the Netherlands reached the third world cup final with a
three-two win over Uruguay in an exciting semi-final in Ketown on Tuesday the Dutch will play the final match against Spain for the ultimate prize of football at
the city on Johannesburg on Sunday so only good orange grays around here I'm sure you'll understand that
however the only media reporting story about a 14-year-old boy who has paid the highest price for his and to shatham for the world cup
the neighbor shot the kid because he blew a little too long on his fuzella the cruise on incident took place two weeks ago
but it's only now brought out by the authorities the young South African has just watched the match South Africa friends
a blue after a two-one victory for his homeland on his fuzella his neighbor probably couldn't handle the sound of that beautiful piece of instrument
a shut the boy down with three bullets he had two conchet wounds in the head and one in his arm
the teenager was still thinking too hospital but died from his injuries
so that's a kind of whole different world cup story huh but you will be reading this in our newspapers
so there's gotta be a positive side on this whole world cup championship
oh yeah Dutch porn star Bobby Teden will treat a twitter followers with a blowjob
her account crew to 60,000 members so she's going to be very busy for a while
I mean our government can offer us such a nice deal so please please God
I have to talk to God now please let us beat the kingdom of Spain and there will be blow jobs all over
Amen
If the Netherlands become the world champion it completes to an additional economic growth of around a half percent
but even without the Dutch economy gets a clear boost
it's all about trust that's basically it and because of the confidence we'll find it easier to spend money
the government are now in the growth of 1.25% this year and 1.75% for the next year
big companies can score with the championship
a much more importantly the Netherlands will get a use exposure in the world
so yeah at this point we don't need a government we just want to win the golden cup
it's going to be an exciting weekend in the lower countries
so my fellow chuckleheads would you please please all keep your fingers crossed
save a little prayer for the Dutch economy
thank you
I'm going to wish you all a very nice weekend
that by now
this is a Norwegian stream and daily source code special report
as reported I believe live during one of the most recent daily source codes
the no agenda official no agenda porn princess and of course adult film star Bobby Eden
has promised through her twitter account
blow jobs to every twitter follower
should the Netherlands win the world cup now from what I understand
the western media has been
visually pursuing Bobby to get her on for an interview to talk about this
and Bobby Eden has chosen the no agenda stream and daily source code audience
to do the only and exclusive interview about this promise
and so I'm very proud to welcome Bobby Eden to the stream Bobby how you doing
it's very good how are you
I'm great first question most importantly what are you wearing right now
nothing
I know you're lying to me I know you're lying to me
Bobby what's going on tell me what's happening this is like a huge media storm
I know it's fantastic
and well as you said
at comments to this then a free blow job
all my future followers do you have exactly on your twitter account
I'm like 30,000 or 31,000
30,000
so in one day, 20,000
so that's like three every second Bobby
I don't know how you're going to do that now you you actually
if I remember your tweet properly you promised that a number of your
associates and colleagues are going to help you out with this endeavor
who else is in on the scheme with you
and see if it's in the secret
so they're all all in so we're team BJ
team BJ
BJ
and now will you be a dressed in orange as you pay off this this wonderful
dead of yours of course with my nice orange set dress
oh lovely now
what if the Netherlands doesn't win I mean you're obviously you know you're trying
to help the team orange win by motivating everybody what if they don't win then
what happens
well then probably nobody gets a free blow job
then it's really sucks
actually it won't suck is it's what you're saying
that would be horrible okay so we say we all have to it to root for
yes of course and then going away so there is actually no chance they're going to lose
Bobby where where will we be able to collect our prize
come after the weekend I guess
best we can not me I will tell you everything where to collect it
and so we just to keep an eye on your on your twitter feed I guess
of course
oh man I'm so excited about this you know and miss Mickey also wants to blow job
by the way
yeah you can't do anything else for Mickey
okay
mmm nice
as long as I can take pictures
so Bobby you're still in the Netherlands or that way
yeah you're still in the Netherlands right now
yes I still have
I'm leaving the third week of July
I want to fly to the country and uh I'm leaving for my tour
So I'm just going to make more people happy.
So tell me about the tour, where will this take you?
I'm sure it's going to stay.
It has a nice holiday and meeting of course with Stakey.
And I will be doing shows in Finland, Germany, Holland, France, and World of
World Tour continues.
Can you do a list?
Sorry.
No, I was going to ask if you're going to do any shows in the United States, anything
while you're here, or is that just pure vacation?
Yes, pure vacation.
What exactly do you want to meet up with you?
Yes.
And how make you, isn't it like hell yet?
Gone away.
What exactly can the fans expect from one of your shows?
Well, on the most shows, I do have a list against you, sir.
I'm doing a very good friend of mine.
So we do the lesbian shows.
Oh, nice.
So everything.
And we do sign names and they can take pictures with us.
It's a beautiful thing.
Yeah, it's a beautiful thing.
Have you had a party?
Do you have any new movies coming out soon?
Or did anything that's that shot that still has to be released?
Or do you have any plans?
Yes.
Everything will come on on my new site.
Bobbyeeterlife.com.
Oh.
And so I've been shooting a shooting and shooting.
But there's nothing else that's with my new books on video.
Oh, that's cool.
We get to see it.
The new boobs, right?
Yeah.
We see.
So are these your own productions or are these, yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
Have you ever worked for vivid entertainment?
No.
I have so many many costumes for them.
Mm-hmm.
But I never, no, I never did something for them.
No, because, you know, the house that we're in now here in the Hollywood Hills,
the Hilltop Watch Tower, Crackpot Command Center, apparently has been featured in many vivid entertainment
productions.
I'm just trying to find out which ones and I was, you know, had this.
The only certificate ones or the other ones, too, because maybe I've done something.
I mean, your house already.
I know.
Bobby, have you come by?
Hey, I know this place.
I know.
I have been over here.
I don't know if it's specifically vivid.
The neighbors weren't that clear about it.
But, well, because it's always secretly there.
Extremely.
Well, and then they always say, please just park the car somewhere else.
Yeah, park it.
Oh, all the inside secrets to the adult film industry.
Right now.
Extremely.
Everybody, I love it.
Well, we certainly look forward to welcoming you here to the studio in a couple of weeks
time when you're on your holiday.
And maybe we can do a little interview from the hot tub out here on the deck.
Of course.
Oh, I'm such a lucky bag.
Oh, wait.
You don't make it.
Of course.
Are you kidding?
Yeah.
I've been working out.
I've got them on this program.
Yeah.
I've had them on the three-byte.
It's a long story.
But it's three months.
And then I get a special prize.
It's, I'll tell you when you're here.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm curious.
Something you might be curious now.
So Bobby, well, are you,
as an in-special preparations or any exercises you're doing to get ready for you?
I'm training my job.
All right.
Well, we will certainly be rooting for a team orange for the Netherlands.
I've changed my stance now.
I go orange all the way.
And on Monday, I guess we'll figure out exactly where and how we can collect once
you post this either on on your Twitter, which is at Bobby Eden or Bobby Eden.
Bobbi EdenLive.com is at our.nl. What is it?
It's dot com.
Dot com.
Great.
Bobby, it's been a pleasure talking to you as always.
And well, I hope you, I hope you make it through next week.
It's going to be a rough one.
I just go for the next team.
The greats, Bobbi Eden, everybody, right here.
I know you're just stream.com and dailysourcecode.com.
Thank you.
You know that it would be untrue.
You know that I would be alive.
If I was to say...
You know that it would be untrue.
You know that I would be alive.
If I was to say...
You know that it would be untrue.
To you...
Girl, we couldn't get my try out.
Come on, baby life out out out out out out.
There's no time to follow in the Maya.
Now that we can only lose
And I love become a funeral fire.
Come on baby, light fire fire.
Come on baby, light fire.
Try to set the light on fire, no.
Come on baby, light fire fire.
Where you know that it would be a truth.
And you know that I would be alive.
If I was to go and tell you,
Mama, we couldn't get much higher.
Here come on baby, light fire.
Come on baby, light fire fire.
Come on baby, light fire.
Come on baby, light fire, no.
Where you know that it's all right.
Come on baby, light fire fire fire.
Come on baby, light fire fire.
And girl, girl, you better
Light my fire with you
You better light
You better light my fire
And we're gonna get my child
Oh, come on there
Jose Fili Siano, light my fire
You know, I, before I ever heard the door's version
I heard this one
I remember my dad singing this
As he played guitar at home
It's just so beautiful
And once again, thanks to adult superstar Bobby Eden
for giving the exclusive interview to the Data Source Code
in No Agenda stream audience
And it really is true
She was being hounded by media all over
Gitmo Nation lowlands
And she decided
No, I'm not gonna give it to those guys
They're never there when I need some promotion
So and by the way
Probably the most listened to
Data Source Code episode ever
Which kind of gives you food for thought of working
Doing the right thing by playing just music here
Or maybe we need to do more porn stars
You know, it's a thought
I went to a garden party
To reminisce with my old friends
The chance to share old memories
Play a songs again
When I got to the garden party
They all knew my name
No one recognized me
I didn't look the same
But it's all right now
I learned my lesson well
You see it?
You can't please everyone
So you've got to please yourself
People came for miles around
Everyone was there
You'll go abroad
There was magic in the air
And over in the corner
Watched to my surprise
The stir Hughes hidden Dylan shoes
Wearing his disguise
But it's all right now
Learn my lesson well
You see it?
Can't please everyone
So you've got to please yourself
Let it stand down
Played them all the old songs
But that's why they came
No one heard the music
We didn't look the same
I said hello to Mary Lou
She belongs to me
And it's saying a song about a song
It was time to leave
But it's all right now
I learned my lesson well
You see it?
Can't please everyone
So you've got to please yourself
Let it stand down
Someone opened up
A closet door
And outstep the journey be good
Laying guitar like a ring in a bell
And looking like a shoe
You've got to play garden parties
I wish you a lot of luck
But it's memories
You're all I sang
I'd rather drive a truck
But it's all right now
I learned my lesson well
You see it?
Can't please everyone
So you've got to please yourself
Let it stand down
See I got to give you guys a little bit of musical education
Because they don't make songs like this
anymore
Ricky Nelson
Father to the Nelson twins
If you remember those blond ambition boys
All right now
They had a couple hits in there
I think they were very early 90s
And he Nelson then
He was quite a rebel in his time
Unfortunately he passed away in a plane crash
And the story goes that they were free-basing cocaine
And then the cabin of the plane caught on fire
Hey man if you got to go you might as well go down in flames
You know what I'm saying?
All right
They don't play this on the radio
I guarantee you that
It's too long
And too sexy
We want you to have a real good chance
Because that's just what we have in mind
Is that all right with you?
Now this is a tool that I can hold
And it's called tonight
Is the night
That you make me want
Now I never intended recording the song
It was a personal point
That isn't till the day that my producer
Happened to throw through the pages of my notebook
He came across the words and he said
We got to do something with these words
It's happening every day
And people want to hear about it
Benny
You see
It's the story
Of a young girl
Making love
For the very first time
Now
When I finally got a melody
I took it home and I
I played it for my mother
I got to tell you a little bit about my mother
You see I come from one of those pretty large families
And I'm the baby of the family
And you know you never grow up to your mother
I never forget the way she looked at me
When I played it for as she said
I like the music
You know baby
The melody is really nice
But I know you're not going to sing that song
But you used to write all that
And if it came one of my biggest records to me
So I want you to do this for me if you will
Every night
Think back
To your very first time
Now give it a little while longer
Because I know some of you have to think back a little bit further than others
Come on now
Won't you play ketchup
And I don't want you wait till I get to give it a massage for you
Oh yeah now
And now
Now
Whether it was good
Or you just smile
And it was good
Or on the other hand
If it was not so good
Here's my stone
Tonight is the night
That you
Make me a warm mind
You said you bitchin' on me
And I hope you leave
I'm nervous
And I'm trembling
I'm waiting for you to walk in
I'm trying hard to relax
But I just can't keep still
No
I can't get your car to stand
I won't play bigger and put all this success man
But I know so little about what love is
I just can't help acting like a child
And I can't do my job
And you're ringing my bell
Hope you're not impatient
After waiting so very long
Or hold me up for you
With my silly hands
And we're both going up to know
I don't know
Tonight is the night
That you
Make me a warm mind
You said you bitchin' on me
And I hope you leave
I'm nervous
And I'm trembling
I'm waiting for you to walk in
I'm trying hard to relax
But I just can't keep still
No
I can't get your car to stand
I won't play bigger and put all this success
But I know so little about what love is
I just can't help acting like a child
And I hope you're not impatient
I won't play bigger and put all this success
I just can't help acting like a child
And I hope you leave
I'm trying hard to relax
I can't just do it what we are doing
Not only will I never realize
But my whole family relationship
It'll all be ruined
I'm only going into my land
All to turn around
So let's just pray
I truly love this world without
I just can't help
Tonight
Oh, I'll never forget
No, no, I'll never forget
Tonight
That's what you made me feel
You made me feel
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Yeah, I won't play bigger and put all this success
I just can't help acting like a child
And put all this success
But I know so little about what love is
And I know it might be too much
I just can't help it
Because I love you
Baby
And I need you
I want you
My love, my love
My love, my baby
I'll never forget
Tonight
No, I'll never forget
That's what you made me feel
You made me feel
Yeah, I love seeing the chat room, everyone talking about their very first time.
I remember mine, 15. My friends, girlfriend, with his permission.
Patty, tonight is the night. Hey, I had some great great ink on Wednesday and USA today.
A little bit thank God for no agenda, no agenda show also for the daily source code,
which is great, which is why I think we're seeing a larger quorum today on the stream than usual.
Of course, everyone's got the epoch and no agenda app as well.
And don't forget, we have the new daily source code app, I'll put a link in the show notes and no agenda.
DailySourceCode.com.
But also for the big app show, and I got to tell you the plan that I set out for myself for the future for the next five to ten years is actually starting to happen.
So incredibly, I got to say I'm proud of myself in a way, but also just really happy when things are kind of in synchronicity and rolling along exactly the way I wanted them to.
And that was a great boost for people grabbing the app.
Now a lot of you listen to the show or techies and a lot of the apps, I'm not really, I'm not doing reviews, it's just a show and I'm just trying to build an audience.
It turns out that 65, I say, maybe even more now at this point, 65% of the audience at least is female.
And I'd say, between 20 and 40, and they really love it because they don't want to wrestle through all the game ratings in the app store, which of course it is.
And by the way, Apple had some actual proof of that taking place with the rogue developer who is kind of unclear how he did it.
But I guess he stole some accounts or a whole bunch of him and started knocking his stuff up the charts.
So I don't have that type of capability nor what I want to do with that way, but instead of donating for the daily source code and for today's show, I'd like you to go out and promote the big app show.
And really, Twittering, putting it on your blog, if you put something on your blog, let me know about it and then I'll retweet that with the link.
Because this thing is started. It's on the verge of going viral. I'm seeing about a thousand people a day adding it to their downloads. It's a free app, but it really trust me when I tell you.
And you should never trust someone who says, trust me. But in this case, trust me when I tell you if this thing really can take off the way I wanted to.
I could do three source codes a day. I could quit everything else and just roll on and do this and we could have a lot of fun and we could play all of the songs that you want all by request.
All for free.
So I'm asking you to help me. I hope brother up, will you help me promote this thing, the big app show.
And the best link to use is the bitley link, which is bit.ly slash big app show.
The part of the airways is landed and he's sounding good to me.
This is the day he saw Scott with Adam Curry.
But still I take down those.
Because all I need is blood and sweat and skin and bones.
I'll take this phrase, where's all your taste? Nobody said it, it's easy to tell.
Because all I need is blood and bones.
And I'll take this phrase, where's all your taste?
I want you to walk this point to you right back in your legs
I'll take you down and like that smile out of your face
I want you to break your mind to take
Don't break you just like this, it's all on that beach
Now we're left to run, I'm ready for the next fight
To bring you in the world right
Let me hear you speak as you are this
Let me hear you, you like to be this
If you've got a no-go, no-go, no-go, no-go
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll be you
Let me hear you, you like to be this
Leave that you in the world right back in your legs
If you've got a no-go, no-go, no-go, no-go, no-go
You don't have a trickle of what's coming out of your ears yet.
You're doing something wrong.
Ozzy, let me hear you scream on the stream.
Noaginastream.com, noagenda, chat.com, and dimsource.com.
Noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noagina
stream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream, noaginastream
When you hold on the reins as we talk you out of pain
And above the law once you were started to have faith
What now will it take for us to never?
This is not a test or never
This is party at the rest of the world
Still proud to admit our mistakes
Kissing the bread and thus we all fall from grace
This isn't just a sad thing straight
To bring a break the rules back into place
There is no middle ground
It's no compromise with your heart and heart
With perfect faith
We spend back and broke this land
It's breaking the soul, it's impossible
And life's still out of the task to touch again
And hope that it stays there
on the reins as we talk you out of pain
But proud to admit our mistakes
Kissing the bread and thus we all fall from grace
This isn't a sad thing straight
To bring a break the rules back into place
They can't cause the struggle cause our human way, you're not there
Find a tunnel way
That's how we'll never know
This is not a test or not
This is party at the rest of the house
They'll come through and make our mistakes
The class city is in the middle of the house
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Rise against appeal to reason
Collapse, post America
Well, everybody's well
Can you with one more while we're at it?
The message is in the music as always
That's why you don't hear that shit on the radio
Wouldn't want the sleeves to get all up any in shit
Now we're with it
Uh-uh
Well, that'll be wrong
But a frame sells firing and making for ourselves the ones
Crazy
Revolution calling
I hear it
All right, all right
Will you accept it that we are that you're not there
It's not a deceit
I hate our WOODRUFF
You're a whitty
I'm afraid of the
We'll try to reverse the
Right preview
Just wash the television, you'll see that something's broken off
God no death for politicians, all that crazy scene in DC
It's just a power metal, but the time is right for changes
There's a problem for you, that you didn't change the song
You've got to be, you've got to be, you've got to steal
I used to trust the meaning of the time in the flow
There was no one, but now I see the pain of everything I knew
Only it's what's with everything from someone
I've got to be, you've got to be, you've got to be, you've got to be
There's a man, I've got to be, you've got to be, you've got to be
God no death for politicians, all that crazy scene in the flow
I've got to be, you've got to steal
Well, I'm tired of all this bullshit, baby
Telling me, don't you beat up by the Communist man
And no shady preachers, back and follow cash
Just make your calls, while giving us everything
Every time they're all in the house now
We're more macacy, million dollar stories to tell
I can't go, I'm losing my own city
We've been in the snow, and I've got to choose
If everybody's making the same story
That all of it is the same, but all of it is the same
We're all right, but now I only got the rules
I have my mind is hurt, you've got to be, you've got to be, you've got to be
I've got to ride a proud truck for the nation
I've got to be!
I've got to be a proud truck for the nation
I've got to be
espace, see me before we forgive
You're the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the
only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who having the name of the life that I have and he's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only kind who's the only one who's the only one who is the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's the only one who's wrong.
As a revolution is calling, and that call has your name on it.
Now, everybody listening on your iPhone, or out of their portable MP3 device, I want you
to very carefully lift up your earbuds on the left hand side there, and stick your finger
in your ear.
Now, do you feel some wetness?
No?
Well, then you're not doing it right, because your ear should be kind of starting to bleed
by now.
If what, let's see if we can park them up a little bit with the brush.
Never got closer to these, my family married me right back to phase 2, never the time and
We burn the meat now, all the way
By the way, we're inside
We've got this man
And we're going to the old days, all the way
Pulling the ends again and again
Swap the wings down the area
I've got your body in me
All night in each race
You get your day on
We're all in change, you think that
The birth and time and truth
We'll hear the stars change
Young the way, we'll hear the stars
For the best
We'll hear the stars change
Young the way, we'll hear the stars
For the best, we'll hear the stars
I'm sitting on the rail, the only stop for the best
Just run the train to think out
I'm on the train and it's great
We'll have to stop sitting on the rail, the only stop for the best
Yeah, light up that tire stick baby rush, a passage to Bangkok
And well, I can hardly believe it, but the chat room is almost committing mutiny now if I don't play this song
I tell you I'm in bed, you win so soon, so make sure to take it to me
The pleasure is to play, play the different ones you say
I'm the chase queen, the only god I've seen is the ace of space, the ace of space
Play the whole lot, well, catch it with the devil, start with the flow, it's all against me
So I'm on the rail, the snake has watching you know
The devil has a great, those takers play, the ace of space, the ace of space
You know I'm going to lose, I got wins with rules, the next way I like it baby
I'm one little forever, I don't think it's a joke
I'm the chase queen, the only god I've seen is the ace of space, the ace of space
Oh man, I met Lemmy at the Golden Gods Awards in Los Angeles, a couple of months ago
What a sweet guy, he's really the ace of space
You know, during that Betty White song I played earlier, was it Betty White? Betty White?
Betty White? I saw Citizen X in the chat room I thought, yeah, I got a melon somewhere, Betty
So I'm slurping that down, and we're only halfway through the journey, snap from Saturday, making your ears bleed, making your soul vibrate
You know I'm going to lose, I got a melon somewhere, Betty White? I saw Citizen X in the chat room
You know I'm going to lose, Betty White? I saw Citizen X in the chat room
I saw Citizen X in the chat room
You can check that to the back
You know I'm going to lose, Betty White? I saw Citizen X in the chat room