Delta Shara Charley 822
For a total of four years and 891 episodes
The Daily Source Code was slamming from the curry castle
Recording, recording, recording, recording, recording
And then suddenly
It stopped
For one year, six weeks, six days and 13 hours
Filled the RSS feed, aggregator stock polling, iTunes, froze
And an audience of hundreds of thousands was left in the con
He's a man in the nose
We're in a new decade, a total reboot
With a higher bit rate than ever before
The Source Code is back
With 16 months and seven months ensuring five nights of time
The 25th century of radio starts here
We're on the nose
He's feeding me out alive
I know it's in the strength of her
On casting
He's fed him curry
He's trying to rip on the answer for barf
Quick me down
The Source Code is back
I was just a five
When I was five
Raise a cane, I was feeding you
Top, change, and now the Morgana's fat
But the fever's gonna catch
When the bitch gets back
If I'm a father, that's all right
If you relax, they're gonna sad tonight
Bitch, the red, the distortion of dudes
I can't hide your feelings
They're gonna find a blue blue blue
I'm a weird time, I'm a weird time, I'm a weird time
I'm a weird time, I'm a weird time
Bad, and you historia the blue
Not F***er the blue
Killed to tight, not big in brains
Sell a so, stop tonight
But the night, I don't know what's my God, what's that?
Oh, it's summer now, and the hair is rimmed, the bills get dry, the way
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a better than you
It's the way I'm a fool, the fight I do
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, you're a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitch, you're a bitches style, bitch, You're a bitch, you're a bitch, you are a bitch, you shit you, you
I do know what's going on
All I miss my freaking hell around
I run around the whole thing
And let him back
Let him back
As right, Shuckle Hands, the bitch is back
The source code, Episode 820
Two of them are brand new location of brand new life
And still your old trusty source code
Man, I've been this nervous in years
It's weird
Loving me here, how I've missed all of you
Blasting out live on noise and the stream dot com
And of course, the podcast is see the available at daily source code dot com
And curry dot com, we're going to be breaking it down today
But first we've got to celebrate the fact that it's a food bar Friday
Turn up your speakers, let's write turn them out
But Shuckle Hands is back
And I've got a way new lust for life
Soul
See me lie to my little friend
ôt got lost in source code
He's so strong
Come on, you're done
Here comes the day
We're low in dust
We're about to change
He is one of the most proud days
He made me want to kill him
On the ocean
And I've never heard he said
I've never heard of him
Some color
Yes, I'm color
We're dancing
Killin' the time
Checkin'
When there's a room
I've got
The truth is
I've never heard of him
I hear it before
I heard of him
When there's a room
I've ever heard of him
Now I've heard of him
All the enemies
All all the enemies
All the dead
All the enemies
All the normal enemies
All the time
All the men get hurt
All the souls
All the soul
All the men get hurt
Always having smiles
All the piss
And the air
All the에서
All the right
Yeah, I'm sure it's different, I'll set it off, no more beating my friends
I don't beat my friends, I'm a winner in drugs, I'm a winner in drugs
Well, I need to start my life, of course I had it in the ear
Yeah, I'm sure it's different, I'll set it off, no more beating my friends
There's more light
Love, not so long
When I hear bones down in the air
When I look on the dress
There's nothing she's
I know it's gonna do a nice practice
K-Man, where do you get there?
Lose up, your skin starts into the water
Badger, get in with what's in the water
Oh, no, no, no, no
Where dance, like different times in chickenlands
Well, just don't mind God
Oh, there's nothing I've been in my ear
And I'm not sure of that
K-Man, where do you get there?
How are you?
I'm not sure about that
I'm brand new, I'm not sure about it
I gotta tell ya, I got a combination of
chills and goosebumps all the same time
As a daily source code is back on the air
After a year, a month
Now more than a month, like six weeks, six days
And what a way to kick it off
The footballer Friday, the chuckle heads in the chat room
And no agenda chat.com, of course
This is now all initiative of the no agenda stream
More about that in a bit as
We still have to complete the opening ceremonies
Of the footballer Friday festivities
This one thanks to Marcus Kouch, long time chuckle head
It's K-T-Night, call a toast
On the Charlie
We watch the cross
From the back-to-crash
We're waiting for the dream
Inside us of my ears
Like the skulls with spine
We lie in the evil eye
Now awake, or sleep
We're in way to kick it off
Call a toast, call a toast
And staring at the street
And all the things you want to be
So what a way to kick it off
Call a toast, call a toast
So easy to believe
Call a toast
But the only side of the stream
Is the magnitude of the scenes
But no one sees you away
From each side, call a toast
It's so sweet to me and don't
The light which I can't
I can't feel the voice
I can't feel the distance
Not a way
Oh, sleep
What's the way to wake now with
Come with us, come with us
And staring at the streets
All I need to do is take it
So I can wake up
Come with us, come with us
So easy to deceive
What are all the ways
Come with us
When all the world is so fun to us
All the world is come with us
I will be here
What happened to the dream?
What happened to the revolution?
When nothing in the dream
In sanity and our solution
I will be the way
Oh, my
Not a way
Oh, sleep
Come with us, come with us
Just staring at the screen
And all the things you want to do
Come with us, come with us
So easy to believe
What are all the ways
Come with us
I will be here
Come with us, come with us
So easy to deceive
What are all the ways
Come with us
All the world is come with us
Oh, sleep
This is something I've been wanting to do for years and years
Doing actual show from the sunny Los Angeles
And now my dream has come true
Marcus couch, thank you so much for sending this women for the Charlie
Think they are from Los Angeles, Cage 9
Comotos, which is something I certainly was
About a year and a half ago
And boy, I owe you guys so much explanation
I need to talk about so much
Finally, let me just calm down for a second there
That was an awesome start for the weekend
It's a footballer Friday
Daily source code, which
Maybe one of these days actually will be a daily source code again
So only just call it the source code
For now at least
So the last time we spoke was episode 821
This is 822
Just picking right up where we left off
It'll be kind of an interesting experiment
Mainly to see if all of the feeds pick up if iTunes works again
I
I don't know if I still need to activate radio, use a land to make some of those feeds work
It'll definitely be on
DailySourceCode.com or dailySourceCode.mevio.com
Curried.com all of those should reactivate
All by themselves, but you'll never know
It'll be kind of interesting to see what happens
I have not will do a little bit of rejiggering here and there
So
I've rebooted fellow chuckleheads
Completely rebooted a lot of you have heard about what's happened in my life
You've probably listened to no agenda and you know that there's been some significant changes
All of which I want to get to today on the show
I'm not quite sure how long it's going to be actually I forgot to start my timer
How long were these shows back in the day? Do we do like half an hour? Do we do?
I can't remember at all
Maybe did like 45 minutes
I just don't remember. That's the beauty of course of of podcasting
Is that it doesn't matter you can start whenever you want you can end whenever you want and boy
I've learned so much about media in general new media
What does work would doesn't work where I think the future is going where I think my future lies
But to understand that first we have to go back to the past a little bit of history
So it was probably about a year and a half ago when I was in a pretty bad place
Actually a really good place in a bad place at the same time
I was in a bad place because I was
Basically sitting up in the attic all day in
Well
If you go all the way back to the curry castle
This is a more or less when podcasting was birthed
And shortly after that I moved to the curry cottage in the United Kingdom
And this was kind of a a personal move as Patricia at the time had
contracted
a a reasonably mild form of heart disease and she'd always wanted to live in the UK and I picked up the whole family and we moved
Just to get away from the entire media
frenzy that was surrounding us at the time and get monation low lands oops, there's no agenda term for you
And
I've been through so much together right remember the first three four months
I didn't even have an internet connection yet the show was growing. I would record it and go out in my car and upload it in the studio
A8
Then we moved around and finally wound up in the in the attic at the same time I started a company in of all places Sam from Cisco
Was flying back and forth every couple of weeks staying out there. I had the curry condo
You know essentially I would have two lies. I'd wake up in the morning. I'd work on stuff. I'd prep
I'd do a daily source code then I'd
Around four o'clock in the afternoon. I'd get on Skype and phone calls and be on with the office until 10 or 11 it was it was pretty crazy
And I also started awakening this is something that we talked about
I believe on episode
I'm gonna say
781. I think it was. Let me see. I actually have it here. I did a little bit of research for the show
Let me see if it was yeah 781 is when I did the big awakening episode
Ooh, there's a this one of the black helicopters coming over now. You guys too early haven't gotten anything yet
I'm right here on the in the hilltop watch shower, which is a pretty much in the flight path of
Many helicopters going down to Robinson the factory, which is in torrents California
So back to the awakening
So I was really in a bad place because I was also smoking like a crazy guy and I'm not talking about cigarettes
I was self medicating to the max
I would pretty much smoke all the time unless I was flying
Which was the crazy thing about it because I you know, it wasn't like I couldn't stop. I just didn't want to stop
It was really
Really helping me feel much better and the show has had a certain twist to it as well
But then I think it was
Well, it all kind of came at once. It was probably when I was introduced to what
Congressman and Dr. Ron Paul was saying and was doing in
In government that I started to look around and say wait a minute
Everything is fake
Everything on the news is fake
The business I've been in is fake and at the same time we were being really honest with each other on the show
And it was such a dichotomy it was such a duality that I was I was really I was kind of freaking out
And then I wrote the
The episode 781 and I really did write a lot of that
Although I actually I listened to it before I started the show
And I was like wow, you know, I could really see where I was and you know what where my mindset was
I was just like whoa, you know, I've basically been
A mainstream media hitman. I've been you know my job has been to entertain the slaves the masses and mean while I'm on
And covering all this stuff. I'm learning about the Lisbon treaty. I'm seeing how the elites of the world have always been in control
And I've been a total puppet
So of course, I'm not going to play episode 781 for you. You should go and
You can always go and dial put it hate. I'll put that in the show notes. I'll put a link to it
So you can listen to it. However good friend of the Charlie Ray
Known as Ray on the Charlie
Maybe a four and a half five minute version of that show and kind of enhanced and and pulled out the
The main bits. I want to play that for you because that'll really give you an idea of where my head started to go
Just about hmm yeah about five months before we had our temporary interruption of service
Stop it stopped as quickly as it had begun
Four years of conversation that we've been to having as brought me to this point
Many of you may feel the same some may be afraid to speak out and fear of ridicule
Fear not chuckle heads together. We're going to face the future the light that is our destiny
Welcome to the next level
Welcome to the Awakening
Awakening now. I say it's uh in a six month
Excursion, but the process is actually something's been taking place my entire life
Imagine a world where you wake up one morning only to realize that everything you believe in
Functioned entirely differently from the way you're receiving it all of your life a world in fact with a truth as often the direct opposite of your reality
My story is a pop
Three kinds of power the power of our minds the power of rule and the power as in what makes our lights glow and keeps our vehicles moving
Individually collectively these three tones of power all the system of energy
My conclusion is that energy innovation was stifled in lieu of this new black hole that would power the
Generators to create a world of energy and motion based on oil
CD illusion and of course we're final five, but we know this is a trick because of the context of being aware
Then we're watching imagine show take a course you'll instantly be the love like a god or fear like
Like you wake it take a red bill follow the other row down the rabbit hole on mail
The man behind the curtain
We interrupt this program to bring you this new splatter
Media in particular television is a trick. I was a multimedia
I was merely meant to give me a slave entertained until the next commercial break
Creating a reality in our minds
There's a servant of the energy at least a gender man is working a media program
I can create content that will make your brain react in a free-determined manner if you really can't figure out how works
And you understand that it becomes ineffective once you're aware of the code
It can easily be borrowed from executing into your personal super computer brain
That's how the new infinite X of EJ with a podcast can do that
Imagine when people would money to plan for their accomplish
Over the decades it built up an impressive infrastructure
Government
Social and monetary systems that they control entirely all of the continued exploitation of us
This perpetual system however has one fatal flaw
It must continue to grow in order for it to survive
It needs us the slaves to be
Inged into it in order to prosper once our houses cars and other true physical stuff has been
Repossessed there'll be no more meaning to the content of money
Remember that none of this machinery would ever been created at free energy
In the able to everyone I think we are about to discover ourselves thanks to the evolution of our species
I'm certain
Martin A has been the finally pre-programmed to evolve and due to centuries of suppression
The internet was of course the elite's big concoca
I simply cannot resolve it
Or what design our beautiful body machinery wouldn't have added the real hair bits to our brains to make us
capable of even insisting love bread
It can't turn up turn up either way most of your still very much asleep in the reality
Created by the masters that own us many of you are awakening
Seeing the truth lies with it
It's so living too outlanding
The elites where she is creaking under the strain of itself and fear of Earth
It's all about the tiny
She comes from one down and now for us need to be awake prepared to take action
That's actually my role to assist in your awakening and to communicate it's a question learning as I can
I don't see an argument yet
All right look praise please told ones
The earth probably won't come to the screeching hall
The plain tsunamis are earthquakes and land mass relocation nor do I fear black
How accomplished you know this will need away the stealth of the night
But I served here not gonna rule any of it out before years of prophecy
I
Awakening
Excellent piece of montage done by Ray on the Charlie and I really appreciate it because it was perfect to be able to reset where I'm coming from
So I started to realize things around me and
Maybe at an age as a little bit later than and I would have wished
I had no regrets ever in life, but boy, I wish I would have woken up when I was 30 instead of instead of like 42
And there are three people who've been instrumental for the transformation that I'm going through
And the transformation that I hope to bring a lot of chuckle heads along on the on the ride for
the first one
Interestingly enough is John C. Devorek by the way don't tell him I said all this okay
Let's keep this little secret amongst us chuckle heads please
You know we started out doing this show
Or just about the right the same time I started doing a radio show in the morning in the Netherlands
And very quickly
I
Discovered that you know this guy was amazing. He was I
I hate to say it because if he hears that he'll ridicule me forever
But he was kind of like a father figure you know and he had a lot of knowledge and and he really didn't care
He just doesn't care about
bullshit
And I was like yeah, I like this guy and I could ask him questions and I could butt heads with him and I could
Throw out crazy ideas and theories and things I've been looking at and investigating
I remember I was still very unsophisticated in reading government documents, etc
And he really started to
Help me shape the way I thought
And this went on for for several months in the meantime of course
You know I'm still traveling back and forth like a madman all of my money is invested in me vio
Of course, I still have a salary and
That helped greatly
But everything else pretty much fell by the wayside you know I find myself sitting upstairs in the attic at the curry compound
At all you know all hours of the day just kind of my own little
Yeah, my own the ecosphere if you will
At a certain point I was even producing mevio today for oh gosh like six months straight
Which really blew my creativity out of the water?
You know if if you have to be creative every single day
This is probably the hardest part of producing something daily like the daily source code
Although it's much easier when it's audio because you can just you know say what you're thinking about
And you know there's no visuals to distract
You can really create a an entire theater of the mind which is pretty much the field that I play in
At the same time by the way radio was pretty much dying on the vine
Thanks to roll-ups like clear channel, etc. So I started to see
Yeah new possibilities
But still I was very very stuck I was
Absolutely unhappy and I really couldn't
Really couldn't figure out why and I don't think I actually knew why I didn't think I even knew I was unhappy because all I had to do was just
Say another hit and boy. I loved my weed
I really loved it and
But the thing is it what it all it really did is is it would
Dumb down the pain or whatever I didn't even know as feeling would bring out the true me so
In essence it's still the same guy you're here and now
And then another thing happened I met Miss Mickey
Now this happened on we're just coming up on our first anniversary of this meeting on April 3rd
This was one year ago and it was
It's hard to even explain what happened but
When you meet someone and there's a physical moment which was just one kiss after I saw her bookcase
And the universe splits open and things start to happen and I laid down the weed and like oh my god
What is going on here? It was like a force of energy electricity had just just thrust me
Through the last membrane of whatever was holding me back from a true awakening and that's not just the physical person it's the
Spiritual person
And the mental connection we made which by the way was not
On the same side of an argument we had when we first met
And then it took me about five months, sorry five weeks
of really
Birthday reburthing myself in a way so yeah, and literally this was the time when I had to swine flu
Yeah, I went through that I couldn't smoke you know as I was completely messed up
My my head was just out of control
But I was starting to become clear. I was like wow wow that sounds like a Scientology phrase doesn't it's starting to become I was becoming clear
And of course, I'd only had one moment with Mickey and
Had not seen her for the during this entire period of five weeks while I was going through the goo and coming out to the other side of the membrane
With pieces of it still cling into me
And just the conversations we had
The thoughts that we shared the music that we shared
The ideas outlook on life and she has her own
Interesting story by the way, which hopefully
In the future I shall come on the daily source code and we'll talk about that because we're both pretty much about what's real
And that's really where I want to take the source code from here getting you to authenticity something that it that is
Not full of hype and BS and crap and even on this show sometimes I've fed you that
But that would become that would be more like business models and
Other things that we have to talk about oh gosh. I feel like I want to do a show tomorrow just to get into just to get into all these
Am I gonna have enough time to talk to you about everything I want to
so
After about five weeks of this
Rebirthing process I was in San Francisco. I'd been there for several most of those five weeks and actually had
Committed to being out in San Francisco for longer periods of time because you know the economic crash was just starting to happen the company
Really needed me to be around
Unfortunately, I was doing a lot of things that I'm well, I may be good at but that I really are not truthful to what I am
Which is a creative being
I was managing
Managing departments going out on the road doing sales calls, you know jerking
Advertises around really just also unhappiness in a way
Whereas I just I'm I'm doing what I'm should be doing and I've learned fellow chuckleheads
I've been to the mountain top of the financial world
It ain't all what it cracked up to be I'd much rather be
Creative and happy and poor
Far from that actually
But it's a it's a lot more fun and and the fulfillment comes from things on the inside and not from things on the outside boy if I learn that oh my goodness
So
I
sent Mickey a an email with a ticket and a hotel reservation in a hotel and a completely different
Part of the city and I said please come to San Francisco
I want to figure out what's going on between the two of us remember that only been one kiss
Nothing else at all not not even hadn't even seen each other physically since then
I said you know what maybe we'll just wind up being really really good friends
Whatever it is please come and we'll figure it out and she did
and
She had me from hello
We spent a pretty much a week in a hotel room and it was all just talking to each other
Well, there's some other stuff
But it really was just as such a deep connection and you know and it sounds like a cliche
But of course, that's what cliches are all about
soulmate twin flame
Lost souls reconnection and we really feel like we've known each other for
300 years and we've been searching and
We're good for another 300 and it doesn't happen to a lot of people
But I think that we're one of the fortunate ones that actually have been ripped apart somewhere in some parallel
Universe and have made a quantum leap and have reconnected through just the craziest
I mean it isn't even logical that this would happen and now I'm gonna get to the third person who's been very important in this change
So after I had told Patricia because I really I had after that week in San Francisco
I came back and I had to be honest. I I couldn't hold up any front and I just had to tell her and
You know I got back in the evening and the late afternoon and the next morning
I told her and I said you know here's what's going on and and here's what's was happening and of course
This is a very sad and dramatic and traumatic process that is still ongoing
Because there's a you know when you've been with someone for over two decades as a lot of intertwined
life
Including a beautiful daughter made by the way purely out of love and we've raised her I think pretty well
And she's now 19 and has her own life and by the way, that's another thing I got to deal with
You know, kid doesn't really need me anymore. Yeah, except for money
But you know I got to think back and put to my own
My own life when I was 19. I didn't want I didn't need my parents anymore
But interestingly enough my mom played a quite a quite a big role in all of this that's happened
So I stayed in the house for the week remaining
You have to try to hold Patricia and I stayed in one of the guest bed rooms and
Something amazing happened to me
Now you recall those of you who were charcoal heads who have been with the show for the past
Well for the four years that was on the air and the and the year that it's been off so let's you say the past five years
You went through my mom get in cancer
through
Most of the ordeal and her passing
We shared that together and I know many of you still will probably think of my mom when you see a butterfly float by I still get emails from people who
Say wow, man, I thought of your mom today
But I really
I really hadn't come to terms with that. You know after my mom passed away
I pretty much went to San Francisco the week after and spent two weeks in the curry condo and
I really wasn't very good at crying. I don't think I'd really really really cried for
15 years
And I still really hadn't and my mom had been been gone for for three and and you know
I don't think I'd really dealt with that
And so during this week that I'm in in the house
I'm lying in my bed and I'm completely sober. I'm completely awake
And I'm thinking of myself. How is it possible that that this meeting this by chance meeting came about between Mickey and I
And let me just give you some background on that
I
flew to see my banker
You know, I think we've talked about her before once a year I'd fly over to Holland in the Delta Sierra
And we'd have a dinner and just kind of catch up
And it was a beautiful day April 3rd. I flew out there and we had a nice
Glass of champagne on the roof of her house and she was going through her own shit by the way
We had dinner to restaurant of her choosing an Amsterdam right near her house on the canal
And after we were you know we'd finished eating we were kind of having dessert. I think maybe a dessert wine
She said hey, why don't I call Mickey and have her come over and join us now
You have to understand that Mickey doesn't really know her
She doesn't really know Mickey other than you know one or two conversations and
This banker fairity is her name actually I believe she mistook
Another client of hers who does know Mickey well
And thought yeah, she was just maybe she was drunk. I don't know she was confused
And so she sent a text message and Mickey received this and thought wow
Well, you know, I don't know. That's interesting. Well, she was in the neighborhood anyway, so she hopped on her bike and
She came by and we had known each other for 10 years, but it never really spoke in more than 10 minutes at that
And
That's you know, that's kind of where it all started to happen. There's a whole back story to that
But that's for another time
But I really was thinking how crazy is it that we get together by some fluke
And really completely by accident and at that very moment
My mom says to me. Yeah, it wasn't easy to pull off, but I did pretty well. Didn't I I'm telling you
I heard my mother speak to me and she was taking credit for pushing the two of us together
And I was I was like what and I started talking back to her and I swear to you
Chuckleheads I had a 30-minute conversation with my mom. She made me write stuff down
Stuff I have to do people I have to look after
Thing and it was it was completely mind boggling
Completely actually I cried like a baby after that but it was just for the first time
I really really connected with my mom after she had passed away should be gone for three years
So I'm a believer in
A lot of things for since that day obviously
And my mom has really been very very close to me. I can feel her around me. I can feel her presence
And it's really giving me a very peaceful feeling
And it's just really wonderful and it is completely helped me on my way to the next level of wherever
I'm supposed to be whatever I'm supposed to do
So those three people are teaching me to spread my wings and learn how to fly and you're invited along for the ride
I'm going to do the distance
I'm going to lie
Stretching to the point of no turning back
Fly away to fancy on a little sweat and feel
Standing in the moon
My senses real
Feel the stretch
I'm so sleepy fast
Can I escape
It's irresistible for us
Can't keep my eyes from suddenly sky
You're tongue-tired and twisted just above us
I
Sips for me
I'll touch my wings
I'll be the one
I thought I thought everything
What I would get
To find my way home
I'm late and empty and turned to stone
I'm so worried tension
I'm saying to find
I'm just running out of time to try
I'm going to keep my eyes from suddenly sky
You're tongue-tired and twisted just above us
Sips for me
I'm going to lie
I'll be the one
You're okay
Sips with me
Are you adding to the notch?
It's 1100.
Let's make it at home.
And then.
Come on.
Round 1.
The boat has all the颍s.
I'm a little brim, I'm a hatey, I'm a baby, I'm dreaming and I'm dead
Across the clouds I see my shadow fly
I've come, all my wants is in vain
I trust you, I'm afraid, I'm lonely
There was so much to do for the night
There was no sensation to help you this time
To spend it at a mission
To take love of this
I'll keep my mind on the side of you side
Turn the time to listen to the sound
I'll keep it on the side of you side
Well, nothing like a little bit of flowing to help you learn how to fly
And the source code A22 just joining us on the stream
And no agenda stream dot com
Welcome
What should we talk about now?
Yes, probably about what is going to happen with the daily source code
And what's going on, everyone has been in a huge debate
As you're going to be, it's going to be like no agenda without John
Or is it going to be all about technology?
Well, you know what, it's going to be about a whole bunch of things
As usual, but of course this show started off
Really is just a test to try and get podcasting working
With guys like Andrew Grummet, the iPodder
And later iPodder lemon team
And then it morphed into more like a reality radio type show
And it's been through a number of different changes
But essentially it's just us, I guess
And the stuff that we're into, the stuff that we're talking about
Of course some of our old friends are still hanging around
And still want to be a part of the show
Which I welcome with open arms
So let's say hi to a couple of them
The first one up
Comic strip
Come on in my European correspondent friend
No other Mickey Carey, you meddling Gringo
Here is Comic strip blogger, your European correspondent
So nice to hear you again
Nice to hear that he's also called back on the internet
And since the work from agenda is a fracking sick of hand
I think feedback from office like myself will be really healthy to your soul
You know, I have missed you comic strip blogger
Yes, you are healthy from my soul
There's only a few people who push back like you do
And I love you for it
So what's up with your opinion?
Yeah, what's up?
You're thinking like Titanic
Yeah, we know we're thinking like the Titanic
And you're keeping your eye on it for us
I have to tell you, and I don't want to point
Think as of blame, but let me say this
In the 1970s when Greece and Spain were joining you
They were getting huge money from you
Much, much, much, much, much, much, much
Much, much, much, much more
The new East European members
They're joining 2004, we're getting
Since then, and now what?
Slovakia and Slovakia and Slovakia are in euro, euro, zone, euro currency
But they are not bringing it down, it is Greece
This is bringing it down now
And Spain, soon, ish
So what is the moral of the story?
Yeah, what is it?
Judices are bad for business
Believe me, emotional preferences are often misleading
You
Oh, CSB, my dear friend, good to have you back
Find him at comicsreadblogger.com
Not the only person who's come back
By the way, it got a couple more audio comments
And of course, the best way to get those two of me
Send them to Adam at bvo.com
And let's see if this works
Hey, yeah, my name is Andy B
And I'm listening to your show
From Des Moines, Iowa
Since about the time that you did a keynote
Around nomdex, I believe that's when that was
Oh, man, I think that was episode 200
Wow, that's quite a while
I love the warble by the way
On your recording, that's so authentic
Yeah, it's been a while
So, I just want to let you know
I do love the show, I'm glad to see it's back
I've been missing it
I do listen to no agenda as well with you and Dvorak
Which is a good show as well
I mean, I love the commentary between the two of you
It's pure chemistry
Anyway, I was just wondering what your future plans were for the show
And I hope to hear this daily source code going for another couple
You know, years
Yeah, that gave me that sense out
There you go, anyway, good to hear from you
Thank you very much
Well, you hit the nail right on the head, my friend, Andy B
Because that's really, I think
I hate to use the term, but yeah, the business model of podcasting
Which we thought would work in the beginning
It's kind of come for a circle, the idea that if you build up a community and audience
And I am and always have been basically in the audience business
Building one, nurturing them, taking feedback, adapting
Then you can actually create
A little business for yourself
And we went down a wrong path pretty quickly, I feel
And this is nobody's fault per se, it's just the way that things go
And the idea of building a huge network
And having enough scale to sell to large advertisers
Well, it worked out and it didn't work out
In one way, it's worked out where
MeVIO, formerly known as Pod Show
We probably do about 100 to 150 million video views per month
And of course, we've more from audio to video in the meantime
And that's enough to actually have some business that you can make profit on with
Pre-rolls
And that's basically the
It's nothing new, that's the thing that's always bothered me about that
It works because repetition works
We buy our soap powder by repetition
As long as you hear
Or see the commercial often and often
It has a catchy enough jingle, you're going to remember it
And it works, it's mind control, it's programming
It's how we vote for presidents, by the way, as well
That's why when you have $800 million like Barack Obama
You're able to become president
Of course, depends on who's giving me that money
Is to what kind of favors you have to pay back later
But that's a whole different conversation
So, although it works
To me creatively, disappointing
On the other hand
We've got the old Senseo Vulcan mind trick
That really does work
You know, you can get people
We were selling hundreds of Senseo machines
Just based on me burping and people remembering it
And of course, my endorsement that I like the product
So, we also had me via
We have a pretty large business
It's more than half, I'd say, of the revenue
Of discount codes
Now, the thing that I don't like about that
Is that it's not all based upon the media
And not necessarily based upon
The audience and community you build up around that media
But more on how good you are
Marketing the codes, to your audience
But also outside of that audience
Which, by the way, also feeds back into more people
Being an audience member of your programming
As well as the relevance
That your marketing provides
Because you actually do a show
And just aren't some kind of shield marketer
But then there's all kinds of external factors
And they're like Google
And, you know, how search terms work
And oh boy, the big SEO
I mean, it's all great stuff
And it all makes money and I'm really happy
And I'm happy it's functioning
But creatively, no
Doesn't do anything for me
Then we stumble upon this no agenda
And what's been really interesting
Is that John and I have figured out
That there is a path
And we're on it
We're a long way from our destination
But there is a path
To creating media
Without advertisements
Or at least not the traditional advertisements
By
Delivering a quality product
First and foremost
And boy, I think we're doing a pretty good job on that
And then by asking your audience to sustain
The product
And if you think about it
Even when you watch television and how many products
You're advertised to and
Just think of movies alone
You've got to go see the movie
And what kind of money you show out for that
And I think that if we would count up
The support that we were receiving
From the no agenda listeners
You probably
If it was a one-man show
So of course we split everything down the middle
And we split the costs etc
If it was a one-man show
It probably would be self-sustaining
If you know
Let's say it was me
And I was living in Montana
And I didn't buy good-looking clothes
You know, I could get by
So the system works
Of course we have to double or triple
What we're doing now in order to focus on it
Full time
But part of the promise that I made
Is I'd bring the daily source code back
Because we believe that the no agenda stream
No agenda stream.com
Can become much bigger than the show itself
The technology is finally gotten to the point
Where we're seeing in-car audio
We're seeing, well, the iPhone apps
Android apps, even some blackberry apps
That are working great with streaming
People are listening to our show
Not by the thousands yet
Live the stream is absolutely built in audience
And it's starting to grow
And there's a huge gaping hole in media
A huge one
It's so obvious like I turned a 747 around
And it's namely that radio has become
Completely commoditized into playlists
And it's not what it's about
You want someone who is
Either in your geographic community
Or in your community of interest
So that you can be
Factual actual talk about things
Happening at that very moment
If I was doing a program
And it was only for Los Angeles right now
I could look outside and talk about the beautiful weather
And I could play a beautiful weather
Record and I would we would connect
Much better that's been blown away
It's been blown up by
Um
Efforts like clear channel
Who have rolled up all of these stations
Into into one disjockey
Sitting in one market and talking to five
Markets simultaneously in the warning
And it's it's ruined an entire art form
And it is by the way
Radio arts and sciences
It's not just you know playlists
That that string your favorite music together
And by the way the experience of
Last FM
And Pandora
And iTunes
It's all great
But sometimes you just you need serendipity in your life
You need someone to play a crazy song
Or to hook into something that you're thinking about
To talk about something
We now have all these instant
Instant feedback loops
Like the chat room
Like forums
And that is
One of the questions that I'll just answer now
People have been saying oh so what's the business model
Going to be of daily source code
Well it's a part of
The business that we're building
The part of no agenda stream
No agenda stream dot com
And if you want to support it
You can go to devorac.org slash n a s
Not just n a but n a s for no agenda stream
And you can become a
A sustaining producer
And we're going to get a lot more programming on here
Besides
Obviously no agenda daily source code
We have devorac Horowitz on plug
There will be lots more
And that in combination with the
Delayed aspect of podcast
Which all kind of melds into one
I think we can actually build a real business
With a couple of people
And everyone can take it as an example
And create whatever they want to
And build up a small audience
All you need is
Really 25 to 50,000 who will
Who will support you
And then you in turn turn around and support other people
It works and by the way thank
God for PayPal
They're right in the middle of this
And those guys are genius
Adam Clark Curry
Born September 3rd
1964 in Arlington, Virginia
There's a broad testing
And internet personality
Well known for his stance
From 1987 to 1994
As a video jockey
On the music video channel
MTV
In the mid 1990s
Curry was a worldwide web entrepreneur
And one of the first celebrities
To personally create and administer
A website
In the 2000s
He helped pioneer podcasting
And is often called the pod bother
Because of his efforts
Disappointed fans of Adam Curry's daily source code
We're left hanging when Curry stopped
Producing the show on February 16, 2009
But now he's back
Let me hear you a little bit of pot saved music
Shall I? This is best for me
Who's back
I know
But I thought you said
Good God
Oh you did
That never fly
But anybody
I can watch you quitting
You got a natural
I can't take care of somebody
But anybody
Return something free
You don't let me
Won't let you
Can give me the true straw
But even can't watch you clean
You got a new movie
Findin' some damn boring
It's got some big button
I just made a velvety
You just won't meet
I know you got all you need
Whatever
Okay
Alone
Those kids are walking
Everybody come naked
Not smoking
But anybody
Can watch you clean
You got a natural
I can't take care of somebody
Got a new movie
You got a new movie
Can give me the true straw
But even can't watch you clean
You got a new movie
When I'm the thing I certainly want to do is bring back a lot more pod save music to the
full.
That Thorne Lee she is from California and you can find her on the pod save music network
which I believe for legal reasons has been changed to the music alley dot com but I think
if you hit pod save music network dot com it still works.
Don't tell Apple.
And looking at the chat room, I p-dub, p-duby fence is in there and yes, I agree
p-dub.
I think you were the first person to ever play Beth.
She sent me a note and alerted me to her brand new tunes on the pod save music network
and I'm very happy about that.
She sounds great and now that I'm out of here in Southern California, I can't wait to catch
one of her shows.
By the way, chat room wondering where the cowbell is, I hate to say it but it's in my
shit that is on the boat right now coming over from London so I don't have to wait until
I actually have it back to my possession soon to come.
The first star that I saw last night was a lie who meant this guy but man, they never
made our dreams fly fly.
Here we are now in the forest sky and we're in the way, here we are now in the test
It's way you've spread the way we've been, we're working this garbage which.
It isn't like you're a black and black woman, but the flavor from the watermelon
Like sweet summer limousine, I've been blinded with my deadby skybar, this town doesn't look the same tonight
These dreams started singing to me, I don't know where, and all my life are
I don't know that I've ever felt so alive, alive, alive
Here we don't know if the forest can't ever end, we'll like it
Here we don't know if it's in danger, we'll like it
Let's go in this city, but if it's our kingdom, you're safe, I'm about to win
I want to wake up, kick in the screening, I want to wake up, kick in the screening
I want to know that my heart still will be there, there's a reason, I'm leaving
I want to know that my heart still will be there, there's a reason, there's a reason
I'm bleeding, here we don't know if the forest can't ever end, we'll like it
Here we don't know if it's in danger, we'll like it
Here we don't know if the forest can't ever end, we'll like it
Here we don't know if the forest can't be ended, we'll like it
to keep my eyes peeled to curie.com to check it out.
So welcome back, Daily Source Code,
along May you live, okay, let's be real,
John C. Duboric is okay in small bursts,
but he kinda disrupts the sexy.
You know what I mean?
Ah, oh, and G-Baby, I love you.
Ah, oh, yeah, we gotta get it our sexy back, baby.
I'm sure we can work on that.
I'm looking forward to it.
And I would mind hearing Roger Smalls as well,
but he's really dropped off the radar entirely.
So anyway, so what are we gonna talk about
in the coming weeks?
I've regained my ability to be reading five books
at one time, and I'm reading five excellent books
as we speak, so I'll be working through those with you.
Tell you about my thoughts, and yeah,
a lot of business stuff, some technology stuff.
You know I'm gonna be one of those smocks
who's gonna stand in line for an iPad,
you know I just can't help myself.
Gotta get one.
All right, we're well into the hour,
let's wrap it up with one more pot safe tune
from back in the day.
Fire ain'ts, only you could make me happy.
As I look down the risk of
I love the way that we are.
It could never go away.
It's just feeling that makes you, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All you could make me happy.
All you could make me smile.
For wild, for wild.
For wild.
I find myself against the wall.
I hear your voice you call it cold.
Just the name of my school reign.
As the only explanation.
All you could make me happy.
All you could make me smile.
For wild, for wild.
I love the way that we are.
The end of the day is busy.
So near the end, still I can breathe.
I need you now, so I can feel you.
All you could make me smile.
All you could make me happy.
I appreciate everyone joining me for the show.
For all of your feedback, for your audio drops, email me,
Adam and mevio.com.
I'll be back next week.
Time to determine but there will be another source code.
I'm looking forward to it.
And I really do love y'all.
Take care now.
Another fine medial presentation.
Stick it in your ear.