Delta Shara Charley, 8-2-9-er, the Snapfoo Saturday.
We're 16-1-7, and've been showing 5-9's up-time turn.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We're not being lost.
We're getting me out live.
I know it's in the street right now.
I'm destined to get a new curry.
In the morning to get a new Sunday.
We're back, baby.
Family, I'm a world black, baby.
Family, I'm back, baby.
Had a child.
Family, I'm the damn thing going by.
Family, I'm sitting with another mind.
Family, I'm the damn thing going blind.
Family, I'm a city of black, baby.
Family, I'm a world black, baby.
Family, I'm the damn thing going by.
Family, I'm the damn things going by.
Black Betty kickin' off with Ram Dam's classic there.
Oh boy, it looks like the chatroom's hose, but that's okay.
We'll get through it eventually.
Maybe someone can check in and fix it.
Meanwhile, there's some great tunes and talk coming up
on this edition of the Charlie.
With the Vapers.
I see this narrative, there's nothing I should do.
Oh, it's in colour.
You're here, it's brown.
You're right, I hate it.
It's a disguise.
I have focused you when there's no one else around.
I got your picture.
I laugh at me.
I laugh at my self.
Or I'm a doctor.
So I can look at you from the size as well.
You can control you not but turning down.
You're true, your invention.
Dark
Gently goENN
I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you
I think I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling it I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you now I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you
It's a total spring, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one
It's a total spring, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cycl
rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every another race, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us let us meet like a cyclone rain, every one of us
That's an intensive acting group.
And I've got the pod daughter hanging out here at the Crackpot Command Center.
And she's probably going to be bored to tears and she can't turn on the television.
What we're doing the show, of course.
In the morning, everybody in the chat room, we know agenda chat.com.
It seems like we have a couple of issues with the Mibbit service, which is the web-based
interface to get into the IRC chat room.
So the alternatives right now are to find an IRC client for the platform of your choice
and log in that way, or I don't know if it's Mibbit or what's happened, but something
maybe Leo Leport and I just broke it.
That's one of the suggestions coming in through the chat room right now.
But that's okay, because it's a snafu Saturday that means I didn't get to do a show at
all.
There was nothing happening on the Fubar Friday.
I actually hope to do something on Wednesday.
It's just been a crazy week.
We've had so much going on, of course, with Christina in town, trying to do as much
stuff with her as possible, and can't wait after the show, we're going to pop on down
to Fry's Electronics in Burbank.
She has no idea what nerd heaven she's about to be thrown into in a pick-up netbook, so
she has something good to use for the next couple of months, while she's back in that
get-monation east.
Hey, babe, are you here?
Can I tell him about your plans?
Yeah.
Plan is, she's going to come back and conquer the United States of America, which I'm very
excited about.
She's going to set up shop here, and we're looking for a place for her, also later this
afternoon.
It's going to be fantastic.
Ha!
It's basically my investment in my retirement plan.
She has promised me an old folk, well, what?
She's promised me an old folk's home with cable and wireless internet, so it's an investment
in my future.
This is the Charlie, it's episode 829-829er for the Delta Shara, and some of our old friends
checking back in as the show starts to crank up again to full speed, nice to hear him
all checking in.
Here's our buddy Steve Runner.
Sounds like cowbells.
Yeah, what do you mean?
Everyone here at the Boston Marathon is listening to the D.S.C.
Hey, Adam, it's Steve Runner from the D.P.A.A.A.A.C. podcast for runners over at
Steve Runner.com.
And from the sounds of the crowd here in Boston, I think overwhelmingly everybody is happy about
the return of the daily source code.
Yeah, I'm in the way of the trend of screaming.
I mean, listen to what I mean.
Yeah.
The about half million people out here, and they're all saying the same thing.
Mr. bringing back the D.S.C. man, we've missed your voice out there, and you sound really
been like you in a good space.
Oh, man, I got to tell you Steve, first of all, it's great to hear you.
Yes, I am in a good space.
I'm feeling fantastic, and it's not just me bringing back the Charlie, it's you guys,
essentially pulling me back into it.
It's real good to hear you, man.
That sound you hear is me going over a computer math chip.
Oh, you've been to my time, it's being uploaded right now to a server somewhere,
so that my listeners can track me as I run, but anyway, thanks so much for returning
back to the airways and this new awakening of yours, it's fascinating to listen to.
Obviously, we've been listening to you over at no agenda, but the SC just warms the
cockles of our hearts.
Good to hear you, man.
It was my podcasting from the Boston, Arizona, on Steve Runner reminding you to one
long and taper.
Yay!
Go to the SC!
You night, Chuckleheads!
Oh, yeah, awesome Steve from the Fidipidations podcast.
Thank you so much for checking in my friend.
Good to hear you, you're still running the inshift.
Do you hear me?
Do you care?
My whole thing in the sounds coming out.
Who is the autobot I am?
I don't fit you real life.
Who underspended?
You look at me as if you're in a date.
It's like the feeling of a humble page with you real life.
You don't know what you just read.
What was before?
When no one listens anymore, what was before?
When no one listens, what was before?
I know one is one, one is one, one is one
I know one is one, one is one
It's no use stopping at all
Do you hear me?
Do you care?
Do you?
And they all they didn't tell me
Being doing blind, no one knows it
I think I'll die in my head, too
The apple boom boom, bombing me
Work out, bomb Bang Bang, bomb out
In the
Until action's coming, and me
What a worse smell, but no one
Listening to eating ball gans
But no one knows all the words
But no one listens, no one's talking at all
For the worst world, no one listens anymore
For no one listens for the worst world
But no one listens, no one's talking at all
Be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be laptops
Do youAnyone?
Do you care?
Do you hear me?
So support the world's hope?
Do you Anyone anyone anyone what's hope?
Do you care?
Just holding his hands a half an hour
All right, when it comes to quintessential 80s music, that's got to be it, missing
verses, words, they really do matter, you know, my stance on that, and I'm just looking
through the archives here, I really need some new jingles for the Charlie new style.
He's kind of hurting on the jingle front, I don't have enough stuff to play, ah, let
me tell you, I'm very excited, you know, I'm setting up a studio here in the Hilltop
Watch Tower Crackpot Command Center in the garage, ah, garage, I should say.
And so I've got, ah, it's completely portable, it's got a great stand with a green
screen.
I learned a very important lesson for someone who's been in television and video so
long, ah, pretty stupid that I screwed in all my light bulbs using my bare hands.
Of course, the grease from my fingers made two of them pop almost instantaneously, how
new of me to do that, ah, I got this awesome camera, which I forget to make in the
model of it.
It's a Panasonic.
It says HD thing that records straight to SD chip.
So I got all that.
I got a, and by the way, everything off of eBay and Amazon, we really did some research
and, and found some cool stuff.
I got a bitch and tripod with wheels, so I can do truck moves, but here's the kicker.
You know, for some stuff that I do, particularly when we do stuff for media for, for
client presentations, I need a teleprompter because I, you know, after all the, yeah, we
did some of the short-term memory has gone, I can still do a pretty good job, but I'm
not as good as I used to be.
So I like to have a teleprompter and I'm actually pretty good with a prompter.
You probably usually can't see I'm reading it all, and I know how to float in and out
of the words.
Look at me that look, I can shut up you, you can't.
So I'm like, I'm looking at prompters, like, you know, 1,200, 1,500 bucks, I'm like,
no, this is crap, man, this is, and then you still have to have a foot pedal or something
like that.
We'll check it out.
Check out this, this set up that I, a Jerry rigged.
So first of all, this is great app for the iPad called Teleprompter Plus.
It's 995, which I think is a pretty good bargain.
It lets you import files from Google Docs, it has a lot of ways to get text into it.
You can have a countdown timer.
Of course it does mirror text.
You can set up the fonts and the colors and everything exactly what you'd expect from
a display unit for a teleprompter.
And there's another free app you can get for the iPhone, which lets you control it through
the connection on the, on the Wi-Fi.
So that's, that's the perfect ideal set up.
Now, of course, you don't want this thing underneath the lens or above the lens or to
the right of the left of the lens, because that you will see.
You want to be looking straight into the lens.
So what you typically have with the teleprompter is the screen is beaming upwards.
It hits a, well, someone called it a 2A mirror, but it's actually a beam splitting mirrors.
What it's, is, I think the official terminology.
So I found this outfit, 2A mirrors, I think it's 2A mirrors.com, the 2A mirror company.
And they make a little frame, which is, it's just a wood frame, a tan made, it showed
up with the, with FedEx yesterday, and it cost me 60 bucks.
I've got a beam splitting 2A mirror in there with a nice hood that goes over the camera.
And it, and the iPad fits perfectly right into the, into the bottom frame part.
And so, well, if you take away the cost of $800 for the iPad, I have a really, really good
solution, incredibly cost effective for my teleprompter.
So I'll be cranking out stuff left and right pretty soon.
That also has to do with my eye, new eye phone app, which we'll talk about in a second
of my key.
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo
-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-
Oh, I think we can make it
So, though, there's no one this time
You burn the light in my heart
Well, you put the spot to the side
I got your heart in my side
You know, I didn't know that
Oh, when I was down, I was a cry
Nobody knows it, nobody knows it
I gave you my heart
You know, I'm bringing my heart
I don't know where to get your heart
I don't know where to get my heart
Oh, when I was down, I was a cry
You know, I didn't know that
You ran from the sky, I gave you my heart
Oh, I gave you my heart
I don't know where to get your heart
I don't know where to get my heart
So, good news for those of you listening at No AgendaStream.com
The chat is back up and working
You can log in at noagendachat.com
It fixed itself miraculously and of course immediately guys in the chat room
We're saying hey any porn stars here today. This is what happens when we do the show live
Yeah, I don't know as a little early for most of the porn stars to be checking into the chat room
Elton John Kiki D real pussy music on the Charlie, but it's great for a snap-oos Saturday
Just kind of makes you feel good. Yeah, we need that a little bit of a mellow happy music can't go too hard on you
Yeah, as he said hard on you can't go too hard on you on a Saturday morning
I particularly since it's only 11 30 and we're just kind of waking up and chilling out sitting here my sweats and
And no wife beater today, by the way. It's just the white t-shirt. So I mentioned the iPhone app
I submitted it on Sunday and
It was waiting for review now last night 7 p.m. Get Monation West time. It switched to in review
So they're reviewing my iPhone app. I cannot tell you how I mean, I'm like a like a teenager on a first date here
It's like I'm I'm very excited about this thing. I hope they approve it. I'm I know that on some of the
There are human interface guidelines. I'm scurting around some of the
Well, the guidelines I guess so I don't know if if they understand what I'm trying to do with the app
Then they'll get it and they'll be okay with it if not I'm gonna have to either
Put some significant infrastructure behind it or
Make it Wi-Fi only which is something I don't want to do
Because it's it's so cool although I must say when you have a shitty connection like when you switch from 3G to Edge
Then it really it really doesn't perform at all and or very well and so I would understand if they rejected on those grounds
I'm just hoping it doesn't take now the four days to get back into review if they rejected it and maybe they'll just approve it
Because I'm very excited about this thing. It's
It's you know, I'm I'm not a a massive coder and it's not so much that the app does amazing things, but it is the perfect
I don't want to give it away. I want you to load it on your iPhone and and see if the magic appears before you're very eyes
That's that's rude. That's really I've done something and once it's been approved
I'll tell you exactly how I did it and why I did it and and
What the point is but it's really going to help anyone out there who's making iPhone apps
So take that to heart if you're a developer or a even if you're just a content producer and you're you're
Working with someone else putting apps together my app will help your app and it's going to be completely free which is
I so believe in that
People who've seen this app who've been reviewing it with me say so what's the business model behind this if it's free?
It's not on and I you don't understand I got to build the audience first then everything just comes automatically or automatically. Should we say
Real proof is in the no agenda stream.com project the John and I are doing a no agenda in general
You know when people like it they'll help you out if they don't like it if the think it sucks
They don't it's that simple
But of course, it's just the beginning the first of many apps
Only just begun that words of Karen Carpenter
I'm sure you've had it all before but you never really had it out
I don't believe that anybody feels the way I do about you now
Sharon rises that all through to us watching the signs along the way
Talking it all the girls are too far
We're getting together together
Today was gonna be the day but I'll never throw it back to you
But now you shut up somehow realize watching that to do
I don't believe that anybody feels the way I do about you now
Just think of
Sharon rises that all new to us watching the signs along the way
Talking it all the girls are too far
We're getting together today
Together
You're gonna be the one that saves me
And after all
You're my one to one
I don't know man I kind of liked that one
It's go home productions mash up with the carpenters and Oasis called Carpenter's Wonderwall
It's kind of struck me perfectly right for us now food Saturday edition of the Charlie
Where we once again welcome back one of our old friends in one of our charcoal heads ray on the Charlie
We interrupt this program to bring you this news flash
I ran expected to launch military exercise in the Persian Gulf this week
Does anyone know what's happening there
So it's going to be a beautiful weekend in Europe
Sun in the sky birds whistling great tunes
It was a great experience last week to hear almost nothing
It's interesting things in the open air which no one had seen since 1911
That was the first year a small airplane flew over the Netherlands
I really enjoyed to see and hear things I usually don't see or hear
Or feel are we shaking more and more or it gets just my imagination
Or in bladder if there are not a week of major and smaller earthquakes around the globe
I finally read in the Dutch newspaper the answer to all my questions
Earthquakes are not natural but caused by unruly muslim women
It says the Iranian cleric who got all this slum gazem said digi
Iranian women dressed far too exposed
It brings ahead of many men going nuts
So they provide for adultery and that's why the number of earthquakes in Iran is increasing
So Adam that's maybe a solution to our problem
No more naked chicks around the globe
NAY
Last Wednesday it was for 20 day
April the 20th is a special day to a certain facet of society
I at the other end had to do some research on the internet to learn about this great event in Denver
After we went through the Iceland major cloud of anesthes
The clock pounded down at 420 p.m. for a crowd of more than 1000 bucks mogers
To lit up the splits and wait for the airports and Colorado to be shut down after a while
They probably see things flying anyway
So in the meantime, our Dutch Christian democratic political party things
Handing out free joints during the parliamentary elections in the Netherlands on June 9th is irresponsible
14 coffee shops in Mastricht
That's a capital city in the Netherlands
Once to reward loyal customers with a free joint as they vote
Can you believe that?
Welcome
So the good news is in spite of what you inhale it's going to be a beautiful weekend
In the lower countries temperatures for the first time this year rising about the 20 degrees
It's finally spring and I'm definitely ready for the weekend
Starting right here on the Charlie
This might be crossing the line
But it's time to just find it
But it's going to be just striking to me
Maybe what you got to do
Say it's all free
I know I'm on the floor
I want to be just like you
I want to be taking this room
Turn down the walls and something
Yeah, I'm taking this
You see, it's greener
This is so much fun
It's easy
It makes me so bright
Yeah
I'm so excited about what I want
After a spots of the teenagers
No more chicks
Don't be afraid
I'll just teach you a little and let it go
I want to be just like you
I want to be taking this room
Turn down the walls and something
Yeah, I'm taking this room
I want to be just like you
I want to be taking this room
Yeah, I got a lot of some surgesmith on the knowledge industry
I'm daily source code episode 829
Thank you very much
Ray for your ray on the Charlie
That's kind of a good wrap up for the week
I'm really liking that
You know in there
And yeah, Ash McGetting
Of course, we were all over that for the beginning
On the knowledge and
Oh, gee, what is that even Richard Branson's coming out and saying
Hey, that was pretty bogus
That made no sense
Why the hell that we have to ground everybody
Well, tomorrow morning in the morning at early service
No agenda, I'm sure we'll talk about that some more
But yeah, it must have been nice to have the sky
It's just completely clear
Cleaned nothing flying around and no controls
For a change
But boy, what a rip off that was
And I got a 19 year old hero who was hoping for another eruption
So she could stay longer
Unfortunately, no such luck
Not often we play an instrumental on the Charlie
But that got a really nice email that came in from Mike Snyder
And you say as I got a track for you that I did
It's totally pod safe
No problem if you don't do instrumentals
I understand
But anyway, I promise you my song does not suck
Let's have a listen
This is real spoken guitar
Wow
I must say shades of the slow hand
They are very nice
very nice Mike, thank you so much, well spoken guitar, pod safe and he didn't give
me a link. I'd love to hear some more. Oh, there it is. Yeah, I'll put that in the show
notes at datingsourcecode.com. MSCGP, Mike Shira, Charlie Golf, Papa, dot wordpress.com.
You know, I got to tell you, I'm sitting here with iTunes Connect Open, not just during
the show, but pretty much ever since it changed to going in review. I'm not quite sure
why it takes so long to review the app. But I guess they need their time to figure it out.
You know, and I mentioned it's like, I'm like a teenager. It's like, I feel like I've
gotten the first base. I mean, review now. Will I get to go to second, third and will I
score? Can I go all the way home? Oh, baby, I'd love to. You know, how sometimes something
can really ruin a song? Well, the Clintons ruin this song when they use it for their
campaign. But I think it's time to bring it back and it can be played again because it
is a great tune. This Fleetwood Mac don't stop on daily source code eight two nine
four. You never don't want to smile. If it takes just a little while, over your eyes,
forget the day, you'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you're not too much, don't stop.
You'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way.
Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way.
Don't stop. You'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way. Don't stop, you'll say things in a new way.
Yeah, baby, we're all up before
Yes, we're this girl, yes, we're this girl
Oh, I don't know this is me who's mine
Give the face closer to my heart
I know you don't be that it's true
I've never met any harm to you
Don't stop, and I'm out tomorrow
Don't stop, you don't see me
Give the face closer to my heart
Yes, we're this girl, yes, we're this girl
Don't stop, and I'm out tomorrow
Don't stop, you don't see me
Give the face closer to my heart
Yes, we're this girl, yes, we're this girl
You know what I mean?
It's like, I hated it when the Clinton did that
I hated when politicians co-op songs in general
It's like politicizing art, man, it's no good
So, what was that now?
Ten years ago, so I guess we're okay to bring it back
Out of the closet and play it again, it's just a good ass song
Fleetwood Mac don't stop on the Charlie 829
Are these snafu set or day edition
And we've been seeing lots of friends of the Charlie coming back
and reintroducing themselves to the new audience
To the old audience
Great to have them all coming back
Of course, comic strip blogger
We'll check in later on this program as well
And I think it was two or three episodes ago
I inadvertently thank Jersey Todd
For sending in some tunes, of course, I'm in to say, Jersey Joe
Had quite a tough time in self over the past couple of years
And it was great to catch up with him
And see the things are going well
And I don't know if it was just the karma
Or if the mistake made it happen
But, ladies and gentlemen, I probably present the return
Of the music colleges, the official musicologist
Of the David source code
You're honored, I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
You're honored, please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
And it's all give a knock
To the hardest work in law here
It's Jersey Todd and Megan
You're honored, what do you say?
He might even fit with this case
Jersey, you said I'd be dead yet
Jersey, you said I'd be dead
Jersey, you said I'd be sure
Now, you're Jersey, you said
Hey, how's it going Adam?
It's Jersey Todd, the official musicologist
Of the Chacha
Damn that feels good to say once again
Man, I've missed a DSC
Well, I'm glad you're back
I hope all's well on your role
Man, it sounds like you've seen more lawyers than I have lately
But she's, you know, things have been crazy over here too
Since we've last talked
The kids are getting bigger, Robin, my daughter
Who was essentially born on the DSC
Wait a minute
Is she dateable yet?
As we texted back and forth back in the day
During her birth, I was texting you from the delivery room
She's already three years old
I saw Charlie five years old
So things are a little crazy
I'm no longer an associate at the front of my work for
I'm now the big partner
So, I'm back as your musicologist
I'm happy to do it
I'll check in as much as I can
But the nice thing about the new DSC
Is even though we still love pot safe music
On your show, I can play whatever I want
And we're not just limited to pot safe music
That's right
So, hey, what do I care?
You don't want to be in suit right?
And I got a lot of pot parts of it
From noise in the UK
This is one of my favorite bands
Got to check out the album, the house and dirt built
It's the heavy on the daily songs called
How you like me now?
Jersey Todd, good to have you back
Thank you so much, can't wait to check out the tunes
Coming from you
Now you need to know
I'll see you up in the back
Back, back, back, back
And I'm in a deal
Yeah, I'm out of fire
And you'll uphold this man
Think and wait till you see
I can't wait
Say you don't know
I need to know
Remember to film
Where I need to go
Yeah, I was alive
And that you can't even get almost to see
Oh, now what you see right through me
Get the same sense and sense on the book you've been dreaming of
Put your knees out, now, coming down
I ain't like it nor, I ain't like, I ain't like me, man
I ain't like it, man
I ain't allowed, man
We're going on Begin with the
It's time to make you fall in pain
Oh yes, oh yes, oh yes
Oh yeah, Regnet Snorsko,Where compression leaps
perfhe beheee
Jersey Tan, thank you so much my friend
And the official music college is not the trot, trot,
check him back in, I'm sure I'll be back sometime next week.
By the way, this coming week, I'm going to be in San Francisco
for a major portion of the days.
As first of all, I'm going to be taking Christina,
as she's flying out of the SFO, and we're both very sad about it.
All three of us are sad about her leaving.
I had really sucks, but she'll be back in, I give her six weeks.
She thinks it's going to be two months,
but I think it's going to be even less time than that.
And then I'm going to be working at the office.
So I don't know about a Charlie, because I've
kind of gotten to this new mode of traveling only
taking the iPad, because I don't really need any more.
And I hate striking down my entire setup,
once it's set up, it's really rocks.
And by the way, there's this fantastic service
that I've been using for a number of years called
LogMeIn.com, which is a free service.
You can access all of your computer's via remote.
It's very similar to VNC.
In fact, I think it even uses the VNC protocol
probably in the background there.
But the good thing about it is they essentially
have a location service, so you don't have to go routing
around for IP addresses and do all kinds of NAT translation,
network address translation, tricks to VNC,
and it just kind of works.
And even though that's free, the iPhone and iPad versions
of the app are rather expensive.
I think there's like 20 bucks, but man does it work well.
So if I need anything from the computer at home,
I can just log right into it.
And it's just really kicks ass.
I got an interesting email.
And as you know, I'm trying to do more with the music
on the daily source code, despite the fact
that there are lots of things to talk about going on the world.
And I do want to talk specifically about this porn stuff
going on at the SEC, and how that will affect us all
and what I think the, and I'll probably talk about it in the
morning as well, early service tomorrow.
How that, that is going to be used for evil ways.
But the email just kind of got my, my attention.
It starts off dear Adam, forget about unpronounceable Icelandic
volcanoes.
The only sound eruptions you need to be wrapping your ears
around this week are right here.
We've got two molten hot new remixes for you of our debut
single, 61, 74.
And this is from Don't Wait a Minute.
At least that's the, the sender on the email.
We met coin-operated boy at a warehouse party in white
chapel last month.
He promised us a remix of our track,
despite intoxications on both sides of that conversation,
which is always the start of some great art, my friends,
editorial provided by me.
He followed through with his word, and we're glad he did,
as he provides for us a garage-flavored reinterpretation
of Don't Wait animates original track with a healthy dollop
of Parallan-esque glitchy electronica.
We think it's pretty epic.
And with a different take on the track, we've got some techno-pop
hybrid with a distinct Euro-pop vibe courtesy of Dirty Disco.
That's next on the Daily Source Code.
Let's get started.
I don't go in.
Ah.
Oh my god, that's too much
So, let's now look at the show
Time to go, let's take a long shower
We'll never change our mind
I'm the morning, you're my cookin' better
That's not true, let's take a selfie
Coming name up on the break
Oh the love, let's go to sleep now
No, what you see the hours
See the lady think, oh the weather like a cow
It's hot in the waves
Like a life that's not true
The pounce became panties
But a pound went from flatchy
And no, the cow was bored
And no, the cows was bored
It could only get worse for guests that are
It could also only get worse for guests that either
Take it out again when it's bored, yeah, that's all
Take it out again when it's bored, yeah, that'sULL
Take it out like this, yeah, that's all
Take it out again when it's bored, yeah, that's all
Take it out
and now this really reminds me of those days.
I'm in it too, you know?
I do like it.
Awesome.
Don't wait a minute.
It's 6174.
It is the COB remix.
And of course, links to all of the tracks played on the daily source code can be found.
In the show notes, a daily source code dot com.
People asking me, you're not just playing potsafe music,
why you're playing non-potsafe tunes as well.
And it's very very simple.
It's basically a Vulcan mind trick.
You see, if you want to get people to hear other tunes,
you've got to make them happy and you've got to play something familiar.
Something they really like.
Something that's been around for a while.
You rarely hear me play Beyonce, by the way,
or something that's current on the track on the charts.
You have to do it.
It's how you put a show together.
If you go to a David Bowie show,
he's going to play some stuff from the spiders from Mars.
He'll play something off the heroes album.
Then he'll play something off of whatever's latest project is.
And I encourage every band to make sure they do their hits.
You've got to mix the hits with the new stuff.
Otherwise, people just won't listen.
It's what it takes.
Ah, okay.
Ah, what should I talk about here?
Oh, yeah.
I had a great meeting yesterday with Dave Matthews.
Now, Dave Matthews is probably the closest thing to an inventor,
a person that I know.
He's created a lot of amazing stuff.
He has a lot of patents on things.
And he's just a great guy.
And he was very much a Bay Area resident for a while.
And we both moved Los Angeles around the same time.
So we hook up from time to time.
We had a meeting yesterday.
Oh, so LA Friday afternoon at the Skybar,
La Mondrian Hotel.
And I laid out a project for him that I'm very interested in pursuing.
He Dave was really good with his hands and with metal.
And he can make things.
And he's got a tool shop and he can do stuff, right?
And I, of course, have none of that.
I'm very bad with my hands, actually,
except for certain things.
But that's for another show.
When Bobby's back in the chat room.
I've been following this guy called John Surrell.
And he's an inventor and he's been working on free energy
or zero point to whatever you want to call it
for many, many years in the United Kingdom.
And it was someone who sent me the link of him on coast to coast A.M.
And I had missed this particular episode.
He was interviewed via phone.
And he essentially is, I think, the granddaddy of the idea of creating free energy
through magnets, magnetism.
And he has the system called the Cyril Effect Generator.
You can see tons of examples on it on, of it on YouTube.
In fact, some Hollywood producer and I made a movie about him called
the Cyril Story.
I think it's the CyrilStory.com.
As Sierra Echo Alpha Romeo Lima.
And that, of course, is a typical Hollywood production.
You know, it's like, it doesn't work.
It doesn't not.
You decide.
And one of those deals.
Now, I'm pretty much a believer in this stuff.
I see a lot of guys down under working on generators based on magnets.
And they're, you know, they're essentially hooking up nine
volts and getting 15 kilo volts out.
It's amazing or kilowatts.
Whatever.
I mean, it seems like this stuff was working, of course.
It goes against the grain of anyone who doesn't think that a,
the perpetual motion can exist, et cetera.
But there's one interesting aspect.
And the free energy aspect is one thing.
It's actually what Dave was most interested in when I told him this story.
What I really like about what John Cyril is doing is this,
this generator of his has an interesting side effect.
And the side effect is that it will levitate.
And not just levitate like, you know, a little bit off the table.
It actually, in his experiments,
some of these rotating discs that he's created have,
you know, actually shot through the roof of his shack.
And he's flown them.
And it looks very much like a flying saucer.
And so here's the deal I made with Dave,
who was interested in the, in the free energy aspect of it.
I said, look, man, if, if we can make one of these,
if we can make them work.
And he has a lot of connections with a lot of the hackers and the freaks
who go to a burning man who have, you know, have stuff like,
you know, super magnets line around in their shed.
Oh, I got a draw full of those.
If we can actually make it work,
I told him I would fly it.
And I can't wait.
And I have faith.
I think we can take to the skies, baby.
All right.
If it was something to turn out.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
The angels.
They're the source.
They're a two-niner.
Take them on time.
Oh.
Salem Boys stars from a paper stand with whisky bottle in naves
where scoorly they're gonna have, put his mingle on a purple
hope I can t see, the science out, can head my shadow up.
For our memories take inside ofdev Pinecrot.
Tell him he's in' toURT
Tell him I've been solitary, good for him.
Take a long ride.
Take a long ride, take a long ride
Take a long ride, I'll be with you
Try to look into the game of mine
Tell them just take a side to my sacred ride
The king is sick, you ain't got no right to come
That's it, get out of my sight
Take a long ride, take a long ride
Take a long ride, I'll be with you
The king is sick, you ain't got no right to come
That's it, get out of my sight
Take a long ride, take a long ride
Take a long ride, I'll be with you
You give them a smile, a lot of them all alone
It's an I've never exactly given myself time
Take a long life, take a long life
Yeah, we're in a moment, take a long ride
Less talk like pirates
We are the pilots, we know too any lead
We say no, we lie around
And if you task us
Do anything, we'll tell you, we don't do anything
But I'll never be, then I'll never be
Then I'll never be, then I'll never be
So let's say we all say all, then I'll never be
I'll stay with, I'll never be, then I'll never be
I'll never be, then I'll never be, then I'll never be
I'll never be, then I'll never be
Justin 23, don't do anything,'t do anything
Justin 27, don't do anything
I'll do it again!
Wow!
Fuck the rest of it, I'm not too good.
I'm gonna pop it up, throw my meth potatoes,
forget the wall, and I'll never cancel it.
You're walking out, never got me at last.
And I'll never be in the ball, and I'll never be in the ball.
By your acceptance love, 2002,
we'll be this bad way like a king.
That way I need a soul full of confidence.
We don't know why you did over time,
and can't take kids.
We don't wait for a lunch, but we don't need y'all.
We can't take crush, we don't fall, we don't shoot.
We must get the cake a rule.
I'll do it again, let's get money here.
Go on, go on, go on.
Go on, go on, go on, go on, go on.
We just make it all, we'll lie around.
We have to run, do it again,
we'll tell you, we don't do it again.
Yes!
Ha! Let's get the fun going.
If you don't do it again, I love this.
Oh, my God!
Nice!
You are the star of the student,
Brendan, Brendan,
we're the sound of you, we don't play the band.
Hey, don't do anything like you were doing.
Sorry, Boris!
I don't know why I don't want to play anymore.
I don't want to sing this song.
I want to play the band.
I don't want to know to the more.
I don't want to play the band.
I don't want to listen at all.
I want to play the band.
I want to get high school.
Sorry, I want to play the band.
I don't want to turn the train.
I don't want to see a play.
I don't want to use turning.
I want to play the band.
I want to get high school.
I don't wanna play, don't need time
I want to play, don't need time
I want to play in parking
I wanna get high Alrighty pay with me
I want to blame for everything I want to give myself
Yo! Oh, that's so really good
Just a little bit of punk, the punk corner on the tour
And I don't want to blame the fender
Comix dripping
Come on, he is my e-friend
Hello Adam for 20k
Former for 20...
But I still celebrate in spirit
So I am all
The red virus be by
guns and on
I am focussing on the future and stuff
But I might say I am apart
By too high-est e-o officials
Oh...
B oldu
Oh, well, they talked about it after
President of the Repian Commission and the guy who you know the guy who gave cause
the EU jobs to his Portuguese pal.
Oh yeah, all the guys at Total Bastard go look at his wiki pedi a page.
I mean even that has stuff that you won't believe.
He's from Portugal and by I'm angry by Hermann Van Rampoy, the president of the
European Council.
Oh yes.
Heiko Hermann.
And also a target of many many jokes by yourself.
Oh yeah.
He's a total dickhead.
Why not?
He's the president of the United States of Europe and all he's doing is reading his high
coups.
And by your boyfriend it worked.
And you know what I'm angry, I have to tell you, these two bosos both and Van Rampoy
didn't come to funeral of Polish president and they make it on the S. I mean come on.
They could just drive through Germany with cars and quickly on the funeral.
They didn't have to cross all shen or see or anything.
So I must admit that you're remarks about him and Van Rampoy as spot on you.
Yo.
Yeah.
Total Bastard.
I'm sure we're talking about Heiko Hermann more in the morning early service at noagendashow.com.
Yo.
Dave Kossemi this.
Dave is a founding producer of the noagendastream.com website.
Showing his support.
Not just for the stream but also for the Charlie.
Journey little mouth.
Undressed me.
A link in the show notes to the video which is hot.
If you're not hologram tricks that is.
You can only guess what that video's like.
Take it now.
Yeah.
Have you ever been faced?
No face with temptation.
Better than race.
For the next morning I'll show you what I look at you.
Orange nose.
Time to meet her.
Oh she won't stop looking at me.
It's a surprise I expected.
Take it now.
You are my fantasy.
Take it.
Take it now.
Do it now.
There's no question, she's too fun
Tell me, yeah, for the ride of my life
Who do you want me to go?
I'm going back to the body, yeah, yeah
I don't know if you can take it more
You can't believe it, yeah
I'm dressed in, come and please me
On the days you've got wings of their names ring
Let me teach you
You're my fantasy
Think it's time for you to come
Tell me, if you can take it more
You're my fantasy
Think it's time for you to come
I'm dressed in, come and please me
On the days you've got wings of their names ring
Let me teach you
You're my fantasy
Think it's time for you to come
Think that's time for you to come
a bunch of other shows that we're adding as we go along at nogendestream.com.
We've got Divoracora, which's unplugged, and we've got that John C. Divorac, JCDJ, interludes,
lots more stuff. For the first time, actually, I got an extra bandwidth bill about
three weeks into the month that hasn't happened, because of course the stream is growing
in popularity, so that's good news and bad news. Good news, because it's working bad news,
it's cost a more money. By the way, it's so cool to use any of the nogend apps I drive
wrong Los Angeles, and I've just got my iPhone. I just plug it right into the little holder
on the dashboard, and the stream works great. I'm listening to it all the time. Christina was
even in listening to the stream. She got the blackberry app, which is kind of a front end
to the web browser, but at least it works. And, by the way, I've been moved into our
priority app section on the blackberry, which is all cool, like that very much.
Before I forget, if you're looking for information about John Cirl, it's CirlSolution.com.
Again, CirlS Sierra Echo Alpha Romeo Lima, put a link to it in the show notes at dailySource
code.com. So, way over the one hour mark, but of course, that is a snap food Saturday,
edition of the Charlie. So, that's okay. If we go a little bit over. And, although I will
miss her terribly, as she leaves on Monday, and it'll be sad not to have her around for
the next two months. And I know she's coming back. That's great. I will say, I got to
talk a little bit softer. So, 19 year old years don't hear me. The one thing I am looking
for, too, is getting nasty again. Kind of can't do that when you're a kid in the next
room, don't you? So, let this be the message.
Let's get it all. We're all sensitive people. We're so much to you. I understand each other.
Once we got to be, let's live. I love them. I love them all. With me loving you,
maybe not not. And, giving yourself to me, can never be wrong. If the love is true, I'll
ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you.
I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you.
I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you.
I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you.
I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I
I'll ask you... I'll ask you. I'll ask you.
I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. Daddy's Roskanna's going.
I'll ask you. I'll ask you. I'll ask you. Daddy's going. I'll ask you. Keep going.
You appreciate what's going on with no agenda stream.com.
Please consider supporting us by donating to the cause.
You can find that at devorac.org-n-a-s november alpha cera, devorac.org slash n-a-s, and
we'll put your name right up there on the sustaining producers page as over a concede that
you are helping out.
What we're trying to do here.
All right.
So we're off to fries.
After I get the show uploaded, we're going to go get Christina Netbook.
That should be a fun experience, and he's suggestions.
Welcome, of course, email me out of it, mevio.com.
Show notes at noode at dailysourcecode.com.
All the tracks that are played with links to the artist's pages, et cetera.
It's all there.
And I will talk to you in the morning for early service.
Right here on nojentestreeting.com, and hopefully sometime next week on the daily source
code.
They're fine, mevio presentation, stick it in your ear, and remember.
Live your life with passion, and as long as it lasts, enjoy your freedom.