All right, as promised, we've got a special guest on today's Daily Source Code.
First time we've actually turned the Hilltop Watch Tower Crackpot Command Center Studio
into something that actually kind of resembles, kind of like a studio, I guess.
A little bit.
You back and forth, welcome.
Hi, thanks.
Hey, man.
Oh, hold on me.
Let me, uh, let me, uh, just take a wee bit of off for a second.
It's a little weird when we're talking when you got nothing but reverb.
So you, um, actually, uh, I met through, uh, your sister who was working for, uh, for
Mickey and San Francisco said, uh, you know, she's like totally hawk and you're totally
plugging the shit out of your stuff.
Like, oh, you got to listen to CD is really good.
And then, uh, and so, uh, me can't listen to, I was like, wow, this guy's really huge.
Are you sure he's Dutch?
It's like, and the first thing I noticed, man, is your accent is, is impeccable.
I mean, you can almost can't tell your Dutch.
Right, do I can?
But, uh, no, yeah, true, true.
So where did you learn to speak with such a great American accent?
Uh, TV.
Just, we just come a little bit closer to the mic because I can't, it's hard for me to work
the board and everything all the same time.
I only have two hands and, you know, I got to smoke as well.
Um, so now, uh, your, uh, professional musician as in, you do this for a living.
I do.
And, uh, you're living in the Netherlands, but thinking of maybe giving it a try over here
in the States.
Uh, I'm fan-to-planning it, fan-to-sizing and planning it.
Okay.
Good.
It's like a little recon mission.
And then Mickey actually asked you to come and perform at an art expo that she was doing in Amsterdam.
Yes.
And I was like, and he had, uh, three guys, right?
Yeah.
Or was it just one other guy?
I had one friend of mine with me in a percussion player from Venezuela.
Uh, we've been friends for some time and, uh, you know,
whenever I can, I hire him.
He was just like banging on some piece of wood like he was sitting on a box, you know.
It's called a cahoon and it's, uh, replaces a full drum kit basically and you play.
Really?
You play with two hands, it's got a little snare inside, so it sounds like a kid.
I have two cahoones.
Is that kind of the same thing?
One cahoon, two cahoones?
Yeah, you need big cahoones.
So you don't have, uh, any percussion with you today?
No, it's just me.
And, uh, you've got your fender, uh, strata cast right in my point out.
Uh, you've got it.
What kind of gear?
Because we're plugged directly into the board here, what you got?
Yes.
I brought a little line six device called the, uh, the pocket pod,
which is the smallest version of the, of the line six pod.
Uh-huh.
So it fits in my gig back, so.
Cool.
So when you perform, what do you do?
Your own stuff?
Do you do covers?
Uh, basically I pay what people want and I smile when they pay me.
It's a real treat to have you here, because I think you're a phenomenal musician.
Thank you.
And, uh, you know, I've been trying over the, you know, past day trying to, like, kind
of spury on that just, uh, give up the lowlands and come over here and, uh,
and give it a shot, man, because you, you got a lot of talent, and I think, uh,
when people hear this, they'll really, really enjoy what you're doing.
Thank you.
And, uh, so what are you going to do?
Yeah, I'd love you just to play as much as you feel like playing, because this is, uh,
you know, we don't have to, like, hit the network news or anything on the show.
Yeah.
So, uh, what would you like to do?
I was thinking of, uh, mixing it up, playing a few covers, um, you know,
some well-known stuff, and maybe a few originals as well, just, uh, you know.
Okay.
Let me, yeah.
Just give me a little vocal here, so I can set your reverb back.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Hey.
Mmm.
That's for you.
Nice.
All right.
You better come on.
Take it away, man.
Say the joke or to the thief.
There's too much confusion.
I can't get no relief.
Business man, they drink my wine.
Plow and dig my earth.
No, them down the line.
Not any other word, no.
No reason to get excited, no, no, no.
The thief you kind of spoke.
There are many here on my nerves.
Who know the life is just a joke.
But you will not weave Ben through that, yes.
And this is not our fate, no, no.
So little, snotspeak falls in our arms.
Who's the hours getting lay, yeah.
Yeah.
Along the watch style.
Princess kept you.
While all the women came and went.
They're for serving too.
Outside in the cold distance.
While can't get grow.
To run his reproaching.
And the wind, the wind began to haunt.
Along the watch style.
And of course, you played my theme song here in the watch tower.
I love it, man.
It's awesome.
I just realized we got an audience here.
But they only hear you singing.
You don't hear as guitar, right?
It's like, and it still sounds good.
Dude, I was just thinking about this.
We got to do something about the name.
I want to make it here.
You could be like, what can we make it?
First of all, I was thinking of cutting off the Birkin and just going with Bosch because it's like a powerful like Bosch.
Yeah.
Although Birkin has a ring to it though.
It's like, you Birkin, you Bosch.
Birkin stock.
Yeah, you'll be big and Berkeley.
Yes.
Okay, we'll work on that.
I'm sure some of the chuckle heads out there might have some ideas.
You want to play one of your own tunes?
Absolutely.
Alright, hold on.
Go for it.
This is a song called Something Good.
All my life I've been on the run.
Killing time getting nothing done.
I've spent so many nights on my own bed.
I don't want to end up alone.
Here the nose, the mistakes I've made.
Here the nose, there'll be hell to pay.
When I'm with you, I don't know what to say girl.
I feel lost, I feel in the way.
All I do is think about it.
Can't begin to live without it.
Hold on to the love you're feeling inside.
Baby, you need to get her.
Could make it through this heavy weather.
I'm not sure I did all that I could.
I just want to be a part of something good.
Something good, but part of something good.
Oh.
Maybe you could take care of me.
You and my heart start a family.
I'm afraid now this feeling's getting so strong.
Need to find out where long goes.
All I do is think about it.
Can't begin to live without it.
Hold on to the love you're feeling inside.
Baby, you need to get her.
Could make it through this heavy weather.
I'm not sure we did all that we could.
I just want to be a part of something good.
Something good, but part of something good.
Oh, I do is think about it.
Can't begin to live without it.
Hold on to the love you're feeling inside.
Baby, you need to get her.
Could make it through this heavy weather.
I'm not sure I did all that I could.
I just want to be a part of something good.
Something good, but part of something good.
Something good.
Dude, did you like come out of the womb with that voice and the chops like that?
Just like born with it?
Yeah, it's awesome.
That's a great song.
When do you write that?
About 2005, I think.
Really?
Go ahead and have a drink of water.
I'll compliment you while you're doing that.
I've been picking hit songs all my life on the radio.
That is definitely a hit.
That's a great song.
It's hokey, it's nice, it's what I think people are wanting to hear.
You got a record deal or anything like that?
I got nothing.
Yeah, it's talking musician.
We love it.
Perfect.
I'm basically playing tourist bars and Amsterdam doing cover stuff.
I play my own stuff whenever I can, but usually the bartenders like us to play.
The stuff that people know, so they buy more drinks, so the bartenders make more money.
Right.
But yeah, I do a little gigs here and there with my own stuff.
I've done a few bigger things.
I was a finalist on a pretty big live music competition back home.
Yeah, what's that?
That's the Hrotoprace.
This is a sponsored by the government.
It's a cultural department of culture, prize or something.
Yes, it's them in Hainick and I think.
Yeah, that's a Dutch government works with Hainick.
Can you, of course, they do.
All right, cool.
All right.
And did that get you any traction?
Did that work for you?
No, no.
And free beer.
Well, I got, uh, there was like an events company out there.
They scattered me and they hired me for some cool stuff.
Uh-huh.
For the world famous Johan Krav Foundation.
Okay, sure.
Stuff like that.
Sure.
Got hired to do some promotional stuff for, you know.
But nothing, nothing serious.
So when you look at the music business today, I mean, what do you see the future?
What do you think you'll be doing and what, what approach you're taking?
Because I presume you want to do this, right?
This is what, this is your passion, right?
Oh, yeah.
Well, I've recently got an in touch with some people back home that are wanting to help
me out.
There's like a small group of independent people that are trying to conquer the world, as
we're all trying to.
Sure.
And what I really need right now is I still don't have a recording of my own
stuff that I'm, you know, fully happy with.
So that's the first thing I'm going to do when I go back home.
Let's be pretty easy to find people who can know.
I mean, these days with, you know, max and pro tools and everything that should be
reasonably easy.
I mean, this will, this will be something you can enjoy listening to.
I don't think it's exactly what you want from a demo.
Not quite what you want.
Well, with you on it, my hair.
Well, do whatever we can.
I'd love for you to do a song by request for me, because I heard you do this.
Actually, I talked about this on the show a couple of weeks ago.
I heard you do this at the, at the art expo.
And I was like, oh my god, the first of all, the fact that anyone,
under 40 knows this song.
Right.
Second of all, would play it.
I was like, it just blew me away.
It's a real mother for you.
Johnny Guitar Watson was like, oh, yeah.
I mean, if you always had this in your repertoire, pretty much.
Johnny Guitar Watson is one of my favorite all-time artists.
What happened to him?
Is he still alive?
I think you had a heart attack in Japan on stage, actually.
Really?
And he passed away?
He died.
What a way to go.
Mid 90s.
Yeah.
But it had like sparks coming out of the guitar.
That would have been even better.
Go down in flames.
Yeah.
It's either on stage or in bed with a beautiful woman, right?
I mean, if you're going to get a heart attack, that's the way to go.
Hear that, Mick?
Yeah.
So who are your heroes?
Is Johnny Guitar Watson one of them?
Uh, yes.
Well, basically, I break my, my musical background down into like three components.
Like, there's the stuff I grew up around because my parents had it,
owned it or listened to it.
Right.
Add the same, sure.
So that's what was that?
What kind of stuff was that?
Uh, that's like the late 60s, early 70s rock.
Okay.
Cool.
You see, I grew up with like peppermint twist and crap like that.
I know all the 50 songs.
No, no.
I was like, uh, yeah, I listened to Rolling Stones, Jimmy Hendrix.
All right.
That kind of stuff.
Right.
And then, uh, when I was a teenager, I was, I was a big fan of Red Hot Chili
Peppers, uh, stuff like that.
Funky, funky stuff.
And then through the funk I discovered, you know, jazz through players like Marcus
Marcus, Marcus, Marcus, Marcus.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
And he mingus?
The whole, like, the real series, jazzy jazz stuff.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
I mean, I love it, but I can't do it.
So stay away from requires actual talent.
And, and a lot of drugs, I think.
Those guys must be way high to do that stuff.
I think you have to be.
Yeah.
How about Prince?
You're a fan of Prince.
Well, a huge fan of Prince.
Okay.
Yeah.
And that guy's amazing.
Everybody says you're genius.
But he actually is.
Yeah.
All right.
One by a new car.
Both the pricing and the right.
Be a downside cheaper.
Here's the woo.
Start right in the bike.
The making milk out of powder.
Got the biggest crime.
The rent's gone up higher.
Long, long, long.
Got the parents' line.
Get to room for the foil.
Make you want to run for color.
And if you look, you will discover.
Get to room for the foil.
Got to go to a disco.
And throw your troubles away.
Got to dance, dance to the music and baby.
That's a DJ play.
But then the lights come on, alone.
Just like a new day would.
Like a new day would.
You go home, face the music.
But don't sound too good, no.
Get to room for the foil.
Make you want to run for color.
And if you look, you will discover.
Get to room for the foil.
Make you want to run for color.
And if you look, you will discover.
Get to room for the foil.
Oh man.
You got to let your own percussion.
Everything going on there.
The same time is great.
It was tricky.
And do you consider yourself more a guitarist play a singer or a combo?
Generally, I try to stay away from the whole singer songwriter thing, which is technically what I am.
People kind of turn that into a genre.
Yeah, like jewel.
Right, even though it's more of a job description.
Technically, Jimmy Hendrix was a singer songwriter.
Oh, hell yeah.
No, I see.
I'm a guitarist singer singer.
Yeah.
You got to look though, man.
I think you know, you do something with like, I don't know.
What do you wear on stage?
Jeans and shirts.
Girls, we need to give this guy a look.
Yeah, you got it in you know, you really do.
Thank you.
People usually say, I'm like, like Michael McDonald meets Eric Laptant type of thing.
I don't know.
Yeah, I can't see where that comes from.
Yeah.
I'm not old.
No.
You're saying I don't know the compliment.
I'd love to hear some more of your own stuff.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
Go ahead and have some water there.
Can I get some background vocals on this?
No, because because my sister's there, she knows the song.
But I can't say.
Doesn't matter.
This is a, this is a song called, called You Should Be Here With Me.
And it does.
I don't care.
All right.
We're getting the whole family involved now.
Exactly.
So if you just stand in behind me, but that'll be great.
No, a little closer.
We're going to be able to hear it.
All right.
Well, it's, it's real simple.
All you have to do is sing along with me on the courses.
You should be here with me.
You know that song.
Yeah, because this, this is the, the audience participation
Proclamation song.
Yeah.
Doesn't work without.
All right.
So here we go.
Here we go.
I'm not sure if I remember
Your pants are all your face
But I'm positive that no one could ever come and take your place
I know you never meant to leave me stranded
You never planned to leave so soon
But I still sit around and picture
How you walk back into the room
People always talk about us
Saying I would could have been so tight
The million words would never fix this no
Because whatever they say, I still need you here tonight
You should be here with me
Not alone
Little little only came and showed me
Just what a man's supposed to be
And though you're on my started crackin
It still looks pretty good to me
I know you never meant to leave me stranded
You never planned to leave so soon
But I still sit around and picture
How you walk back into the room
People always talk about us
Saying I would could have been so tight
The million words would never fix this no
Whatever they say, I still need you here tonight
Because you should be
Here with me
You should be here with me
Where could I want to?
Oh, the love is real, when we touch I can't deny it, I listen with my skin, and that's when I begin to understand it.
Your hands speak so true, mine could never reach for others, they would just reveal, a love that can't be real, because I love you.
I need your touch so bad, only your hands can't reveal, I feel without you.
Then I look for you as real, when you're gone, I ache baby, because I need you close to me, when I run and hide.
I need your touch so bad, only your hands can't reveal.
I know that love is real, when we touch I can't deny it, I listen with my skin, and that's when I begin to understand it.
When I am far away, and wake up to another dark day, you touch me and I know that I love you so, though I might not show it.
I need your touch so bad, only your hands can't reveal, I feel without you.
Then I look for you as real, when you're gone, I ache baby, because I need you close to me.
When I run and hide, need your touch so bad, only your hands can reveal.
I'm sitting here, I'm listening with my eyes closed, I can't place your voice, it's really unique, and this is going to sound really weird, but the closest, does anyone ever compare you to anybody, they say you sound like,
everyone hates when you do that.
When they hear you do stuff, they want to give you compliments, so they like or know, so I usually get, oh, yeah, you have a beard and long hair and a guitar, so you're Eric Clapton,
you know you're John Legend, you know you're Michael McDonald, I get those are few names.
First of all, John Legend is our neighbor here, and he better watch his house, you'll be moving in, but I have to say a white Stevie Wonder.
I had my eyes closed, and it's meant as a compliment, obviously who can be Stevie Wonder, but you've got something,
and by the way, it was a beautiful, beautiful chord jazz, that's really, really nice stuff. Do you place Stevie Wonder, do you do any of his stuff?
I, yeah. I'm going to put you on the spot or anything.
Actually, I used to do superstition.
That's really tricky with that percussion, but maybe some handclaps, we can make it happen.
How about some cowbell? How about some cowbell?
Are you going to glue me into where we do the cowbell, no?
Very superstitions.
Riding's on the wall.
Letters bound to fall.
13 months old baby.
Broken looking glass.
30 years of bed look.
Good things in your past.
When you believe in things that you don't understand, you will suffer.
Superstition in the way.
Hit, hit, hit me.
Very superstitions.
Wash your face and hands.
Read me over the problem.
Do all that you can.
Keep me in the dead dream.
Keep me going strong.
You don't want to say me.
Sad is my song.
When you believe in things that you don't understand, you will suffer.
Superstition in the way.
Very superstitions.
Nothing more to say.
The devil's on his way.
13 months old baby.
Broken looking glass.
7 years of bed look.
Good things in your past.
When you believe in things that you don't understand, you will suffer.
Superstition in the way.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to listen to the strings of the guitar.
Now you know why I play the records, not make them.
Do you want to do one more just to play his home, your favorite song?
One of my favorite songs has to be Marvin Gaseong.
Baby, baby.
Oh, I bet you wanted how I knew about your plans to make me bloom.
With so much God that you're new before.
Dreaming to us, guys, you know I love you more.
You took me by surprise, I'm gonna say.
When I found out yesterday,
Don't you know that I heard it through the grapevine.
No much longer would you be mine.
Said I heard through the grapevine.
And I'm just about to lose my mind.
How they hung it, yeah.
Now I know the man that's supposed to cry,
But these tears I can't hold inside.
I'm losing you when in my life you see.
Because you mean that much to me.
And you could have told me yourself.
That you loved someone else.
Instead, I heard through the grapevine.
No much longer would you be mine.
Said I heard through the grapevine.
And I'm just about to lose my mind.
How they hung it, yeah.
Now I know the man that's supposed to cry,
But these tears I can't hold inside.
I'm just about to lose my mind.
And I'm just about to lose my mind.
People say they leave half of what you see.
You're son and none of what you hear.
But I can't help but be confused.
If it's true, won't you tell me, dear?
When you play and let me go.
Follow the guy that you loved before.
Don't you know that I heard through the grapevine.
No much longer would you be mine.
Said I heard through the grapevine.
And I'm just about to lose my mind.
How they hung it, yeah.
How they hung it, I know that you let me go.
Cause I heard it in the grapevine.
Said I heard through the grapevine.
Said I heard it through the grapevine.
All right, that's beautiful, man.
That's great.
Thank you.
So I think I figured it out.
I think it should be, I think you keep the Birkenboss.
Just keep it like Birkenboss.
Not Bosch because they can't figure that out here.
And they say, but you just gotta be John.
Just John Birkenboss.
I mean, it sounds good.
You know, it sounds like like you've got some years under your belt.
You know, you've been around the Mississippi Delta.
All right.
I'm like that.
I'm just saying you see that wall there.
And this wall, this brick wall.
Yeah.
So we got aerosmith, platinum CDs, Michael Jackson, platinum CDs.
Next time you come back, we'll have the John Birkenboss CDs there.
That's a deal.
Yeah.
I mean, really appreciate it.
It's very cool for you to stop by and do this for us.
No, thank you so much.
Yeah, you welcome.
Anytime come back.
And anything we can do for you.
Maybe people will be reaching out to who heard the show.
Where can they reach in?
Do you have email address?
Uh, yes.
The easiest thing to do would be Google my name, which is J-O-E-P.
Yep.
B-E-R-K-E-N-B-O-S-E-H.
And I got a dot com.
I'm on my space.
I'm on Facebook.
All right, I'll put some links in the show notes as well.
DailySourceco.com.
Some people can find you.
All right.
The great you back and bust everybody.
Yay.
Thank you.