Delta Sheriff Charlie eight four six the Fubar Friday edition
time on the operation of the machine become so
OAS makes you so sick and hard that you can't take part
you can't even passively take part and you've got to put your bodies
upon the gears and upon the wheels upon the levers
pile the apparatus and you've got to make it stop
For 16.57 minutes you're in 5-9
Time down you・ spanking, to say face
I'll know can you go, talk a lot of game on yen you know
Static on the way, make us all say,
Whoa, the people up top push the people down low, get down
And don't be every moron,
Static get mad if you haven't yet heard,
Gonna take what I got, don't be absurd,
Don't fight the power, nobody gets hurt
If you've ever heard it down, then you go very shit
We don't run, we're in the guns, I know
And look when make a move, there's my people say,
So got everything out of control, never everybody go
Every way, we don't run, we're in the talk
Give us the money, ourcription,
Or how do we guard the words?
So a lot of this change in his voice will tell us
We get your thoughts out of control,
The people are up top and up you put down the kick down
And I'm running it like that
The fun and the attack is exactly what I'm at
Someone between a kick and a high hat
A pin in a contract, a pitch in a contract
So give us a combat and I'm letting them know
They're ain't shit, you can see them in me back down
I know so, push the button, let go
Think most, it ain't everything that I control
Everybody go
Welcome!
Professor, Theрамord
We beat at no feels, Break our chains
One kick, a slope
We are on track withAll eight
The 70's and 70's
The 1980's are on track with All eight
The 70's are on track with All eight
We're on track with All nine
Let's play that sound for no heuer
From the front to the back, in the side of the side, if you feel what I feel, when I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up
with you, I'm up with me, I'm up with you, in the side of the side, if you feel what i feel, I'm up with you , I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up, up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with you, I'm up with
People run into the people on it and unless you're free, the machine will be prevented from working at all.
A little bit of a Lincoln park to kick off with food bar Friday.
Everybody just didn't source code episode 846 coming to you from the hilltop watch tower correct
My command center
Who baby I am once again tripping on aspirin coding nicotine
And something from Mexico would be a corona. Let's rock this puppy out
I'm shovelin to take the sand
But my head's in Mississippi
Theblees has got a hole in me
I believe I'm can't dissee
But I wasn't heaven
I can't forgive my man, I'm a night in my first dream
I thought I was heaven
But I was jumped into the parking lot
But then it feels a little silly, a little bit
And it feels like a little too
But I was jumped into the parking lot
And it feels a little silly, a little bit
And it feels like a little too silly
And as night I saw a lake of cappella
She was full to call for sleep in me
She was home in peace from how they were
About some new years
And as night I saw a lake of cappella
She was full to call for sleep in me
About some new years
And as night I saw a lake of cappella
She was full to call for sleep in me
About some new years
And as night I saw a lake of cappella
So yeah I was кусers
So when I saw i saw someramble
I'm still kind of recuperating from, I don't know if it was a super duper jet lag,
or if it was just, I don't know, some kind of 24-hour flu bugs.
So I'm not sure how much energy you'll have to make it through the entire projected
three hours of the day to source code today, but I've got everybody hanging out in the
chat room, no agenda chat.net, as we are live and no agenda stream.com, and you know what
we have to do, we've got to go out and we've got to propagate the formula.
Remember, it's on the inspiration time to say, I'm formula is this, we go out, we hit
people in the mouth, bring it back to yard of Arabia, the way it used to be, before
it was all automated and computerized, taking your requests, it almost, we want the air
waves, condiments, we are the air waves, 3G, Wi-Fi, all feeling alive from the crackpot
dimension, in the middle time, we want the world that we want in the air, we want to say
and how we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we
want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves,
we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air
waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air
waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the
air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air wave scary, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we want the air waves, we
What's absolutely no way I could do a show last week, so I'm so happy we're back on the air everywhere with the remote.
Why the air waves?
I'm running out of steam already.
I think I need another sip of this corona, that'll probably help me out just a little bit.
Hey, excellent, excellent song choices.
You guys are semi-market couch in the chat room.
You sent me a whole slew.
Clap-to, Randy Asher.
You have to send me this one.
You know it's 420 somewhere.
Pop the mud, stole.
Kind of the way I'm feeling right now.
I gotta get this shit out of my chest.
I know this sucker behind the desk.
You try to tell me that you know best.
Without your fingers, without your head.
It's sunshine.
It's how it feels to me.
But I can't because of it.
It's a new dream.
It's a new view.
It's a fire.
I'm so chill like you.
I gotta chill at the front door.
When I get the time to take you.
I don't understand why I'm so well-o-o.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o.
Yeah!
I gotta get this shit out of my back.
I run and suck those blood out.
I won't crack.
So fucking sick of your heart at the desk.
You're a young thing.
I stop your name.
The sunshine is on its way to me.
I'm not a camera call.
It's a new dream.
It's something you've wired.
Get an iron.
I'm so chill like you.
I gotta chill at the front door.
When I get the time to take you.
I don't understand why I'm so well-o-o.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o.
Why do I always waste my time?
No, no, no.
Yeah, I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o.
I am my worst-a-pin liar.
Fucking liar.
So chill like you.
I gotta chill at the front door.
When I get the time to take you.
I run and suck those blood out.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o-o.
I gotta chill at the front door.
When I get the time to take you.
I run and suck those blood out.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o.
It's not your thing.
I'm just a fist-o-o-o.
Making your ears bleed with a trotting.
And you know the parties can wake when Bobby even shows up
in the chat room, no agenda chat.
Net, the official porn star of the chuckleheads.
Coast to coast globally and worldwide.
Bobby, nice to see you, baby.
Fuck you.
Just punch you.
This is crazy.
One more time, baby.
I'm thinking that I'm suck those blood out.
Making your ears bleed with a trotting.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o-o.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o-o-o.
Making your ears bleed with a trotting.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o-o-o-o.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o-o-o-o-o-o.
Making your ears bleed with a trotting.
I'm thinking that I'm not a fist-o-o-o-o-o.
The King's got a bowl of wheel
Sitting out on the mountain top
All the top singing about the blue
Like at home
Mississippi's dirty copyfields
I'm on the team
Troy City's on the top of the wheels
It's the same
I'm on the bottom of the sand
So I'm going through the moon
And I'm going to take my home
Cause I ain't got nothing to lose
And I'm going to take your soul
It's feeling better
I'll be the dude
Tell me about it
It's the right
Here I am
Don't need a suit
You're going to need a fireball
I'll kill you
Never know what to say
You can kill me
Yeah
It's all sex
Don't fucking know
All sex
It's all sex
It's comedy
Men you lose
户
All sex
It's all sex
户
You can't see
It's all sex
户
I'm the vacuum old Jesus
It's all sex
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey I can't see, I wish I fell, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
a
real
Time to take it
To a whole new level
Been out on the road for over a week. Get my nation lowlands met a lot of
No agenda fans of course also chuckle heads
So I've been out Roman
I
In a road begun, I'm afraid I am stripped of all my pride
So in her I do goodbye, and she keeps me set as fire
Gives me a warning, and the dust in the drug that creed
Only knowledge will I save, to the game you still save
Move on, run, run, you man, back up on, don't need what you will
Oh, I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind anyway
And I'll read a file anyway, I need you where I'm wrong
Where only my head is so dead
And you're because of the road, I attempt to steal you
To the unknown, I don't want to resign through
By myself, I'm not a law, I asked no one, it like size I've severed
Let's buy out the more I can, what the being better I bring
Move on, run, run, you man, back up on, don't need what you will
Oh, I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind anyway
And I'll never find anywhere I'm wrong
Where only my head is so dead
But I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind
And I'll take my time anyway, I need you where I'm wrong
Where only my head is so dead
And you're because of the road, I attempt to steal you
To the unknown, I don't want to resign through
By myself, I'm not a law, I'm wrong
Where only my head is so dead
But I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind anyway
And I'll never find anywhere I'm wrong
Where only my head is so dead
But I'll take my time anyway, I need you where I'm wrong
But I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind
Where only my head is so dead
Maybe it's just recovering from the sickness that I'm reminiscing a little bit
But I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind
And I'll take my time anyway, free to speak my mind
Ain't no pussy when she's gone
It's my hand when she's away
And when my dick don't get no service
My dog gets really nervous
A county hurts the unfair
I wrapped my dick in my big mass
I shared my birthday with my boss
He said I love the secret sauce
I can't leave a little thing alone, ain't not pussy when she's gone
I want to make you happy, I want to make you happy, I want to make you happy
Hot pockets, ready to sleep, and sleep, yeah, make okay
All right fellas, what's up?
All right, we're getting so hot, really let the bad things sit in your stomach
All right, we're getting so stressed, I like to tell you everything
Oh, what's your man at the back?
It's a matter of fact, size, it was red at the sun
And the girl is a cold, and no one ignore anything
She's the passionate one
Oh, yeah, it's like lightning, everybody was fighting
But the music was soothing, and they all started to ruby
I'm the man at the back, she's the every one attack
And the girl is the cold, and no one ignore anything
She's the passionate one, no one ignore anything
All right, we're getting so stressed, I like to tell you everything
Oh, yeah, it's like lightning, everybody was fighting
Something so different ahead, again
All right, we're getting so stressed, I like to say everything
And the girl is everything, since six days, it has been so easy
All right, buddy, now that the man's the back of the red is more than anything
You can take that to the bank.
Put down your speakers!
Oh shit!
Oh yeah!
My life thing!
Everybody was wife thing!
My music was soothing!
But the old story is booming!
Oh baby!
Yeah!
And the man of the box said it!
Everybody jacked!
And he jacked it to a ballroom place!
And the girl in the corner said fire!
Everybody will tell you about who you listen!
Ballroom place!
It is ballroom place!
Yeah!
Ballroom place!
The pool!
It is a ballroom place!
Nothing like a little bit of 70s jam on the Charlie.
I'm getting my second man name in my third win by now!
And ramping it up, I was prepping for the show,
looking through all the Gmail, seeing what I could find,
and it came across this one from GX2
from about 36 shows ago.
I think you'll enjoy it even more,
the second or third time you hear it.
And it.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5
5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5
5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 6, 5, 5,
I love you, love you, love you
I love you, love you
I can't just ignore it, I can't just ignore it
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
The audience is still there, you stupid dick-wad music directors and program directors
who think you know what you're doing, spit not everything on computers, you've ruined
radio.
That's why we're here.
And I got a couple of requests that came in and you can always email the to me at
them at curie.com and I have a Dropbox account as well by the way.
So if whenever you put something in a Dropbox, especially who are sharing music,
I really, it's very handy for me for a number of reasons so that would be highly appreciated.
This one comes from down.
And bloody curie, snafu Saturday, wasn't that an outrageously good particular episode
of the Daily Source Code.
If you don't know the Daily Source Code, go check it out, people, you'll have an amazing
time he's playing the soundtrack's of our life.
And my life in particular, Adam, I'm four years older than you buddy, and that is exactly
the soundtrack of my life.
But mate, you've missed one track, one track that I'm going to email to you so that you
can play it.
It's my Russell Morris, the Australian artist.
You may not even know of him.
I'm surprised if you haven't because this is an outrageously good song.
This song is not a song.
It's not even an opus.
It's a religious experience.
And I want you to play it as a soundtrack to my life and the soundtrack to all Australians
lives for anybody who's over 30.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
This is Russell Morris and the real thing.
Come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing,
come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing,
come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing,
come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing,
come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing, come and see the real thing,
Love, I believe that I've really been
Come and see, we'll make you come and see
We'll make you come and see
And I'm not too sweet, I'm not too sweet
I'm not too sweet, I'm not too sweet
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no oh hi hi there set the
pink hair dye. Oh, you're on the poopout.com diet. I wish, no, it's nasty. I'm actually feeling
really queezy. So current life status, go and see Peaches later and talking to her executive
producers next week about possible show. Okay, cool. And maybe meeting with a channel over here
to present. Don't tell anybody. I'm telling you, I'm just giving them a little hint. All right,
so you post it a link on a tweet to a song that I actually got from iTunes. Do you know
who the name of these guys are? Crap, I don't know the name of the guys. Let me see if I can find
it. Hold on a second. Is it a dickhead song? Yeah, exactly. Yeah, let me see. I hope you told them. Have
you told them, no, the reason why I, it's the grand spectaculars with the song. I know. I know.
I know. Because I was watching her and like this is her. The song is about her. She is what we call
a shortage asshole. He's London pretentious dick who thinks it's uber cool to be all different
and hang out in a record store and drink coffee and like be vegan. Fucking vegan.
Just one year, I'm a fixed bike. You got a plus one year. I'm like you tonight. I play sea.
You will be a sea.
When it's when you visit, just a pair of empty frames.
Dressing like a nuttle, no, I never go to the craze. I remember when the kids are stupid
for me names. Now I'm taking over their mistakes. Well, no, my life is a dickhead.
Oh, my friends are dickheads too. Come quickly, let's be dickhead.
Be in a dickhead's group. Be in a dickhead's group. Be in a dickhead's group.
Be in a dickhead's group.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. On my iPhone, you take it bitches on London feels upon the blocks
so everyone goes, we're having new age fun with the vintage feel.
Coolest kids to lower health rates, exclusive list of kids, my name, I go to...
You couldn't get it in. Never pour that pack of fags I only roll my own.
Look in your mouth, the pinkest star but star but roe. Say I look in me, I really don't.
I'm the coolest guy you never know. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, my life is a dickhead. Oh, my friends are dickheads too. Come with me, let's be dickhead.
Be in a dickhead's group. Be in a dickhead's group.
Lovers with no size. Be in a joke, meet solid hip hop, in determined sex, reference,
something retro on my necklace.
Basically, I'm a part-time blocker, I'm a salmon and jewelry line, I'm sick, I'm sick,
reading this icon up to the kind of mistakes by the battle's life.
Are you okay with the eyes, I think in ease...
Yeah, I'm currently running my own magazine.
And it's sort of a bad play法
and all the versus SS9's that thing that I've done and the tambst ate spr Skillмы or white buff.
The video really has to be seen too, to fully enjoy that being a dickhead.
Available on I.Tunes, and of course you'll be able to find the entire playlist of
at noagendaentertainment.com.
I need some guitar baby.
I need to get back in here.
Joe Wells!
Bring it on baby.
I know where you're going.
I don't think there's anything right.
You don't think it's your way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah and yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, don't, yeah, yeah woo, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, like yeah, yeah yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, sure yeah, yeah,
I must admit, I can't explain, and it's all thanks to my brain.
It's true, the baby I'm calling for you.
All right, something wrong with the actors here have not got a clue.
Baby I'm calling for you.
It's true, the baby I'm calling for you.
The baby I'm calling for you.