Delta's Sierra Charlie 836 Food Bar Friday extravaganza
Who's 16-year-old assistant in ensuring five nine's up-time turn?
The 21st century of rainbow stars here.
The 21st century of rainbow stars.
The 21st century of rainbow star.
The 21st century of rainbow stars here.
Park a man sent a clue where I am out of control
Successful launch of version 2.0 of my app in the app store
It's been a pretty good week
And if you're listening to Noah Genesis Dream.com join the party in the chat room, please
Noah Genesis.com, it's where it's all taken place
We're all the people coming together requests on for the full one
We're fighting
Now first of me way to the lowest station
We're late, we're going home, we're left inside
They'd let John and Robin ring on the ring
We're the least out of the station in the ride
And it's a two-ball six-layer in the two-layer
We're my regular group tonight
Three, five, seven, nine, couple, one, nine
What a waste, I'm coming up with a morning light
We're getting pretty early too, we're all the Italian
This song's a tough one, we're gonna be on you
They know you're setting up for the back of my neck
They know what a good-looking man you know
Two, four, six, eight, never too late
We're my regular group tonight
Three, five, seven, nine, couple, one, nine
We're sun coming up with a morning light
But the ring don't boot you to choose to lose the turtles
You know what I know when you're acting right all wrong
No one knows if you know we're leaving nowhere
Gotta keep on going home with a morning light
Two, four, six, eight, never too late
Just be my regular group tonight
Three, five, seven, nine, couple, one, nine
What a waste, I'm coming up with a morning light
Two, four, six, eight, never too late
We're my regular group tonight
Three, five, seven, nine, couple, one, nine
We're sun coming up with a morning light
But table, we're sun coming up with a morning light
All right, so I figured out what was going on with the sound set
It seems like my housekeeper cleaned the mixer
She had just a couple of knobs for it
Basically, over modulating the entire system
I was just happy
To roll up some band right there at the top of didn't source code
Three, six, two, four, six, eight, motorway
Going back to the mid 70s
And it's an all-request footballer Friday
I've been very busy writing them all down
Searching the iTunes door and finding what you want to hear
Today to get your weekend started
Time's up time
See what's become of me
All right, so I figured out what was going on with the sound set
It seems like my housekeeper cleaned the mixer
Time's up time
See what's become of me
All right, I looked around
All my possibilities
I was so hard to please
The ground
He's a ground
Time's up
He's a haze
He's a sailor
Winter
In my salvation I'll be found
Down by the side
He's bound to be a better eye
Than what you've got planned
Carey your career
The ground
He's a ground
He's a haze
He's a winter
And I'll tell you how it's my friend
That's the needs
He's been the saviour
He'll show past away
Simply pretend
That you can be the mechanic
The ground
He's a right
She's been changed for the scenery
We've been tied in a touch of the stream
Won't you stop everything we do?
Hey, what's up?
How are you?
I'm fine.
Where are you?
Make sure you're fine.
He's on the right track.
Okay, this is.
Yeah, it's hard to hold it.
We'll be breaking it down and talking about some stuff that's going on a little bit later on in the show.
We'll be going for the next hour, maybe two depends on the feedback.
Kind of tunes you guys wanted here.
I think we're kind of in sync today, which is nice.
Don't roast it on the Charlie.
You know, spritz.
We'll be breaking it down and talking about some stuff that's going on.
But don't be sorry.
Coal right skin.
Let's take care of it in the rain.
Have a fresh and delightful night.
We'll be breaking it down and talking about some stuff that's going on.
We've been broken down and talking about some stuff that we've been talking about.
Let me put you in the picture.
Let me show you what I mean.
The besides is the main document that is going on.
I ain't no care about you, my queen
Then it won't you in the picture
Let me show you what I'm in
Over the size of this world
I ain't no care about you, my queen
I have a dream and a single light
Don't put it out
And she's all right here, she's my sister
Hey, man, get your hands off my sister
She's in the screen, she feels like a sound
I forgive you, boy
But don't need time
Call my skin, make it in the rain
Have a touch in the light
On your head
Let me you say
Ah!
Hey, man, again
On your head
M
Let me put you in the picture, let me show you what I mean
Let me sign your is my sister, ain't okay, man she's like we
Let me show you what I mean
I'm pretty sure I'm going to take you on the version of a musical journey today during the
836 episode of Daily Source Code, I got quite neglected mix line thus for you.
You've been some, uh, dare I say it, 50s music and maybe even some nice or maybe something from
last week. So be prepared for a very wild ride indeed, you chuckle heads.
Play something you never hear on the radio. Only a live version of a song.
Only the direst rates can really pull it off every single time consistently the substance of swing
in though. It's a way it didn't depart a beta
tell the rim and you stwn you work, play it on the ice
but it's going acceleratorReggle filter
Feel a way lady in the music
Yeah, but now you're stupid inside, but you don't see you too many things in.
Put it out in the ring to eat a chance, go down.
Come and kiss too many other places.
Give it a hold, say, blow it that sound and blow it up.
We're down south, we're all down south, but then tell.
Yeah, but now you're stupid inside, but then tell.
We're all down south, but then tell.
Can you feel it?