Delta Sierra Charlie eight four eight these snafu Saturday edition
I fall for law here, the law world. I need it money card. I had none. I fall for law here, the law world. I fall for law here, the law world.
I live my baby and it feels so bad and yes my face is for her. She's the best girl I've ever had.
I'm all for law here, the law world. I fall for law world. I fall for law world.
I'm all for you, I'm all for you, I'm all of you, it's just my gives.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no any, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh man, it's been one of those days, it's crazy!
The clash, I fought the law in the law one on the daily source code episode 8-4-8 coming to you from the Hilltop Watch Tower.
Crackpot Command Center is a snap-through Saturday edition, so we will eventually make your ears bleed.
Instead of kind of easing to everything, as I am multi-multi-tripple tasking today.
I am so sorry that I'm so late with the show, those of you in getmonation east,
and the United States of Europe, and even the Holy Land check it out on the chat room.
No one's in the chat.net.
I'll tell you what I've been doing later on, but first was rolled out one of the Marcus Couch tunes he sent in from Captain Clothes.
I've been hanging around this channel for, I've been coming around this hotel so long.
I've been hanging around this channel for, I've been coming around this hotel for way too long.
I wish we were all dead, so burned, just hide it from me like watching TV.
If we just look a lot better, like to know I got to get out, but it's just so tight,
wait by the chains keep me in the room, this channel for, I've been pulling around this hotel too long.
I've been hanging around this channel for, I've been pulling around this hotel for way too long,
but I've got a trick.
Let's go.
Let's wear it for a little bit.
Let this girl that's on us to the ban and play
She says, We're a husband veteran, I've been lying right here on the floor.
Relaxing, this time he You've weighed a
But what is my money?
Hated what I am, after the last rain and hit around
This town on the corner
I've been coming around this old town so long
I've been hanging around this town on the corner
I've been buying around this old town
For way too late
I've been on the corner
I've been buying around this old town
For way too late
I've been hanging around this town
I've been calling around this old town
For way too late
I've been waiting for way too late
Bring him back the art of radio
The way it used to be the way it should be
The way it's going to be in the future
This is the daily source code
We are on the Snapfru Saturday edition
I've got to tell you Marcus Couch saved my ass today
I have absolutely no time to prep for the show
Although what's great is all these Dropboxes
Everyone's created
Apparently what happens is you just update the Dropbox
And more shit falls into it
And I open it up and it's like
Oh there it is already to load into the system
Totally loving that
I really appreciate it
But of course it's going to benefit everybody
Which is the cool thing about it
You put it together at your show
It's the source code for the chucklehead
No sometimes
I don't know why
I'm so talented
Just seem so homeless
I ain't really sure
I'm going to seem like a middle of a good child
But just a little bit more
In focus
But when she runs her arms around me
I can't come out
Ross of woman
Cos I love my三-year girls
Tell her I'm my father
I'll find no fucking drama
One more of the shit
You can talk.
She leads the road
She is your lead hit
Every now and then I get down to the middle of the day I'll just stop
And as myself, the wild gonna come
It just seems so useless to have the word so hard
And nothing ever you seem to come from it
Because I should know it's really
This is when you're lost by the moment I came to give the guy
Look, it feels so good, it's all free, it's all right
I know we never know, change our minds about it
Yeah, you're welcome
Yeah, it comes with me
Yeah, she looks so right
She's a need to know
Watch it all
Every time it seems like another level more about myself I'll reach out
Now I'm home, something
Yeah, I just catch myself wondering
We were in about some silly things
No matter the nothing
And then she knows me that
She realized I'm gonna know I can't get it down
I'm gonna feel so good, so free, it's all right
I know we never know, change our minds about it
Yeah, you're welcome
Yeah, she looks so right
She's a need to know
Watch it all
Yeah, you're welcome
Little message from my buddy Ray on the Charlie
If you could send me the direct link to your Dropbox
That would be even better if you could share it with me
That way I can grab all those awesome tracks you've got on there
And of course the Ray on the Charlie for episode 848
Wow, 848 episodes already
Holy crap, have we been doing this for a couple of years?
Am I just nuts?
Oh man, it's a beautiful day here at the Hilltop Watch Tower
Crackpot Command Center not a came trail in the sky
Which is always good news
Although last night we were in the hot tub
And I looked up and there they were middle of the night
1030 came trail in a way
Oh, there you go
Of course everyone's sick
Yeah, this is what happens
But today it's nice we've got about 80 degrees
It's just fantastic
And because last night it was occupied doing other things
That's why I didn't get around to taping my episodes
For the big app show of course now I'm doing two
We've got the iPhone version and the Android version
And it's a lot of work
I desperately need to get what do you call those?
Yeah, an intern
I need to get an intern here to help
Someone who can actually do Final Cut Pro
That's all I need
Then I would free up 80% of my time if I just had that
So that's something that we need to put the word out for
If you know someone who can be
I'll pay him not very much
An intern in the Los Angeles area
Near the Hollywood Hills
It would be highly appreciated
You have your food bars back
Your snafu's back
Everything on time
I'm a one-man band
Rollin' out the tunes that you put together on eight, four, eight
The chuckle heads unite, bring him back radio
The art of it, the way it should be
Worldwide and global
When it fathills out my life is still
Trying to get up that
Repeat healer of hope
For a destination
Are you lost quickly when I knew I should
That the world was made up of this robberhood
A man
For whatever that means
Into a crazy times
When a mind met
Is you getting all that
What's in mind
In a
I am feeling
A little peculiar
In so a way
Keep the loneliness about sight
And I take a difficult
Then I can't feel high
And I dream from the top of my lungs
What's going on
Are you lost quickly when I knew I should
That the world was made up of this robberhood
A man
For a destination
Are you lost quickly when I knew I should
That the world was made up of this robberhood
A man
For whatever that means
I'll be alone
And I dream from the bottom
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
for non-blans, what's going on?
FORZ ..
It was a totally love track, just a nice first afternoon Saturday.
so one of the interesting things here with the setup is that my PFF, my pre-fader-лosing interface just
Get the shit, so it's very hard to listen to tracks outside of the broadcast, but under my best.
Still be able to keep the show rolling.
Take you a little bit to the higher ground.
But keep the show rolling.
Keep the show rolling.
I'm so done.
I didn't like the slide again.
Because my last time on it, my leather hole looks same.
I'm so glad that I know my leather hole.
They're gonna keep the show rolling.
Keep the show rolling.
Keep your show rolling.
Moving again.
Let's keep on turning around
Doesn't find me to run
I'll love
Love us
Keep on loving
Believe us
Keep on being even
Just started sleeping
presque but not comfortable
From what I've got to say
And so I'm dreaming and not trying to look dead
Just finished I'm about to try and noticed
Oh, this is really...
This is bugging me.
I think I'm gonna have to do some intro reconfiguration here for a second.
Yeah, and that's what I thought would have.
I hope for you that fix something.
Let me just double check.
Yeah, totally did it.
Just a little resample on the audio interface.
That's all it takes.
Yeah, that's one of those things.
Just a little resample on the audio interface.
Yeah, once you got that done, then you're all cool.
It's a daily source code.
We are totally situation normal all fucked up.
It's how we roll, setting resample rates in real time.
If you are listening to us on the Norwegian-Destream and Norwegian-Destream.com,
where you need to be, is in the chat room.
At Norwegian-Dachat.net, join the party.
Talk with the friend of mine.
I was in a car crash, it wasn't the war,
but I never been quite the same.
Little while less like I was there.
You've been watching humans trying to get around.
Oh look, there's a red machine.
I don't outside if it looked the other way.
Wouldn't believe the things they do.
I don't know.
I don't know why I didn't figure this one out before, man.
Really, the way to do this is Dropbox.
That is just so outrageously cool.
I just get a shared Dropbox.
I opened it up.
It's there.
The songs appear magically when they've been synchronized with my computer.
And then I just drag them into my playout system and then they're gone so I know that
I've played them.
It's like freaking amazing.
I love this.
From now on, Dropbox is the way to go.
I've even signed up and I pay for an account man.
This shit is just totally out of control.
I'll have my own stuff more under control in about 15 minutes to be able to really focus
on the show.
I just got to get these episodes out.
One of them's rendered for Android, so I'll be putting that up in the iPhone.
And then I'm going to make your airs bleed.
Airs bleed, I promise you.
You know why?
It's not even my airs to bleed.
You need to roll out some cowbell today as well.
It's the doors and they want that.
It's the door and they want that.
You're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a
woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're an, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, or you are a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman, you're a woman
I see your hair is burning.
Heels are filled with fire.
If they say I never loved you, you know they are alive.
And now you'll free away.
Midnight now is Rome.
I've seen cars that taples past, never so warm.
So alone, so alone, so alone, so alone, so alone.
No gentleman ain't better madness.
So chain a move, fly at the center.
Midnight now is Rome.
I, you are looking in the middle of the city of L.E.
I got another note in your room.
It is now.
It is night.
Wow.
Help.
I, you are looking in the middle of the city of L.E.
It is kind of cool, right?
Since when did you hear that one on the radio last?
I mean, certainly in that version.
Like that long extended version.
The doors, Jim Morrison, dude.
That guy was super freaking cool.
LA woman here on the daily source code episode 848.
Of course, they have got a nice chat room filled with all the chuckle heads.
They are hanging out various parts of the world.
I do apologize for being so late.
I know a lot of people are going to have to check out and get monation east.
And in the United States of Europe, it is just a little bit too late.
But I will get to the Ray on the Charlie and as well to come extra blogger who has
something waiting in the wings.
Because it has been a crazy two weeks.
It is kind of the last time since we spoke with each other.
Because I have been heads down.
Building, releasing the big app show for Android, which out of the gate is a phenomenal
success.
I am pretty amazed at the Android app community.
At least the Apple Hallics.
I had no idea.
I mean, every single episode, thousands of accesses.
Of course, a lot of these apps are free, which makes it even better.
Alright, this one should probably get me through to where I need to be and get in this
crap for least.
It is traffic.
Low spark of high hill boy.
If you see something, it looks like the storm.
And it's shooting up out of the ground.
And your head is spinning from a loud guitar.
And you just can't escape from the sound.
Don't worry too much.
It will happen to you.
We want your young ones playing with toys.
And nothing like your hearing is only the sound.
The percentage of playing is the new high price.
While you're living beyond all your means.
And the money in the suit has just bought a new car.
From the pocket he's made on your green.
But today you can swear that the men are shocked.
I've got nothing to make any noise.
But it was on the board at the lighting to rest.
Was the loss of the high hill boy.
And you just can't escape from the sound.
And nothing like your hearing is only the sound.
Would you ask for something like another chance?
Or something similar as this?
Don't worry too much, it'll happen to you.
And stars, your sorrows, your youth.
And nothing will not be spared to you.
And all you sound are the last part of the high hill boy.
The person said, job playing against the high price.
While you're living beyond all your means.
And the man in the suit has just bought a new car.
From the top of these made on your wings.
But today you can square that the name is shot down.
But the lock in the lake ain't nice.
But it wasn't the boy.
The lady to rest was the last part of high hill boy.
Higher boys.
If I gave you everything that I owe, and as for nothing in return, would you do that same for me?
As I would for you, I'll take me far right, and strip me of everything including my pride,
but spit it as something that no one destroys, and the sound that I'm hearing is only the sound of the earth that I need for you.
Yeah, back in the day, we used to throw that right.
We had to either screw a groovy or take a really long shit.
These days, it's just to do other stuff, compress files, get them ready, upload them, sorry about the dropouts once in a while.
The stream that is somehow Firefox likes to take all resources available on the machine, the minute I fire up a web page.
I'm not quite sure what's going on with that.
Almost there, I'm almost ready, but I think we can start bringing out the cowbell for a second, can we?
Yeah, let's say we need to try and make careers bleed.
We're still a bit of Mississippi Queen.
And we're going to strip the queen.
We're now running out of things, we're running with the other way.