Delta Sierra Charlie, 8-2-3!
We're 16 months to 7 minutes and shooting five nons of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We are way nons.
We can't get any of our lives.
I know you're the strength of your honesty.
It's a battle curry.
Don't you got to let me know.
Should I stay or should I go?
If you say that you are mine,
I'll be here till the end of time.
So you've got to let me know.
Should I stay or should I go?
It's always days, days, days, days.
You're happy when I'm on my knees.
One day is fine and next is black.
So if you want me of your back,
Welcome on and let me know.
Should I stay or should I go?
Should I stay or should I go now?
If you say that you are mine,
Show me what you know.
Should I stay or should I go?
Let me know.
You're happy when I'm on my knees.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
You know which clothes even fit me
Come on and let me know
Should I cool it or should I blow
It'll get on me
I see you
You know which clothes even fit me
Come on and let me know
Should I stay on Shura Go down
Should I pull it on?
If I stay here will be tough
Should I cool it or should I blow
It is daily source code episode 823.
We are on the air, just about everywhere, global transmission starts now on no agenda
stream.com.
If you are listening and you are near a computer, please, it is up at the chat room, it is
all the fun, it is no agenda.com.
2 of the show that is back, I think the question the class asked us to answer, I think
I should stay, and you know what, it is like all of a sudden the show is just kind of getting
ready to roll out of me, I am ready to go, didn't even have to do all that much prep, although
I would like a little more pot-save music, I do have a couple tracks coming up for you later
on, and we are going to be talking about a number of things.
In the vein of laying it all out there, open source divorce on the chuckle today, that
should be interesting, got a couple of old familiar voices, he will be back, and yes, one
counted one promo that I will play for you, for the next hour, the source code is
back and in your face, and this is the outstanding long version of this song which you
never hear on the radio anywhere, which is why it deserves to be heard, deep inside your
membranes, jam in the plugs, Martin Offers got it for you, let it reverberate, it will
be heard, that's the way to do it, you play the guitar on your TV, I am working, that's the way to do it,
you play the guitar on your TV, you play the guitar on your TV, I am working, that's the way to do it,
you play the guitar on your TV, you play the guitar on your TV, you play the guitar on your TV,
you play the guitar on your TV, you play the guitar on your TV, you play the guitar on your TV, trust yourself,
you play the guitar on their TV, you play the guitar on their TV, you play the guitar on his TV, you play the guitar on your TV,
you played the guitar on their TV, you play the guitar on his TV, you play the guitar on their TV, you play the guitar
on their TV, you play the guitar on their TV, you play the guitar on their TV, you play the guitar on their TV,
See howtime moves brings as you wait a 3 minute
Broza, move, here's Color TV
Oh, right
Oh, up we mind
Go 푹
Snow right, where is
As I put you in the middle of the road
It's got to move me to the refrigerator
I've got to move me to the refrigerator
Look at you
I should have been to play the guitar
I should have learned to play the drums
Look at that mama, she got it
Thinkin' in the camera, I met her
I look at her, so
And he's up there, what's there?
Come while you know it's us
You're bringing on a bundle like this
Oh, that's a ring
That's the way you're doing it
You're doing it for nothing, it's a chick
It's so free
We've got to be strong like a wave of the moon
Because you catch it, you're never ready
We've got to move me to the refrigerator
Yeah
Listen, yeah
That ain't working
That's the way you're doing it
You play the guitar on the empty thing
That ain't working
That's the way you're doing
One, two, one, four, nothing in your cheeks, I'm free
Six, four, three, I'm free
One, two, one, four, nothing
One, two, one, four, nothing in your cheeks, I'm free
Six, four, three, I'm free
Six, four, nothing in your cheeks, I'm free
Two, one, four, nothing in your cheeks, I'm free
One, two, one, four, nothing in your lips, I'm free
One, two, one, four, nothing in your cheeks, I'm free
Two, one, two, one, four, nothing in your lips, I'm free
I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on
it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, and I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm oh, on it, I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on there on it
Okay, I'm getting complete.
Thanks for the chat room, and I had Twitter that the stream is in Mono once again today.
It's something that I definitely have to figure out because there's nothing like hearing
mock-knock-flur in stereo.
Oh, oh, I'm in dire straits, I just think you're showing up again.
In the extended version of money for nothing, chicks for free.
Which I'd say is kind of what we expected with podcasting back in the day, isn't it?
At least I did.
I thought, hey, it's gonna be great.
Now what we got to do is just do some shows, and the money I'll show up.
And of course, didn't turn out exactly that way, but I do want to correct something.
I said, on the source code, on, was it Friday, the Football Friday edition.
Dave Winner actually was right that podcasting and blogging may not necessarily result directly
in money, but it does give you ways to make money.
In association with your programming.
And I do want to mention that is exactly what Mivia was finally stumbled upon.
And if you want to know more, then hit me up with an email and I will forge over to Brian
Callwell and he'll definitely let you know how we do it.
So although you may not make revenues directly, it's definitely important.
I'm gonna play one more song, which is an amazing mashup from Rock Sugar.
Oh, just got turned on to have never heard of these guys before, but meant they are awesome.
They do the mashups in a new jacket.
Kind of live.
It'll blow you away when you hear what they've done.
Don't stop the salmon.
Damn it!
Oh yeah!
You.
Just to sit at home, for the rest of the stuff it's just,
It's worth of me not trailing the new way.
Yeah, yeah.
I see the wind, the smoke and the moon,
The smell of the ship I've been through,
From the sky I've seen every night,
In the dark, in the dark, in the dark, in the night,
I've seen the wind, the smoke and the moon,
The smell of the ship I've been through,
From the sky I've seen every night,
In the dark, in the dark, in the dark,
In the dark, in the dark, in the dark, in the dark,
In the dark, in the dark, in the light,
In the dark些, we're in love with this boring world!
I can't talk about your spirituality,
It's just, you're right, I will pretend I can no longer...
Just some way long life.
Who are you?
So we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're
losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're loses, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing, so we're losing
Oh, never, never lane.
How was that, how was that I smell, I love you?
Deep white.
Keep on going.
Don't stop.
Band us called Rock Sugar.
This track don't stop the same man.
I've got a whole album filled with mash-ups like this.
As far as I can tell, they've completely replayed,
we've mastered done everything all over again.
And I just love it.
It's fantastic.
I had to actually rip that off of a YouTube video.
I'm going to put links in the show notes.
You can find those at dailysourcecode.com.
And I've ordered their album and you can't download it.
It's not available on iTunes.
You're going to only get the physical product.
But I wanted to play this for you so badly.
I couldn't wait until I got the album.
I'm sure that I will be playing more from their CD in episodes to come.
They've got a lot of...
And they do live shows, too, which is perfect for the old people amongst us.
So yeah, just going back to making money with alternative media.
There's so many different ways to do it.
But I have to say it's no one going to come from the old fashioned way of,
hey, you only can go through one gate, one gate of mainstream goodness,
deliver through to your television or radio.
And therefore lots of people have forced the listen to it.
No, we have much smaller audiences in much smaller.
I'd have to say compared to the way it used to work.
But you can do a lot of things in conjunction with your show.
And sometimes it's just provide relevance to the business that you're doing next to it.
So besides the ever pervasive GoDaddy codes,
which I will be putting GoDaddy codes back into the show notes at dailysourcecode.com as a part of the show.
The only way I really asked to support this program is by supporting the project that John and I are,
you know, putting together essentially is no agenda stream.com,
which we believe we can build into something of significant value.
And if you find value in no agenda stream.com, then go to devorac.org slash NA S.
And that's where you can donate to the stream become a sustaining producer to keep it going.
And we're actually hiring people to do stuff, which actually does cost money.
Coming to you from the hilltop watch tower once again today.
It's a beautiful day in Southern California.
The people's Republic that is in Los Angeles.
And I want to talk to you about a couple of things today.
One of them is this incredible experience I've been going through,
which of course is nothing new for many people.
They go through separation divorce.
It happens all the time.
Unfortunately, a very high percentage of people talk about that on a 22.
But for the past, gosh, it must be seven or eight months.
I've been working with Patricia's lawyers.
And I have to say lawyers because she's gone through three of them at this point,
although I begged for a form of mediation, which I thought would be much easier.
And she actually had a lawyer who pretended like she was coming in as a mediator.
And then all of a sudden turned into her lawyer.
And I actually, I had a lawyer for like two weeks.
And then I fired him.
I said, dude, you know, forget about this.
I'm not going to waste any money on you.
And I still beg Patricia not to waste money on these stupid lawyers because they are so evil.
In this process.
Because we talk, you know, we have conversations.
I picked up Christina from her house when I took over to London a couple weeks ago.
And we actually had a pretty good chat.
And, you know, we've been principle agreed on, hey, let's just split everything up.
Whatever that is, that's fine.
And I've been nothing but easy.
Because I feel she deserves half of everything that we built up together.
But then you get these asshole lawyers.
And I have to generalize.
I'm sorry.
Certainly it comes to divorce attorneys.
And they're just crazy.
I spent, you know, and so I've done so many contracts.
And that's what a divorce is.
You know, at the end of the day, there will be a piece of papers settlement agreement.
And it'll be filed in California.
And it's very simple.
There's no fault divorce in the state of California.
It'll be under irreconcilable differences, which is correct.
And, you know, talking for seven, eight months answering long letters and, you know, going into detail.
And by the way, the internet is great.
Because you can look everything up.
You know, lawyers in general, I think, are just translating a different language.
And takes and work off your hands.
But I, yeah, I felt it was very important to be, you know, personally involved in this whole process.
And understand exactly what they're saying.
And maybe we can learn something from it all.
And so I went through seven or eight months of basically bringing it down to, you know, to two very simple items.
One really is, you know, I think a lot of you know, that all of the bank accounts, everything was in her name.
She has control over all of that. She moved out of the,
um, our place in London and took everything.
I have some boxes arriving with my studio, by the way, that's been salvaged.
Wait for that to, we're that to arrive.
Then I can definitely get the stream back in stereo.
And, you know, my books and my nicknakes, that's essentially, that's kind of what life is boiled down to.
My books, my studio equipment and my nicknakes, which is like my, you know, my, my star trek communicator.
Yeah, important stuff like that.
Oh, and by the way, the machine gun that my grandfather brought back the Japanese submachine gun.
He brought about it from the South Pacific, which I do want to talk about later as well.
So we go through months of back and forth and, you know, then the lawyers are, well, here's the family code and they look up the family code and, you know, you can answer that stuff.
It's not that hard, really. It's not that scary.
But what we're so disappointing is,
then all of a sudden, you know, you get a draft settlement agreement.
And everything we discussed for the past eight months is all still in there.
All the things we agreed upon is all turned back.
And now it's basically starting all over again, because yet another law firm has to be involved in the United States.
And it's just, you know, they're just ripping off.
They're ripping her off. And of course, you know, nothing I say is,
is going to convince anybody of that.
It's just more time. It's unbelievable, unbelievable.
Of course, I'm very happy that she's doing quite okay. Certainly financially.
She has no issues whatsoever. She's never had a problem with that.
And I just hope we can get all of this behind us.
And everybody can move on and we'll be done with it.
And then eventually the press will die down, which has been very,
whoa, that's a big helicopter, which has been very challenging in all of this.
I mean, it's one thing to separate. It's another thing to separate with a lot of media attention.
Because, you know, you have to catch yourself.
It's like, you know, you'll read something like, I never said that to anybody.
I didn't talk to any journalist. And then you read something else from the, from the other side.
And you're like, I can't believe she said that. You gotta wait a minute.
Wait a minute. That's probably not true.
So the smartest thing I think we've both done is make sure that we are able to,
basically ask each other, hey, did you say that? Did you mean that?
And so, you know, it's a dichotomy.
On one hand, on the personal side, things are kind of going along pretty well.
But on the legal side, they're just drawing it out and making an expensive stupid process.
Anyway, my dear friend, Angie B, who sent a comment to me, by the way,
which I want to play for in a second, also sent me along a song.
And I definitely want to play that for you, because it's very appropriate.
And not only that, but it's pod safe.
And it is one half of everything, but the girl, which I've always appreciated as a,
I guess as a band, and I always thought they were pretty awesome.
It's Tracy Thorne.
This is appropriately titled, Oh, the divorces.
The words will mean a bit to you, I think.
Who's next? Who's next?
Always the ones that you least expect.
They see in so strong.
And turn out she wants it more all along.
And each time I hear a host part, I examine my heart.
See how it stands.
Wonder if it's still in safe hands.
Who's friend? Who's friend?
Who's been caught out in somebody's bed?
I should have guessed that day that his phone wouldn't take you text.
He was a gentleman, I wish him back home.
I wonder who he shouldn't take sight.
But that one was his fault.
This one is her fault.
No one gets off without paying the ride.
And I wonder why the divorce is.
And the honeymoon, the wedding rings.
The afternoon handovers by the swings.
Huyens. Huyens.
His songs seem to look through different bands.
Your still so young.
The romance just as easy as it's begun.
Now let's kids to tell.
And the girls.
I'm cast to hear.
This one's different.
And each one of course is.
And always the same.
The divorce is.
Who's next?
He's nice.
Tracy Thorn, oh the divorce is pod safe and you can download this track from her website.
Thank you so much, Angie B for turn me on to that.
I want to grace song that is.
And it says that it's all right there.
In fact, I need a little bit of love right now.
I need Angie to bring me the sexy back.
Hey baby.
Hey, Adam, it's Angie B.
Thanks so much for including me and the DSC last week, just wanted to share some of my thoughts.
My posts of the show up on my Facebook and Twitter and, you know, it seemed to inspire
a lot of conversation, heard from some of the old media folks I hadn't talked to in a
while, from one who had stopped podcasting and said he was inspired to get back into it.
I think he contacted you privately as well.
Also talked to some folks about pod safe music and, you know,
Angie, before you keep going, thank you so much for that Tracy Thorn track.
Because I would really like to do so much more with, with pod safe music.
But I also want to make a show that's really entertaining.
A lot of music out there in general is crap, pod safe and not, but please go to pod
safe music network.com.
If you're an artist, read how the system works is pretty simple.
You upload your tracks, you make them available for all the podcasters and other alternative
media producers to use them and give you credit and help you basically promote your stuff.
And I think we've pretty much proven that this works.
I still see 20 to 30 new tracks going up every single day.
I'm just looking for more fun stuff to play.
So keep it coming.
Gosh, you're such an inspirational guy.
I think that's is why we all miss the DSC.
There's just that personal human quality that you've always had in the DSC and you had
it in spades last week and really just the show left me at the smile on my face the rest
of the day.
I just get, you know, remembering old times and feeling all warm and fuzzy and it's just so nice
to have the DSC back.
I say, take it slow, don't overdo it, don't get back into every day thing, just do it
when you're feeling it and we're going to feel it too.
And I just want to say we appreciate you, man.
Oh, Angie.
Oh.
Now, I'm going to take it to a home or the level I love you.
You know that, especially love your voice, check out Angie at the chill cast.
Well, you know what, a lot of influences, a lot of reasons why I brought the source code
back.
And I am doing it totally when I feel like it and I've changed a lot of things in my life,
you know, now I'm living in Los Angeles, still going up to San Francisco a couple of times
a month to be in the office and contributing there, what I can't I can do a lot obviously
being in the same time zone through phone and Skype, which of course I did for four years
from London.
So, makes a lot of sense there.
I think I mentioned on the previous show that I've been, I've got this new book, ADD.
I'm able to read five books simultaneously once again.
I'm trying to pair that down to three, but I'm doing pretty good with the five.
And one of the things that that I think really hit me, one of the books that really brought
me back to what I wanted to do with the source code, now that I can really talk about
everything and I feel open enough to talk to you guys about everything, that's going on
in my life, which really works is this book called Authenticity by James H. Gilmore and
B. Joseph Pine II, who are the authors of the experience economy.
And the book actually has a subtitle, what consumers really want.
And it is authenticity and, you know, the DSC has always been a playground, so once again,
you are in my guinea pigs and I'm just trying to give you 100% authenticity.
And I think it works.
It really does.
Now, I've always been as authentic and real as possible on this show, but, you know, often
a lot of things have been going on that I really just couldn't talk about it and feel
as appropriate.
And I think I'm over that, which is really nice, really is.
So let me say one other thing then, which I see is a topic in the chat room, not right
now at noagendachat.com, remember when we do the show live, it goes out on noagendastream.com,
is about the health care bill and I'm going to make it real simple.
If we believe the system works the way it should work and I'm just going to have to have
some belief in that, then a majority, albeit a slim majority, a majority of the country
through their representatives in government, I know it's all disputable and debatable,
but that's maybe something for noagenda.
They voted for this health care bill.
Now, I believe that the public was poorly informed and perhaps, say, we're even lied
to, certainly words matter and when you say that the congressional budget office says that
this will reduce the deficit by a trillion dollars over the next two decades, that is definitely
bending the truth as the CBO is said, it might affect the deficit in the second decade
by a trillion dollars.
They have not explicit.
They don't even calculate past 10 years so that just can't be the truth.
But it doesn't matter.
And the way it works in our system is, okay, we all voted.
We have a majority to do this, so let's do it and we'll support it and we'll see what
comes of it.
If it doesn't work out, then all right, then we'll, we'll, we'll have to
change it or adapt it or whatever's necessary.
And of course, in politics, there's no winning or losing.
There's only battles that continue.
And that's the way it's supposed to be.
I think it's healthy.
It really is.
And let's see what happens.
You know, maybe we're all wrong.
Maybe it's great.
Maybe it isn't.
But history will definitely show if this was good or not.
And we'll have an opportunity to correct this is a great country.
And yeah, I'm, I'm a little concerned about what it might have regarding financial implications.
But we'll see now by that same token, I feel that we should also revisit some of the things
we're doing as a country such as the war in Iraq, the war in Afghanistan, which as far
as I know are illegal, unconstitutional, seeing as the Congress did not necessarily write
a war, an act of war against either of those countries, I think there's a lot of shenanigans
going on.
And that's something that needs to be top of the agenda right now because that also, by the
way, we'll save us some money.
That's the crazy thing that I feel is, you know, we all need universal health care, we need
to take care of people.
On the other side, we're, we're throwing hot lead at boys and girls and, you know, drone
shooting people from out of the sky and deserts, it's very disturbing to me, particularly
when you see shows like the Pacific, which again I'll get back to later on.
So Bruce Cockburn kind of sums it all up, how I'm feeling about what's going on, the
side's health care, and there's quite a lot to be worried about, a lot of things we need
to change.
Check out this track if I had a rocket launcher on the Charley.
Here comes the helicopter, second time today, everybody scatters, and hopes it goes away,
how many kids they've murdered, only God can say, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, I'd make somebody
pay.
I don't believe in guarded borders, and I don't believe in hate.
I don't believe in generals, or they're stinking torture states.
But when I talk with the survivors, the things do a second aim to relate, if I had
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket
launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, I'd would not have
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket
launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, some sort of a
rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a
rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had
a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a rocket launcher, if I had a one launcher, if I had a rocket launcher,
matter we've really got to be careful perhaps we need to teach our kids how to
read a little better now there's a book I'd like to write the book I'm
learning to read some John and I can work on long-term projects it's the
Charlie episode a 23 I don't know why it doesn't need to matter how hard
to try keep that in mind I'm whose eye is right to explain to do time
oh I know time is a valuable thing watch it plot by as the pendulum swings
it's locked to countdown to the end of the day the clock takes life away it's so
fun really didn't look at the globe watch the time you'll write out the window
trying to hold on didn't even know or wasted it's all just to watch you I kept everything
inside it didn't even know what tried you know from the party when it meant to be
you'll eventually be a memory of a time I tried it's so fun and that's so
fun it doesn't even matter I had to fall to live it all but in the end it doesn't
even matter one thing I don't know why it doesn't even matter how hard you try
keep that in mind I designed it's rhyme to remind myself how I tried it so it's
my way you were mocking me acting like I was part of your property
remembering all the times you've bought with me I'm surprised it got so
things aren't the way they were before you wouldn't even recognize me anymore
that's you knew me back then but it all comes back to me
you kept everything inside it didn't even know what tried you know from the
party when it meant to be a memory of a time I tried it's so fun and that's so
fun it doesn't even matter I had to fall to live it all but in the end it doesn't
even matter I put my trust in you your steps far as I can go for all this
there's only one thing you should know I've put my trust in you
I tried so hard and that's so fun it doesn't even matter I had to fall to live
it all but in the end it doesn't even matter I had to fall to live it all but in the end
it doesn't even matter
love that song
love that band Lincoln Park in the end on daily source code episode 823 broadcasting live
on no agenda stream dot com which is so cool now that we have iPhones and androids
and even a black barrier to has some kind of app that you can listen to listen to
streaming media we got cars coming out with streaming media I think there's we're
really in the next five years we're going to see some really interesting things
happening with streaming audio and the connections we can make with it I
definitely plan on being a part of it but also I'm very interested in this you know
I was I really have to say when I got that memo that got that first iPhone and I
dropped it in the toilet after a week and it was completely toast and then you know
I tried to bring it back to life I still have it by the way it's coming in one of my
boxes it does still fire up it still comes alive unfortunately the touch screen
is completely broken so you can't do anything with it you can't even answer a phone
call remember I put it in the kitty litter to try and draw the the moisture out yeah
great experiment and of course I was really angry then because it's like you can't
take the battery out so I really straight away from the iPhone for a long time
I really became loyalist to Nokia the E71 in particular really did a great job
for me for quite a while and then the Android came out have to say I was really
digging the Android really like the apps the whole paradigm what I'll call an
app phone I don't I think something like the Nokia E71 is really more like a
smartphone that's a phone that has smarts in it but this new thing this thing you
know the it's the iPhone basically launched and I think Android is doing good
job of providing a version of it is an app phone and I love the open architecture
of the apps and being able to you know having a lot more control over it but
man I just don't think you can beat the experience of the iPhone and they're
and I think that Apple is surprised by the experience that they've they've
created it's really it's really a game changers really transform the way people
use mobile device I know it's done that with me I mean I even I don't own a
Kindle but I do find myself actually using the Kindle app for the iPhone to read
your book in fact I'm reading genius of the beast still almost done with that
from whenever I have a chance because it's such a happy positive book and I
can pick it up in the middle of the night if I wake up which I another thing
what the hell is that all about yeah I sleep like six and a half hours and I'm
awake and I ready to go and yeah it's like five thirty in a morning and
what's up I don't seem to be able to sleep longer than that anymore yeah yet I'm
not tired I'm on an airplane I'll just say I'm going to be a couple chapters
here it's fantastic and I'm just amazed by the yeah it's the closed business
model and there's lots of pros and cons about the way Apple does things but
I'm not adverse to it you know if you wanted to deliver a real experience to the
the I wouldn't say the lowest but the broadest common denominator you have to
take control of the the hardware the software and some of the services and I
think they've done an excellent job and I have been working on my own iPhone app
for coming up on let me see three months now which is interesting because I
really wanted to do was much of it myself as possible which meant firing up
X code and learning objective C which is no small feet I can tell you it was
easier to learn the language of the lawyers than it was to learn the objective C
but if I reconnected with a number of people who are doing some very interesting
things making it a lot easier and more affordable for people to create their
own iPhone apps and I think I'll be talking about that in the next week or two
as I get my iPhone app launched first it has to all come together I did have to
outsource some of the graphic work which I really suck at and so I found a
couple guys who I knew from the package it's rogue rogue sheep and they've
done a great job on creating even something as simple as the the apps icon you
know that's like you really got to think about do you want the icon to show
what the app does or do you want something that be just pops out and people
always say oh yes I remember that app I know what that does and it's something
that is really very visual and grabs your attention and says click on it you know
all these different things that have to be queried and then of course I'm
going to go through the whole process of understanding how Apple's approvals
work which will be interesting since there is some video component to this app
oh yeah I got some video projects in mind and a video component is you know
can really trip you up on the approval process based upon bandwidth it's being
used when the phone is in mobile mode so I'll keep you up to speed on everything
that's going on with that but first before we go any further say hello to my old
little friend
what father this is a prolific program from San Francisco California
yes yes I had you call in the agenda number one eight zero yes and decided to submit
to my own return I am I intend to contribute back your DSC the reason I
haven't been going to be no agenda is because a we don't play any comments and
no agenda that's why guys don't play and the top we talk about I know a very
little or nothing about I love it when I can't understand what you're talking
about pp
I already love that
there's a friend of mine I'll call him for now
pakey bond because that's because of the office in London you have no
mistakes I think you know he is yeah he's been saying to mention the
information about his work at Goldman Sachs and I know you guys are all
working over there and that realm of the universe and I love the fact that you
talking to me give me as much insight information at least your thought
process is good stuff
regard the stuff you've been talking to agenda regarding Goldman Sachs
and rest of it he will he will hopefully also be contributing stuff
regularly probably by email because he doesn't really write it like his voice
pretty cool you know he'll be telling me what he has to say and I just want to
say welcome back with Mr. very much pot father many thanks Adam cheers
a prolific program I think is so much you've had sounds like your diction is
gotten better although I still wish I was high when I was listening to you
I love this song thank you Kevin for sending it in I have a feeling with this
the mega multi media
see I think it goes a busy in the cooking job I want to be the next
great put me on the front bit got to be leader of media new way
hey hey hey hey hey I'm moving in the show
hey hey hey hey you know it ain't anything goes
now I'm being built you know well I don't have a good birthday
get out of Hollywood's money line everywhere
and just got plenty of it's more similar at the top of all
that's with me that I said hey hey I'm being in the show
hey hey hey hey you know it ain't anything else it's less than zero
got to be a mega multi media hero
got friends and family I got remote control I got cable TV
got nails had cheap pet I got a mountain of crap on the internet
join cop in at a home but I want to be mega multi media hero
yeah I love the lyric I turn on my MTV but it doesn't see me yeah that's exactly the
problem isn't it oh man remember to self got to do a show about the
mind control of the music industry so much we've got to talk about a lot of
catching up to do and a couple of comments came in let me just roll this
one out for you hi Adam welcome back with a DSC it's great to have it back
after all this time of course it's so slow that it was just last week that I
published a podcast all about the history of RSS and I say in the roundup by the end of
that that the final daily source code happened in February 2009 and then of course a few
days later wouldn't you know it but another DSC appears or should that be SC anyway
SC DSC whatever it's good to have you back doing the more personal source code of your
lifetime podcast that's the stuff I think really works not so much the conspiracy theory
stuff it's the from the heart stuff that really connects so keep it up just don't let it take
you over and if you want to hear what I said about you and they whiner and
closures and podcasting have a listen to show 33 of the IT author podcast from about
407 30 onwards all the best bye all right man thank you so much for saying that in
and thanks for the show by the way and I recommend people listen to the whole show don't
just shuttle ahead 41 minutes hey no no no no it's actually worth it to listen to a couple
shows in their entirety don't you think Chris Moiles from BBC Radio 1 was talking about
at the other day we've come a long way with podcasting when this is what he asked to say
he came back with this for the knowledge that some of our listeners don't know what podcasts
I think most don't they don't know what a podcast is right yeah now maybe he was meeting some
stupid people I thought most people knew what a podcast was so alad is written a
layman's cell you have the best of the miles podcast so he's written a script
and I went well podcasts instead of like you know being on the radio like a broadcast
it's a podcast it's on your iPod but I guess you know necessarily on your iPod that's why
they're called it no it is in the arm because they're also in the internet
while they were called neck cast from like no I don't think the iPod has anything to do with
podcasts or things coincidence you must do surely I think it's coincidence
well I mean I'm not a scientist but I thought that was the connection
I thought because we talked about this guy in the air before Adam Curry who is known as the
podfar worked at Apple if he did that she went to MTV if he did that's why I don't think it is
I think it's just coincidence the sound similar and he's very techy and he is pretty much credited
with making the first of a podcast there you go I've just proved my place
oh go I'm right yeah so I win now moving on Alex if you were to explain to one of our
list by the way can you just text in if you don't know what a podcast stop stop stop stop there you go
that's worse than what Wikipedia has to say
now I think it's all gonna melt together though that's pretty good people you know they got like
I got my I got this show on my iPhone on my iPod and yeah it's gonna be streaming in my car radio
people oh yeah it's gotta be it's becoming ubiquitous which I like I really like a lot of these
iPhone apps and Android apps that's stream a show or that give you and we finally got the bandwidth
I mean I just want to say one thing about podcasting it's original intent and when Dave wine
and I worked on the enclosure element for RSS it was original intent was to have your computer
doing something in his downtime and sucking in content that you would know about but your computer
would say oh I have something new for you and basically time delaying everything and now things
are so snappy in general even though we have pretty much the worst broadband infrastructure in the
world or 15th on the list or whatever in the US in general you could pretty much get on demand
now and uh case and point you can also do things live this streaming works pretty well
and uh above all you can still just put out whatever you want to put out
then if you've got a show that you want to promote on the source code I'd love to let people know about it
people in just three don't discuss it just yellow or each other I wish I could say what I really
think and have people actually listening is there any place where people discuss the hot button
subjects of the day without disrespect yes there is it is called plain dudes radio what is
plain dudes radio see a unique experiment it's a podcast about diverse opinions on philosophy
in our world who are the plain dudes I work as a bookkeeper I drive a truck I'm back and I drive a
try and I deliver pizza and chase weather and I deliver TV programming at a network television station
plain dudes radio diverse views from common people discuss with intelligence and respect
a one-of-a-kind experiment in communications come and join us at www dot plain dudes radio dot com
I love it as the kind of shows I love listening to I don't have enough of a commute only a
couple times a month up the San Francisco and boy do I pack up the uh the iPhone with uh with
shows when I'm doing that of course everything that we talk about today will be in the links at
daily source code dot com and just thinking about the early days of the source code the the early
days of podcasting there is a group of girls who I must give major props to because they really
help me understand and they were the first ones I think I really work with in a pod safe environment
they said hey you know what just come to our shows we're kind of crazy we do this thing called cocktail
pop please play our song or any of our songs we'll put them up anywhere so people can download them
if you feel I get in the CD do that and you might want to revisit them link in the show notes to
these wonderful girls one of my favorite songs of all time from the list of these bitties
it's not like he doesn't know just what to say to make you feel right stay up night think of him all day
oh well his song is true but his head keeps getting in the way
now it's not like he's got a nasty disposition
wants to keep you locked up tight knock the bright bear for the kitchen
he's a hell of a boy only only half of a man
no it's not like the boys are better born on the run side of town under the wrong
on the wrong day he's a hell of a boy but only only half of a man
just what do you think you will get if you persist thinking this is the best you can do
say no to your life girl I'll be fine you know it your life's going to say no to you
easy calm easy calm life's too short to live it's not like it's more than you can say
do have that pretty boy sit and next to you listen you hold in your hand
he's a hell of a boy but only only half of a man
let's give you his bitties he's a hell of a boy and they are pot safe links to this
track and all the tracks played today in the show notes a daily source code dot com all right
I got to go start doing my taxes we're getting very close I filled out my senses form yes
I don't want to go to jail and I cannot wait to speak with many of you again Thursday morning
for the early service at no agenda it'll also be on the stream no agenda stream dot com if you want
to support that initiative and this show please go to devore act dot org slash n a s and show your
support it will be highly appreciated see if anything else I think that's it cool to see
what on the chat and of course for you chuckle heads will be back Friday with a food bar Friday
edition of the daily source code another fine media presentation stick it in your ear