coming you live from the hilltop watch tower crackpot command center it's
Adam Curry and Bobby Eden and we are wet. This is Delta Sierra Charlie 841.
We're 16 million citizens in showing five nons of time.
The 21st century oil stars here.
We're giving a lie.
I know it's in the strength of our podcasting. He's Adam Curry.
We're riding a camp leader fight.
My goal is to come in us with late night.
Can't believe that my head feels right.
But what I need to make me tired of those girls.
Girls, girls, girls.
I'll wait and look at you live.
Girls, girls, girls, girls.
Dancing, they all know some strength.
Girls, girls, girls.
We're lips, big guns.
We're lips, wings, wings, wings.
We're through a queen.
I'm hoping to hear you sing.
Yeah, you girls, you're just keeping me free.
We're your best when you're out to be.
Girls, girls, girls.
I'll see you forever too.
Walking in the light night.
And time will tell.
Girls, girls, girls.
We're raising here with the same veil.
Can't you read the news?
We're the soul to hold your feet on.
Can't know she didn't need it.
Let me see my eyes.
I'm trying to feel good for it.
I'm just in the toy.
I tell you what girl they're calling me.
I'll be your forever too.
Just tell me, I'm sorry.
You don't want to meet me.
I'm just in love with you.
We're the host, there is quiet for God
but God never needs we never would dance.
For one man's, I got the foes of another one
Muscle broke down, which is love
Don't scare us, girl
But the body's shopping the heart
Can't scare us
Trapped my tears, where I lost my heart
Can't scare us, girl
It's on the chin that I'm in
And what is weird, right now
And it's a world where we can bring you
No, no, no, no
No, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no
Hell yeah
Do I have a vision life of one?
Nothing but girls, girls
Everybody, Watin Denny's source code
Episode is actually eight, four, two
I was so flustered starting this off here
At the watch tower
I went back to last Friday
But no, it's not a footballer Friday
It is a wet Wednesday, I'm the Charlie,
as promised, lots of good rock and roll,
lots of tunes, and we are, oh, here she comes.
Bobby Eden in the pool, how are you doing, girl?
Very good.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, well, yes.
We, uh, there's something with the wireless mic,
it's a little funky, but we decided not to do the hot tub today
because it's like, it was like 95 degrees here in Los Angeles.
Yeah, it's really, really hot.
So we're in the pool, we've got the wireless mic set up,
we've got some laptops, uh, just to use the towel, Bobby.
So, um, you know, so you don't put your wet hands on the, uh,
on the keyboard.
Oh, I think it's your hair.
But it's that's supposed to mean, you don't want to use my hair
to dry anything.
Well, actually, that's the thought there, as long as Miss Mickey's
not looking.
So Bobby, what the hell are you doing in Los Angeles?
Does it have a great vacation?
Yeah, how long have you been in the States now?
Because I know you've, you've been traveling, you've been around,
you've been doing all kinds of stuff.
I know.
I've been here now for five weeks, yeah, five or six weeks.
Wow.
And two more to go.
And any work or just, uh, just pure vacation?
Just holiday and I do all my cam shows because I can't stay away
for my computer.
Yeah.
Yeah, the way to make it say, do you do those on, on Dutch time now?
Uh, or, when do you, when do you do?
I do, I just want to be doing show right now.
Yes, I actually was supposed to do a show right now.
Oh, no.
So you're, you're actually giving up your valuable cam show time for, uh,
I did one before I came here.
Oh, really? Did you tell everyone that you were going to be over here?
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
She's in the pool.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah, yeah, that's funny.
I like it.
Wow, well, Bobby, you, um, you brought along a whole bunch of music.
And I definitely want to talk about, uh, you know, what you're up to.
And I know that some, maybe some stuff that some exciting news,
you can, uh, talk to us about.
And, uh, and we've got some cool stuff to give away as well.
Yeah.
Like, uh,
promo clothes, promo clothes.
My cam show.
Yeah, baby, we love it.
Oh, yeah.
And by the way, no video guys.
That's the only thing that we agreed upon because I didn't want you to see my ugly ass naked.
Oh.
By the way, Bobby, you look very healthy.
Thank you, too.
And by the way, let's go beyond.
So what is wrong with an innocent, efficient time reaching needs to tell.
So be my inches and feet on the path.
What does it come to?
Plays us to go.
I've got to leave it.
I'm on a job.
He Ryan,
Raji like a man in the face.
But buddy, he's burning.
That's the shot.
He sized his tummy.
He breaks out lull.
That's easy, easy.
Just have to make it, we're so much better
The night is cold, I have to go
And for the time being, you're like this, you're
You're sleeping, isn't it?
She's ready to win, on the hot to nightfall
Love it the same
You're like a rock, you like a hurricane
My life isn't there, here I am
Rock, you like a hurricane
Here I am
I love you, like a hurricane
The sun comes out, is my most shaky
Real life, get it's blurry, scratch my skin
Someone is wrong, and not I'm a city
I've got it, I have to go
And for the time being, you're like this, you're like a hurricane
I love you, like a hurricane
Here I am
Rock, you like a hurricane
I love you, like a hurricane
It's going to be like a hurricane, this is Adam Curry along with Bobby Eden, how do
you build yourself, Bobby?
Can we just call you a massively famous porn star, or do we say adult film star, or what
do you like to go by?
Whatever you're going to call me, baby is all I'm going to call you.
So, you know, it's so fascinating because you actually, you're so well-known in outside
of the Netherlands, where you're from.
Did you start your career in the states or where did you really get, how does one get into
this?
I'm not saying that I would want to try it or anything, but, uh, want to do a casting with
me?
Yeah, because it involved a couch, we just sit here in the pool and just, uh, we do it
in the pool.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, when I actually started, I first did like for four years with men's magazines,
like it's playboy, hustler, penthouse, all the stuff, like the top shelf's one.
Well, how did that even happen?
You just said, I just said that over pictures to penthouse.
And they said, yeah, baby, come on, bye.
Uh-huh.
Good, you know, who made the decisions back then?
No, it was a better year.
Oh, so this is Dutch, Dutch, okay, yeah, yeah.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And since then, since I was in the magazine, I actually got a model agency in the
Netherlands, a glamour agency that wants to have me, so I went there and they gave me a few
jobs for the rest, I did everything myself.
I just took the plane to the states.
Right.
That was it.
They're up with an agent.
I never saw and never knew.
I only knew that he was wearing a baseball cap.
Uh-huh.
And his name was John.
Right.
So you got on a plane.
You go see this guy with a baseball cap named John and then what was your first
movie you ever did?
My first movie was for private and I think it was explosive women.
Right.
I see that.
Get on the other side of the pool, you.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Explosive.
Yeah, what was the plot of that movie?
Do you remember the story line?
Please come in my face.
Cool.
Yeah.
How is that?
Not originally.
Well, yeah.
You know, that's what guys want though.
What is not what guys want?
I mean, what does every guy want?
You would know.
Hold on a second.
Guys, get your girlfriend, get your wife.
Have a listen right now because Bobby Eden knows exactly what guys really want.
When it comes to sex, what does every single guy want?
I think they want a fantasy.
That's it.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
Okay.
But there are like different guys.
I have so many different guys that email me like some of them just like to wing, unlike
the most hardcore movies that they can see, like, only the real big, well, big shit.
I'm pretty hard-crushed up and I'm pretty, I'm actually a wimp.
But there are also...
Yeah.
I've seen your movies.
You're no wimp.
Excuse me.
She says it.
You're doing stuff that I can, yeah, no, you're not a wimp by any means.
Yeah, it's compared to other, it goes sometimes, and I'm pretty finilla.
I think.
Okay.
But I do like it's rough sometimes.
Yeah.
That's what I must hear.
Do you enjoy it?
I haven't done a movie in a while, but you're doing some of your own independent movies,
now, is that what you're looking for?
Yeah.
For our website, Bobby EdenLive.com.
Is that with just you, or with girls, or with the farm animals, or...
That is with me.
With me, with girls, and the stuntcock.
Oh, really?
A stuntcock?
So everything is almost in POV style.
Awesome.
So you can imagine.
So how does one apply for the stuntcock position?
Is this like a hand model, and you look through pictures, through headshots, and...
I just look at the cock.
That's it.
And what a great job.
I'm in the wrong business.
Speaking of fantasies, we got to Billy Idol lined up with flesh for fantasy, which is
one of your requests.
Now that we went to Billy Idol, thank you very much, by the way, for inviting us for a great
time.
Have you been in a long time fan of a Billy?
Yes.
I love him.
And he was so sexy, and you think?
I probably, you probably won't love him.
No, he looked good.
Yeah.
I was surprised.
Nice body.
Yeah.
It was like 54 or something.
I know.
I was surprised.
It was okay.
Yeah.
Did you get a lot of shows, a lot of rock shows?
I think porn and rock and roll somehow always feels like it goes together.
Well, lately I go to shows, but with the scorpions, I don't read.
I didn't like that.
It sucked.
Suffolk to relax.
There's still alive, right?
Yeah.
It was in the key club.
Okay.
Yeah, perfect.
And it went to steel pants, or actually two days ago.
Really?
Yeah.
That was fun.
I love that.
That's awesome.
Well, let's play some Billy Idol here for a second and we'll be back with more of adult
superstar Bobby Eden on the Daily Source Code streaming live at noagendastream.com.
Don't forget the chat, noagendachat.net.
We have a chance.
We got a special surprise everyone hanging out in the chat, stay tuned.
I didn't like the music, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like
the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like
the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance,
I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance,
I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance,
I didn't do anything without the dance, I didn't like the dance, I didn't like the dance, down,
It's out to midnight, why don't you feel it all right?
Oh yeah, tonight's a light day, I used to want more days to know how I am.
In the name of the door, the last questions I read all.
Oh yeah, bass two bass, I'm back to back.
You've seen and feel me, my shakes are shining.
Rich, let's hope and to see.
We come high, let's hope and to see.
So we were just trying to reminisce about the concert.
I don't remember playing the song, but you do.
Yeah, I guess I had more to drink than you did.
So we're reading along with the chat room at no agenda chat.net.
If you have any questions for Bobby, now it would be the time.
I even saw someone just voted by in the morning.
Very nice.
We appreciate you guys thinking with us.
Bobby, I know that you were in Vegas for a day or two.
Yes.
You care to tell me what happened there?
Or is this one of these what happens in Vegas days and Vegas type things?
No, I can tell you.
Are you ready?
Do I have to sit on the side of the pool or something?
No, you can stay.
All right, all right.
I will be a live part.
Okay, what happened in Vegas?
I got married.
What?
No.
Yes, Elvis gave me a way.
This guy back over here with the guy who came with you to the night.
You got married in the box?
Yeah.
He's going to be with us.
Nice.
And it's a real, you're really, you're off the market now.
You're done.
Yeah.
But I'm still, but I'm still, you know, available for some, you know.
Let's keep the fans to see a live good.
Yeah, I like that.
I'm just like, wow, you know, but you're not going to stop.
You're going to keep doing your shows and definitely.
God, I love you so much.
You're so awesome.
I cannot stop.
Those breasts by the way, Bobby.
I know you're so proud of you had them done.
They are awesome, man.
I'd like the way they were before.
Because they're better now.
Yeah.
Was that a tough decision?
Actually, yes.
Yeah.
Because I was chicken.
I have seen so many bad book jobs, and I'm pretty happy with it.
Yeah.
So.
Were you ever done here in this day?
To those Americans?
No.
Those are Dutch books.
Yeah.
But actually, by an American guy.
Okay.
Of course.
I see.
Americans know how to make books.
You do not want to have your books made in any other country, but America.
We understand books really, really well.
Yeah.
And what do your fans think of they commented on it?
They all are happy.
They love it.
They're like, did they grow up?
Yeah.
And I'm like, what?
You noticed?
Oh, man.
Oh, those.
Just a little.
Well, one thing I know is I can't drown now.
No.
I just grab onto you and I'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
I'll be with rare bags.
Yeah.
That's right, baby.
We're here with these old bags.
In the hilltop.
Watch tower track.
Come on.
Got a whole lot of money that's ready to burn.
So get those stakes up higher.
There's a thousand pretty women waiting out there.
They're all living and they will make care.
And I'm just a devil with no despair.
Some people are always beggars.
People are always beggars.
Oh, I wish that there were more.
And the 24 hours in the day.
Now, even if they were for it more,
I wouldn't sleep a minute of a way.
Oh, those black jack and poker and the roulette.
We're a lot.
A fortune one and a lot.
It's on and every hit deal.
All you need is for hard and a new steal.
People are always beggars.
Where do you need the unflagging and your warm and discretion?
All those holes down the drain.
People are always beggars.
Turn and day in the night.
Turn and night in the daytime.
If you see it, it'll watch.
You'll never be the same again.
I'm gonna keep on the run.
I'm gonna have me some fun.
It costs me a month, very less dime.
Here, by wind, I'll broke a bill.
Always remember that I had a swing in time.
I'm gonna give it everything I've got.
They look for these, let the dice stay hot.
But then we shouldn't sell them with their fresh shots.
People are beggars.
Tell you, okay.
Viva Las Vegas.
Bobby even compiled her own playlist.
So these are all her favorite songs.
You got some real good ones in here.
In fact, you could program a daily source code any time.
You've got all of our songs here, man.
That's amazing.
It will be a partnering crime.
You can be my partner in a lot of things.
I've just decided, Mickey, it's too bad that you're leaving me.
No, Mickey.
It's too bad you're leaving me because I have a new girlfriend.
This is my new partner in crime.
No, I like Mickey.
Yeah.
I get out of the pool now.
You know what?
I can have you both, okay?
I can handlaid.
Now she's talking.
Yeah.
That is one of your specialties is women.
I love women.
Yeah, me too.
Pretty picky, but when I like them,
I go, just go.
Have you ever like had to do a performance with someone
that you just thought, no, you're rich?
Yes.
And did you go through with it?
Or did you just walk away?
I went down and I went up again.
Oh, no, was it that disgusting?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Tell me what happened.
Yeah, it was actually, it was one of her first go-go.
And there was actually supposed to come another go.
So these girls show up.
I'm like, well, where should I go?
Just like she couldn't come.
So you have this girl.
She looks kind of hot, and I'm like, okay, cool.
All right.
I wonder what's going down.
I'm like, oh, what's it like?
We're going up.
Just not fresh.
No.
Oh.
Poor girl.
This is disgusting.
So went up.
I look at the camera when I'm like, I don't know.
I said you're going to make this up to me.
So.
Wow.
But I make her work mine.
So that's good.
But do you really get into it when you're, when you're, yeah?
Yeah.
They all sit all right.
I'm convinced all of, well, adult actors just say that.
Oh, yeah.
Really enjoying it.
I'm really into it.
I'm really coming.
Well, let's say, like, you have good days and bad days.
But most of the time, like, 95%.
I choose my own actors and actresses.
And most of them are friends.
So I make sure I'm going to have a great time.
Right.
And if I don't like it, then well, then probably you will see it in my phase or whatever.
But like, I think 95% that I've done with the scenes, I enjoyed it.
And do you have a real script and a whole idea of what you're going to do?
Or just, is it kind of free form or how does that work?
It depends for which company, because they actually decide which you're going to do.
Like some, some like companies tell you, do whatever you want to do.
And some companies like, for example, private will, you know, direct you into it.
Yeah.
Isn't that water home?
I really do love it.
I'm, I think I'm going to have to stay in the pool for a little while.
I can't get out right now.
If you know what I mean.
Let's point another song then.
How about that?
This is David Lee Roth.
You big fan of Anne Hayman.
David Lee.
I mean, whatever.
Why California girls?
Because I love it.
We're in California.
Makes so much sense to me.
We'll be taking some questions from the chat room.
We've got the laptops here at the pool, Miller, gender chat.net.
Just put them up there.
Bobby is reading along on the laptop as well.
In the meantime, Diamond Dave, California girls on the Charlie.
Well, he's close through time.
I've been waiting till no stars can wear.
Me and the sun.
They're hooked with the waving top.
They're not the outfit.
I'm down there.
I've been waiting till stars can wear.
They really, really feel all right.
The dawn of girls sweep the waiting.
He's saying if there's objects on their thigh.
I take it home to pick energy on your neck.
Playing on the road.
Yeah, when we play on theOne Air Society
Sapphire Systems.
The way it's closed, it's the sunshine
In the room, it's all been so dead
I've been a free journey
I'm wild, I'm close by a hungry person
I've been all round, it's great being world
And I've seen all kinds of girls
In the game, but I couldn't wait to get back
In this stage, back to the theaters
Girls in the world, I've taken a kiss
This song, while you're young
Who wish they'd love to think of
I wish they all could be gathered on your feet
Girls in the world, I've taken a kiss
This song, while you're young
Who wish they all could be gathered on your feet
Girls in the world, I've taken a kiss
This song, while you're young
I've taken a kiss
Diamond David Lee Roth, which they all could be
California girls, and right now I'm surrounded by a couple of them
I've got the lovely and his Mickey here, splashing around in the pool
And Bobby, even here, I'm glad you didn't decide to wear a bathing top
No, do you even own one?
I do own one, because where I'm staying
I'm sorry, we're in America, that's the right
It's like crazy that we make the best porn in the world
In America, yet there's so prudish about everything
You would have to agree, American porn is the best, right?
Why can't I say no now?
No, seriously, that was okay
I mean, you won't insult all of America, if you say it's not
But I think American porn, maybe because of the language
You know, it's like, yeah, baby coming up face, you know?
Yeah, that's better, it sounds good
You just say it in Dutch, it's like snipping a work
No, no, it sounds like you're going to throw on
But French is cute too
You've done French movies?
I've done one
Did you have to study lines for that all?
I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone
I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone
And German is, well, I think German is pretty hard, it's like harsh, but I like it
Yeah, but German films are always like, come in and then got a fit to it
It's like a snush, yeah, I think it's nice
For nush me, I don't even want to know what that means
You better not be for nush in me any time
Just take that girl
Let's take scare in you
No, no, you need to have a lot more going
Disgare me, I think
Couple questions from the chat room, Memphis Jeff says
Bobby, you've obviously have to keep the sex appeal turn on
Full as a self promotion vehicle
He says salesman getting burned out from being on too long
Hell, even Adam got tired of sucking advertising cock
What do you do to get yourself turned on?
I do not so many movies, it's like a lot of bills too
So I keep it exclusive and fun
If you don't do them every day, then it's a new experience every time
Who the hell does it every day?
There are girls doing it every day
Every single day
Really?
Can you bring that to you?
How can we didn't bring them by?
I think of you some numbers
But seriously, every day that's outrageous
How can you even do it every day?
No
Can you imagine if they have a private life
And they would then again
Yeah
Do people recognize you on the street?
Do you dress down or dress differently?
So you're a little less recognizable
Well, I think I'm kind of down to earth
So I don't wear a really full on makeup
What's going on?
To destroy the supermarket
Or if they do recognize me
Then people are not gonna say
Like, I saw you in this movie
I went on you
They're not gonna say anything
I would
I guess what I would just do
They're about me, you know what I was doing
Exactly
You must have a lot of regulars of the webcam shows
Who would drop by
Do you know them by their face?
Yeah, because they actually turn on their webcam
Really?
Yeah, by face and by their cock
Do you think that's a turn on for a lot of guys
To show their face to you?
I think so
Interesting
Yeah
I like it when I get, you know, being watched
So
Wow
Do you like it?
You're getting, you know, being watched
I don't know what I'm touching myself
Yeah
Yeah, I think so
Yeah, I don't know
Shall we try that later?
Watch me
Mickey, will you set up the gallery?
She's always watched
Funk wants to know
Bobby, if everyone has a fantasy
What is yours?
My fantasy
He's getting a big orgy
What goes
And guys
I'm in the middle
And they wash it me
With fresh fruit
I'll over my body
And leak it off
Really?
That's truly your fantasy
Yeah
And have you ever fulfilled that fantasy?
I mean, it seems like we could get a, I mean, Mickey, get the camera
What's that?
It seems like we could arrange that
And you've ever done everything like that?
Sometimes
If you can keep it a fantasy
Then it's better
It's nicer
Nice better
You say most guys who, who call in your webcam shows
Are they, are they married or in a relationship?
Yeah, a lot of them are
Yeah
And, you know, actually some of the girls like wives
They come on chat too
When they do it together
Really?
Oh, that's kind of hot
Yeah
So I like a few couples there too
And I like a few guys that just want to talk
Or, yeah, play games
I love a guy that play games
What kind of games?
It's like blind games
No, mind games
Minds, psychology
Games
They do, yeah
With my sports
Puzzles
No
Crossword
And you help them with the crossword puzzle
Yeah
We even watch, you know, soccer together
If there's like a big game on
Speaking of which
I know
Man, team, team Bobby
Team DJ
You know, we were all like really excited
I even got John C. DeVore
To sign up to your Twitter feed
He was following you
And then they lost
I mean, you must have a lot of
Disappointed fans out there
Yeah
But there is a
Yeah, a consolation
What do you call it?
Consolation
Price
A really?
Yeah, and they can win
Also some stuff
If the trader may be the best picture
With me actually in it
So they need to perform in the picture
Wait, let me get this right
So they have to take a picture of themselves
Yes
And you have to be in the picture
Yes, I have to be in a picture too
I'm very clear
Or just a picture
A big cardboard cutout
Yeah, they can see whatever they want to do
Be creative
And they can win like a package
DVDs, poster, shining cards
Do you have a lot of merchandise
Do you have like, do you have the Bobby
Even real doll?
Do you have one of those?
No, not yet
Have you ever considered it?
Because they're expensive
But they're good, man
They look good
But they're good
Have you like felt one inside?
No, have you?
Yes
And how does it feel?
How does it compare to the real deal?
Real real
Really?
It's scary, yeah
Let me just have to ask Santa
See if I can get one of those
You can have one behind the window
When Mickey is going, just put her on
Just sitting there next to the clouds
I don't think I could have sex with the doll
I just don't have sex
But it's good just to have to have one
Yeah, it's good just to have one
And maybe then too
Because when you're leaving the house
And she's not alone, no?
Please don't
Right, baby, don't worry
I'll be gone for just a couple days
I'm in San Francisco
It's a freak out of neighbor
But here's Bobby, the real doll
You can lose her
Mr. oil wants to know
Oh, second
As you're aware that Adam is a former Soviet spy
If you were to be in a spy porn film
What would your spy name be?
My spy name
Yeah, like
What did you say?
Bobby Curry
That's not Russian enough
It's got to be Soviet
Bobby and Bruce Gaff
I don't think we can answer this question
Yeah
But you asked me to
Decuab Nika for you
I love Nika
It's kind of an interesting choice
Yeah
And you particularly
And I like the songs
I do actually show them
But I'm touring
Oh really?
Of course you do touring shows as well
Yes
No shows you all you were in Los Angeles
Why not?
Okay, you were just on vacation
Have you done shows in America though?
No, not really
Well, I did the AVN
Adult video
Yeah
What is it?
Network
Adult AVN
What is it?
Well, the adult
Is it a video award?
Yeah
That's in Vegas, you should write
Yeah, that's in Vegas
That's in January
That's where I've been a few times
Do you nominated for anything?
No
Not this year
I haven't done
You know, won't be for a while
So, okay
But you're going to do one soon
And you're going to tell us about that next
I hope
Of course
Okay, good
What do you want?
Anyway, you're gone too
Love, love, love, love, love, love
Love, love
Hey
Thought so long
I didn't taste it together
But now
But now it's going away
Hey
You
But stop it, but stop it, but stop it
Am chanting and learning about the song of the skull
Love, love
Don't worry, we don't explain
God to God, love, love, love
Lainer sits on my Zephyr
Give your dollar and shine
And kiss love, look up
Look up, look up, look up
Walk away
Hey, hey, hey
Jesus, look up, look up, look up
You see, it's like there's something
I'm not just a team, I was just a good judge
I'm not just a judge, I'm just a genius
I'm not a man, I'm not a man, I'm not a man
I'm not a man, I'm not a man
I'm just a good detective today today
You're not a detective today
It suits me, it suits me there
You don't believe me, anyway
Even though I don't believe you
I wish immortals beumental
Instead of Space I'll Only Last
Out For The Road
Somewhere in the world
Once I've left...
I'll be called monster
Everybody's gonna love today,
and everybody's gonna love you
Everybody's gonna love you
Everybody's gonna love me
Everybody's gonna love today
Everybody's gonna love
Everybody's gonna love fattier
Everybody's gonna love tonight
Everybody's gonna love you
Everybody's gonna love me
I love today on DSC 842 coming to you from the pool. We've had the transmitters kind of breaking up a little bit.
But I don't care how I'm in the pool with Bobby Eden.
It's worth it.
Yeah, it's worth it. Absolutely.
So while the song was playing a couple of people came up with some really good,
so be it's by adult names for you.
Yeah, we've got Natasha Sakamoff, which I think is good.
Yeah.
And Molotov cocktails.
That could be a home movie, by the way.
Do you imagine that?
That's Natasha Wang.
What was her?
Natasha. Natasha Sakamoff.
That could be.
We could do a home movie.
Yeah.
Seriously, could I produce it?
Sure.
Want to stare in it?
Uh, it's done cock maybe.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Then we'll do it then.
And I actually would do it with Mickey.
And then you could feel like good.
Yeah, this is something like a very good idea.
A lot of a sudden I'm really liking this.
Mickey, say yes.
We're going to get in so much trouble for this show.
I'd be gentle Mickey.
Oh, yeah.
So, uh, she likes it right.
Yeah, no, she does.
She does kind of.
And I'm the vanilla one and she's.
Yeah, no, it's, you know, it's, uh, what's that?
I think you should remove yourself from the pool area.
You're, uh, you're getting way too into the show.
Uh, a question from Shaki, I think.
Bobby, did you ever fulfill a random fantasy from a fan?
And if yes, what was it?
If no, would you ever do such a thing?
No.
Never ever.
I bet the fans, you know, if they come out to see what shows and stuff,
a bit, they're like, are all hoping you will.
Yeah, and they ask me if I do fan fucks and everything.
But I'm sorry.
Is that a category fan fuck?
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, a lot of girls do it.
Really?
Yeah.
For free?
Well, I don't think it's for free.
So, fascinating.
Yeah.
This is a very interesting business.
But I think if you want to fulfill a fantasy, then it should be a fantasy.
If it should be a fantasy, I agree.
You think that that's a lot more important in your line of work is really the fantasy aspect,
versus the actual physical stuff.
That's what I think.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Okay.
I think.
So every, now you want every night of, uh, is it, uh, are you on your own side?
Or we're, we're, we're, we're, we find you.
I'm a webcam babes, uh, dot com.
You know, huh?
And you can find me four or five times a week, most of the time two times a day.
Really?
Yeah.
And, and for how long are you on like an hour or a hour?
Most of the time for two hours every time.
Right.
Uh, it depends.
Like, if I have a lot of fun and, you know, there are a lot of people in.
And I will stay longer.
Right.
It seems like if there's a lot of guys and girls and couples in the world,
where else calling that, you know, it maybe doesn't feel quite that personal.
How do you, how do you, how do you manage that?
Do you have like a million windows open on your screen?
And you can see everybody or how does that kind of work?
Well, we call it like, there are like, people that come in and go out like right away.
But like, after a while, you get to know the people.
If they've been like, my memory is pretty good.
So, um, yeah, if they actually tell me the story,
the most of the time the next day, I will be a member of the name.
It's like, I think I'm training my memory.
So, you know, if there is a special guy, yeah, it's good.
Yeah, it's good.
If there is a special, a special story or a special guy,
a little bit more like, the assholes are probably won't remember or.
Right.
I'm sure you, yeah, I'm sure you must get a fair amount of those, too.
Yeah, maybe once in a while, that's so often.
Tell me about your, I think, and girls on it.
Like, well, yeah, I'd hope so.
Yeah.
It's one of your specialties.
What are the girls want when they, what do they want to see?
They're the talk.
Really, really.
It's like dirty talk.
Yeah.
Cool.
And do you type that, are you actually, is it live voice connection as well?
I can do sound, but most of the time they hear my music or they hear me sing,
because once you get into somebody personal, then everyone can hear it.
So they all want to ask you, like, scream my name and my name.
So I'm not really into that.
Right.
You're like, most of the time too many people in.
If there's one or two, then it's fine.
All right.
I type it.
Do you also do private sessions with people?
Uh, no.
We are like one on like one, so they can, like, check with me one on one,
but there are also other people that can few exactly what I do.
Okay, but if I'm chatting with you, then no one else can see one.
No one else can see one.
Yeah.
You can, like, click on private and then reprived.
So no one else can see it.
And if you stay in the main chat, then, of course, everybody can read it.
But most of the time, I click on the name right away, because I think it's something
personal.
Right.
Interesting, though.
The girls want dirty talk.
I know.
That's, there's some, I got some girls.
I'm like, oh, yeah, we do this.
Sweet thing is she was like, no man, open your pussy.
Let me eat your out.
And I'm like, oh.
And then what's the dirty part?
Everything, no.
Everything is like, you would be amazed.
Is it like that?
Go ahead.
I'm listening.
Well, I get this for myself.
Oh, shoot.
Guys, I try.
Yeah.
I think we actually, we might have already out of control right now.
Yeah, I'm trying.
We might have a couple of minutes in the chat room.
I don't know.
I think silver might be one of, we don't have a lot of female listeners, unfortunately.
I'm not quite sure why that is.
Maybe too much of a boy's club.
We're going to change that.
So tell me about your own psych.
Because this is kind of recently, you relaunched or you really put it all together.
Yeah.
I've relaunched my new site.
It's BobbyEdenLife.com.
And I have every week.
I have a free cam show there.
Okay.
For my members.
There was a forum.
You can see new pictures, new videos.
It's all exclusively shot for the site.
Mm-hmm.
So where you can, yeah.
You can't find it anywhere else.
And I'm very interactive.
Uh-huh.
She's very interactive.
Yeah.
Very interactive.
What is it cost to a membership?
I think it's $29.
Yeah.
And you get a free cam show for that as well?
Yeah, every week.
Really?
How long does that cam show?
4 an hour.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, that's a good deal.
That's very good.
Yeah.
I love that.
I got to see it.
Mm-hmm.
What does it build?
Something else like librarybooks.com.
What?
When I charge to my credit card.
How is it show up on my statement?
To be honest.
I don't know.
Who cares?
Pet love for pets.com or something.
Yeah.
But also, when you're joining, you get like seven or eight out of pills.
From the DNA.
Because I'm part of the detonation army.
The what?
The detonation army.
Same as the kiss army, but then detonation army.
Okay.
And who are the other girls?
Ficky fats.
All just.
They're American.
I'm actually the only European one.
Huh?
Well, Ficky is actually from Norway.
Uh-huh.
She's hot.
Is she really tall?
Is that when I'm thinking of her?
Oh, I know.
She's very hot.
Yeah.
No.
That's good.
Yeah.
You're driving me crazy.
I'm meeting with her next week.
I'm going to do a cam show.
Yeah.
So they better sign up so they can see it.
And that'll be on your side.
The cam show.
Yes.
I'm so becoming a Mickey.
Can I spend 29 bucks a month?
I'm not a member yet.
Yeah.
And do you take like direction for your pictures?
Do you do certain things in your videos?
That people want that that your members want to see?
They can do re-crest on the like forum what they want to see.
And maybe if I'm a good move, we can do it.
It's a fascinating business.
I've always been intrigued by the adult industry mainly because you're always like three steps ahead of really transactions online.
I mean, just, I remember back in the day,
Casa Rosa was doing live shows.
And even it may only been like one frame per second or something.
Yeah.
They're already in charging money for it.
I know.
I mean, I would argue if we say that the adult business really makes the most money online to probably any business.
Maybe it's equal to air travel.
But I don't know.
Do you have any, any view on that?
I think it's, well, it's certainly a business that is always there.
Yeah.
And I think it's a billion, yeah, billion dollar business.
I'll take one percent of that.
Mm-hmm.
That's nice.
Just a start your own side.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I need.
I need to get into porn.
Together with Mickey.
Yeah.
I'm like, I joined in.
Well, that's plan B.
If nothing else plans, tens out.
If the listeners don't support,
then we'll have to move to plan B.
We can always do that.
But how long do you plan on doing this?
Well, as long as I just like to do it.
Mm-hmm.
I'm no 30.
Oh, that's where it is when I said that.
I, girl, you don't look a day over 22.
That's good.
Yeah.
I'm trying.
No, as long as I like to, like, perform.
But that's why I only do it now for my side.
Because, um, I think, you know, I...
Well, you're building your own empire.
Yeah.
You're on, uh, brand Bobby.
And as long as my body, you know, still looks okay to do it.
Like, if I'm, let's say, well,
50.
And I look like a sack of potatoes.
Mm-hmm.
There's a market for that.
Yeah.
But I'm not really interested.
Oh, you're getting ready.
Like, oh, my God.
I'm getting ready.
Oh, my God.
All right.
Now, let's take a vote, everybody.
Do you think Bobby's still good for these?
Yeah.
I think we're still good for these.
I don't know why.
Absolutely.
I'm glad you chose this next song, Bobby,
because I've not heard it in a long time.
Cinderella.
Yeah.
I mean, God.
I've seen it recently.
Oh, boy.
Really?
Where?
Here in, in, just, yeah.
It was for the scorpions.
They opened up for the scorpions.
Wow.
That's crazy.
How was Tommy Keeper's voice?
Was it still up there?
I think it was really good.
Yeah.
I really like what they were doing back in the day.
And they kind of like disappeared.
I'm not going to show what happened.
It just got kind of weird or something.
Oh, the disappeared now.
I saw them live.
And it still works.
He still got it.
This is, uh, don't know what you got till it's gone.
I can't tell you baby.
What we've run.
I can't make you feel.
Won't you feel so lonely?
I let it show.
I can't give you back.
What's been heard?
How did it come and go?
To all that's left.
All the world.
I can't give you.
If we take some time thinking of baby.
Take some time thinking of you.
If you pray that one of you.
Don't know what you got till it's gone.
Don't know what he is.
I can't tell you.
Now that you're what I've got till it's gone.
I can't feel the things that the cops have paid.
I can't give you back.
You have so far away.
The same.
I can't tell you this all the way.
Take some time thinking of you.
If we take some time thinking of baby.
If you pray that one of you.
Don't know what you got till it's gone.
Don't know what he is.
I can't tell you.
Now that you're what I've got till it's gone.
I can't tell you this all the way.
Take some time thinking of you.
Don't know what you got till it's gone.
Don't know what he is.
I can't tell you.
Now that you're what I've got till it's gone.
I can't tell you this all the way.
Take some time thinking of you.
Now that you're what I've got till it's gone.
Don't know what you got till it's gone.
That's huge.
Thank you.
I love that.
How many codes are you giving me?
What are they thinking about your vocation?
I'm the Benjamin of the family.
What are they thinking about?
I think I'm a huge fan of the adult industry and I promote it wherever I can as long as it's safe and as long as it's all done within some adult context and not crazy.
I think it's a great way to do it and I think that what you guys together doing with all the promotion and using the internet is fascinating to watch and I hope you can really continue doing this for a long time.
I think that's what everything you do with all the work you do.
You're a scrapbooker?
Really?
Good idea.
Thank you.
It's the edge of the world in all a Western civilization.
It's understood that Hollywood's self-caliphonic education.