Delta Sierra Charlie 851, the food bar fucking Friday.
We're 60 minutes to set minutes and show you five rounds of time.
There's minutes, the 25th century of radio starts here.
We don't need enough thinking.
Kriss didn't mean me alive.
I know it's in the street, I'm broadcasting.
It's Adam Curry.
Yeah!
For more Friday, it's quick time.
You're the reason.
Come on, slaves.
Can't you do it to me all night?
She was a fast machine.
She caught the water.
Cleans your wildest fouls.
Get a woman out of here.
Ever seen she had to sack your size.
Get a man out of there.
And knock on me out for those America.
The last taker you're all in the shell.
Hand me fighting for fear.
She told me to come, but I was all ready there.
Got the wildest hot chicken.
That was quick in my mouth.
Say it again.
We won't make you lose you.
Should be all night now.
Get you.
The double time will not seduction law.
She's one of a kind to judge.
What a nerve.
Those are just another.
Call me and be a lot of me.
And come back for all night.
Have to cool it down.
Take a nerve round.
Now it's back in the ring.
To take another swing.
That the wild's wild's shaken.
The wild's quaking my mouth.
Say it again.
We won't make you lose you.
Should be all night now.
Get you.
The double time will not seduction law.
She's one of a kind to judge.
Should be all night now.
Get you.
We won't make you lose you.
Should be all night now.
Bring it back to the Arctic Radio.
Globally the way it used to be back in the old days.
Now on your ephones.
On your computer screens.
It's all over the place.
It's a daily source code.
The full bar Friday episode.
Five-one coming you from the Hilltop Rocks Tower.
Black Rock Command Center.
I am your humble human resource.
You're slaves.
He had to bring you the tunes that you're dropping in my box.
We got to fill up with some more cowbell.
That's what I'm looking for.
By the way, in case you didn't know it's time to lay down works.
Stop what you're doing.
It's the full bar.
Just what we do.
Go agenda chat on that where the party has happened.
Right now.
Let's see now.
So bad and pretty.
Booly with the style and ease.
And I feel like.
From a classroom.
It's it's love in the bird's degree.
Oh, baby baby.
I want you.
Tell you about my heart.
Oh, baby baby.
To your taste.
You're only enough to dance.
Love away.
Oh, love away.
To the life away.
A life while.
Well, you'll be beautiful but just watch.
And baby go.
She's all bad.
Just what you're선.
You're nothing,
I'll give you leave if she knows.
Oh, baby baby sure.
Tell you about where.
Oh, baby baby.
You're only enough to dance.
The night when.
Yeah
There is definitely something about sitting in Southern California and playing
Diamond David Lee Roth, back in the old band Hale and Dave's damn tonight away.
It just feels so incredibly good.
I can't see the cam trails today because of the cloud cover, but we do have some sun
coming through here briefly at the Crackbox Command Center.
We're high up on top of the hilltop watch tower, Crackbox Command Center, and later on,
your dedication is a request by a Skype on the show.
It gets your song's tracks, we need a real break, it's all shake up, we're having
told about you, but we're not so good, we won't be in shame on the truth, we're in our
home.
Oh, I'm gonna be around
Okay?
Open the thirty,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, one, no, no, you know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no way, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you, you, no, no, no, no, you, no, no, no. No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm tired, don't let me down, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It's time to put down your head with some hope in it.
Now you'll miss a winner.
Take it home.
Oh yeah.
Now you'll miss a winner.
It's time to put down your head with some hope in it.
Dennis Horses got a 5-1.
I'm out.
I'm curry.
My only job here is to make your ears bleed.
I'm going to try to do just that.
As we get rolling into the weekend.
Could he be playing an instrumental song?
Oh no.
You can't play that on a radio.
Someone's got a sink.
He's got a last 3 minutes and 32 seconds.
That will be so long.
Frankenstein.
Oh yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, the eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyeless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyeless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyeless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless eyesless
I'm not going to do it!
If I stick it up, I'm not going to do it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
The
All day long, I'm in your place, but nothing seems to be fine
Think you're gonna lose my mind if I don't find something to find
Can you help me?
Not you for my brain
Oh yeah
I need someone to show me the meaning I can find
I get to see the things I've to make just what I mean
Yes I will be right
I need someone to show me the meaning I can find
I get to see the things I've to make just what I mean
Yes I will be right
And so I do it, it's worth standing here now
I'm telling you to enjoy life, always like us, but
Daily source code 851, Ozzy Osborn officially now deemed a neanderthal
by some jackass in the British press
It happens, you know
In the morning to y'all, you human resources and slaves who are hanging out in the chat room
In the chat, done that is where we roll it all out
The big parties happen when we stream live, no agenda stream.com
Jump on in there, we'll tell you how to figure out how to get some music played on the show
All you need is a dropbox account
You need to go, you need to go
You need to go
So come there and try it again
And come there and try it again
But no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no no, no, no, yes, what is going on?
Chile peppers.
Higher ground on episode 851 of the daily source code of is your official group, our Friday.
Hey, how many of you who has show fans in the chat room? How many of you have been around for 851 episodes as everyone heard every single one?
Have you do you remember the very first one boy has shit changed since then and a big in the morning to my fellow hilltop Dweller
Eli Roth who I think has finally figured out that no agenda stream dot com doesn't actually work on your iPhone
You got to listen to it on the computer. He's he's just got his iPhone. So I he has not have not installed the App yet
But I know he's he's about halfway down the hill
So he's like my early warning system when the zombie start climbing up the hill
They'll unfortunately get to him first
See I know you're not real man because I'm loaded okay
I've had some experience in that area
Besides that whole wrap for yours is bowl anyway good evil. It's all the same crap rock and roll is the only thing that counts dig hard
As blistering awesome heavy metal rock and roll
This one comes from nerdy dude's draft box love this track
Not sure I know where this comes from but title of meals whenever gets you off
It's the only way she knows how to get back get so late coming out of the night
Leave the rock and roll it could she loves to play it's a sweet place for working queen
Leave it on it's way to late days away
Yeah, I'll go with what you know
What I believe
What I miss you out now baby
What I miss you out
No, no, no, what I can't see you
What I miss you out now baby
What I miss you out
No, no, no, no, no, what I can't see you out
Yeah
What I miss you out now
Flaring working on the street
Keep some treatment of a sweet machine
Let it think nose with the ruler's right
Saving his dreams of a corner inight
As hisむ lips with the power's caれる
Right around him's time
His fast is all worthwhile for the hustle andkiem
Feeling nervous Jason
What if I kiss you out now, baby?
What if I kiss you out?
No, no, what if I kiss you?
What if I kiss you out now, baby?
What if I kiss you out?
No, no, what if I kiss you out?
Yeah, what if I kiss you out?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
The other loves can't chase an old stream.
Sitting in a swim guitar, his knees, sinking tired of the snowing tail.
Knows him well, he can roll the clouds.
One way to keep one way, man
Rise and bust, make new tonight
The city of angels, the city of dream
The city is the one thing needs
You gotta go with what you know
What are you doing with me?
You know how I can cross one of the next two
All right, here's a little test you can perform right now
If you're listening to the sound of my voice
And you have headphones on or earbudging
Take out the headphones, take out the earbud and check
Is there a trickle of blood?
No?
Well, then we can fix that
You have not yet been completely assimilated
Don't worry, we'll use them as something else later on, you know
Right now, I just want to play some songs that will make you blue
Come on, we have a name on!
So close at one forces
Or the same at one forces
Some of those at one forces
Draw the same at one forces
Or the same at one force
Now you do what they told you
We are to fly
We're ready to Fly
I'm just a fight, but they're gonna be a bad thing
Super full, super full forces
All the same, they're gonna cross
Super full forces, super full forces
Super full, super full forces
All the same, they're gonna cross
Kill me, kill the game all
Now you do what they told you
Now get in the tree, now get to what they told you
probability hunter, I can do what they told you
Now you do what they told you
Karna, dude you are fed
Now get in the tree, now get to what they told you
ya, turn the up, turn the up, turn the up, turn the up
Come in the tree, now get to what they told you
Now you do what they told that you are fed
You tries to do what they told you
Now you do what they told you
Now you want to push, turn the up
Today, I'm just a fight, but they're gonna be a bad thing
Take the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life.
Take the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth
in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in
life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life, the truth in life
Twitter package from Yemen, which, of course, as you know, is home of all the best
manufactured printer-toner packages in the world.
Could this be a coincidence that this is on October 29th, the very day that transportation
security administration promised us they would start with enhanced pat downs at all
United States airports?
Is it possible that's a coincidence?
Or is it just retaliation against the British transport authority saying, uh, and you
guys always turn around like a, like a skin and I shape more than others.
Oh shit!
That's what I say.
Fuck up. Don't be afraid slaves.
We got each other.
Ooh, looking this drink and figure friggin' to it.
We can love biting us, looking shit, stepping mother,
fucking spunk-loving ball, busting cock,
fucking fist, fucking lift, Mac and dirt, squint and cool,
living ever-giving useless man.
Ooh, looking this drink and figure friggin' to it.
We can love biting us, looking shit, stepping mother,
fucking spunk-loving ball, busting cock,
fucking fist, fucking lift, Mac and dirt, squint and cool,
living ever-giving useless man.
Useless man.
useless man.
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next.
You've lost Matt.
You've got to just be waiting for me.
You want to just be.
Stop it, I've got this feeling inside of me.
You can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me
, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be too fast to me, you can't do anything for me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast do anything for me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast to me, you can't be fast
Can you play?
Thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video
Thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching
this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank
you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this
thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching
this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank
you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this
thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching
this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank
you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this video, thank you for watching this
video, thank you for watching, we've got a new on Johnny Ballet, let's get rocking
Only the road again.
I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that
I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come up like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I have never come out like that, I've never come out like that, I've never come out
I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I
think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think
I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I
think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think that I think I think I think I think I think I think that I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think that I think I think that I think I think I think though I think if I think that I think that I think I think I think I think I think that I think that I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think that I think that I think I think if I think it think I think I think that I think I think
I think that would kick some ass and please, by the way, when you listen to this program,
if you have downloaded it, do me a favor and burn that onto a CD and stick it onto a
USB sticks and just stick it in your shit somewhere.
So in a hundred years from now, when historians are looking through all of our,
because the hard drives, of course, will fail, even the, even the CDs probably won't be
readable anymore, but it would be nice if someone could find this and say, wow,
those guys were in some crazy shit back in the day, weren't they?
Hmm, that's interesting. Stupid slaves.
So our president, just at least in get my nation west, our president and a get my nation
proper was on the Ministry of Truth channel.
Oh, yes. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. I can't wait to talk Sunday in the morning with John about this one.
Well, these, these, these, these just baggage of toner from Yemen,
because that's where I get all my toner shipped in from.
Indeed contained explosive material.
Okay. So first of all, enhance pat downs, everybody. TSA to grab your crotch, opt out,
do not go through the naked body skin as refuse at all times, and second, of course, it's time
to a march into Yemen because we can do some amazing horizontal drilling right into the oil
feeds of fields of Saudi Arabia. It's amazing how simple it is when you are awake and know how it works.
More I know agenda Monday, a Sunday morning in the morning.
This is the greatest and best song in the world.
Trippied.
Long time ago, me and my brother Kyle here.
We was hitchhiking down along along some road, all of a sudden.
They're shined a shiny demon in the middle of the road.
And he said, play the best song in the world, or I'll eat yourselves.
Well, me and Kyle, we looked at each other and we each said,
okay, and we played the first thing that came to our heads, and just so happened to be the best song in the world.
It was the best song in the world.
Look into my eyes and it's easy to see what I want me to do and what I'm making today is destiny.
Once and it's time for me and the soul, when the sun does shine and the moon does grow and the dust does grow.
Needless to say, the beast must stun us, or when crack with his rubber tail, and the beast was done.
He asked us, be your angels, and we said nay, we are but men rock,
well, I know, this is not the greatest song in the world now.
This is just a tribute.
Couldn't remember the greatest song in the world now, no, this is a tribute.
Yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, ooh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh
I literally am proud to be a mother fucking fucking bitch!
Oh!
No doubt about it.
That is without doubt the best song in the motherfucking world.
I mean, there's just no way you can deny it.
That's what it is.
Totally tenacious D and tribute.
Everybody stand up.
No ladies and gentlemen, please rise for your get-mo nation.
National anthem.
Second law.
In the morning get-mo nation.
We are all charged up to be human resources and service.
In all lands and all ships and seas.
From the east to west down north to the lowlands and beyond.
We are happy and distracted slaves.
We are here for nation's home.
John, he should have said sea, but a John devour I dig in nullification.
Awesome.
Hell yeah.
It's spreading my friends.
Absolutely.
I'm trying to find the right songs to play on today's show because of this craziness
that has come and down the pike now with the explosive material.
I mean, it's like the whole script was set up.
You know, does the president really need to come out and say that,
oh, it had exposed a material.
Of course, I will immediately confess that
there's more than one bottle of corona here on the table.
Yes.
Warnings, the slave is drinking.
Be very careful.
He may start to see things in sound incredibly like the truth.
We must shut him up.
This cannot be.
Because as you know, the newer things have taken over the asylum and the way we like it to be.
That shouldn't have let him touch a brush.
That's right for the body standard.
Clean it for the cynics.
Oh, once it's west of the people's wrist.
Oh, you know what you never knew we made.
Oh, we're all wounded on the wrist.
Don't look near the Calvator ness.
Oh, let's kill him like you disagree with this morning's case.
Oh, there's a man around next to switch.
Oh, and the clear will go for me.
Oh, we're all wounded on the wrist.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh I'm not gonna fuck.
Tell me if it's empty, then nobody is fine
While everyone remembers that one
Fun boy three, of course they had a huge hit with banana ramey and what you do is the way that you do it
This was actually I think it was from a motion picture soundtrack
But I do remember playing that back in the old days
Yeah
Well, let's see we can get into a little different mood here for a second. Then give me some crazy like that
Yeah crazy bass kind of guitar and then hit me with some drums
Whatever happens to, Liam's trying to say, he got a nice pick
That made his new spell, whatever happens to you
Do land here, to play on me raw
An essential pencil
Whatever happens to, Liam's
Whatever happens to, what he does
Whatever happens to, on the heroes
Other Shakespeare's
They watch their own bun
Whatever happens to, on the heroes
Now for heroes anymore, no more heroes anymore
No more heroes anymore
Whatever happens to, on the heroes
Other Shakespeare's
They watch their own bun
Whatever happens to, on the heroes
Now for heroes anymore, no more heroes anymore
No more heroes anymore
Stranglers, no more heroes anymore
Whatever happens to, on the heroes
Simply lost sight of them somehow
They're round of desserts really carefully
And you can't find them
Some of them might even be chuckle heads
Or as we now say, meal confederates
Hell yeah
Well man, I've had an incredibly busy week
Of course, every single day
I need to get a couple episodes out
Now double the work loaders
We're doing the big app show on iPhone and on Android
So I kind of, you know, so if I want to do three episodes in advance
I basically have to do six
Every day though there's editing involved
Still have not found an intern I can pay some patents to help me out
And also still not found a real way to make money off of it
But I'm enjoying it, I'm certainly learning a lot about apps
So let's see Monday
My day was interrupted although pleasantly
By a lunch with the lovely Victoria Ricanio
Who some of you may remember from, I think, tech TV
But I met her at John C. Devorex
Thanksgiving Party last year
I dinner, I should say
And oh, what a lovely girl that is
So we bitched him on about the television industry
That's always fun
Then on Tuesday, Chris Perchiers
The big man from Boise, Idaho, good friend
Who is a documentary filmmaker
And SEO expert
The guy, the two kind of go hand in hand
Had lunch with him and the lovely Miss Anne
Then on Wednesday
The incredible Super Agent Matthew Lescher
Who is scouring the Hollywood
Work scene for Christina
And also working, she's the one by the way
That gets me the celebrity interviews with the big app show
We've got some pretty cool ones coming up
We're still working on the hoff
The hoff is hard to pin down
Because he's insane
We've got, we see the Super Star girl from Little Liers
Coming up soon on the app show
We've got, oh, what's her name?
Smoking Hot Alien from V
You know, the leader of the, of the, of the alien
She'll be on soon
And I think actually next week
I have a Rick Schwartz back on
From Yahoo's fantasy football life
So it's definitely starting to be something that's kind of on the circuit
So, you know, all I know is once you have audience
Then somehow money usually follows
So hopefully, well, it probably took 18 months
It always does with stuff on the internet
And I do appreciate all you guys blogging about it
I wouldn't mind a little bit of help on the android version
If you could let people know that it's available on android
I think I have about 10,000 installs
I'm not bad for the first month, but I need a little hit there
And if anyone works at Google
Who do I have to blow to get featured in the marketplace?
Please
Then yes, they had, I can't tell you too much about this one
Because I promised because it's, you know, we're still working on the concept
But I went on a road trip with the Eli Roth
Who, of course, is our favorite bear Jew from Inglories bastards
Also a fantastic director, producer of the horror genre
And we're working on a project which I'm very, I mean, I'm literally
I think about it, I get a boner
It'll be completely punk rock, very offensive
And I can't wait to share it with you guys
But need some work, so maybe around Christmas time
We hope to have something that we can show to the general human resources
And slaves
One hour into the show, time for Ray on the Charlie
All we want is Ray
Hey everybody, Ray Mold
Harvey
So today we're going to transport you back to the early 80s
Ladies and gentlemen
For other charcoal hats who didn't grew up in the Netherlands
Descible radio wasn't illegal radio station
In Amsterdam, in the 80s
This pirate radio station, focused on young Amsterdam, was mainly playing disco music
Imported from U.S. and U.K.
It was like the station called set
Tomorrow's music today
So what's Adam Kennedy with this?
Before Adam started his professional
Milty Media Hitman career
And did some radio programs
On Descible radio, under the alias
John Holden
Remember, it was the early 80s
Adam was, I think, 17, 18, 19 years old
At the time Captain John had to make his own jingles
Listen to this
So, sport you for Captain John
Fuck
To be
Ain't
Mission Control
This is Captain John, our sister is our go and our light's agreed
Where do you think of Mission Control?
We have a vlog
Major three, I can't hold him
She's breaking up, she's breaking up
Oh fuck Ray
John Holden
A man barely alive
We can rebuild him
We can make him stronger
Faster
Better than any man before
We can set that go
Six million dollar DJ
Captain John, your pilot of the airway
Captain Marilyn
Isn't this great?
No, it's embarrassing
This is our shuttle king, is he early?
Captain Skull
Holden
So, how did they sketch and John sound it on air?
Let's listen to some old air checks
Not your DC pad
DC fell heavy
Culture club
You're here, you want to hurt me
You're here, you want to make me cry
Because you're club room that I'm kissing to be clever
But everybody
Version records on tape
We have a fabulous phone in and about 12 minutes here
And you can do it
One eight four, one six eight
But of course you can do that same number right now
Ooh, you've got to go ahead with the whole group
That'll be it
One eight four, one six eight
Do you be ready to talk to me live at first
Good morning
Hello
Who's this speaker, please?
Alina
Hello, Alina
How are you?
I'm fine
Well, a very good morning to you
Yeah, it's easy
So how much you grew to there, Alina?
Yeah, I want to do it
My creatures to try to shoot paper from the law for cleaning
Biggest degrees in the old rocker old star
Cliff Richard
Where do we go from here?
All right there, why do you have to be a hardbreaker?
14 best, the hour 14 best nine
18th of
What's the mind?
Oh, yeah, that's october, right?
It's still a little bit sleepy
You're working to be in your car
You know, weekend radio, I'll give you radio
I know you six more and two
Soundtrack to my life
So you still got your headphones on and I'm
Yeah, barely right
I have to be honest with you
Chocolate hats
When Adam did some radio work for decibel radio
I was ten years old
I didn't even listen to that radio station
I was only watching bushy and Adriano
Whatever
But my older friend, Kay, told me
There's a particular song that reminded him of decibel radio
Soundtrack to my life
The rhythm advanced to down
66 hours per weekend
This soundtrack was the last single
To be released before the band split up in 1983
DB music
Missing it is out of the question
It was used by decibel radio
On the top of the hour set it on the one from music
96 point of view
Adam Curie, Elias John Holden on the wheels of steel
Playing thin lissie
The sun goes down
Can we show all of very nice weekend
That by now
There is a day
We're almost lost
This is the blinds of hell
Sentia to the days
She knows that I don't want to run
She comes close, she comes close
But my older friend, Kay, told me
There's a new song
The sun goes down
She tries to be a little bit more
But she is still captured, captured by his head
She knows that I don't want to run
She comes close, she comes close
But my older friend, Kay, told me
The sun goes down
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, thanks for watching and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see
you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and
uh uh uh uh uh uh um uh uh huh uh brother uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh um uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh um uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh um uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh um
The sun goes down
She tries to listen to the see-through
Well, well, well, well, well, Ray
Fuck you very much
There were some better recordings of me on decibel radio dude. That's not the old
Always appreciate it. Some of your best work my friend. That's for sure. Hello and congratulations
You've been listening to the use for Viagra. The vagina mixes from Pusper
Rotto you by Pusper Entertainment and Pusper.
Thank you for popping in. We hope you come again real soon
And to show our appreciation, here's a little Viagra bonus for you. Enjoy
Take that, stick that in your hat, will you?
Daddy source code 851, the food bar Freddie from the Crack Park Command Center
I atop the hilltop, watch tower
And get my nation west of the California IA
And I'll show you how to get my nation west of the California IA
Yeah, news is blue, the news is blue
I didn't don't wait to get it to you
What can I do? What can I do?
I'll never bother you
Got to move to the trick I'd be
That isn't all I need
Just take it but it's too dry
I'll be crazy, I'll be crazy
Yeah, doing alright
Yeah, I'll be on a Saturday night
Come up, man
Go down, just go away
I'll be crazy
I'll be crazy, yeah, I'll be crazy
Yeah, I'll be crazy
I'll be crazy, I'll be crazy
Yeah, yeah, I'll be crazy
I'll be crazy, yeah, yeah
Grab a seat, grab a seat, yeah, grab a seat, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, grab a seat, yeah
Yeah, the heart
It's exactly the kind of track I need to load up into the CD player of the 99.99 sub-9 or 0.3 top-down
cruising around perfect sniffing the tears have not heard this version before from driver
seat but of course that's the whole point here is the chuckle head around the world but to show
together the way it works is get yourself a drop-box account loaded up with some tunes
and then invite me to share the folder with you working with a couple of guys in the chat room
no Jenna chat.net to set it up on the newly acquired network area server so that I don't have
what is it now it's up to like 20 gigabytes now and it's all in the MacBook Pro actually thank you so much
from your no agenda support donations I was able to purchase a network area
storage device of course I did do the research and it's funny how you know you can
everyone it's like religion is what this is you know this one sucks that one's better
this is the best that one blew up on me and I basically was going for price and performance and of
course the hard drives are really the most important thing so I did go for a ready NES duo which
you know I think was the best choice available it's been moving all of the stuff I have so many
archives of things people have sent and stuff we just need to keep and need to keep with
prosperity but also to access from other computers at the same time it's just it's incredible
how much data is being chewed up doing all of this stuff here but the Dropbox solution has not
yet been found although I think vision in the chat room has something for me it looks like he might
have compiled a python version that I can then load up on this arm-based processor.
sounds like actual work so the Dropbox right now just filling up my hard drive but it's good
and what's kind of cool is I set the viewer window to date modified so when someone updates the
Dropbox then their Dropbox pops up to the top of the stack and it's right at the top of the list
so I know there's a new track in there I'd love to get some of the chuckle heads on and we did it
on the last show last week on the snafu Saturday had you guys uh calling through Skype and I'd love
to do that again to get some dedications going from around get monation the way you do it is
after you set up and share to fold it with me in Dropbox then drop in a little text file with the
song that you want to hear or whatever you want to do and then please add your Skype name and I
will then contact you from the hilltop watch tower cracked by tonight's center could it be any
simpler well yes it could but then again I'm just one guy here it's not like I got interns
on the round to help me buddy it was some drop that it was on the wrong you know that
and it's on the track and it's just you want to fall on our Friday
and my mom was there before the song and my mom was there you can be read the part for my mom
but my mom was there don't take you on and I'm not full and my mom was there that it's good to be natural
and my mom was there that it's good to be natural
and I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that I was there that
I was there that I was there that I wanted to tell I was there all the matters
And my mama's there, going home, that's your after, and my mama's there, the doors, all the matters.
tubes running across the door, all the ways outside.
It's all the always on the right, just as puntoвол is.
It's all the way on.
Um, what's your mama?
What?
Right now.
There's a hole over.
Yeah!
I'm just broken.
Just a thousand words.
Anyhow, if I see you close to just a few words, I can't find out.
You know what, yeah?
Give me the gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
I give it all, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
I give it all, gimme, gimme, gimme.
When I take a down, imagination, tell me.
I'm just going to shake up down.
But if I want to like a much lie, I'll put it on.
I like a mama, gimme, gimme, gimme.
I'm just a thousand words, I can't find out.
I'm just going to take a down, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
What you want to, what you want, oh, I give the money with the money,
that you want, oh, I give the money, that you want.
I give it all, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Give me the gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Yeah!
Give one of them, that.
Only my dead love of the fan, man, I'm like,
a big treat, well, I'm not much of a politician, he's here.
Yeah!
But much should be far, but that's what it's getting, man.
I'm not gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna.
Oh, my god, no stop here!
Sweet of energy, if you already whipped up the bike,
oh my god, you gimme, a little bit too far.
I'm not going to be far away to crush the cake!
What the heck!
When you're just in the middle of my mind,
Would you know what you're hoping for?
If not, believe me!
I want you to see as much as you can, and you see me!
I'll go man, I'll put you up there for a thing!
I'm losing my mind, first time this time!
I'm losing my mind, first time!
I'm losing my mind!
You're one of my best!
I'm losing my mind, first time this time!
Dangerous!
Scattered swordsman was the battle for an old genius,
I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I
I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm sorry, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I'm a little scared, I
So answer the question. What you fucking worry?
I'm fond memories of hanging out with the Beast of Boys of Montrose.
Switzerland overturning cars. I'm sorry. That didn't actually happen.
Beast of Boys actually coming from Sir Walters Dropbox, which I love this system.
By the way, if I've played one of your songs, do me a favor and remove it from your Dropbox.
So we can show up some space for some other human resource dropage to occur.
In the morning to your Sir Walters.
No, he was on mute probably.
In the morning Adam and fellow chuckleheads.
Yeah, how are you doing then?
It's great to be on live Adam.
Yeah, actually we're doing something completely new this time.
I still have my Skype here at the Watch Tower set up to automatically accept and transmit video.
And I only realize that when you flip down your video, I'm like, hey, he's trying, oh shit. He's looking at me too.
Actually kind of gives a different dimension to it. Now I can see what all of the human resources look like is pretty awesome.
So that's good to see your fully dressed Adam.
Yes. Well, yes. You're only seeing the top half though, luckily.
That's part of the good news. We'll see what he's drinking there.
Sir Walters, I've got my corona here and what do you got?
I'm drinking some red wine. Oh, very nice.
Right. But you were drinking something else there from.
I thought you were like, oh, I get just a glass of water to clear my throat.
Oh, okay. Sounds like you're from Get Monation Lowlands.
Yeah, true.
Where in the lowland are you located?
I live in Hill for some.
No, really costs capital.
Yes, yes, media central. Oh boy, you work in the business or you actually have a life.
No, no, I don't have a life. I've got the AC and no agenda.
But I've got a regular job.
All right, Walter. Well, certainly appreciate your support of everything we're doing.
Certainly, I know agenda. And what's the temperature like?
I mean, the real the political climate and temperature of the lowlands right now.
You guys finally have a government. What's happening?
Well, we've got a government, but I don't think much is happening.
They're just talking to say and bullshit at each government talks down there.
Yeah, I guess so.
A lot of talk about shutting down the internet, though, in the lowlands about restricting
and blocking sites and all kinds of shit seems to be going on.
Well, they're talking about it, but not much has happened so far.
Hmm, okay. Well, that's the good news then.
Sir Walter, you have a very interesting request.
Actually, something that I kind of glossed over didn't really mention it.
I don't know if a lot of people know, but Solomon Burke, who, of course, is a legend.
In what we call his genre, we call it soul.
We call it, what would you call it, Walter?
Well, someone once called him the King of Rock and Soul.
Yeah, it's kind of a little bit of a hybrid.
He passed away when he was on his way to the lowlands.
And the story is a little, a little sketch.
I'm not quite sure what happened, but I get to die on the airplane or like when he landed
or he never got, he never actually entered the country, right?
He didn't get through customs.
Well, from what I got that he passed away after landing, but before getting off the plane.
Shit, I forgot.
And hard landings, but that really beats it, man.
Kill the fucker passengers, that's no good.
Yeah, it was actually coming to Amsterdam to do a show for promoting his collaboration album with The Dutch Band The Deck.
Yeah, I didn't even know about them.
Yeah, I didn't even know he had done that.
And you have a track. Why don't you tell us about it?
And I'll be happy to share it with the fellow chuckleheads.
Well, The Deck is a Dutch sort of rock band and they've custom awesome songs in Dutch.
And I'm not sure who translated it, but someone translated some of the lyrics into English.
And the album is called Hold on tight.
And the song I'd like to request is what a woman and his featuring Jules Holland.
Wow, this is like a fantastic collaboration.
The Deck, Solomon Burke, and Jules Holland, no less.
Was this actually recorded in Holland, where was the track recorded?
I haven't looked into that. I don't know where it was recorded.
But one of the songs was on YouTube about a year ago.
And I've been waiting for the album to be released.
And just after it released he died.
Wow.
So, Rest in Peace.
Post Jim is Salute from the chucklehead, Solomon Burke and The Deck.
Featuring Jules Holland and Sir Waldo.
Thank you very much for being on the show.
And we'll talk to you Sunday in the morning.
Thank you for having me at him.
And I hope you'll enjoy the song.
Turn it up.
Yeah, you.
Yesterday I was nowhere.
There I'm back again.
You're the sinner, but everything.
And I feel 10 times a man.
What a woman.
I won't only sing those.
I can't be beaten up.
Life is chasing top, Vera.
But the dance trying to stop
Who what a woman.
constrain.
What a woman.
She takes her higher.
But you won't kill.
Drive it down, extend to the ground.
She gonna wreck you,
Let's just make it feel just like the crowd
Let's stand on our own
We're all warm, all warm, all warm
I egg
Super boy
If you give up, but you want to
Drag it right down the ground
You're the badlongers
Tell me there, spend your money
Make it feel like the crowd
If byeue you
Yeah, steady, I will know where
But yeah, back up here, but you didn't see them up.
Prove everything, and I feel 20 times of man.
The world of moments.
Only what a world that is new for God.
We are the world of woman.
A real good woman.
Let's not mess with man.
What a woman.
Who a world of woman is new.
Hard to tell you what a woman...
What a woman.
Who are you?
We're harder than a woman.
Whose a woman?
My grandmother.
Who are you?
壯老師!
I'm you,ули!
I know but you!
I want to tell the world, what am I going to do?
Hey, try to breathe in!
And you will live in the wind!
Adam Curie, the second best thing you can do by yourself.
In the morning!
You're talking for my car when you're no other time.
Now that I'm smiling, the girl is a speed I drive.
You tell me it's all right.
Your mind is a pain.
You say you just want me to take you for the drive.
You're just like a star.
Say how to get through you.
I'm starting to cry for you.
It's my heart that's slowing down.
I'm trying to get off the side of time.
I'm not the only source of cues of hip and man.
Tired cracks all across your back of it.
I can see you have just learned about it.
Darling, can't you see my signals turn green to red.
And what you are going to see a traffic jam.
Stand up ahead.
You are just right.
So hard to get through you.
I'm starting to cry for you.
I'm not starting to cry for you.
Jimmy, gross, a bit of cross-town traffic reminds me you've got to pick up the drive
thing later.
Thank you sir, Walter for his appearance on the Charlie along with his request for Solomon
Burke Dijk and of course featuring Jewell's home.
By the way, the Jimmy Hendrix song kind of reminds me of this a little bit.
I don't know, it's just for some reason I feel like I've got to play this afternoon.
As the girl, what you wanted to be, she said, baby, can't you see?
I want to be famous, I stole the scream, but you can do something in between.
Maybe you can drop my call, yes I'm gonna be a star.
Maybe you can drop my call, and maybe I love you.
I stole the girl and my prospects were good.
And she said, baby, that's understood.
Working with peanut, that's all very fun.
But I can't show you a better time.
Maybe you can drop my call, yes I'm gonna be a star.
Maybe you can drop my call, and maybe I love you.
I stole the girl and my prospects were good.
But she said, it's me, I got someone to say.
I can't no call, and it's bringing my heart.
But I found a driver, and that's a star.
Maybe you can drop my call, yes I'm gonna be a star.
Maybe you can drop my call, and maybe I love you.
Maybe you can be a star.
Somehow I always thought that had to do with sex.
It's just me or you know, I'm gonna try that tonight, baby.
You can drive my car.
Beatles on the Charlie episode 851, more Skype in a second,
and stay tuned, keep updating the Dropbox, if let me know where I can reach you.
GX2 will like this one for sure.
Play your video.
We were the suitcase.
We'll live in the disco.
I forget about the rap place.
Let's do the milkshakes and the long-awakage.
Let's do the milkshakes.
Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Master Miss
Alright this has got to be chicks tues for all right it's
hard to tell because you guys don't name them properly I got 20 folders called
DSC yay ever since then
Nick struke her band and walk in the park please
I've not heard this one in a million years
And I can't see where I'm being led
I give the world to set the clock back and act like a man
But we're back and I turn
To save myself
But this confusion
I'm walking the ball
I step into the door
I'm dripping into the door
I'm getting away
Let's see this day
A walk in the park
Away from all the busy streets of my mind
I seek a straight path
I seek a shady place
In which to unborn
But why do we go on
Inside of the stakes
Inside of destruction
I can't be found
Depending on the situation
I'm walking the ball
I step into the door
I'm dripping into the door
I'm getting away
Let's see this day
A walk in the park
I walk into the car, I step into the car
I can't move away, you're escaping today
I walk into the car, I walk into the car
I can't move away, you're escaping
I walk into the car
Alright, well, I gotta tell you, I'm extremely excited about the next guest we'll have on the show
A long time checklehead, who could it be? It's going to be a great one
But after this song, Danny Warholz, down like disco, on your footballer Friday
I walk into the car, I walk into the car
I walk into the car