Delta Sierra Charlie 847, the Fubar Friday extravaganza.
I made the deal, 1310, I wanted to die, I wanted to die, I wanted to die, I wanted to die, I wanted to die, I made my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to
Make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, my body is rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body so rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to made my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to make my body too rich, I wanted to
Well, let me speak feel I've got to you when I'm here to you
I'm home with you
I'm home with you baby
Just a little, well well well well well
You're going to do it
Swing Bar
SwingMan
I want to get a little drunk, one that does what I should, one that won't make me feel too bad,
one that won't make me feel too good, one that won't make me die, one that won't make me talk too much,
I'll make my face break down, one that won't make me nothing, one that won't make me feel like I'm feeling how bad you are,
I'm the lord of you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, no, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, there yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Because I'm not about to change my words
I'm living it up to my day
So, to tell us, to tell us
My soul cuts make me happy
Love yet again
I'm not about to change my words
I'm living it up to my day
The last one's ringing through the night
And it says me over the light
The twins' fingers in our food
Trying to burn in their space in the night
Now I don't care just what they're saying
Because I'm not about to change my words
I'm living it up to my day
So, to tell us, to tell us
My soul cuts make me happy
Love yet again
So, to tell us, to tell us
My soul cuts make me happy
Love yet again
I'm living it up to my day
So, to tell us, to tell us
My soul cuts make me happy
Love yet again
So, to tell us, to tell us
My soul cuts make me happy
Love yet again
I'm living it up to my day
So, to tell us, to tell us, to tell us
To tell us, to tell us, to tell us
to tell us, to tell us
To tell us, to tell us
To tell us, to tell us , to tell us
To tell us, to tell us, to tell us
To tell us, to tell us
Baby, maybe it's we love, we're dead
We're looking to knock on the dancing girl
Everything on the middle of the matter
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
You can't dream, you know what's my damn brains
So I started humming in a god of the dust
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh-oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh go, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I, oh, oh, oh, oh, oho, oh, oh, oh, oh, I, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
top watch tower crap rock man center we got to plans to build a new studio down underneath
the deck which luckily won't cost too much money it'll just be a c-man wall and some
soundproofing and that's why I've decided to really work on the whole set up the gear
everything is new new but of course the tunes are still the same song you've never
hear all the radio anymore
maybe I'm a legend, not the best texture of the world
that's what sometimes in my life that I don't feel anymore I don't know why it's taken
but it's okay as it's probably the same on your way baby you don't understand
just what I've been going through maybe you'll never come and you'll only stay
there's more maybe I'm a legend, waiting to start to live my life
maybe if you can't make it then I'm a legend
let me tell you something you don't know
I love things always make sure I have so hot times in my life that I don't feel you
no, I don't know just who you are but I'm really willing to try maybe
maybe I'm a legend, not the best texture of the world
maybe I'm a legend, not the best sight, not the best sight
so I'm probably just going to be harping on this new setup for a little while because it's so weird
not that many physical buttons yet the multi touch controller works perfectly and of course with new setup you need some new jingles
copy I want to go home and then you got a great morning ride everybody let's go head down
what's everybody got about to see come ahead and set me free get down get with it I said I've got
home baby watch everybody do the dance I say that I'm a legend it's been a long time
I don't know just who you are but I'm really willing to try maybe I'm a legend
what's everybody got about to see come ahead and set me free make it get down get
I said I've got home baby watch everybody do the dance
I've got home baby watch everybody do the dance
I said I've got home
I said I've got home baby watch everybody do the dance
baby watch everybody do the dance