Delta Sierra Charlie 828
We've 16 months to 7 minutes and showing 5 lines of time
Turn the 25th century of radio starts here
We're not being lost
We're getting me out live
I know it's gonna strip down from hot casting
Here's a new curry
Hey everybody
It's me, it's me, it's me
Is the food bar fried in this
Aviation grounded in Western Northern Europe
But we're flying high
I'm a drunk on my friend
It's for war, it's Friday
From the hills I'm watching our
It's quitting time
Check it, it's warm
She has red rooms
And she goes back
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
She got my mouth
She got me, it's me
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Say I'm a drunk on my sixth
Do I need you?
Do you know what I mean?
Boy, I'm a drunk on my sixth
Say I'm a drunk on my sixth
Do I need you?
Do you know what I mean?
Say I'm a drunk on my sixth
I'm a drunk on my sixth
I fell from the sky
Yesterday
Give me my hand
Oh yeah
I didn't try that
We made a great shot
On Saturday
We got you in jail
I ain't wanna
Everything on the money
Yeah
trust me
Everything on the money
Even though
Everything on the cut
It airs
Everything on the bank
Yeah
Oh, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
you, you, you, you, you, you,, you,ara, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, I, Joey, go at the side, on the beat of battle. Hm, yeah, I'll show you it. Yeah, I'll show you it. I'll show you it. But it's not too long. You have a scalded shelter in auve with you, you, you, you, installation now you, take a little closer,
Yeah
Oh
I'm too easy to keep you away
You can't be a shukong
You can't be a sh Enough
Back to the pain
You can't be without pain
You can't be a shukong
The Karl's Cup
Popped from Move on Machine
Kickin' off
Barely Georges Code Fossil
To it
The fibre frying Seriously
Calm
All Man Officially Apple 16
Is the Day of Silence
You gunna Google it
I don't think我說
I don't think we're going to adhere to that moniker today to you.
We got to get ready for the weekend.
We got to kick it off and style.
If you're listening to this, know it's gonna stream.com.
The party is over at know it's gonna chat.com.
Oh, my little pretty little pretty little.
When you go to give me some time, you're on it.
We have a motor, a motor, a motor.
Gonna come in a little further.
I ain't sure I don't have some motor,
give it up, jump to 30 miles.
I always get it up.
Oh, the time, what the young guy's kind,
my, my, my, my, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
One more motor, my, it's your honor.
Oh, my little, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I ain't sure I don't have any motor,
keep it in the mystery.
Just the main, run it,
there's a lake that my fly in sure honor.
We'll give it up, jump to 30 miles.
I always get it up.
Oh, the time, what the young guy's kind,
my, my, my, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
Momo, Momo, Momo, Momo, Momo, Momo.
Momo, Momo, Momo, Momo.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no of no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, people, think I say more quickly in this world.
Where you took me to.
To me is a just a matter.
Ty after all, a 뜨.
Is it just aDad?
To the land and me!
Somebody is not the anymore free.
To play I have been to bed.
To the orphan.
I am seen resending, you know?
To...
To them?
To the they who fight up and...
To think I'm a?)
Somewhere there?
I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a
lie, I'm a little bit of a lie,
I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie,
I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm
little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie, I'm a little bit of a lie
And, of course, we need to kind of shake it all out, get rid of it as it's Friday.
So, I'm gonna get hard on your ass.
Marcus Counts brings us magnified.
TV killed me on the Charlie H2D.
Bang it.
TV killed me.
And, me with a blow or no, alone in my life was such a mess.
I'm throwing the towel in, thinking the hair from the rain,
that I just can't compete in.
It's TV killed me.
You're so perfect.
So perfect.
Thank you.
You saved me with your worry.
It's gone, yeah.
Your plan seems so senseless.
One out firelessness.
Join me if you're brave.
Come to my grave.
TV killed me.
I want your words and take shape of my pride.
And with your courage and strength, we'll fit away.
It's you saved me.
Now that I'm wiser,
The dream was a spider.
You heard me with your promises of promises.
TV killed me.
Find out.
I'm sending my Marcus couch Marcus once again.
You saved me my proof of magnified TV killed me.
Perfect for the footballer Friday.
Daily source code episode 828 and the chat room is buzzing.
We're almost in a perfect state.
All we need of course is one of our porn star friends to show up.
And then it'll be outstanding for the footballer Friday.
But of course, you can't have everything.
Although Bobby Eden did promise.
Well, let's need to hear you know there.
Hey, what the hell is going on?
I've been on the phone all day.
I've been getting email messages from people saying, hey, you know, I got a friend over
an Amsterdam, someone in Luxembourg.
They need to get to different spots in Europe.
Can you hook me up?
Anyone with an airplane?
So I've been calling around to all my general aviation buddies.
And everything is closed down, not just the jets that fly at higher altitude.
And this of course, because of the ash cloud that is supposedly floating over Western and
Northern Europe.
And I got to tell you, this is something really weird.
First of all, the weather is beautiful in get-monation lowlands.
Everything I'm hearing from my boys is it is beautiful flying weather.
It's never been so clear.
I can't count the number of emails and tweets that I've received from people saying, hey,
it's really nice all this ash stuff that's supposed to be here because, well, there's no
chemtrails.
It's nice and clear.
Blue sky, perfect aviation weather.
But no, we're all grounded.
I heard one of my buddies was flying back from France.
And he took off from a small air strip.
And of course, it shouldn't be too much of a problem if you're flying with a
non-turban engine at low altitude.
He immediately got to Mirage's next to him.
Another report forcing him to land, by the way.
Another report from a guy took off from a private strip in the United Kingdom.
Royal Air Force forced him down.
This is weird.
You know, it's one thing for air traffic control to say, hey, you know,
buddy, you can't fly because it's dangerous.
It's another one to have air force jets forcing small,
sessmas, and moonies, and TBMs down on the ground.
And I have heard a couple of theories that, hey, maybe something else is going on.
I'd love to get a weather report from people in Europe who are in the chat room.
Because there's just no ash.
Now, I know there is ash.
And I know it's up there at high altitude.
But there's nothing at lower altitudes yet everybody is grounded.
And actually, got an email from the Candyman,
a frequent contributor to the show into a Norwegian and a Norwegian stream.
And he said, oh, it's got a nice, you know, people who are in town,
or we're all having a party, and we're hanging out.
And I get the very distinct weird feeling.
It's a little bit like rearranging the deck chairs on the Titanic.
It feels strange to me, and it could last for days, weeks, or months.
This is a disaster of economic proportions that we do not yet know.
The outcome, but it's bad.
It is football.
Fits in where the theme for today.
Billy, I know the remedy.
It's a little dancing.
It came dancing to my food.
And last night, a little angel came up and on the floor.
She said, hey, come baby, but I just hold up.
And if it excites,
grey half from above,
the house,
in the night hall,
she brought more, more, more.
We'll rebel yet,
she brought more, more, more, more.
Why not?
We'll never know, baby, more, more, more.
We'll rebel yet, more, more, more, more.
She don't like saving, she won't save her baby
The world's our love and she's needs to live
What sets you free, what's it to me baby
What sets you free, I need you here by me
In the midnight hour, she come home, home, home
With a rebel year, she come home, home, home
In the midnight hour, home, home, home
With a rebel year, home, home
With a rebel year, she come home
With a rebel year, home
With a rebel year, home, home
Yes, yes, yes
I want the world to be faded
A thousand miles with you
I drive your tears upon you
A million times to begin
I'd sell my soul
One bullet you burn for me
I give you all and I love me
Yes, I give you all and give you all the time
I give you all the pain
In a midnight hour
She's my mom, mom, mom
Will her ever live
She's my mom, mom, mom, mom
Oh, in a midnight hour
Mom, mom, mom
Will her ever live
She's my mom, mom, mom, mom
She's my mom, mom, mom
Will her ever live
One, two, ah. Well, that was totally weird. All of a sudden, all of my MIDI controls
just went blank. Ah, hate it when that happens. Billy Idol and the Rebel Yell on the
daily source code A2A, it is the chuckle all the chuckle heads in the chat room at nogen.chat.com.
I just want to continue just for another second here about this ash cloud. I got to
tell you, I just have a really, really bad feeling. Of course, there's all kinds of
theories, theories rolling about in in circles that I travel in about what could really
be going on. But it makes no real sense to ground even general aviation. I mean, particularly
when the skies are just absolutely clear. And they've got these jets forcing people down.
It just, it feels bad. The amount of economic damage this is causing is huge. And the
reports that are coming in, you can't rent a car anymore. The trains are packed. The traffic
on the way to the boat terminals is just outrageous. How long will this last? Do we really
think it's going to be over within a day or two? Here's the latest I've got apparently
tomorrow morning at 10 a.m. They may be opening up the skies over Europe again. But this
volcano in Iceland is still pooping out this pew. Is that even a phrase you can use?
I'm going to probably shut up. Ah, shit, not that one. This one. Don't worry, CSB coming
late. It's totally full bar Friday, that's obvious. It works so far, but we're not out yet.
I want to know what you're thinking. Them some things you can't hide. Got a pretty cool email
from Scott Taylor, who's been to Corresponding with Paul Ross from Information Society.
Remember those guys? Infosoc. My way Paul says hello Adam. He remembers me from the old
MTV days and says, go ahead man. Play my shit on the Charlie. Love to do that. Pure energy.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, go, no, no, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I can't see, No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no- we're all our way, we're just done for 1 and all of we're doomed to fight for
You're feeling down the walks of your mind
I know I like to break you down
Don't walk the world out to you
I could show you
The more you say it's true
Maybe I'm tired
It's a game I can't play
You are tired
But nothing else to say
I don't know
What you're thinking
There was something you can't hide
I don't know what you're feeling
Tell me what's on your mind
Don't walk the world out to you
You're feeling down
You are tired
I want to know what you're thinking
Never something you can't hide
I want to know what you're feeling
Tell me what's on your mind
I want to know what you're thinking
Never something you can't hide
I want to know what you're feeling
Tell me what's on your mind
Yeah who knows could be pure energy
Information society on the daily source code
This is episode eight to eight
So I just want to harp one more moment here
By the way pun intended
I want to harp one more time here about this this ash cloud
But of course so always starts of volcanic eruption
With some shift in the tectonic plates
So we don't really know what's going on
But all the lame stream news media can talk about
Is oh the flights the flights
Yeah how about the mail?
How about airlines that are used to bring stuff
Over from well China?
How about food moving around?
You know there is a rather interesting percentage
Of aviation that is not just moving people around
You know
This is this is really pretty big
I mean remember how horrible it was
After nine eleven companies went out of business
Not just aviation companies
It's I just think it's really big
And I don't think people are really looking at
The extent of what the damage really could be
And I hope that the authorities aren't being to
Cavalier with locking this stuff down
I mean we do have to keep stuff moving
And I know that we have some friends at euro control
I'm not going to mention who but long time listeners
And actually donors to know agenda and the know agenda stream
And hopefully we'll be getting some more insight information
As it comes along
I will say though by no coincidence
This article from new scientist
Titled mysterious radio waves
Amitting from galaxy nearby
Something strange in the cosmic neighborhood
It opens
An unknown object is nearing galaxy M82
And it started sending out radio waves
And the emissions
Looks like nothing ever seen anywhere in the universe before
Now this thing appeared last May
But now it's starting to
To send out radio transmissions
And it does not fit the pattern of radio emissions
From a supernova or no way
Usually they get brighter over a few weeks
And then fade away over the months
But this just may get louder and louder
I'm just saying
Of course we had some tragedy
Earlier in the week, very early in the week with the Polish president
And the large portion of the Polish government
Parishing in a fiery plane crash in Russia
And no better than to talk to our European correspondent
Who actually hails from there to give us his take on what actually went down
Comic strip
All right
So you just be like here
Hello Adam Los Angeles Gary
So in the 1939 German signed with Russians
Packed code Molotov
We've been through a pack
Yeah, we talked about that on our agenda actually
Yeah, and in fact this pipeline is exactly what
Kaczynski said was the new version of that
And this pack divided Eastern Europe into spheres of influence
And the coast among others, annexation
Invasion annexation of Estonia by Soviet Union
Estonia is the country where Skype was developed originally
Yes, of course
I always thought it was them
April 9th last week
April 9th 2010 Molotov
Revenge of pack to zero started
There were big celebrations
To start building pipeline from Russia to Germany
Under the sea without going through Poland or any other countries
Yeah, which would of course piss Poland off
Poland could talk about maybe sabotaging the pipeline
All kinds of stuff could have been happening at that point
CSB and announced only a few days before this tragic accident
One day later
One day later an airplane with anti-Russian Polish President
Creshti Russia
Coincidence?
I think not
Yes, what?
That was pilot error
Dao
CSB, you may know a lot about Europe
But you know sure about aviation man
Pilot tried to land in deep fog
Yeah, yeah
You've been reading too many reports from the FSB
Deep fog
It was a 1500-foot ceiling
It wasn't all that deep on an airport
That doesn't have instruments
It was such landing
Not also not true
They had FAR radar
And the traffic control tower had them on a glide slow
So they absolutely knew where they were
And the instruments were communicating with the instruments
With the instrumentation on the ground
That's what you can read from the same report by the way
And Russia
Once from European Union
To abolish the visas
To EU relations
And I have to tell you, I agree
Russians are more European than some old EU members
I don't
I will not say which
But
Right
And they should not
They should go to European Union without visa
Okay
You
Well, take my comments to heart there
CSB
I think we need to look at that a little bit closer
That finally got my rock sugar city in
And I got a plan track
Heaven and Heaven
So guys, do the matchups live
I love them
Oh
Thinking about our young years
It was only only
We were young and wild and free
Now nothing can take you away
Even down and over for
That's over now
Keep coming and back to work
And be the one I want
When you lie here in my arms
But finally we have to live
We're never
And never listen to our way
I should do it every day
We're never listen to our way
Oh
Thinking about our young years
It was only only
We were young and free
So it was only only
We were living
And never listen to our way
I wish to learn
My heart was just a lie
So I wish to learn
And never listen to our way
Instead of smiling
I never listen to our way
Otherwise
I'm walking in with a girl
I'm on the train
And I'm on the train
It isn't too hard to say
We're never
And never is it too far away
We're never is it too far away
We'll find our way
We're never is it too far Correct
We're never is it too far away
No matter what your friends say, I'm the one that got up on the road.
Man, I don't know who masters that ship, but as loud rock sugar, you can find
him at rock sugarband.com, heaven and heaven from the album filled with mashouts.
And just totally kicks ass.
I have it on my iPod listen to it continuously.
I love it.
I want to give a shout out to Andrew Bryn Joe, the guys at mevio for making mevio.com compatible
with iPads and iPhones.
Unbelievable how they did it, but HTML5 implementation worked like a charm.
It's just so much fun watching it now on the iPhone.
Back to the movies with a damn new world.
I want to give a shout out to Andrew Bryn Joe, the guys at mevio.com, heaven and heaven from the album filled with mashouts.
News of the program, this is the daily source code my name is Adam Curry.
The original Danny Ogre news thoroughbred ly.
We play music like...
you used to hear on the radio.
You know?
And just kinda do a different stuff in hang out and talk and play sweet tunes and ahhh and oh yea
We've got friends.
We call him Chuckleheads.
Oh my fellow chuckleheads, I'm gonna be a part of us against a name of rain on the shore.
Hey everyone, how are you doing?
Before I forget, don't fly the Delta Shara across the northern part of Europe.
You could be facing a major cloud of ashes.
As you know, last month, an island volcano under the glacier erupted for the first time since 1823.
7 to 800 inhabitants were evacuated.
Airports were shut down and flights grounded across northern Europe.
In the meantime, China is dealing with a 6.9 magnitude earthquake.
The death toll rose to 617, and more than 9,000 people had been injured.
But striking about this, the earthquake to place well just to desaster exercise in the neighborhood was being held.
Didn't we talk about this before?
The Earth is shaking more and more and I feel that's increasingly the case.
It's going on.
In the meantime, my homeland's the Netherlands is dealing with the economical crisis.
The Dutch Defence Department bought new bombs for the F-16 fighters.
This seems to be needed to make it possible to hit targets at a greater distance so we can't be harassed by the enemy.
These bombs of the type of Shara Delta Bravo 1 made by Boeing.
Cust our government in a amount of $40 million.
While the authorities in Iraq had issued a warning for a new weapon that terrorists increasingly used to attack.
On the magnet bomb, well that's gotta be a lot cheaper.
So that's $40 fucking million dollars.
Another 2 million dollars are about to be wasted on a stupid sucker game.
In order to prevent clashes between supported groups, a massive police department will be prepared to
the cup final between F-Nort and Iraq's in Rotterdam on April the 25th.
What's going on man?
It's just a terrible waste of money.
Anyway, there's gotta be some good news.
Twitter has more than 105 million users.
There are 300,000 new ones every day.
Go find her best owners and announce that the website attracts
118 million human visitors monthly.
Currently, each day approximately 50 million messages are posted on Twitter.
Well, I think it's a great way to communicate to the world.
So, as you see, a lot of numbers are messing with my brain.
And I feel the need to come down and enjoy the weekend.
Take care Adam. Bye bye now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Thank you very much, Ray.
Always great to have you and Ray on the charming.
Crazy way to get your kids.
You shoot the silicone in your lips.
In your figure, make your sad.
You start the fat right off your back.
Make up your mind about your chance girls
You can puff him up, so no problem with any girls
Only one thing they can fix
No I won't let you be in this line
That's the only you'll have
Getting nothing by that
Yeah, I'm out on the world
You're the only boys and girls
Hell, hell, the kind of green
Hell, hell, to what I see
Hell, hell, hell, there's monologue
Tell her that she's beautiful
I put her on a pedestal
But as you cook a trip less
Imagination kicks in
The more you think about sex for
We're someone else, the better it gets for me
You have a perm for seeing a life
Besides cheating on the wife
For fucks sake, shows off the same
Hell, hell, monologue
Hell, the world is a good
Hell, hell, the kind of green
Hell, hell, to what I see
Hell, hell, there's monologue
Hell, hell, hell, there's monologue
Today's adoption is a hot thing
You can get a child from nearly nothing
You take him home to an enemy
By all of you get with toys and candy
But all the money that you work for girls
Can compare with you a little bit
There's only one thing they can fix
No, I won't let you be this glad
And that's the only go hell
Can you nothing about that?
Hell, hell, monologue
Hell, the world is a good girl
Hell, hell, the kind of green
Hell, hell, do what I see
Hell, hell, this monologue
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
My special request for Miss Micky, a new Cmodon World
Find Dutch product once again from Gimmonation Lowlands
Love that track
It's funny to see the, uh, the gootaheads in the chat room all going
Ah, I've heard that song so many times
Yeah, how do you know what?
It's time to share
So not a heavier attention
I know we have plenty of cis admins
And network admins who are
In the realm of chuckleheads who listen to this show
And no agenda either or
Two things one
If you are waiting for the email for the cis admins opportunity
The cis opportunity
Haven't sent it out yet
So you haven't missed anything
It is forthcoming
And thank you all for sending in your emails
And your interest in the project
Which is purely a money-making venture for you
My way of giving back if you're interested
One other thing though that we did talk about
I think on the previous early morning Sunday servers of no agenda
We need a push notification server for
Well for us
Not just the no agenda
Malicia but for the chuckleheads
And the reason why
Is I'd like to make a service
That anyone who makes an iPhone app
And potentially
Um
I'm not quite sure how it works in Android
But for G phone apps
But you know let's look at the iPhone
And the iPad
We're talking about a universe of 50 million
We need a service that anyone can tie their app into
Because this gives you better than email
It gives you these notifications
So at any point if something happens
And we need to convene
Everyone can start firing off messages
Through their apps
And they'll start popping up
And for some reason I think it really could work
So we have to hook in
iPhones that subscribe to
Um
This service
And then
Can receive messages that send it out
To the uh
Was it the Apple push notification server
And once we have that
I think we could have a pretty
Interesting network
That we could use to our advantage
And just looking around
Times are drawing near my friends
Now I know I've been a long version of money
For nothing not too long going
If we were a Friday
But this is a mashup from DJ Moore
And here really brings it all together
The dire strength of sex
There's those basement jacks
Queen you name it
All messed up on the Charlie
And then you know
That's the way you do
When it gets out on your team
That ain't working
That's the way you do
One and one of them is just the free
That ain't working
That's the way you do
Let me tell you
When guys end up
Baby get up
That's the way you do
If we look you
Just don't know what to say
Better before you
Better when you do
Yeah, it's the way, stop
Do it now, no way, do it now
temptation is what we're doing
Yeah, it's the way, stop
I never wouldn't do
I shouldn't blame you to take the gates out
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
out here for for most of the week and she'll be here next week if she could even fly back
I keep hearing these little hints she's dropping like oh maybe I won't be able to fly back
right now she's outside by the pool hold on let's see we can get her on hey Christina
come on in for a second you got to meet it have you ever tried to get a teenager offer
you're doing Christina come here for a second this will be fun hey babe oh here she
comes who boy I'm live hey just say hi to everybody so come a little bit closer
tell me about the concert what happened I was meant to have a free ticket to go
to Coachella festival what is the Coachella festival I'm not entirely sure but I
know it's in a desert it's good Palm Springs yeah and so this morning I'm
already and stuff I'm really excited and then I get a text saying oh my mom's
has had a stroke oh shit is the guy who was gonna who are you gonna go where yeah
the guy who had a free ticket I didn't even have to show my boobs and he had a
free ticket and why you didn't have to show you I didn't even have to show one boo who
raised you child you that's the problem so no now I can't go because he has to fly
back to Germany I don't know how he's gonna do that maybe he's gonna swim or
something they're so much black smoke but he's gotta do it so I can't go well to
find something else to do I know I'm so depressed in the L.A. sunshine I mean
so terrible being by the pool yeah it really really blows doesn't really does
yeah you'd like be in here love being here okay well everyone and there's
some people in get monation he's too we're listening and they actually
it's a beautiful day there there's no smoke at all yeah but we're still better
the weather's still better over here exactly so well we'll see maybe we can find
some kind of show this weekend you can go to maybe someone in the chat room has
an idea yeah maybe maybe they can take me would you show me boobs I know it's
pens how good the show is get out of here all right yes there she is she
exists she's real and we have more friends here on the Charlie remember Troy
who needed an iPod well he's back hey Adam it's Troy Rutter from Rutter's
ramblings and also Troy needs an iPod hey long time no cure yeah glad to hear
you again I must admit I took a little break from everything podcast in the
last couple years but all my shows up on mebios still still bring in the
listeners I it's amazing how many times those are downloaded so I'm really
appreciative that you still maintain that service up there for all of us yeah
podcasting oldies but hey I just wanted to say congratulations for getting back
to LA and getting back in the scene I wish I could I'm back in Iowa so I kind
of missed the LA life every now and then but definitely keep up the good work
and I appreciate hearing all about the iPad and stuff because all right now I'm
living by curiously through your adventures with the iPad so anyway we'll
talk to you later and hopefully I'll hear from you soon all right bye
never mind bleeding couldn't stop the reason sick of fatigue unromantic maybe just
to fade that's the room never left in my room never mind it doesn't matter
anyway no cut half as mad as what you meant to say what they're massacred just
nothing went away so you know the lines we could pass it on first try to
make another line it is scary what you're trying to tell us on the missing drop of
the
Oh, yeah, remember those guys, machin' out at one stage left.
Wrap it up daily source code, 8, 2, 8, the footballer Friday edition.
I promise next week we'll get one in, probably around 2-0 Wednesday, just as blacked out
conference I had to go to, so I didn't quite make it, sorry about that.
So if anything else happens in the meantime between now and Sunday or next time we speak
on the daily source code, I'll be sure to fire up the chat room and the stream.
As you know, no commercials on this show.
It's all courtesy of the sustaining donors of no agenda stream, no agenda stream.com.
If you want to support us, all you have to do is go to devouract.org-n-a-s-thas-no-vimber-alphas-shera.
I'll talk to you again, Sunday morning for early service and sometime next week on the
daily source code until then, live your life with passion, my friends, and as long
as it lasts, enjoy your freedom.