Delta Sherry Charlie 855, it is the Fubar Friday extravaganza.
We're 16 months and 7 minutes and showing five lines of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
And nearly no life, I know it's just three times.
I'm testing kids and I'm carrying.
I've been told about you.
But what they've been said must be true.
And my mama, now that you're,
does talk to me all the time.
Now you're missing me.
I saw you missing me.
So many times, it's all I've been.
You ain't known and played to me.
Been ticked upon me.
I ain't so glad I didn't see you.
The best part of my whole adventure
does talk to me all the time.
Now you're missing me.
I saw you missing me.
So many times, it's all I've been.
Now you're missing me.
I saw you missing me.
You missing me.
Now you're missing me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
What's wrong with me?
to start somewhere.
It has to start sometime.
What better place than here?
What better time than now?
Rage against the machine under the air,
really short code oops, I wanted to play this one actually.
Please, gentlemen, please rise for your contamination.
National anthem.
You missed it a lot if you win.
In the morning, get ammunition.
We are all charged up to be.
Human resources and servants in all lands and oceans.
We are not just slaves but human resources and we're happy and we're distracted.
We are bringing back the art of radio globally through the interwebs.
We are bringing back the art of radio globally through the air globally through the interwebs.
For those of you that are new to this program, it's very simple.
You get a dropbox account.
You throw some songs in there and you invite me to share it with you in the before you know it.
We're playing songs that everybody likes.
Over the hills and far away Gary Moore on the daily source code 855.
It is the final week before Christmas.
And currently day 12 of not smoking.
And let me tell you, that's why I didn't do a show last week.
I didn't know if I could do it. I didn't know if I could get through a whole show without smoking.
So today we'll be a first for sure.
At least three hours of smoking music.
Oh, I might not be alone.
Tomorrow you travel around this town.
And let the cops chase us around.
Has this gonna stop?
We might be bound to get this place.
It's your seat.
You can trust me in lots of things.
It has not to sleep around.
Deep feet don't expect too much from me.
It might not really jam.
Sorry it was to be with you.
Even like I've met a tool.
If I hadn't blown the whole thing here as well.
Might be here with you.
Tomorrow you travel around this town.
And let the cops chase us around.
Has this gonna stop?
We might be bound to get this place.
It's your seat.
I'm sorry.
I may not be there tomorrow we can drive around this town
And let the cops chase us around
Has this going so that might be better than tears
It's just me
There's only one thing I can start
Wow
I never played the fuck out of that song on MTV
Jim Blossom's hate jealousy
Here on your daily source code you full bar Friday
December 17, 2010
One of the last shows for this year
And the party of course as always
is at no agenda show dot com for the
No agenda stream dot com for the stream of course
No agenda chat dot net for the real party
And everybody is hanging out
Wait for their song to be played as they drop it in my box
It's Friday
And yes
I am in love
It's just me
So that's what it is
In order for the party to be played as a monster
No agenda website
Here on YouTube
Max
I don't care if one day's blues, you say it's grey and when you say it's
First day I don't care about you, it's brighter, I'm in love
All day you can fall apart, you say when say break my heart
All Thursday doesn't even start it's Friday, I'm in love
Saturday, break my heart
Someday always comes to play
The Friday never has it's day, I don't care if one day's blues
Tuesday when say heart to touch, first day never looking back
It's Friday, I'm in love
All day you can fall apart, you say when say stay in bed
All Thursday watch the walls in stead is Friday, I'm in love
Saturday, break my heart
Someday always comes to play
The Friday never has it's day, I don't care if one day's blues
Tuesday when say heart to touch, first day you can fall apart
I don't care if one day's blues, you say when say heart to touch
All day you can fall apart
I got a pair of them.
Two days grey and one day change.
Such a day in way.
So they always come simply.
The Friday never has it's end.
Just up to the eyes.
It's a wonderful surprise.
See your shoes and your spirits dry.
Don't let you frown and just smile.
See guys, she's spinning round that round.
Always take a big bite.
It's such a gorgeous sight.
To see you ain't in love with love in life.
If you can never get in love with this dog,
It's Friday, I'm in love.
I don't care if my face moves.
You stay straight and Wednesday too.
Thursday, I don't care about you.
It's Friday, I'm in love.
I'm late, you can fall apart.
You stay Wednesday, break my heart.
Thursday doesn't even start its Friday.
I'm in love with those of you who support this program or the no agenda.
Know that your support at your appropriate giving level has enabled me to bring on Kevin the blade of the intern.
It's so beautiful because not only do we rush to everything today and I recorded my big app show.
He's an editing in the other room, but he also went out and got me lunch.
My god, my life has changed so much and I really, really appreciate all of that.
Great to have him here.
Sorry about starting just a little bit late.
Just as I was ready to go into the second round of app shows, I needed to record today.
Christina called me.
She learned a very important lesson.
You can't count on other people.
She was at the gym, which is not exactly the next door to where she lives.
And someone was supposed to pick her up.
And it's been raining all day in Los Angeles, supposed to be raining for most of the weekend.
And she did not take any money or a, or even a bank card.
It's like, oh, Daddy, can you please come and big me up?
And what are you going to say, man? What are you going to say?
And yeah, so it's, it's very interesting not to be smoking and doing a show.
Actually, I was talking after no agenda on Thursday, yesterday with John C. to Warack.
And I was saying that, you know, it really my entire thing has always been, you know, the lights are low.
I've got like my one light going on. I've got my mixer and almost totally in the dark.
I've got my green Pfizer on and I'm doing my radio shows.
You know, that's kind of the, that's the old school way of doing it.
And with that, of course, you need to cigarette.
Those days, my friends, unfortunately, are just over.
I don't come in.
I don't take the source code.
I don't get caught in the source.
I don't go in.
I am a miserable world.
Because you need an end of it without you.
And without you.
So now I'm nothing to you.
So fuck you, too.
Now you tell me that you're rather than me.
But you're gonna just get your promise.
You'll be lying.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
So fuck you, too.
So now I am nothing to you.
I am not in my mind.
Who's losing and I'm losing all the time.
I know I am nothing to you.
So fuck you, too.
Now I'm nothing to you.
Now you tell me that you're rather than me.
So fuck you, too.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You tell me that you're rather than me.
But you're won't blame my life.
But you'll get it, you'll make it to get with my soul.
So now I am nothing to you.
So fuck you, too.
That's kind of the way you feel by the way.
It's so good that Miss Mickey and I stop together.
And I'm very, very proud of her action.
I didn't think she could do it.
And I guess 12 days and mine as well be 120 days or 1200 days, right?
But definitely, I feel like saying fuck you, too.
Can't help it.
Anyway, we still should be able to roll through the source code nicely today.
Bring you all kinds of tunes, take you on a musical roller coaster ride in Johnny Cougar.
Because there's a black man with black hair.
Little black man.
He's got it.
In the state running through his front yard, you know what you think?
He's got it so good.
And there's a woman in the kitchen.
We're not feeling it's love.
And it looks better since they don't.
I can't remember when you could stop a flower.
I already thought America, you and me.
Ain't got America, something to see baby.
Ain't got America, home on the free air.
Little black houses for you and me.
Oh, yeah.
We're running.
Well, it was a young man.
In a decent, a list of rock and roll stations.
He's got it.
Wait a minute, oh man.
Yeah, the prethels is for you
Oh, you said I thought you and me
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah
When there's people and more people
And what do they not know?
Go to work in some high rise
And vacation now that's going for me to go
Ooh yeah
And there's winners
And there's losers
But they ain't no big deal
Cause I'm simply my baby
Paced the thrills
The booze
I can't
All the way
That's better
You and me
And that's better
I suck in the sea
That's better
All my free
Ooh yeah
Look at the cows
That's better
Ooh yeah
You and me
And that's better
That's better
Some of the sea
All my free
And that's better
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Little big house
Little big houses
But you and me
And that's better
That's better
The best country to live in
As far as I've concerned
Even though we have our issues
We got our problem
I just realized
Because I'm looking at the chat room
People are talking about the
Stopping smoking thing
We've been through so many things
Together on the show
For those of you been around
For
Most of the 855 episodes
Holy crap man
We've been through
A lot of things
Geez
Some believeable
Including my mom actually
Dying from lung cancer
All the way full circle to me
Stopping
So I don't have to die from lung cancer
Although I have to say
I've always loved my smoke
I've always loved rolling my own smokes
I've always loved smoking pure tobacco
There's many times a day
When I'm almost doubled over
Going like, oh god
I want a smoke
And then of course Mickey will say
Well we can smoke
We can have one smoke
Like no we can't have one
Smokes
Like no you start
It's perfect
We're keeping each other in check
I have to say we've discovered a couple things
One
Our lungs are not trying to escape
Through our orifices
In the morning
Which is nice
And I have to say
Within only a few days
We have already noticed
Enhanced sexual pleasure
If that doesn't motivate you
I don't know what does
That's about the only thing
We actually can do is humanoids
No license required
By the way
Over the past 46 years
I've got pretty good at it
And I have to say
That's about the only thing
Next to the only thing
And that's about the only thing
That's about the only thing
When I come home baby, my house is dark and my thoughts are cold
You ain't around, baby, we're teenagers and I don't know what to do
I'm getting tired of waiting and fooling around
We want somebody, you won't make it feel like we're all leaving home
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I think it was the moonflower album that I just kept playing over and over and over again at home when I was a kid
I always love Santana man, the Cardo Santana is the sound of his guitar
It's just so outrageously recognizable and just fantastic, I love it
Alright, chat room, so you guys all into the sex talk now that I mentioned that
And of course there's some funny lines in there and I figured well if you guys are having fun together
Maybe I can play something we can all enjoy a little laugh as a community
Some of them are hairy, some of them are bald, some are kinda scary and this is what they're called
Good job, good job, good job, good job
They call that thing for China
Some belong to virgins, they're really tight and strong
But big or small, I love them all, that's why I sing my song
The joy, the joy, the joy, the joy
They call that thing for China
Some of them are smelly, like clams and fish and such
Some smell like a summer's eve because they've been dushed too much
Some smell like a summer's eve because they've been dushed
They've been dushed too much
Some smell like a summer's eve because they've been dushed too much
Some smell like a summer's eve