Delta Shara Charley 824
We're 16 minutes and 7 minutes and showing 5 lines of time
The 21st century of radio starts here
We are in a freaking preview of life
I know it's gonna strike our podcast
It's Adam Curry
See you in the next one, little friend
Adam Curry, I'm living in source code
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go, the moment is day nine
We go through a time one
Keep on this and that fine
Let's keep on this
We're finally in the back seat
We're better in the beginning
We're facing the back seat
I'm moved
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go, let's go
When they move
I don't know
I'm already a bit ready to go
The moment is day nine
We go through a time one
We keep on this and that fine
We're facing the back seat
There's no shame in the back a little
One thing I wanna know
All friends of red cat
All living this day nine
You go through the top one
And if you can listen to them
We're gonna speak for everybody
Because the pilot is in the back seat
The general is in need
But they said the back seat
We're gonna speak for them
I-O!
Let's go!
It's a fire flower
And it's the belly source code
How you doing everybody
Come on you from the hilltop
Watch tower in these
People from the way
I've Southern California
Get on this and west
Here's one for you, Beyla
You're saving my life
Gather around
Everybody, how you doing
Anything you like
Oh yeah! You want free college
Muscaditch
More kids in the school
Whatever you like
You have come to the right place
Why?
I'll tell you why
Who can take your money
He's a bug
All the fears, the government
Oh, the government can't
And the government can't because I mix it up
We'll rise and make it all taste good
The government takes everything we make
To pay for all of their solutions
Hell, care, climate change for the show
The role will wait the constant to show
And who can give a bailout
Tell us to behave
And make the founding fathers roll over in the grave
The government
Oh, the government can't
And the government can't because I mix it up
We'll rise and make it all taste good
The government takes everything we make
To pay for all of their solutions
Their economics are fiction
Soon we'll have to eat our dishes
Oh, who can be a failure
And so many ways
And instead of getting fired
Hey, we'll give ourselves a raise
The government
Oh, the government can't
The government can't
And the government can't go
They make it all taste good
And your uncle Sam can't
Because if he exists it will
as it makes it all taste good
And a field so good
Because the government says I should
Oh, yeah
Is that guy awesome or what?
10 Hawkins, the government can rollin' out on the Friday for you, which is
footballer, the weather is beautiful here in Southern California, and the Charlie is on the air
everywhere.
You may be checking us out at noagendastream.com live, check it to the channel where
if you can, there's a party going on there, noagendaget.com, and we'll be breaking it out
today's tape was goin' on, on the Charlie.
1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 1, I love this song, believe it or not, recommendations for my tunes.
What can I say, try to find your bros, I am governor, cherry brown, I are a smile that
never frowns, so I will keep a rest, I can't, I will keep a rest, I can't, I will keep a rest, I will
sleep the way, I will be clearer one day, I will not mend all of you in the middle
in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in
the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, lose thecomb, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, the middle,
That was one of those
Now it's night to be dated for
I can not act in your front door
It's the sway, denim, secret police
They have come for your uncooled names
I'm quite a thin dude in town
You're the nicest, I'm just a man
Don't you worry, it's me, it's short
Boy, I'm trying, it's a pretty girl
I'm a gay boy
I'm so gay, I'm so gay, I'm so gay
Don't you worry, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me
I'm a gay boy
I'm a boy, now, I'm a realist
I'm a boy, now, I'm a boy
I'm a funny, a thing I just read in the chat room
This is of course being the deaf candidates
Who's thought in my lifetime
The actually would it kind of all be dead
Because the kind of fun you're brought to some
Daily source code eight twenty-four
It is the full bar Friday
And why would we do one more?
One more before we break it down and talk a little bit
Just one more to get into the mood
Ever since I played this track
Or these guys in the previous Charlie
I've just been going nuts about all of their stuff
They got a great album
It's rock sugar
Pray it for a sweet weekend
Once upon a time
Everybody wants a new way
Everybody's got a way of stopping
Everybody needs a strategy
Everybody wants a new way of stopping
I can't see the fear of you
Everyone wants you, don't come without me
Everyone's over here, you're all alone
Everyone's with you, you're all alone
When it comes to me, don't make it around
You're the one who made all that
You're the one who made all you
All right, gotta be honest with you, this is uh
Did you tell me, do not have the CD yet
for YouTube, but it just sucks too much
to even for me to listen to it.
Damn.
Ah, that wasn't exactly what I was expecting.
Well, I can't play anymore Rock sugar
until I get the CD.
It's, I even tried turning off the compressors, everything.
It just would not work.
So yeah, we'll just win that one down.
All right, I think that we get the idea.
We're all kind of mashed out and we're ready for,
ah, for a full source code, let me tell ya.
A lot of interesting things going on.
The number one would have to be based upon the comeback
of the Charlie episode 821, one of the gossip magazines
in the Netherlands did a full, an unbelievable transcript
of the show.
Now, you recall I talked about my mom
and a spiritual experience I had.
Well, ah, the way that turned up on the front page
of this rag was, dead mother tells Adam to leave Patricia.
And let me tell ya, if you listen to the show
and I actually contemplated pulling clips from it
so you could hear it.
I couldn't have said anything more opposite of that.
And then there was even a little inset that actually came
back to me in a weird way.
You know, I think I made an off-handed joke
about Christina.
And that came back as Adam says,
Christina only calls me when she needs money.
It's just unbelievable what these guys will do.
Now, of course, a contact with the ex is not that great.
So that created a little bit of friction,
ah, which is completely unnecessary.
But you know what?
And I had a long chat with Ms. Mickey about it.
It's like, this is what I do.
This is what the source code is.
This is what I've always done.
And I'm not gonna let it a couple of weenies
in Gitmo Lowlands with a circulation of 50,000.
Maybe they have more.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not gonna let him stop me from talking about,
you know, sharing stuff amongst friends
as we're doing here.
And let's face it.
You know, the charcoal is coming back
and it'll take a while to build up the audience.
Although I will say that based upon
just everyone's iTunes reactivating,
it kind of worked.
You know, it was a nice little surge there.
It was nice to see the numbers pick up.
Now, let me just say something about this rag.
You know, obviously,
the media has made, and the Netherlands has made a nice little,
amount of money off of, you know, my personal situation.
And I have another example that I was thinking about
about how Nate, and you could say that it's intended,
and maybe it even is, and I'll take it down
that rabbit hole if you don't mind.
I was thinking about Tiger Woods.
And first of all, your Tiger Woods is a multi-billion dollar
franchise, multi-billion, I think he himself has made
over a billion dollars, no kidding,
like really a billion dollars in cash
throughout his career, which has been quite long at this point.
And so you kind of think that with all of that money
writing on it, if he made a billion, then several,
several more billions were made by, and TV licensing
deals for broadcast and sponsorships.
And I want to tell you kind of how that works
and what I think happened here, because, you know,
we don't really get to talk about this on no agenda,
and for good reason, because it's really seen
as the real news, you know, the distraction,
but there's something really big going on here,
when you look at an athlete who,
he didn't really bring back golf.
In fact, the numbers on golf aren't up all that much,
but people were watching golf for Tiger Woods.
Broadcast numbers, and I did a little bit of research
on this, broadcast numbers were double,
any golf tournament if Tiger Woods would play,
double if not triple the amount of viewers,
because you know, the guy is like beautiful to watch.
And it's emotional, and it's a story behind it,
it's really fantastic.
But there's a real problem going on in the golf sector,
because where's all this money made?
It's made from corporate sponsorships,
and who are the main sponsors of golf?
Well, you know, that's pretty easy
besides some obvious luxury goods.
It really the financial industry.
And how does it work, you know, you got your clients,
and it's just like Formula One,
which is also pretty much down the tubes.
Now, I think Richard Branson is trying to being a bring it back.
But you know, when you're swimming in money
and you're in the financial service sector,
no, you're going to take the company plane,
you're going to take your big whales,
your big clients, you're going to fly them down,
you're going to have a good time, watch Tiger Woods,
the phenomenon, and so tons of money
was flowing in from financial services,
which, of course, really can't,
well, they might be able to afford it,
but they can't do this stuff anymore,
because their shareholders would revolt,
and that's actually already happened a couple of times.
So they're pulling money out.
And the way these television contracts work
is let's say there's a $10 million title sponsorship
for one of these, and I know how this works.
So I'm giving you the really insight.
Tell me, and that's pretty much a standard title sponsorship,
$10 million, probably four of that will go
to the television contract, let's say CBS.
And then another, oh, let me think,
you know, the person who wins a tournament
may get 20% of what's left, so of the six million,
you know, maybe one and a half or something like that,
or a million dollars, and by the way,
the rest of the tour of the half that at least thing,
the top half will all make some money.
So there's lots of money flowing around there.
So that money is now edging out,
and there's just no money to go into the television contracts.
And in fact, some contracts,
people might have been very happy with this whole Tiger Woods thing
and may have not been too sorry to see this come out,
because, oh, now we can cancel our contract.
And believe me, with a multi-billion dollar franchise
like Tiger Woods, there's no way people didn't know about this.
I mean, the guy wasn't hanging out with these women
without anyone else to know.
And let's say, ludicrous to think that.
So what to do if you're a media company,
any type of media company,
and you want to still make money off a Tiger Woods,
but you know that the money that he was good for
just isn't coming in because these big contracts
are all ebbing away.
Well, you might as well have a scandal
because then you can make money off of the guy
for years without paying a dime.
That's exactly what went on here.
It's exactly what happened.
By the same token, Michael Jackson,
worth more dead than alive.
So if they didn't actually kill him,
if they didn't actually expose Tiger Woods on purpose,
they certainly are complicit in the whole story.
And I'm just noticing some of this happening myself,
how they'll make money off of anybody
and anything without shame.
And that's okay.
Ooh, I don't even think about you, no more.
Well, maybe you think you broke my heart.
I'm gonna let you know of you.
But take a lot more hurt than what you got
to break this boy into.
Plenty of women in this world
and I'll find love a new deer.
So don't you trouble your girl, the girls.
I'm not thinking about you.
Just stop, breathe, tending.
I'm cold in my life waiting by the phone.
Hope in my car to say that you're sobbing.
Baby, don't be a fool.
You'll never, that fool.
I won't cry, no dear in my eye.
I won't choose a close-up action to give you
no sadness, action, I got no despair.
I don't even care.
So go out and find another to take a loving
y'all love it if you dare.
I don't even think about you, no more.
I should have known no one from my start
that you'd be the other dealin.
When we ordered in that restaurant,
and you ain't my new two.
But I'm gonna fall see your appetites.
Go on beyond the menu.
Holdin' my best friend in his new bed.
You're all the best to you too.
So stop, breathe, tending.
I'm cold in my life waiting by the phone.
Hope in my car to say that you're sobbing.
Baby, don't be a fool.
You'll never, ever, that fool.
I won't cry, no dear in my eye.
I won't choose a close-up action to give you
no sadness, action, I got no despair.
I don't even care.
So go out and find another to take a loving
and you're loving it if you dare.
Oh, cry.
No sadness, action, I got no despair.
Don't even care.
So go out and find another to take a loving
and you're loving it if you dare.
Oh, cry.
So the charcoal heads who have been run
for while recognizing Pete Hopkins.
I won't cry.
He had his, of course, God's say for dear friend Pete.
Good to have him back on the Charlie.
Of course, these days, he's a number one on whipseneb.com.
And I was looking at a way, I guess.
And I got to tell you, I'm really excited about being out here,
because there's a lot of people I know that I'm just looking
forward to reconnecting with.
That was just a chatting with the Jeff Smith earlier today.
He's got an album coming out pretty soon.
Can't wait to play that on the Charlie.
And I even believe he and Angie B are looking to do
in a couple of, you know, with the love spirals.
Maybe doing a couple of shows out here in Los Angeles.
I'm really looking forward to reconnecting,
because all of that stuff is just down the hill these days.
Ah, yes.
Nice.
Oh, yeah, I wanted to say that I got a huge compliment
from Patricia's lawyers, an off-handed backhanded compliment.
I might say, you know how I've been basically answering
all of their proposals and emails and doing it all myself.
And actually taking some pleasure in understanding
what they're saying and how this process works.
Also, because, you know, I'm not going to, I can't afford a $400
on how we're lawyer.
For me to tell him what to do for him to talk to the other guy
and for that guy to tell Patricia, no way.
I've been through that too many times, no way.
So her law firm, I should say, squares that these responses
are not coming from me.
They're coming from a lawyer.
I, uh, no.
Anyway, looks like we might actually just work it out together
and get rid of all these lawyers, uh, and just remove them
from the middle, which I hope works out.
She was going to call me today and, uh, I don't know,
haven't seen anything yet, but, uh, I'll keep you up to speed.
Just trying to solve all of that amicably as amicably as possible,
because let me tell you, and again, I'm just generalizing
on the lawyer stuff, but man, these chisters really make it difficult.
It's really, it's really just crazy, particularly if you kind of agree
on things and then they make it more difficult.
Who you can't call him, uh, bastards.
Hey, uh, a couple of you sent me a link, uh, regarding bill gates
and Toshiba being in, uh, cooots or investing together
in some kind of miniature nuclear reactor, uh,
what's the name of this company, uh, terror power that you should, uh, you know,
what I would call a backyard nuke that you could, uh, basically drop in and have, uh,
power for the rest of your life and not even have to do anything
no maintenance. I mean, there's a, there seem to be a lot of confusion and of course,
if we have, uh, savants on this show and we're bringing them back,
the one guy who would know all about it would be atomic rod atom.
So I popped him an email and within minutes, he got back to me.
Hey, Adam, atomic rod atoms here, great to hear the DSC back on the air.
You asked me to help clarify the news that is going around regarding bill gates,
Toshiba, terror power and small nuclear power plants.
Fast company got it a little confused. Bill gates is definitely interested in the traveling
wave reactors that burned depleted uranium or used uranium from traditional reactors.
Toshiba is definitely interested in small reactors as well as large reactors and they have a
design for a 10 megawatt reactor they call the 4s. And there is a company, uh, known as Hyperion
that is developing reactors that are small enough to fit into a hot tub,
but fast company combined all three concepts into a single reactor and came up with a
rather confusing article. The traveling wave reactors minimum size is approximately 300 megawatts
electric that's more than 10 times as large as the hot tub sized Hyperion reactor.
Toshiba and gates have a lot of items in common because they both like long-lived fuel systems
and then we'll have some material issues that they have to solve together.
Hope that helps and if you have more questions about quote backyard nukes just let me know.
I'll try to help clarify in a short period of time. Take care and great to hear the DSC back
on the air. Keep playing great music and keep making us all smile. Thank you very much.
Atomic rod atoms everybody are a atomic backyard. Actually I like that new that
new meme the hot tub nuke we should keep it at that. Hot tub nuke expert and he's got some other stuff
he's researching of course he has his own show if you want to more about it and I'll put a link
to that in the show notes. I'm very interested as you know I think probably when we dropped off
about a year ago I was still very and I am still very interested in alternative forms of power
and we've got a huge work table here in the hilltop watch tower. I'd have to say this thing is
wow what is it maybe ten eleven feet long and you know I've got all kind basically half of it
Mickey has the other half and I've got all my stuff piled up and eventually my studio will come
from London somewhere around mid April I think so I'll have some more of the the outboard gear
that I love so much piled up and ready to go but also it's great for experimentation and I've
been seeing people doing some amazing stuff with magnets and I just got to think there's something
there and a lot of this experimentation is still being done down under in Australia and if you
you know just look on YouTube you'll you'll see plenty of videos and amazing experiments in Australia
of course the thing that always goes wrong is people who come up with these beautiful works of
engineering art essentially and I'm no tanker I'm not really good with you know with metal and
real physical stuff I can tinker with code and computer stuff so it's going to be interesting actually
I'm looking at drafting a friend of mine and helping the out but whenever someone comes up with something
like this and they're always going get investors and they want to patented and I don't think anything
like that is ever going to work it's going to be something you can build at home it's going to be probably
a combination of some magnets and perhaps a Tesla turbine in order to jack up the power output but I
really do think there is something there so atomic rod the race is on man between your hot tub
nuke and my free wheel of love suggested by a Jason Rodilsky longtime charcoal listener said
remember you used to play this on the chock I sure do we the living it's funny how the smile in your eyes
I slowly fade in with last days and July the year is drowning like the calendar rose thin
and set away again your back against the wind and when the cold wind blows your gun
and I will hold my head again but you can run from the truth
of the London rave
who saw the beaches my world is called and we impress me flowers and the pages of the
diaries your key it's don't feel as spice I need a bit of a huge sleeve as a calendar of
the wind blows your gun and I will hold my head again but you can run from the truth
of the London rave
yeah
just see the love you mean
last ever summer on your dreams I swear I believe that someday you will stay I can't do
all the even I'll take it anywhere of you to anywhere when the cold wind blows your gun
and I will hold my head again but you can run from the truth
Marcus couch in the the chat room in no agenda chat calm just wondered what was up with
the sappy bitch music hey dude you know something for everybody my friend please please please
that of course is we the living great song and pod safe as always and a lot of stuff going on
in uh get my nation east in Europe I really try to keep tabs it's um it's way different not
living there anymore so I don't get the full influx of media but there is some amazing stuff
happening that were quite unaware of here in the United States it's you know or it's just being
called uh the Greek bailout which uh really well I want to break that down for you in the second
and just give you some thoughts on that because it does affect all of us and essentially our parents
are to blame oh yeah our parents are baby boomer parents but first comic strip
comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip that's our European correspondent so
Adam the pacific carry yes you see your European Union correspondent see as be from comic strip
block.com by the way I love the return of the Charlie comic strip you made head over to
comicstripblock.com have a look at that it was uh yeah scary funny and yet strangely accurate so
recently I was in Brussels copy that of Europe you know yeah yeah I know as we're all the
bastards hang out in bruises and in their Instagram on the top of the Atomium the menu was
only in French I couldn't get one in German all in English yeah the Atomium isn't that the
uh the building that looks like uh like an atom with all the balls connected with with sticks
like an airplane what do we call those uh Tinker toys that's it another example since 2012
the president of European Union Parliament will be a German guy Martin Schultz but uh Tiel 2012
it is a Polish guy a Yezzy Buzek and Buzek speaks English German Russian Polish but the
French is our first in him and our first in this uh EU foreign affairs riksann Catherine Achtorn
to learn French I think the French you have too much power don't you think that they have too
much influence in you you you know you guys voted for it oh I'm sorry you didn't vote for it
through the Lisbon Treaty what am I thinking let me tell you what's going on in Europe and uh and by
the way this is all being done with the help of uh of Goldman Sachs uh fine United States
based institution I won't say found it but based institution um so as you know uh around 1980
when this whole European Union things started money really started flowing into Greece and Greece
was actually was was doing okay you know there was yeah there were high taxes I don't think the
the the the tax collection rate was that high but really there's only about 20 families that
ran the country and they ran it pretty well uh you know if you know if that's what you want
and you like to be in Greece and I think most people were happy there but once the free money is you
are pointed out on an earlier report to comics or blogger once the free money from the EU started
pouring in it started coming into these Greek families uh the oligarchy I guess should call it
and uh well you can only imagine what happened you know there was uh the brand new airport was
built the company that bid on the airport to bid to build it for 220 million euros it wound up
costing 750 well you can only imagine what happened with the the stray 500 million euros you know
of course people put all in their pocket so lots of money was coming in and uh subsequently
all of this money needs you know you got they got to do something with it so they put it in
Switzerland and another fine places around the world but also brought in all of the American
franchises Kentucky fried chicken and uh McDonald's and oh and let's not forget Ikea just to bring
you know some European franchises in uh pushing out the little guy obviously the little uh
little shop on the corner and uh and the government started borrowing money like nobody else's
business because they could and because it was available not that it was really necessary
and so now they've uh got to pay back I don't know like uh 40 billion euros minimum but probably
260 billion euros in total and what really went wrong is that the and this is the same thing that
happened I think with our our financial problems here in the United States the the baby boomers that
means our parents um and I'm literally on the edge of the baby baby boomer generation but let's
just say our parents you know what they really had to do to secure their pensions and their retirement
funding is they had to sell us their homes and uh you know and pass everything down to the next
generation but the bubble burst you know people got too greedy it didn't happen everything the
devalued deflated and of course all these pension funds they don't actually have all your money
uh they're you know they're speculating with it it's like the social security fund in America you know
it's like they don't actually have all that money and a big pile that they're going to start
dishing out no they're using it for other things and they know they have to pay out a certain amount
to X number of people who retire at age 65 this year and they'll be a little bit more next year
and the year after that and of course it's accelerating because the baby boomers are going
but what happened is uh the financial institutions were about to fall over and that's this happening
now in in Europe Greece uh sure Italy will be actually united kingdom is the one you really have
to watch out for they're really in trouble and there's two ways to handle it one is you can do what
Ireland did and said all right uh austerity measures measures uh everybody retired three years
later and uh we're going to cut your wages and raise your taxes or you know you get a bailout
so France and Germany what they're most worried about is their pension funds because if these
companies go bankrupt which is not a problem by the way it won't bring down the entire world these
companies are going bankrupt people lose money but who are the people they're going to lose the money
it is the baby boomers and their pensions so they're going to saddle us up with all this
debt and all this crap so that they can retire happily and I have seen this I have seen
there was someone in our office who um she'll go unnamed uh but she was uh just into her 60s
and the attitude of the baby boomers of our parents and you know you can hate your parents a little
bit that's allowed I think from time to time it's like I just want my health care I don't care
about anybody else I don't care about the young kids I deserve I want and that's really the
problem that's all I deserve I should have safe life a fair life everything should go my way
well guess what it just doesn't happen that way all right
I'ma get in it's a daily day I'ma get in it's a daily way they're coming for you everyday
while I'll say the truth I'm a holiday the army recruiters in the parking lot
hustling the kids dead juggle in part listen young man listen to my pain gonna make you money gonna
make you a land by my mom here's what you get on M16 and I can't love this you're my
common with one less leg but this thing I surely keep a bullet at your chest so come on
come on sign up come on this one's nothing like the Vietnam except for the bullets except for the
you that's gone so we keep it on to you coming home
higher by a fire by a fire by a light of the light of fire by a fire so we keep it on
yeah every president tell me if you will how many people those are smart bomb kill
how many of them do you think we got the general says we never miss a shot and we never ever ever
keep our body count we kill and so efficiently we can't keep count in the afternoon the
rebel still fighting or being fields keep on providing the best heroin their money can buy
and nobody knows where some are being hiding the press conferences keep on lying
like we don't know so we keep it on to you coming home
higher by a fire by a light of the light of the fire by a fire so we keep it on
you coming home higher by a fire by a light of the light of the fire by a fire
yeah so we say indian indian number and machine guns on a new transit line the war for oil is
a war for the beast the war on terror is a war on peace telling you they gonna protect you
and telling you if they support the truth and don't let them fool you with their milk and honey
no they only want your money one step forward and two step back one step forward and two step back
why the veterans getting no respect ptsd and a broken back take a look at where your money's
gone seen take a look at what they spend it on no excuses no illusions light up your light up
bring home so we keep it on to you coming home higher by a fire by a light of the light of the
fire by a fire so we keep it on to you coming home higher by a fire by a light of the light of the
fire by a fire so we keep it on to you coming home higher by a fire by a light of the
fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire by a fire
not a
it.
My cof argentine spearhead onidy source code eight twenty four a slow small is the message as always in the music
The less.
mention, uh, not unimportant, that, uh,
John C. Devorick and I are really on, uh,
on a mission to build out no agenda stream.com,
Daily Source Code now a part of that.
It seems to be, uh, working out okay for me to do two shows a week.
Not quite sure if that's going to work out every single week.
So maybe even more, uh, will be daily.
Now probably not, but I still like the Daily Source Code moniker.
Do you have more things coming on to the stream, though?
And that's where we need your support.
If you would go to no agenda stream.com,
that's where, of course, you can see all of our sustaining producers is a link right there.
If you want to donate, it's Devorick.org slash NAS.
Your support will help get more, more Charlie's on the air,
more no agendas on the air and eventually build a stream,
which, uh, you can just listen to all the time.
I've been, uh, field testing this myself.
Of course, now I have a car for those of you have been listening to no agenda.
You know, that, uh, I bought a, uh, a 1999 range rover.
The urban assault vehicle, which I can always use for our getaway,
because it'll be easy to drive over dead bodies and rubble when the shit hits the fan.
Just in case, um, but what's really working well is listening to the stream on the iPhone.
You know, particularly because it's, uh, well, it's still,
it's rather, uh, low bit rate, uh, it's the same bit rate.
You're hearing the show at right now, but you can kind of just, you know,
flick it on to name whenever you want.
You know, there's always something playing.
Uh, I've got, uh, John's interludes.
He's working on a new one, by the way.
Uh, we've got, uh, Devorick Horowitz unplugged, uh, the daily source code,
no agenda, looking to build it up more and more.
And I'm seeing on average, on average mind you, uh, now it's not spectacular yet.
But it's, uh, it's about 100 people at any given moment or listening to the stream.
I think that's pretty amazing.
Particularly when you take into account that the New York Times, right?
I asked someone this question, what do you think the circulation is of the New York Times?
Uh, and you'll hear anywhere from out 10 million, 20 million.
No, actually it's about 900,000.
900,000.
So we don't have that far to go, particularly where the beautiful advent of
having the delayed mechanism of podcasts for a lot of these shows and the fact that radio sucks.
Radio everywhere just sucks.
It's two minutes of radio programming for, for a minute of commercial.
Just blows.
Yeah, there's some good stuff.
I'm not going to say everything is horrible, but, you know, thank you very much.
Clear channel, but thank you Internet for blowing it all up.
For, for making people roll up stations have one guy sitting in one market talking to five.
It doesn't work that way anymore.
Those days are over.
Newspapers are next and then it'll be television.
And then it's going to be really bad for a while.
They'll be really, it's really going to suck for everybody.
And then I think stations and initiatives like no agenda stream.com will eventually
start to, to the garner a lot of, a lot of momentum.
It's, you know, a hundred, yeah, it's nothing yet.
Of course, the overall audience of these shows combined is much larger.
But when you can just flick something on or something comes on at a certain moment during the day,
you watch, you watch how this is going to change.
And I sometimes in five years ahead of the, ahead of the curve.
That's okay.
What else am I going to do?
I got nothing better to do.
I don't know, Adam, I don't know if you remember me, but this is Tokyo Dan.
Hey, Tokyo.
Do you remember me?
I wonder if you're still pissed at me for what I said a few years ago about the pod,
safe music network.
You know, I heard this comment when I was loading it up.
I'm like, I can't, I don't know what you're talking about, Tokyo Dan.
I, of course, welcome back.
Good to hear you on the show.
But I don't idea what you're talking about, man.
So whatever it was, yeah, I'm still pissed.
Hell yeah.
Anyway, um, I'm glad you're back with the source code is nice to,
hear it, it sounds just like the early days of the source code before you became awakened
and started talking about all the conspiracy stuff, which, eh.
Well, hold on, let's not call it conspiracy.
Well, actually, you can call it conspiracy.
I don't care what you want to call it.
You mean when I actually started understanding how media really works and what they were really doing
and how I was complicit in the entire system.
You mean those days?
Yeah, absolutely.
It's only gotten worse than.
But yeah, I, I feel you.
And it wasn't easy.
It wasn't easy for me.
It wasn't easy for the people around me.
And I don't think it was easy for the chuckleheads, either.
Like, oh, oh, what's wrong with that?
I'm, let's look up the definition of the schizophrenia here.
Sometimes like to hear, but not all the time, I kind of, I tend to agree with what you say
and I do listen to the noise in every once in a while.
And by the way, that's cool.
You don't have to listen to every single episode or have to listen to it.
There's no rule that says you have to listen to no agenda in its entirety.
Check it anytime you want.
It's kind of funny, though.
How people are so willing to sit in a dark room with a hundred other strangers,
spend $50 for the pleasure of sitting in a seat for an hour and a half
completely silently watching a movie.
You know, you think that you can listen to 45 minutes of the source code
or two hours of no agenda actually learn something, not be interrupted by commercials.
And you can fart whenever you want.
But I'd prefer more of a tech podcast that listen to a lot of tech podcasts
and just, you know, some music and stuff like that.
Just like the daily source code used to be.
And that's what it sounds like you're doing now.
But really got me interested was when you're talking about developing an iPhone
app, which is really cool because that's what I've been doing for about the last few months.
I want a bottle kind of books and everything bought some macintoshes
and I've been working with XCode and studied Objective Sea
and getting back into programming.
Yeah, you know, it sounds like you kind of on the same track as I am.
And this started for me also a couple of months ago.
I got to say, you know, for me there's almost no difference in the amount of effort
I have to put into responding to a lawyer's letter.
As there is to programming some functionality in Objective Sea.
And I have to say, I love this XCode thing because they set up with an application
that's kind of bare bones and ready to go.
And you just start copying and pasting and adjusting.
And of course, there's absolute truth in programming.
Because if you miss type something, one word, one, you know,
semi colon or anything like that, it's just not going to work.
But it's, yeah, I'm amazed that how much I could actually accomplish and get done.
And I'm very excited about my iPhone app.
Still not released.
I haven't even submitted it to the iTunes store yet.
And I can't tell you about it because it doesn't do it justice.
I've done something that I believe no one has thought of yet.
I can't even, I don't even want to tell you that.
I don't want to say anything until you actually have it in your hands.
When you have it in your hands, you're going to go, oh shit.
Okay, I get it.
Now I understand why he couldn't talk about it.
Go by the way, the iPhone app that I'm developing will be free.
And I'm looking forward to the episode, the third episode of the new source code.
When you talk more about your app and your programming.
I have to hear more about that.
And as far as podcasting goes, your comments about the expectations,
you know, not living up to the expectations I agree for there.
It's kind of a pipe dream.
Love people expected too much.
I have an podcast that's for almost a year and a half.
No, and I don't think I'll ever go back.
Anyway, I'm looking forward to the next show.
Take good news.
Hi, Tokyo Dan.
Thank you so much, man.
Good to hear from you.
I don't really have time to open up phone lines like I had previously,
and to go through all voice comments.
So if you do have something you'd like to contribute to the show,
just maybe the best thing is to drop it off at drop.io.
It's a free service, pretty good service.
Got a lot of, you know, I love what those guys do.
And they've got a lot of, with bang stuff,
but it's also just handy, just to drop it in.
I think I also have a drop box, actually.
That might, that might even be better.
Adam at mevio.com.
Not what you're, how you share the information about your drop box.
But let me see.
I'm looking at it right now.
Do I have anything new in there?
No.
I don't think so.
I think you can just drop stuff in there.
If you know my email address, I'm not quite sure.
So that's a way to get it to me.
Just, but basically just put a,
an MP3 together and throw it off to me.
All right.
Moving up, we're actually coming up on one hour.
And I have a five o'clock appointment in an hour and a half with,
ooh, yes.
With a tax person.
We're coming up on that time as well.
And you know me, Mr. Last Minute Man.
Adam coming.
Take a sauce code.
All right.
Crank them up.
This one's from Marcus Kauch Singh as he sends it to me.
This will really put you in a great weekend mood.
I'm sure, man.
Yeah.
Power Man 5000.
Do your thing.
I'm the turnings from our friends.
Hey.
You.
Yeah.
Have, you.
You.
Are you kill?
Does all you.
Does all you suck?
No.
Does all you scar?
Does all you resist?
It's time to turn it on again.
I've been laughing dim.
When they tell you that you say?
Just be on me, just be on me, just be on me, just be on me, just be on me, just be on me
Just be on me, just be on me, just be on me
Just be on me, just be on me, just be on me, just be on me, just be on me
Just be on me, just be on me, just be on me, just be on me
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, Razzle, R
on the full bar Friday the source code episode 824 i'm not quite sure when we're going to hit it on
when we're going to hit another source code next week monday i'm going to up north to
flying into oakland going to pick up the delta siera which is oakland north there's a southern
part of the airport where the big planes come in and then the northern part going to meet captain Dave there
we're going to fire her up and she's been sitting there for a number of months so we're pretty
sure the battery's going to be dead we're going to fire her up and then we're going to fly her down
i think the sand hose is a as the plane has to have an annual before April 1st otherwise it won't
be allowed to fly at all so that kind of sucks because that's actual cost involved and it's been
on the market for a good six weeks now without a couple nipples maybe but you know it's like boats
you know it's not a really good time to be selling an aircraft but there you go i don't have enough
time to fly and a part of my plan for 2010 was to have that is my backup so i can really focus 100
percent on a no agenda stream dot com and on the shows that go along with that so what that means
for everything else well you make up your own mind you can certainly see through the veil
so i'll talk to you get on sunday for early service no agenda around nine o'clock sometime next week
for another charlie and until then my friends please live your life with passion and as long as
it lasts enjoy your freedom another fine medial presentation stick it in your ear