Delta Sierra Charlie 834, Food Bar Friday.
We're 16 months and seven.
We've been showing five lines of time.
Turn.
The 21st century of radio stars here.
We don't need us.
We can't see any of us.
On the knowledge and the strength of our podcasting.
Here's the bedroom curry.
All the babies who are Friday.
Everything's fucked up.
You don't repair.
Let's get the chance of it.
Not in the way that we hold in it.
It's not in the way you say you can.
It's not in the way you've been treating the friends.
It's not in the way that you stand here.
It's not in the way you look all the things that you said it through.
All the life.
Love is that always on time.
It's not in the way that you're told that it's weird.
It's not in the way you say you're my blue.
It's not in the way that you came back to me.
It's not in the way that your life's set free.
It's not in the way you look all the things that you said it through.
All the life.
Love is that always on time.
It's not in the way you look all the things that you said it through.
All the life.
Love is that always on time.
It's not in the way you say you're my blue.
It's not in the way that you came back to me.
It's not in the way that your love's set free.
It's not in the way you look all the things that you said it through.
All the life.
Love is that always on time.
When you want to chase me down, I don't know you
I can't just hold them cold
And so soon
I don't want to be here, like a close thing in the air
I don't want to know you're the stars you've reached my head
And I don't want to know why life's just so unfair
And I don't want to know you
I can't just hold them cold
Yeah, you're so damn cool
Cool, and those who are here inside me
Who knows if I'm here or else
Who knows what you're inside me
Who knows if I'm here or else I'm not
Guys, why are you so
We can't leave forever
Everyone's pretending to be ресpitated
Now you people are dead, don't look in need today
All in your brain, but you'll be me
And you walk in, you don't die in the rain
With the way, the arms will sink in the night
Yeah, what is mine in my brain?
There's the full bar Friday, this is the Daily Source Code
A 3-4, we're one or not nicotine, caffeine, aspirin and coldine
And boy, am I feeling full bar and everybody?
For whole, we're gonna be doing it all, request later on
So get ready, of course I believe the ugly kid Joe damn cool
Was from the open source Daily Source Code, which rolled out last Friday
When time Warner Cable was muffled by head again
The Dow was down, the Euro's down, cold is up
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
He gives to me, but when I took a good look at me
And what is the prize?
The stick of my eyes, good oldies and black
And I remember someone who was taking a two by two
And lately I've become the one who looked at you too
There was a flag flag, the one my morning
There was a flag flag, the one my day
There was a flag flag, whatever thing you're running
I was walking back once again, flag flag
flag flag
I walked in the day, my usual way
Looking for a two by four
And calling my crew, I could see you
Or maybe I just wanted to
And I remember the time when the sunlight fell on my head
And lately I've become the one who looked at you too
There was a flag flag, the one my morning
There was a flag flag, the one my day
There was a flag, the one my day
There was a flag, whatever thing you're running
I was walking back once again, flag flag
I was walking back once again
I was walking back once again, flag flag flag
And we were walking back once again
And I remember the day when I saw the mask on my face
And I knew that it was time to put the thing in his face
I put the black flag on my morning, I put the black flag on my day
I put the black flag on everything around it
I was walking backwards again, black flag on my morning
Black flag on my day, I put the black flag on everything around it
Black flag on my day, put the black flag on everything around it
I was walking backwards again
King's Ex, black flag on my morning, yeah, that was one of those all day for me
All kinds of crappy, as lawyer talks, starting at 8 a.m
For me, I hate that shit
We've totally got to roll out some love later on during today's Charlie
Cause man, I'm in need of some of it
If you're listening to this on the stream and no agenda stream.com
Log into the chats, join the party, no agenda chat.com
That's where it's all going down, looking for the porn stars
And all my friends are on board on the chat
You know the name, we call them the Magnificent
Seven
Four pairs, knock on my jeans and your bankers too
Let's get up there and learn those words
When I'm in the crazy team, what's your song or what's it?
I am an event of the M2, turning out a bugle loop
Get you up by the guest, but I'm long can't you keep it up
We can make hold up, can't be so late
So cheap and we'll fall in pain don't drop in the insets
We can just bounce next to your pants
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, there is no TD for us, they are all tied, they are like the
guys, they are tied, they are doing the right to grab the ball, it's easy.
Why don't we have friends to take?
But cups can chip things on the pavement.
Now the news is not to addiction.
You're the man, you're the bitch, the bitch.
It's all your monster.
She's a lot, so it's too few.
Don't get inside the ham, he's gone.
Bitch, a bitch in the car.
My cowboy's stupid TV left.
You let it!
Whoa!
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
You let it, stop, stop.
Oh!
So get back to work and sweat someone.
Because someone will think and forget out the dog.
This no good for man.
To work you hate your skin.
You stop, he's wixing, sweetly, sweetly.
You're the fuck, you're the sweet.
But it can't what it's you.
You let it, stop, stop, stop.
You let it, stop, stop.
Take your car.
I don't like you.
Don't you have a stop.
Lock it up the start, get your car, I don't care
Tell the marks, a fire with English came to the ticket at the 711
I'm so screwed, but he had sex, and those living, and this is a revenge
What have we got?
Yeah, what have we got?
Yeah, a lot more of that came from today on the Charlie.
The clash, the magnificent seven, got to talk about all kinds of things
going on here at the Hilltop Watch Tower Crackpot Command Center
But first we must recognize that day it is too late.
One, two, three.
I'm to eat a son.
Can you provide some?
I need some emotional rescue.
Spin one of those days.
It's kinda crappy.
We're gonna put the knife on soon, let the knife go
We're gonna change your mind, so we're gonna do
We're doing deep in, you got it out
We're just gonna pull the knife, which makes house
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Don't you know how this is, what never happened to me, it's okay
Just let the knife disappear, it's okay
I've been your savings, the best and true, I come to you, I'm selfish, no rescue
I come to you, no rescue
Come here, I need that knife that's gone
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, you know? E, Incorrect, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, there.unky new one, oh right by, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah do yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah
Baby man
But I was crying
Love a child
Okay, I was crying
So I love a child
But when I'm in my mind
I'm in my mind
So silent in the night
Sistered in
I'm in my mind
I've been asleep
Snitting bags that are true
I'm under your emotion
Rest you
Under your emotion
I'm in my mind
Yeah
It's you
I'm in my mind
Oh
Yeah, as you quickly mind
Tonight
With every night
I would be your night
In shining armor
Coming to your emotion of rest you
You would be mine
All of me
I would be your night
Sunshine
Oh
Alrighty
This is
Maybe it's time to tell you my rolling stone story
I am hyped up man
This mix of caffeine, esterine, codine, and nicotine
And of course with an oatmeal throw
Pretty amazing
Here we go
So
I met Jagger a couple times
When they released that horrible album
It included the Harlem shuffle
I went to London to interview them
And the time I was dating a girl at the office
who later went on to become quite a big star
In the Netherlands on television
Anyway, so we're waiting there
There's one of these press junks
It's like going on for hours
And we're all set up in a hotel room with a camera crew
No one shows up
And like 130 in the morning
It's Woody and Keith
They come rolling in
Literally hammered out of their minds
And first thing to say
We got to go into the bathroom
Okay, and so they start snorting co-graph of a bowie knife
Which was interesting to say at least
Add a good little interview there
And these are early days
Very, very early days
I'm talking 83 maybe
Something like that
And it was like hey man, we got to get a picture of you
And Ron wouldn't keep Richard so
Yeah, we could put that in the newspaper
And announce the interview
And it was like oh no one brought a camera
At the time I had one of those very first co-dact disc cameras
Remember those?
We put like this stupid disc in and it gave you the really shitty quality
I guess my mom had given to me for my birthday
And so I got one of my briefcase
So I whip out the co-dact disc to take a couple pictures
And my producer takes the disc with the film
Back to the
The state government controlled run press center
Because this is all public broadcasting back in the day
And for it to be developed
And then they're going to go you know take those pictures
And put them in the newspaper
And that's when I had one of these four had slapping moments
And I'm like oh crap
I took some pictures of that girl on the co-dact disc
Kind of as a fluke right because I didn't think I'd ever get the film
Developed anyway because there was no one could even develop it
But these were like compromising pictures
So we had to break into the state government controlled run
PR department to go retrieve the film
In the middle of the night
And I still have the pictures
This one's by request
Uncle Sam
Brother Ali
I think you'll dig it
We're going to see if
Tony Jerome and the bag maybe work to sit out
Straighten me out right away
I like it so far man
Yeah
Brother I'm digging it
Come on
Let's go
Welcome to the United States
Land of the sea
Home of the slave
Grand Imperial Guard with a dollar is sacred
Let's do the ship for your come on
Smoke a mirror straight to the stars
Stolen for the cross in the name of God
Bloodsheds in the side, creeping in broad
But instead of pages that are all good and long
The co-cut in a latched key child ran away
One day and started acting sad
King away the wild things are daddy's proud
But the woman in tired and passed it down
Him poured it in torture
The work falls to never heal the wounds
A ship to curse on
That a grown-up girl like a nation
Holdin' up an artist
For the part of David, can you feel?
Nothing can save you
You questioned the rain, you get rushed
And it rained up
Frist rays, but I must be insane
Because I can't figure single God
Tamp waiting to change
Who belongs to the United States
Land of the sea, home of the slave
The grand Imperial Guard with a dollar is sacred
And power is in charge
Land of the sea, home of the slave
The grand Imperial Guard with a dollar is sacred
And power is in charge
Home of power to the fat and lazy
The fuck you will blame me
And ride it and hit me home
Only two generations away
From the world's most despicable slave
Or if you trade
I and it's no many ways to the greater human being
That it can't be changed to this day
Legacy, so ingrained in the wave
That we think we no longer need change
To be enslaved
And all this is a shame
To dislike, the overseer's even got a rate
To long the way
Because the children can escape from the pain
And they bond with the pause in the hatred
And that veins
Giants separate the man from his soul
You only strengthen him and lose your own
We're shoot that fucker
If you walk and hit a frog
Mind him that this is my own now gone
We're welcome to the United States
Land of the fleets
I don't want to say
Grand Imperial Guard with a dollar is sacred
And power is in charge
Welcome to the United States
Land of fleets
I don't want to say
Grand Imperial Guard with a dollar is sacred
Hold on to me when I have heard
You give money to the bombs
On the corner with a sign
Bleeding from their guns
Something about you don't support a crack here
What's the thing happens to the money from your tax?
Shit the governments to outing
With a built-in dollar, a weak kill
Prown people, habit
He's even if you ain't on the front line
When that's a yell crunch time
You right back at it
Lay look at how you bustle in backwards
Head to into the year and up
What they subtracted
Three out as well, must your salary pay for that man
Man, that's a sad man
See the big ass plasma to see
Where they may damn bad, the point to damn camera
Only a poor question's get answered
I'm stangeless, tough for that national end
Welcome to the United States
Land of fleets
I don't want to say
Grand Imperial Guard with a dollar is sacred
And power is in charge
Welcome to the United States
Land of fleets
And power with a dollar is sacred
And power is in charge
Long to equality
Lol
Do you understand
Man, we passed away
I'm wondering when you get upset
And the other thing is
What exactly you have?
Is anything to say
I'm worried about age
And I want to omdat
That if I don't get upset
Is it mean to piss off your bad
Hey, I did have some good stuff happen this week, um, my of course, uh, or late last week,
idea of time to talk about it because of the, uh, they see my cable went out on what
Thursday.
Yeah, right after the show, actually, right after, uh, no agenda, even on the upload,
I wound up uploading through three G.
Tethered on my jailbroken iPhone, uh, but, um, uh, my, uh, iPhone app or iPod Touch app
launched.
It's called The Big App Show and, uh, holy moly, I got like 70,000 installs in that
first week.
Of course, I was somewhere below the fold on new and noteworthy, and, uh, that really helped.
And shit is working.
I'm so, I'm so happy.
It's like, uh, I can't believe it.
Now if only I could get a little more promotion for this thing.
If I could go 10 fold, then I could make an actual business out of it.
I just love it, though.
It's kind of like, you know, being an app J. So now instead of promoting records and promoting
apps, and it's cool.
I get to pick some cool stuff, and you instead of, uh, musicians behind it, you've
got, uh, engineers and, uh, developers, and I don't know the sum above the just kind of,
I'd like it.
It kind of strikes a chord.
And, uh, folks who are using it definitely like it, so, um, uh, any ideas for promoting
it, you know, it's like it's really hard to do SEO or search engine optimization on an iPhone
app.
It's like everyone on their mother is trying to do that shit, so, uh, I just got to figure
it out.
It's weird.
I have no idea how it works.
I see apps that are hot and have like three reviews, uh, and don't even have, uh, five
stars and, you know, they're considered to be hot and like, well, how does that work?
So I just really don't know how it works.
But anyway, I'm very excited about that and I've been, uh, pretty busy, uh, putting
together, uh, new episodes as I call them.
So I want to think everyone for the encouragement along the way.
It's been a pretty fun ride and, uh, looking more, uh, looking to do some awesome stuff
with that.
Now, the, um, yeah, thank you very much for a pimping big app show on Twitter.
I appreciate that.
Um, so last time we had the daily source code football Friday, it got into a really
cool place where everyone was like throwing out song ideas and it's just, it was, I was really
into the mood, man.
It just really kind of hit me and so I, we haven't had a lot of suggestions coming
yet on the chat room, but I'm hoping that'll come through.
Uh, I probably have another half hour music and a couple things that I've just been collecting
over the past week and a half that I want to play for you, including a nice little
mashup.
The odds of the airways is landed and he's sounding good to me.
This is the day he saw Scott with Adam Curry.
He rocks burning down the street, the rainbow went out of the window sound with a sign
of speech.
She and guns ready to go.
Are you ready?
Hey, are you ready for this?
Are you hanging on the edge of your seat?
I'll have no way in the bullets to the side of the beat.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, nothing to do, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you. No, no, no, no-no, no, no, no, no,
I don't have to watch my stuff
You'll fired the bands above you
Yes, we fired the bands above you
I mean now I'm pumped up
I'm not an animal just fast anymore
Now I'm pumped up
And now I'm pumped up
No, I'm didn't start
Now I'm pumped up
If maybe somebody has gone to the erle
I don't know what to do!
I don't know!
Man, I kinda liked that when I came across a nice little mashup for you!
Okay, let's do something a little lighthearted, shall we?
As the requests are starting to come in and know agendachat.com.
I've got some good ones there!
Hey, Mr. Oil, is he your birthday?
Did I miss something here?
Pretty bad if I did!
That would be a shame, wouldn't it?
In the sunshine, when we're young as around with the men, it's a shame
In the way you hurt me, it's a shame
When we're young as around with the men, I'm sitting all alone
On the telephone, waiting for your call
When you don't call, it's a shame
When you miss around with the men, it's a shame
In the way you hurt me, it's a shame
When you miss around with the men, you're like a child
When you're young as around with the men, I'm sitting all alone
On the telephone, waiting for your call
When you lose me, that's your truth
In the way you want it's a shame
When you're young as around with the men, it's a shame
It's such a shame
The way you mess around with the mess
I tried to speak with you
So you're not so true
But you won't appreciate the love we try to make
All it took got to be a shame
The way you mess around with the mess
I tried to speak with you
So you're not so true
But you won't appreciate the love we try to make
All it took got to be a shame
The way you mess around with the mess
I tried to speak with you
And you won't appreciate the love we try to make
The way you mess around with you, make it all
It's a shame that way you hurt me
Oh, it's a shame that you made it
The way you mess around with you, make it all
You got my heart in danger
And I'm not afraid of it
I just can't make up my own
Look at this
Oh, oh, oh, oh
It's a shame, it's a shame that way you hurt me
That song just makes me happy every single time I hear it
The spinners, it's a shame the way you run around with my heart
On Dayby Source code 834
It's the footballer Friday, just in the Charlie
A couple of requests that came in throughout the week
From my buddy Werner, who works
Let's just say he works at a major airport somewhere
Well, let's call it Gibbonation Lowlands
And he actually sent me the track because it wasn't available on iTunes strangely enough
So I asked him to bootleg it for me
He said
And by the way, as you know, moms have priority on this program
You guys have been with me there through us some tough times there says my mom passed away about half a year ago
And for some reason whenever I hear this song
I always have to think of her this some kind of awesome energy and it and I really would like to hear it on the Charlie
And of course, we will comply gladly and I have to say it is a song that makes
everybody happy, Robbie Williams
I don't know how to say it, sorry kids we got no replay
I got more than I need when you let's shout out on our own
Are you out of my mind?
Get me with the sound down from the sky
We got to get out of the sky
What did we do when we're due to that?
And if you got no love for me then I'll say goodbye
If you let it change
Don't let love be over the change
I got more than I need when you let's shout out on our own
Are you out of my mind?
Get me with the sound down from the sky
And of course, we will comply gladly and I have to say goodbye
I got more than I need when you let's shout out on our own
Are you out of my mind?
Get me with the sound down from the sky
And of course, we will comply gladly and I have to say goodbye
If you want to come make a stand
It's when it's in your head
We both shall be loud
If you let it change
Don't let love be over the change
I got more than I need when you let's shout out on our own
Are you out of my mind?
Get me with the sound down from the sky
And of course, we will comply gladly and I have to say goodbye
If you let it change
Don't let love be over the change
I got more than I need when you let's shout out on our own
Are you out of my mind?
Get me with the sound down from the sky
Guys, definitely a musical genius Robby Williams
Let love be your energy
Special request from Warner there and get donation lowlands
And finally some good songs coming through
So I'm taking the request of no agenda chat dot com
On iTunes or as I mistakenly typed in the chat room
I tubes doing that as fast as I can
Here's something that someone pointed out to me
As a song that was done 25 years ago
The message still works today
It's about Afghanistan
The place where we ship in drugs from the US military doing that
On secret cargo flights
It's all about the oil out there
Not about some stupid dickhead in the cave
Called Osama bin Laden
The big scam
Listen to paid vacation
Whoo
Oh
Go
Golden glass
Moxer
SIt out
Know the coil
I scoop thats back
놓 Tte
Get your manipulation cates
It's the best, it's up, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's
up, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, y'all, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, the devils are in a maze! It's not here. It's not here, it's down, it'sbout us. It's just a slide. It's all over and you get away from me. It's not there anymore, it's down. It's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it's down, it
Oh, take your sauce cold
And I'm coming
I know, oh, oh, oh, oh
Gats, you're carrying sauce
I don't go in
You know, they say he'll have no theory like a woman's score
So vengeful and mother hurt has been done wrong
And I think she's sick
Yeah, she's keeping up live on her nerves
Trimble along both lines ready to drop
And in time city you build this thin
And for us to partner, we build these towers
A battle in filtre more
Spoon out of the moment
They both deposit the children
A drop in bottles, the risk you reach
A poverty side, under the collar
Taking prayer out of schools
And we try to race, college, creation is
Emerson, the theory of evolution
Airwater land, mind, body and soul
Pollution kids, stepping on land, mind,
Smoors, we all lose and we chase and fall
Sighters and racing from our bibles
The gold and rules are youth
And we come in more suicide, or who teaches them
You are not in a wonder, they want to fight
You race, my hip, but crit you feel like
With a skyscraper's graffiti to sky
And replace a satellite's graffiti to mine
So children with your man-made love
With graffiti to work all us out of hiding on the wall
We got ABC, NBC, MTV, DMTV, DMTV, DMTV, DMTV
HSPSL, A&E, STC, MP3, MCC, D-I-C
N-R-A-G-O-P-A-D-D
The fight for free speech, lack of responsibility
These are positions of power and our net
For knockers, because in the whole career
The next knock at the door can be tapped
The caber is to rent the white house
And overseas, race and separate
This vicious militia's mood is the Hindus
The Muslims, the Christians
Cut it be your biggest marry
Your wrist language, your wrist oil
That imported them home with its leg
Anguish, so cars can deplete the ozone
On highways, the scratch across the land
We're Indians once raised families
We're in denial, the world is afraid
And you say there's no more slaves
Be the land
With skyscrapers, graffiti to sky
And replace the satellites, graffiti to mine
The children with your man-made love
With graffiti to work all us out of hiding on the wall
We're Indians, NBC, MTV, DMTV, DMTV, DMTV
We're addicted to addiction
We did live in a fiction for money, public respect
The army got to go kill the yonder contracts
We'll let the blinds kill
The sort of morbid hate in this picture
That I just painted isn't a fit for me
A hand I realized just how tainted
I think it really is well in New York
When I saw a teenager being arrested
For tagging a fucking wall
Graffiti to land
With skyscrapers, graffiti to sky
And replace the satellites, graffiti to mine
The children with your man-made love
With graffiti to work all us out of hiding on the wall
We're fighting on the wall
With graffiti to land
With skyscrapers, graffiti to sky
And replace the satellites, graffiti to mine
The children with your man-made love
With graffiti to work all us out of hiding on the wall
graffiti to land
With graffiti to land
With graffiti to mine
The children with your man-made love
With graffiti to work all us out of hiding on the wall
With graffiti to land
It was actually pretty therapeutic here for me
It's good I get everything out of my system
Before we do no agenda
So it won't go like freaking nuts and shit
By the way, I've stopped, actually listing everything in the show notes
For the daily source code because I figured these days
It's so incredibly easy to just use shazam or soundhound
Or something like that
And you can just go get the songs yourself
It's like show notes for almost old fashioned these days
And I do have to admit I was having dinner the other night
And I shazam this song
Just because it was such a groove
I'm like crap I haven't heard this in ages, man
Remember the chic chair?
Do it all together now
You're listening to other colors
On the dirty source code
The chic chair
The other body style
All right, everybody is old enough to remember that song in the chat room, raise your hand
without talking.
Oh crap, you know that stupid dance we used to do along with a song man?
Well, that's not bad to have a little bit of nostalgia on the show from time to time.
Perhaps I can take you back with another song from the soundtrack of your lives.
Strawberry letter 23.
And without one.
And the DJ used to throw this shit on, we go nuts.
Yeah, the one in his face, because he's got the girl made from his ass.
Time to go back and beat him, make it reggae.
Mix it with your fun.
Brother John's another source code from our Friday.
Hello, my love.
I heard you kissed me.
The red magic said to play in the air.
Look too.
All through the morning rain I gave.
The sun doesn't shine.
The rain goes in waterfalls.
Run through my hand.
In the garden, I see.
What's the purple shower belt?
The blue one's burning.
The color's interesting.
Pretty music.
So happy.
I love the blue flowers.
They come from my channel.
Feel sun shines.
I'm cooking.
A playground for a laugh.
If you try to ask.
Or is it cool?
If you don't even know CB.
I'm going to be with my baby.
I'm free.
Fly to the home.
All around the city.
Stay with them.
And look at this green.
See speakers of the sky.
We have never been close.
As long as you can't breathe.
Don't fly high.
Up in the sand.
From here we'll start the baby.
We'll let it run.
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, this video is used to murder you through the.
The
This reminds me of time.
I want you to help and please.
If you're feeling hot first, I'm my shirt.
Dying with droid, droid, hiding cold sweats,
Quivering and seeing you all.
Throwing more or so, you need me naked.
Let me wait for this doctor to try.
All you can do is do it.
Change my attention, going to change the show.
Throwing more or so, you need me naked.
Let me wait for this doctor to try.
All you can do is do it.
Throwing more or so, you need me naked.
Change my attention, going to change the show.
Throwing more and so, you need me, naked.
Throwing more or so, you need me naked.
I don't know for some reason I'm just not feeling it I'm looking at the chat room today and
there's so much talk about what's going on in the world and about the golf and oil and
they say I don't know is it's a weird vibe there's oh I think the world in general is a kind
of an a weird vibe today you know maybe just the whole past week or something and of course
say Europe is starting to fall apart or what we know is the European Union better known as the
United States of Europe the euro now dipping below one dollar and twenty cents one nineteen is the
final closing price for the week it's just not bold very well I think it could all the way
down to to parody now with a dollar one to one so of course time to see what's really going on
the United States of Europe with our European correspondents comic strip comic strip comic strip
come on in my friend in the morning to other mixed related carry since be here your EU
correspondent lawyers when I was living in Rome Italy a patron visiting in Vatican the Pope liked
dope I was dropping by to Palazzo the Conservatory where original EU granting treaty was signed
signed in the same city where the Roman Empire was granted coincidence I think not EU is
Roman Empire to zero and I think it will also fall not just because of financial coetter
of you know who but because EU politicians penalized citizens by savings and austerity measures
instead of focusing on productivity innovation and stuff and the whole because we can't
Eurovision 2010 now this is from last week yeah in oil rich Norway country I have heard a rumor
this year the senior from eastern of Italy and because of this I said we have to organize Eurovision
next year and this week I was bankrupt myself I said yeah yo so this would of course I should have
realized that this was from last week I didn't have time to play it well I guess your prediction
was pretty wrong there CSB didn't happen there was no no Iceland winner of course I really
messed it up I know agenda by saying that it was held in Russia I was kind of a year behind
held in Norway and Germany one of course Lena the daughter of a builder burg member oh yeah you
can't you can't just make this shit up I'm telling you good load listen I'm really
where will you join this one listen you monkeys you've broken the floor now I've been broken it
we don't know if you fully know the old we now we made one so if you can all make a bit from
the abyss because the first ones to go I've got to be those lovely many blue jerseys and I
will come from Essex got it all right and our pools for all I'll see you at the
home
Lent nous !
That's great.
SIG mit !
Lent nous !
My cover run !
There's just some loose picking from the box now.
Oh baby!
I'm the loser!
And during the block hands, a first-in-your-never here on the radio.
Hit me with your rhythm stick.
And I've heard I'm getting some frelationsia if I play this song.
Well, shit I'll do that!
Over what?
I'm ready to come inside
You look at me as if you're in a date
It's like the feeling of a humble page with your real life
You don't know what you just read
What the world's world
What no one listens any more
What no one listens to the world's world
I might as well pull up and come to a wall
Who's the world's eye?
I know what I can call the one thing
And my own soul
That's the left and the left and the left
It changed the direction
I know what the story was killing
You look at the fresh light in the floor of the stage
I see you like I still
What the world's world
What no one listens any more
What no one listens to the world's world
Do you hear me?
Do you hear me? Do you hear me? Do you hear me?
Do you hear me? Do you hear me? Do you hear me? Do you hear me?
That's exactly the kind of awesome stuff to come out of the chat room when people really
get into the vibe, missing persons words.
This is another request we just thought was kind of cute.
Billy Preston, also known as the fifth needle.
Billy apparently has a huge cut, by the way, and that's a music industry secret.
Nothing from nothing leaves nothing.
You gotta have something, if you wanna be me.
I'm not gonna try to beat your ego, but that's ego, it's too cool for me.
I'm not tired to beat, so fast, but that minus is too long to see you, yeah.
I'm not gonna be me.
Nothing from nothing leaves nothing.
You gotta have something, if you wanna be me.
Don't you remember, I told you.
I'm not so good in the world, I'm too good in the end, yeah.
You gotta have something, if you wanna be me, you gotta have something, yeah.
You gotta have something, if you wanna be me.
You gotta have something, if you wanna be me, you gotta have something, give me well.
You gotta have something, if you wanna be me, you gotta have something, yeah.
You gotta have something, yeah.
Alright, let me get back into the live. There we go. That's better.
I should tell you my Grace Jones story by the way.
This is a group too.
Now I'm going through my personal iTunes collection
to bring out some shit for it.
Pull up to the bumper baby and ride it into Queens.
I've been down those city streets
when you look at that.
Won't you pick your favorite stream
from the red this time?
I've been up to the bumper bar from the bumper bar from the bumper base
I've been up to the bumper baby
and you're not having a thing.
ride it into Queens.
Pull up to Queens.
Don't ride.
Get ready.
Money.
안녕.
A pride.
I'll not.
Bit's externals.
Come on, shit.
Get the cow on.
One to you come in
One to you my friend
Ruby, back in, up while now I'm in my mind
Ruby, Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
I'm all up to God, Ruby, Ruby
Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
Ruby, Ruby
I'm getting all the good requests coming in one after another and I got to go download
from my two and just in time to actually get them on to the stream.
Yes, thank you for requesting this one hadn't heard it in a million years.
Wow!
I got the remage version for you.
Remember the word you were wrapping hood?
Words in papers, words in books, words on TV, words for books, words of comfort, words of peace, words to make the fighting cease, words to tell you what to do, words are working hard for you.
If your words but don't go hungry, words have always nearly hung me.
Words of nuance, words of skill, and words of romance are a little.
Words are stupid, words are fun, words can put you on the run.
You wizard, you you carter, you are stupid, you're stupid, you are stupid, you are stupid, you BOYS were everything.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, yeah let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go let's do the same way with
Wrap it up for the common good, like us and list the neighborhood.
It's okay, I've always heard it.
This is a word you've never heard.
Okay, bye.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can take that to the bank.
You can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank
that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that by the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank and taking that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you can take that to the bank, you cantake that to the bank, you can take that to the bank
I'm late, I'm late, I'm late, I'm late, I'm late
on your speakers
We should be able to take this up to the two-hour mark
I got enough songs to jam it for a while here
That's what is supposed to be out of group art finding
Now you're making it feel good! Seriously!
I had such a shitty morning and now I'm kind of into the vibe
and feeling just like just like I can really dance!
Whatever happens to you
Liam's trying to scream
He got a nice pick
That made us use burn
Whatever happens to you
You'll land here
To play on me raw
As I show up on the wall
Whatever happens to you
Are the heroes
Are the Shakespeareals
They watch their own man
Whatever happens to you
Now for heroes anymore
No more heroes anymore
No more hero anymore
Why do I deserve you
Out of the heroes, are the Shakespeare's, they're like their own man
Whatever comes from the heroes
No more heroes anymore, no more heroes anymore
And I think I was 13, I'd be jumping up and down in my room
Jumping from the couch to the bed, across to my head against the wall
I just love these guys, the sprinklers, no more heroes anymore
What happened to the heroes, they're all gone, we don't have any more heroes
Where are the heroes?
What happened to the heroes, they're all gone, we don't have any more heroes anymore
Sorry about that, little bit of a fire, it's crazy that I'm playing the cash mode
And it's actually sounding a lot like I'm doing some fire radio here, this is nuts man, I love it
You need to do it more often, just take those old records off the show
I've seen listen to him by myself, today's music ain't got the same song
All I've been told to have a rock and roll, don't try to take it to a disco
You never even give me how I'm wrong
And 10 minutes I've been leap for the dough, stop playing it all time, rock and roll
Still I've been all time, I'm rockin' roll, they can't abuse it just through the song
I've been listening, I've been feeling all time, I'm rockin' roll, ready for my help out here
I've been listening, I've been listening, I've been feeling all time, I'm rockin' roll
What happened to the heroes, they are all gone, we don't have any more heroes anymore
Yeah, bro, call me a relic on what you will
See all the fascists, they'll never do
Today's music ain't got the same song
I left it all till I'm rockin' roll
Still like that old time I'm rockin' roll
The color music just suits us all
I remember some of the days of all
And the full time rockin' roll
Still like that old time I'm rockin' roll
The color music just suits us all
I remember some of the days of all
And the full time rockin' roll
Still like that old time I'm rockin' roll
The color music just suits us all
I remember some of the days of all
And the full time rockin' roll
Still like that old time rockin' roll
The color music just suits us all
I remember some of the days of all
And the full time rockin' roll
Still like that old time rockin' roll
All right, now I'm officially tired
Bob, see you getting a silver bullet of bear
And then the old time rockin' roll
And now for something that I just need
Because I need to calm down for a moment
Please sing with me with queen
Funny Mercury
Just watching the show
Over and over again
You and was tired
It made up his mind
To leave his dead life behind
His boss acts the river
While you'd been up again
To get those crazy notion
Right out of your head
Say the hood
Do you think that you are
You should have escaped
I've been ever apart
Spread your wings and fly away
Fly away
You're still together
Because you're still together
Just because you're a free man
He spends his evening alone
In his heart there won't
Keep in his mind to himself
He'd be living soon
Wish that he was my man
Away
Nothing in this world
Ooh
Since he was smart
I've no luck at all
Nothing can be easy to live
Now it was time
He made up his mind
This could be my last chance
His boss acts the river
Now it's the boy
You're always dreaming
You've got the real ambition
You won't get away
Save me by
That you're the way you are
Why can't you be happy
Have to have the rule of life
So what is spread always
Fly away
Spread your wings and fly away
You're still together
Because you're still together
Because you're free man
Come on honey
I've met a lot of people throughout the years
And some of them are no longer with us
Because one of those people who I really miss
Oh man
And we knew for so long that he was sick
And we were like swarmed as secrecy
And it was just horrible just seeing him
Just seeing him go down the tubes
Yeah
Cool
I'm tired
But I'll play a song for you
That I was looking for
I would be probably
I think probably close to 10 years
And I would request it from record companies
And they would you know it was weird
Because like a one-hit wonder
You're going to laugh when you hear the song of course
And it finally showed up on iTunes
And this is a song
That when I was in the
See I think it was junior high
Yeah
It was like you know when your hormones are raging
And this I one girl that you're like really crazy about
Of course I won't look at you because you're a total dork
And the lyric from this song
Which always got me was
I'd ride with you
On the handlebars
You'd laugh from runaway
Well you'll hear it when you hear the LSE brothers
I'd like to stay in love
With you
All summer and after I'll keep
You weren't through the weather
You've forgotten it's one day
You're saying those love play
Like the ride my heart is so good
With you
On the handlebars
You'll have to run away
You've forgotten it's one day
You're saying those love play
All summer and after I'll keep
You've forgotten it's one day
You're saying those love play
To love you, to love you, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it
to love it, to love it, to love it, and love it, to love it, you love it to love it, to love it, to love it, to love it, and love that I'm not a bitch for that I love it, and wish that to love it, and be on it.
Deep breath is breathing so low
When we tear our seeds all the way
Flouring, feeling the epic orange again
For again, all the way
Deep breath is breathing so low
When we tear our seeds all the way
Flouring, feeling the epic orange again
She gets hungry, but dinner and it
She loves the dinner, doesn't come late
She'd never bother with anyone she'd hate
And that's why the lady is a tramp
Doesn't like dice games with barrens and herbs
Well, go to Harlem, festin' irmin' and pearls
Will not dish the dirt with a rest of those girls
And that's why this chick is a tramp
It's up to the free, cool, with the rest
Life without doubt, she's broke
But it's so, doesn't like California
It's cold and it's damp
That's why the lady is a tramp
She gets far too hungry, babe
We bet for dinner and it's
She adores the dinner, doesn't come late
She'd never bother with someone she'd hate
And that's why the lady is a tramp
Doesn't like dice games with barrens and herbs
Never makes a trick up to Harlem diving
Shiny Lincoln's in court
She won't dish the dirt with a rest of those girls
That's why this chick is a tramp
She loves the free, fine, wild knockout
Kube Kube, groovy with dinner hair
Life without a care
She's broke, but it's so, she loves California
It's cold and it's damp
That's why the lady is a tramp
Turn the bar, live with medicine, square garden
I've got the entire album, you should know
And it's one of my favorites, especially the overture
The opening with Howard Kossel, but that may be for a different daily source code
Let me keep you in the vago some songs you never ever ever hear on the radio
But it's a part of your education
Some are journeys tonight, agra, and you're one of the places
I've been all our kids, we'll save our friends
I've a cozy little flat in what is known
As old man hadn't, we'll settle down
Right here in town
We'll have man hadn't
The Bronx and Staten Island too
It's lovely going through the Sioux
It's very fancy, on all the fancy street you know
The subway charms are so
When bombing breezes blow to and fro
And tell me what street compares with my street into life
Sweet push cards gently glide
Ding-bye
The great big cities of wonder store
Just make for a girl and boy
We'll turn that hat into an island of joy
We'll go to yankers
Where true love conquers in the wild
And starve together dear
In chiles
We'll go to Coney
And eat baloney on a roll
In central park we'll stroll
Where our first kiss we stole
So do so
And my family is a terrific show they say
We both may see it close
Someday
The city's glamour can never spoil
The dreams of a boy and girl
We'll turn man hadn't into an island of joy
That's right
I'm just a little bit dismayed at the chat room
Not knowing who this is
How can you how dare you not know the voice
Without a doubt the voice of an entire era
Elef it's Gerald
Oh my gosh, I can't believe you guys didn't know that
How about this one then?
Surely you from the 70s rule
Remember this one
Little clowny guy
And we made fun of it in get monation
East on big brother
I hated some good tunes before I became a joke
This one is without a doubt one of the best songs ever written
Leo Sayer on the Charlie
For a funny version
When I need you
I just close my eyes and I'm with you
And all that I saw on a give you
It's only a heartbeat away
When I need love
I hold out my hands and I touch love
I never knew that was so much love
Keep in me one night and day
Miles of miles of empty space in between us
The telephone can't take place all your smile
But you know I won't be traveling forever
It's cold out but hold out
And do like I do when I need you
I just close my eyes and I'm with you
And all that I saw on a give you bay
It's only a heartbeat away
It's not easy when the road is to a driver
On it that's a heavy load that we bear
But you know I won't be traveling a lifetime
It's cold out but hold out
And do like I do when I need you
I just close my eyes and I'm with you
When I need love
I hold out my hands and I touch love
I never knew that was so much love
Keep in me one night and day
When I need you
I just close my eyes
And you know I won't be traveling
Keep in me one night and day
I just hold out my hands and I'm with you
And all that I saw on a give you
It's only a heartbeat away
All right you're listening to all hit radio
And it's 53 degrees at 13 minutes past the hour
And right now and I'll request line
I've got my pleasure on the phone
Hey babe what would you like to hear
Hey babe I'm sorry I can't hear you too
Well you can have to speak a little closer
In the phone okay babe what would you like to hear again?
We are observing your life
Hey Mike I'm sorry babe but that's not on our playlist
And by the way you sound great over the phone
Anyway if you give us your request we'll be glad to play it for you babe
So let's hear it
We are observing your life
Oh listen Mike I'm sorry babe
But we can we like to make
I'm sorry Mike we there's my contact
Oh with you
Baby
In your mind you have capacities you know
To tell a path messages through the vast unknown
Please close your eyes and concentrate
With every thought you think
Upon the recitation
When we're about to say
Calling occupants are the deplinatory craft
Calling occupants are the deplinatory
Most extraordinary craft
Calling occupants are the deplinatory craft
We're observing your life
And we like to make
I contact with you
We are your friends
Calling occupants are the deplinatory craft
Calling occupants are the deplinational craft
Thank you, please, and to spare the police, man
Oh, don't you give us a sign
Yes, a sign that we wish you
Come, we can meet tomorrow
We'll stay here
With you mine, do however beautiful
sentiments are
And brings with thought energy
Fabi and the lord
You glows your eyes, You concentrate
Together that's the way
To send the message we need to say I will contact you
Go away my happiness, I've been to a planetary ground