All right, everybody, as usual before a big event, the first thing we do is...
...all rise.
Please, gentlemen, please rise for your contamination.
The National Anthem, and you may sing along.
In the morning, get ammunition.
We are all charged up to be.
Human resources and servants in all lands and oceans,
...from the east to west,
...our number two,
...the lowlands and beyond.
We are happy and distracted slaves
...if our Japanese are...
...in the morning.
Delta Sierra Charlie 854,
...the football Friday,
...and this is I Am Your Slave Edition.
We've systemmed these assessments
...in showing five lines of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We need to be nearby.
I know it's in the three lines of honesty.
It's better to create.
Everybody today, I am your slave.
Brand new spirit of radio coming here
...from the hills of Watchtower, Cray Park, Command Center.
We'll move to my little friend.
All right, here we go.
I'm giving source code.
It's quitting time, everybody.
Crack it up.
We're at the Narbaw.
It's a full railway, it's crackle with light, right in the sand, up there so that the energy
Emotions will be stuck in time, it's way late, that we can't feed our faces all night
All this machine, remaking my music, you still be a fan of it
Not one phone in charge of it, it's really just the question of your honesty, yeah, your honesty
One night's gonna be leaving the freedom of music
A literary crisis and then he is compromises, shatter the illusion of integrity
That's not opinion, that's science
And science is one call of a bitch with a 14-inch strap on
Dying against the risk of the energy
Emotions will be stuck in time, it's way late, that we can't feed our faces all night
Unbelievable the out of boring of love we got today, I'm gonna pay you back
I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay
I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay me back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'mma pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay me, I'm gonna pay you back, I'm gonna pay you
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
And say the news will reach me
And say
The news will show
He's so full of fire
It's not gonna stop me
But who's fire
There must have got the message that
The sugar is always found in the music here
On the Charlie
On your Delta
Share Charlie
On the source code
Without Stern
Before it leaves him Fox
To make $600 million
By doing this online here we are
Our little group of chuckleheads
Having a really good time
You see, I know you're not real man, because I'm loaded okay, I've had some experience
in that area besides that whole wrap of yours is bowl anyway, good evil, it's all the
same crap, rock and roll is the only thing that counts dig, hard ass blistering, awesome,
heavy metal, rock and roll.
You see, I know you're not real man, because I know you're not real man, because I know you're not real,
because I know you're not real man, because I know you know you're not real man, because I know you're not real man
because I know you're not real man, because I know you're not real man, because I know you don't shown you
Say I'm the black little baby, I'm the streets of Berlin
You won't be the mission, she ain't all the same
We're in control now
She doesn't need a lot of rules
I'm getting a lot of questions
I never think that they do
But where else will I be?
Sex
I'll be the hell
So after two, number 13
Love is just where it'd be, yeah
I'm the hands who will suffer
To rip it off your skin
Break up the leaves
She's blowing an octave
Surgeoned in every way
I feel like I'm in a breath
But I won't be the reason
Sex
I'll be the hell
So after two, number 13
Love is just where it'd be, yeah
Sex
We're in control now
She's blowing an octave
I'll be the hell
So after two, number 13
Love is just where it'd be, yeah
Sex
We're in control now
She's blowing an octave
I'll be the hell
So after two, number 13
How did it happen?
Talk about your value for value of this program
Entirely funded by Chuck O'Hex Worldwide
Who kicksstarter.com
I really had no idea if it would work
And lo and behold, fuck you guys came through
I totally, totally, love that
And of course we've got to Bobby
Even in the chat room in the origin of chat.net
That should be some value for your money right there
No one said it
I am so pumped up
I've read the future show bright eye
Better wear shoes
I've studied nuclear science
I love my classes
I got a crazy teacher
Anywhere's dark glasses
Things I go in grades
And they're only getting better
I'm new and I'm all right
Getting good grades
Looked you're so bright
I've got a way to change
I've got a job waiting for my graduation
Get it out of here
I've got a lot of fear
Things that go in grades
And they're only getting better
I'll do it all right
Getting good grades
I'm future so bright
I've got a way to change
Oh
I've got a lot of fear
Things that go in grades
And they're only getting better
I don't do it all right
Getting good grades
Looked you're so bright
I've got a way to change
Oh
oh
I've been waiting for you
I haven't closed your eyes
In the sky
Perfect
I don't want to lose
I love my classes
I've got pretty beauty
There's time for classes
And things that will be great
There's a whole different meta
Time to raise the ending
It's just a little bit.
You and I are ready.
Getting good grades, the future's so bright.
Oh, I got it with your shades.
Bobby, even in the chat room, I'm gonna ask for an hour, I got it.
Bobby, take your panties off, ladies, everyone wants to say.
We know that you've got a special Dropbox for the Charlie,
so we love you to help us out there.
I will be talking a lot about the brand new model
for the daily source code later on today,
but first, not just shades, because the future's so bright,
I think we need some ear muscles,
because your ears are gonna bleed.
They go to the Tells, but look forgot.
Let's go, let's go, an.
Oh no, I'm going to,
hah!
I want to get your out.
Yeah?
I feel pretty good.
And I get, that I feel good,
praises I blade,
Oh, we all got it through no black things,
I know I'm falling so hard
When it comes to the girls, it's better
But don't worry about it, it's better
It's better, it's better, it's better
And let's dig out the chair
Let's dig out the chair
I have to get out of my
I have to get out up the chair
Let's dig out the chair
And let's dig out the chair
This lazy lady and the second baby
Liar goes over the pool
So the same way
I've thought this as a suit
I know I'm fallen out on my way
I have to get out of my chair
I'm intoity I'm intoity I'm intoity I'm within the ground
I'm within the ground
I'm cornered in all your dead
I know that there's no reason
In you side, I'm in fire
I can far and I'm in fire
I've been waiting for you
Hello you
to be standing through the dial continuously
to get the type of music mix and assortment
that you get on the daily store's going.
Break the down and a minute to thanks
some backers of the daily source code project.
And all of you, thanks for dropping your tracks
to the Dropbox and sharing it with me.
Fuck, I can't spill for the city!
Going to the city!
Got you all the money!
Got you, shout it's pretty!
I'll leave it all behind.
This is my decision.
I'm coming home to stay this time
because I'm in full Barcelona.
I'm in full Barcelona.
Full Barcelona.
Oh, oh, oh!
Freedom of the cleanest, sitting in the sun.
But I can't my dream back.
I can't open my eyes.
I'm in full Barcelona.
Everything is in here I've got
It's out of full force in it
I'm a full force in it
It's a fish out of water
I'm just a man in the hole
The city lies to the police
I don't want to go
I'm just a person waiting
I'm gonna hit the bridge
Just a friend to sleep
I'm tired of laying by
Hang it around
I'm gonna catch a train
I'll be a sea-bound
I'm just a person waiting
I'm gonna catch a train
I'm just a person looking
I'm just a homestay man
I've got to hit me, I'm just a homestay man
I've got to hit a homestay man
Stay fit to the crowd
Which I've got to not be in
I'm that much happy's good and laugh
When I see my inner city, it's time
I'll be walking on a crowd
There's no fool, I'll sit there
I'll be fool, I'll sit there
I know I made it look like I said it all up there Bob, you even join us in the chat room
and know it's in the chat.net, but I just can't take any credit.
This is what happens when magic takes place my friends and magic it is.
Bob had a full for the City of the Avisors Code episode 8, 54, a brand new model for the show.
So here's the story briefly.
I've been following this Kickstarter.com website for a while ever since the diaspora project
raised a shitload of money for them to go off and start that project which is actually running
now and I'm keeping my eye on that and I said to myself, you know what, maybe this is a model
that we can put into place for all the chuckle heads to come together and add some value
for value on both sides of the equation and I set up a project which was very an interesting
process where you basically write you description and you submit it and then it took
them like two weeks to get back to me even though I'd said I want to do this last week,
last Friday for the show.
I said, oh, I'm really sorry I really backed up and so they basically they do go through
some kind of screening process although I think they have basically freelancers who are,
you know, just looking to see if it's something that can make them money because they do
make money off of the whole idea through the payment processing which goes through Amazon.
But what I love about this is you set your goal and you set your minimums and you set
your prizes and your little incentives and no one gets charged unless the money is raised
so the way we did is minimum of five dollars to donate to the show which has now been collected
from everyone.
Thank you so much.
I think it'll take 14 days before it actually comes to me so we'll see how much is left
over at that point.
$50 would get you a Skype call and we have a couple of those coming up during today's
extravaganza and a hundred dollars or more would it be an executive producer credits.
So let me mention them again.
Dave Hoffman for $120 and $0.45 cent 1,2345 of one of my favorite numerology additions.
There crazy hurts $100 at him.
Burke pile.
Of course, we know him from the bat signal pocket no agenda, $100.
$50 from Sir Kelly Spongberg, $50, actually double nipples on the dime, $55 and
10 cents and then there's a list of other donors.
I want to mention everyone your donation.com,
Vunk Linky is another one of our donors,
then we have, let me just scroll up to the top here.
Nick Rogers, Tanya Wyman, Kevin Alcock,
Isaac Dago, I hope I'm pronouncing this right.
Dave Keckish, Robert R. Woolridge,
Gitmo Slave, Adam P, Martin Osterhout, Michael Greer,
Noah Brotso, Grant Jones, Ken Medlock,
Randy Asher, there'll be Sir Randy Asher,
Luca Nelson Ferreira, A Nelson I do,
and Simon Smith, Onion Union, Mr. Wolf, Scott Singer,
John Montoya, Yurune Sweppy, Joel Filiol,
Michael Oakley, Landtricks, Daniel Rubbethal, James Brown,
John Michelle, Brandmary, Moxie, Paul, and Frank Nell.
Thank you all for making the show possible.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, shit, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
But I can't find you
Such into the day, into the night
They wouldn't stop for the London
They didn't know when they didn't understand
And we were asking why
Yeah, I'm our way, yeah
They wouldn't shout
And I'm blind in my mind
All that you see wasn't on and down the stream
All the shadows in into the night
They didn't need to lose my number
Because you're not anywhere
They're all came from you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
They didn't need to lose my number
Because you're not anywhere
They're all came from you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Keep on it, keep on it
God keep on it
If you know you're not anywhere
You know that I'm on your side
God keep on it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Keep on it, keep on it
They didn't need to lose my number
Because you're not anywhere
They're all came from you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Keep on it, keep on it
They didn't need to lose my number
Because you're not anywhere
They're all came from you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
They didn't need to lose my number
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Keep on it, keep on it
They didn't need to lose my number
Because you're not anywhere
They're all came from you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Keep on it, keep on it, keep on it
Keep on it, keep on it
They didn't need to lose my number
Oh...
Keep on it, keep on it
Keep on it
They didn't need to lose my number
Cause, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Keep on it, keep on it
Y Inaudible
I just got the score
They did't take on you
Your C please
Just the score
I just got the score
I'm getting worried, got the idea from in the first place, but I'm pretty sure that's not going to happen.
I would be highly surprised if it did.
Since Apple is so hell bent on protecting us real slaves from bad words.
Oh no, not bad words.
You know, the stuff we use here at the kind of stuff that Bobby Eden talks about in the chat room.
You know, I'll be no good.
No, my friends, I think we're on something big here, and I'm very, very proud of what the chuckle had to do.
As we all came together, of course.
I don't know if we're going to do this every single week.
I feel like I could give you a couple of freebies.
I don't think we can necessarily have to raise money for every single Charlie,
but I really do like the fact that it worked.
I just take a leap into shore.
Now, of course, not everyone is able to contribute monetarily.
And I think we had about 42 or 43 backers of the project.
Lots of other people have been supporting this show.
We've got chuckle heads worldwide who have put together by dropping a song to your drop-box sharing that with me.
And we've got people who do actual work for the program like our buddy Ray.
All we want is not just Ray.
Hey, chuckle head.
Hey, you're complaining to me.
Oh, we've got to be a part of us against a game.
Ray, what's our goal?
This is me.
A very special hit list.
And this he let us out of Ray on the Charlie.
Checkpoint.
The monthly Dutch magazine for Veterans of War is publishing
in December edition with Veterans of 15.
The magazine asked 75,000 veterans of war
to send in a top three most clay songs during a mission.
And it made the top 50.
From young 12 World War II veterans to those who were sent to Afghanistan,
they all send in the three most favorite songs.
So let's check out the top three of this Veterans of 15.
Number three in this very special hit list.
A song from 1984 played by a Dutch orchestra.
This is I want to go home.
It will be nice.
God willing to be God willing to be God willing to be God willing to be God.
Music from other lands, my friends.
And back the years to train to the earth.
Number three in this top 50, I want to go home.
Played by this Dutch orchestra.
And then let's take a look at number two.
All their veterans chosen especially for the numbers of the British singer Vera Laine.
We'll meet again in at on the 22nd spot.
For a song from the time you say goodbye,
finished in second place on the Veterans' top 50.
From the time you say goodbye.
From the time you say,
Cheerio, cheerio, cheerio, cheerio.
Music, where do you take our handshake true?
Oh my God, I love this right.
For your journey as you go.
Keep a prayer within your heart.
That's the time we'll surely fly.
To the day when we shall meet again from the time you say goodbye.
And now ladies and gentlemen, this is number one.
This song with the appropriate title, we gotta get out of this place.
The British pop group, the animals, is the most popular song among ducks' groups during their mission.
In this studio part of the city.
When the sun revives to ashes.
People tell me they're here.
No, we're just in front.
Now my girl, you're so young and pretty.
And one thing I love is true.
Give me a dead loop.
Oh, you try to miss you.
I love you.
Watch my lady face.
Watch his hand and turn her face.
He's been working in slain in his life.
Oh yes, I love her.
Now my girl, you're so young and pretty.
And one thing I love is true.
Give you a dead loop.
Oh you try and miss you.
What's my daddy in bed at the time?
Watch his hand, better turn it crazy
But we're gonna sleep in that place
I know we've been a firm and so hot
But I'll be with you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We gotta get out of this place
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We're all in a better life for me and you
Somewhere, baby
Somehow, no, baby
We gotta get out of this place
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We're all in a better life for me and you
Leave me, baby
I know it, baby.
You know it too.
I know it's not very original, but hey, the song by the animals from 1965 came with a large
maturity on number one. It is especially popular among young veterans. Many of them play
this song every day, a singing out loud during a mission. We got to get out of this place
because it was a song for American soldiers during the Vietnam War.
So I'll make it in checkpoint. It made this top 50 to celebrate the 100th edition of the
magazine Next Week. And I wish you all a very nice weekend. Bye bye now.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm flying just in the club. I'm crossing, I'm ready. I'm trying not to
think I'm winning the last one, but we're ready again. Oh, oh, oh, we had it. Right, did it really turn
at night? Oh, brother, it's cool. We've had it, but not by the moon. Oh, oh, oh, we had it. But at the time
it seems a bad toy. It's a surprise to my children for fun. There it is.
My husband's had it, and I'm today with all the kids. I've gone away, gone to my next school.
Every time that he's done well, he's alone and Vince is kind.
So I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready. I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready. I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready. I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rainy life.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
I'm going to run, I'm ready.
I'm going to run a rain, I'm ready.
OK.
I'm ready.
This is gonna be laughing at me right now,
she heard me talking about how scar I was.
All right, and now for the fun stuff,
let's get back to reality.
Frustration and discord,
affirming in every city.
And if I read out what the digital fees
I'd love a little bit of the century.
And the balance of Rachel,
my little ring, everything I see
that will set it free.
Oh, make them turn the time she left her.
All right, we're new,
I like democracy,
so I share everything that comes to me.
I can't let it to the handrail,
I can't let it to the floor,
I can't let it to the middle,
you better protect you,
all that you claim belongs to us.
You cannot do what you cannot touch.
All that you face just never really yours.
All that claim belongs to us.
We were so we were so close of faith,
but we were like you can follow the rules.
All right, we're new,
we're new,
we're new now,
we do things with those rules you not
And maybe we won't, all that you claim belongs to us
You cannot tell what you cannot touch
All that you think just will never relay yours
All that you claim belongs to us
They stick to a post and expand in the empire of oppression
And with the tiny group of real self-employed rulers
Control every aspect of every life
Every aspect of every life
All that you claim belongs to us
You cannot tell what you cannot touch
All that you think just will never relay yours
All that you claim belongs to us
You cannot tell what you think just will never relay yours
That's what I'm talking about
I'm talking about you
We know it might be hard
We never explained it
It's shit you've never heard before
Just noticing my draw box and shows up
Share with the pirate anthem under the daily source code episode eight five four
And of course, we always are looking out to try and find songs that
Well, you may not have heard before
And this may be a version you've not heard before
It's live
Five is Jim Carr and Simple Mines.
You're amazing along the course.
Just wait until the drum hits.
Here we go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I hope you can see your bad.
I hope you'll know that soon.
You know the best.
So can you tell us about given me everything inside now?
Love's strange, it's so weird, I don't think of the ten of things that we won't be able to know
I'm so sure, you must be cool as a part
When the clouds disappear, you'll find me, don't you?
I don't need a family, I don't go home, don't you?
I don't need a family, yeah, I don't have it, yeah
Come on
No, just try and pretend
It's my feeling of laughing
Yeah, hang on
I'll touch you
Open your eyes
Close your eyes
sogenan
You stop
Don't shoot
Forget about me, I'll be alone
I'll be dancing, don't make me go too
Take us apart, and go to space
You love me, love me
Don't you, forget about me
I don't, don't, don't, don't
You just stand above me
You're my way, I never love you
One, two, three, four
Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad
You recognize me, from my baby
One, one, five
Rink his phone, Rink his phone
Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad
Dad, Dad, Dad
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Don't you, forget about me
I don't, don't you
Don't you know that I'm dead about me
I still want all my life
So I'm all alone with you
Don't you know that I'm all alone with you
I'm all alone with you
Tell me about the sexuality it's in your DNA
Jogs, jogs, jogs, and jogs
Let's vote for Jogs
Jogs, jogs, jogs
Let's vote to Jogs
Let's vote for Jogs
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Checking out the chat room that's where Bobby Eden is hanging out today.
I think she's doing her live webcam show at the same time, and she puts in a request.
Well, of course, all of the snails jump on that one.
Yeah!
Bobby, I think you should open up at least five, three minutes for everybody, right now.
By request, stop the odds!
Ah, okay.
It's all in one.
You fool yourself.
It's very life secret.
We're in long time, okay?
It's all-right.
Richard was Earth.
For one is ruined.
And you gotta sing.
The masked man is hungry, she needs to tell home.
The river inches and feet are well
What this is your new place has to go
I've got to leave it, I'm on a job
Here I am
Dropped you like a hurricane
The bloody spring starts to shout
These ideas come me, breaks down the light
Thus easy for you to stop with lose
Just have to make it, we still are done
And I am calling, I have to go
And go be sorry, you lies in your eyes
Your slink is little season, and it's your win
On the hot season nightfall, bloody busy
Here I am
Dropped you like a hurricane
I am calling, I have to go
And go be sorry, you lies in your eyes
Your slink is little season, and it's your win
On the hot season nightfall, bloody busy
I have to go
And go be sorry, you lies in your eyes
Your slink is little season, and it's your win
On the hot season nightfall, bloody busy
Here I am
Dropped you like a hurricane
All right, seems like Bobby has some air
Ultimate lyrics though
Dropped
Although maybe it's exactly what close
Mine I had in mind when he wrote the lyrics
To rock you like your hurricane
The scorpions of the daily source code episode
Eight-five-four, the food bar Friday
Making your ears bleed all around
Get monation my friend
Like a home on a sun that's invisible there
Cause we're living at the mercy of the pain in the fear
Until we get it, we'll get it, let it all disappear
Waiting for the end to come
Wishing I has dreams to stand
This is not what I happened
It's out of my control
Fly what the speed of life
Thoughts were spinning in my head
So many things were left, I said
It's hard to let you go
When I want to take the move on
When I want to feel the light
When I want to do a straight this light
To something new
Holding on to what I have it
Go
Sting in and down to trying to forget the past
When this was never meant to last
I wish it wasn't so
When I want to take the move on
When I want to feel the light
When I want to do a straight this light
To something new
Holding on to what I have it
Go
Yeah, what was that?
When I find a what is gone
I thought it felt right
But everything was wrong
I've caught up in the highest storm
Trying to figure out what is life will be
And I don't need to know what kind of things I said
I'm out getting moving in my mind with this
Thinking of the pieces now where to begin
I just put a hand in this morning again
When I want to do a straight this light
To something new
Holding on to what I have it
Go
Sting in and down to trying to forget the past
When I want to do a straight this light
To something new
Holding on to what I have it
Oh my god
That's who I am
I wonder if only 10 in the dark
That's who I can't even
Of where I'll just go home
And try to break
And go morning
1, 2, 3, help!
My telegrammit!
To death lost their kids.
Talk down those fingers!
Oh yeah!
Get your body down, get your feet down, get your feet down, get your feet down, get your feet down.
Lead the layman!
Got the down there right, got my heart down tight.
Gotta be right on the ceiling.
My heart's in the darkness, now I'm sick of it.
I love the sound.
Don't worry, I won't let you on this time.
Bye!
Time to
Now I am on the.
Now come early!
I'm on the, now I'm on the ceiling.
Oh Oh No!
Let's go, I will get to you
For all you'll be every time
You'll make a goal in life
I've heard of you, and I'll see the world
We'll go for great
No, God, I've given the name
You'll make a moment
You'll see how it is
You'll make a goal in life
Directed by created by some military
I'm gonna go to the night
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, let's be alive by ourselves.
Yeah, oh, what a gem showed up in the Dropbox.
That is the fruit fighters, the tie and mother-down classic queen, of course.
There you go.
Live at Hyde Park for those of you who are wondering.
Another song you'll never, ever hear on the radio.
And since we have all kinds of different categories of songs here on the dating source code,
we've got our cowbell songs, we've got our ear bleeding songs.
I think it's time to introduce a new category.
Let's do a round of fuck you. What do you think, huh?
I think it's a perfect test.
And I've got a bunch of shoes and a five with magic.
I still don't be wager.
But I know I've got to take it.
I think that's the machine.
And all of that's crazy, my shoes.
I still wish you would bet with a fuck you.
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
I can't afford to provide it.
But in fact, don't think it's fair.
I guess you use a catchbox.
And I'm more on a target.
I've got a way you play a game and fair.
I get to the pool.
I fall in love with you.
Oh, she's a girl.
Well, I've got some rules for you.
Yeah, go to the hotel. You're a little boy.
Oh, he's here.
I got a bunch of girls.
I just wanted my birthday.
I was a senior.
I got a bunch of girls.
I still don't be wager.
But I've got to take it.
And all of that's crazy, my shoes.
I still wish you would bet with a fuck you.
No, I know.
I can't borrow.
I can still relax.
Yeah.
Trying to keep ya.
I'm just being alone with you.
As I keep, nah.
I get to the pool.
I fall in love with you.
Oh, she's a girl.
Well, I've got some rules for you.
Oh, I really hate your way as well now.
She's a girl, a girl, a girl, a girl.
I got a bunch of girls.
I just wanted my birthday.
I was a senior.
I got a bunch of girls.
I still don't be wager.
I'm not way back to you.
And all of that's crazy, my shoes.
I still wish you would bet with a fuck you.
No, baby, baby, baby.
Why?
I tried to tell you about my love,
but she told me this is what I had there.
Yeah, she did.
Is it what I love?
Why?
I love you.
I still love you.
Yes, I'm like in this category.
And the theory.
Fuck all of you, we're here to rock.
And now we're here to rock.
And jump all the ways have to fuck her hard.
In fact, sometimes that's not right.
To do.
Sometimes you've got to make some love.
If I can give her some smooches too.
Sometimes you've got to squeeze.
Sometimes you've got to save me.
Sometimes you've got to save.
I'm gonna fuck you.
Softly.
I'm gonna screw you gently.
I'm gonna call you.
Sweetly.
Discreetly.
And then you say, hey, I brought you flowers.
And then you say, wait a minute, Sally.
I think I got something in my team.
Did you get it?
I for me.
That's fucking teamwork.
What's your favorite position?
That's cool with me.
It's not my favorite, but I'll do it for you.
What's your favorite dish?
I'm not gonna cook it, but I'll order it from Zanzibar.
And then I'm gonna love you completely.
And I'll fuck it, but you discreetly.
And then I'll fuck you completely.
And then I'm gonna fuck you.
I'm gonna fuck you.
Because words, you better better.
Rap is your body!
Wow! Are you ready for a rap body?
We've got to do it!
Rap is your body!
The way you feel, you don't jingle, but you're jingling
So break over here, I'm cause it's heavy in the middle
I move like a moucher, the grooves are like rules up
She wanna learn, so we face school, and it's cool
But not like this, we close the turn
One more time, one two, and a thing, you wanna give it
If it fantasies, we'll live it, so let's out, all right
The world is the same, lady, love in my baby girl
Spread your wings, so we can fight around the world
Harmony, charm it, you figure it's up to call me
When you drop the kiss of Suzy, you drop the bomb on me
She asks, it's stretching, flex it, flex it
Be me the position, okay, don't get up
Let's do it like bodra, Buddha as the best
We can't let out have the love of touch and head on my chest
Let's win that beat, I'm the one who'll be on the side
What's going on? What's going on?
What's going on? Who's going on? Who's going on?
Now that we got so what'll we want to do?
No money, tell me, let me go!
Get a more one time!
Now!
Oh!
Keep it home, got it!
Yeah!
Keep it like move!
Now!
Yeah!
There we go!
Yo!
What can we do?
What are we gonna do?
Those are red, then follow some food!
Well, good to funny if you get money, good to bother.
Just your way, how do you what I got to keep the bubbling?
Do you alright?
Do me right, my room's some dope dope!
Tell your man what time it is, it's been called, bro!
I'm not quite sure, as the water's going down, but I'm feeling hungry, don't you worry!
I'm not the thing I have!
We are hungry, what'll we want to do?
Do you have me, the way we go?
Get a more one time, now that we got so what'll we want to do?
Go home, be gone, try to listen!
Tell your man what you got to keep the bubbling, let me go!
Come home, be gone, get a more one time, now that we got so what'll we want to do?
There we go!
Keep it home, got it!
Now that we got so what'll we want to do?
We're gonna be hungry, what'll we want to do?
Got you, got to keep the bubbling?
Going away, gonna do with this love.
Oh two years now.
Yeah, can't fare our way!
Don't you know what it's like?
Go home, be gone, baby!
Oh yeah, come on, you're right, you baby
Oh, that's me, I love what I'll be gonna tell you
Here we go, keep with it, keep it, keep it, keep it
Move on, it, give it to me, you do
All I've been man in my breath was naked, get to your roof and
Hoping Block squeaks man, but hell you don't see, I said I love it
But then in the fiefing style you don't quit, you got to keep on
till the truth, just do it like it, I don't stop
And I'm creating a whole body, nah They're mine's shells, I was actually gonna play
another non-stop track, but reminded me of a good story, I got to share the story.
What are we going to do with it, baby?
I remember Carol, lovely Carol, who used to drive the bedcar limousine in New York City.
This is 1989, and she was telling me a story about her.
And maybe it was in the early 90s.
When Mariah Carey was, she broke up with Tommy Matola.
Good move, by the way.
The slave driver, Tommy Matola, she was married to him.
And she kind of went nuts for a year or two there.
Maybe even three years.
But she was hanging out with heavy D in the boys in the bedcar.
Now the bedcar was a Lincoln limousine, Lincoln towncar stretch limousine.
And the back seat could literally fold down into a bed.
And Carol would drive this car in a new car, very well.
She was really sweet.
But she told me all the inside dirt.
And literally, she told me about the time she took Mariah Carey with heavy D in the boys.
I think it was the metal lance of some concert.
And she wasn't quite sure whether it was Mariah or whether it was heavy D.
But she thinks it was Mariah who actually pooped in the back of the bedcar limousine.
That boy's slim is fucking in heaven.
If that boy's slim is fucking in heaven.
If that boy's slim is freaking in heaven.
You're walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still just walking in hell and you're back, we're still
Hey hey hey hey
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
know, you know,
You're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock,
you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you's a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock, you're a piece of rock
I don't need my youth
No, I need it to pop and beat
The mama, where am I?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I don't even want to hear what I say
I'm gonna do it now, we're gonna do it now, we're gonna do it now
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I don't need to say
I'm gonna do it now, we're gonna do it now
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I don't need to say
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I don't need it, we're gonna do it now
Oh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
No, we're gonna do it now
Ooh, oh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Oooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I'm the fan of the day
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's just an hour
No matter if it's a thing
It's free to make a man your mind
But he's the needin' inside of you
It's up to you
We got the cross to the side
Do me a thing
No matter if it's a thing
We're gonna dance
Do me a thing
I burn my burn and I say
shit man, we're gonna dance
Don't be bad, don't be bad
Don't be bad
Do you a man?
Yeah
No matter if it's a thing
You're a man
Yeah
Do you a man?
No matter if it's a thing
You're a man, no matter if it's a thing
Yeah
It's just an hour
No matter if it's a thing
Let me see you do me now
Raise your arms, raise your knees in and out
Let this act of freedom's way
Cut it, it's fire in the face
As you can from here I would say you ain't My a
too
Elves
fang Sing
Gets
you
You
Eat
recept
Throw
You
I'll go
Ziggart
I'm sure I don't know, I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm
Sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure
Thank you so much for dropping that we've got a whole new category on the Charlie
here.
That's awesome.
You know, last night I was freaking out and tell you around 6 o'clock.
I was getting stuff prepared for the show for today because I really wanted to rock
and hard for you.
In time Warner Cable drops out for over 3 hours and then we're failed.
I'm not the trash, I think I am talking trailer park.
Come to my mansion, get your watch, we sneak it at the dark.
I'll take you higher, higher, I take you lower.
Slower, I make you talk that talk and walk that long.
I'll fuck you by bitch, I'll fuck you by bitch, I'll fuck you by bitch.
I'll fuck you by, you just can't see.
I'll fuck you by bitch, I'll fuck you by bitch?
I'll fuck you by bitch, I'll fuck you by bitch.
I'll fuck you by, do you just can't see?
I' cook you by bitch, I'll fuck you by bitch, I'll fuck you by bitch.
I could ride to just can't see no more
I'm super fried bitch, I'm not that guy bitch
I'll fucking run and leave you face down
Thought you'd give rich thing, fucking with the player
And the people of the nation, you have a busy server
I'll fucking ride bitch, I'll fucking ride bitch
I'll fucking ride to just can't see no more
I'll fucking ride bitch, I'll fucking ride to just can't see no more
I like the long hair swinging in the kelp grind
I'll throw them young stars, fucking with the version of mine
I give a fuck about your papa or your mother, my walk up on your ass
And it's left your brother's safe
I'll fucking ride bitch, I'll fucking ride bitch
I'll fucking ride to just can't see no more
I want the fans to be a matchin'
I want the fans to just kiss
I want the fans to talk to me
Hey stop swapping pictures of Bobby even in the chat room y'all
I want the fans to kiss
I'll fuck you blind bitch
That's uh, oh, there you go. It's from that new category. We've kind of just discovered
I'm trying to reach crazy fair to as one of our top supporters and donors and the funders of today's
Navy source code episode. I quite sure what's going on with this guy.
We got a couple people. The call will for the show is over.
Kind of said that all doesn't keep my property. Everybody.
I'm not sure if you can say I was made for love and hate.
Tonight, I want to give it all to you in the darkness.
That's so much I love you and tonight, I want to play it at your feet.
Cause girl I was made for you and you were made for me.
I was made for love and you made me do what I've made for love and hate.
And I can't get it over you, baby. Can you get it over me?
Tonight, I want to see it go right, feel the magic.
There's something that I've been wanted at this night.
We're going to make it all come true.
It's a girl you will make for me and girl I was made for you.
I was made for love and you made me do what I've made for love and hate.
And I can't get it over you, baby. Can you get it over me?
Tonight, I want to see it go right, feel the magic.
There's something that I've been wanted at this night.
I was made for love and you made me do what I've made for love and you made me do what I've made for love and hate.
I was made for love and you made me do what I've made for love and hate.
And I can't get it over you, baby.
What now? The call the crisis. I've faced a crisis. I've turned on your Skype.
I've tried to make good on my promises here. You need the Skype's up, baby.
Here's how I was made for love and you and lovely Miss Mickey.
You just got back from wherever she was and oh man, she's so nice.
She brought me a tasty, month-centose sandwich from Subway, lovely.
And of course, that's the best of my spear, which is really what everybody loves when we hit that on the show.
All this energy coming me. Back where it comes from. It's such a crude attitude.
It's back where it'd be lies. All the little kids growing up on the skin, so don't leave them rocks.
Leave the rocks, time and change. You need the emergency. Go, leave the rocks.
Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks.
Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Mama knows what she doesn't care. She's got worries too.
Seven kids, I'm on your fair, and the grandest in all you.
All little chicks with a grand-centose, go, leave the rocks. Leave the rocks.
Leave it in sync with the safety, bit your, leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks.
Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks. Leave the rocks.
I've got some records from World War II
I play them just like me granddaddy
It was a rocker and I am too old
Can you believe that rocks?
Cleveland rocks, Cleveland rocks, Cleveland rocks
Cleveland rocks, Cleveland rocks
All across, there's the official home of the Rock and Roll Hollow's fame
Cleveland, Ohio Great Rock
Alright, come close.
Alright, I want you to stick the earbuds really deep into your ear for a second.
But I have some little secret I have to share with you.
We just have to whisper.
No one else needs to know.
I push my fingers into my veins.
It's the old day, so it stops the egg.
I thought it's made of all the things I have to take.
She's a smell of land.
It was its way inside.
It's the fading side.
Good night.
I am streaming till my face collapsed.
I've waited as my time to last.
Now all I do is live with so much pain.
I wish for this, I've missed it out.
I'm left behind as little fat you can't show what you did not create.
I've got to say what I've got to say in the last world.
I guess I'll claim the best for last.
My greatest feeling is like one of the best.
You love the way you can see the pain.
No one else needs to know.
I've pushed my fingers into my veins.
It's the old day, so it stops the egg.
It's the fading side.
I've not got to make it.
Not a aid.
Look me!
With all my love.
It made me feel like a pain.
Now all I do is live with so much pain.
You're no more Attorney for this day.
I've got to say what I've got to say in the last world.
It's not the day, but it's made of all
The things I have to tell the day
It's just never meant
What's it like inside?
The pain is on
I'm not gonna make it
Oh God I've got all the things
Made All I've got
All I've got is the pain
Oh God is inside
Oh God
God is inside
Oh God already inside
Oh God
You got it Einstein!
The separation is not your lie!
OH, there an ice in the open
Speak slowly andms me now!
It goes main for the things God has to say!
Children'll never ask for his help!
And I hate the pain of God, I'm not going to make us
All of us, all of God is insane
All of God's sins, all of God is insane
Yeah, nothing like a little bit of slip, not for everybody here on the daily source code
A lot of work going on behind the scenes, and we're actually going to dial in live right now
With crazy fair to one of our largest supporters
Hello
Yeah, in the morning to you crazy fair to how you doing, man
Hey, man, I'm great
So what happened, dude? Did you get the wrong Skype name?
Yeah, I think I did
I was looking at the notice you emailed me and it had a different Skype name than the one that I got now
So we're all set, we're good
And now are you in Toronto, crazy hurt?
Hey, man, I'm the world's right, now I'm not in the moment, so
Okay
The northern part of all of this is happening, and it's about to
One of the clicks from from Amsterdam
Yeah, and it's only about a hundred clicks out of the North Pole
Yeah, so it must be colder than a witch's tip up there right now
Yeah, man, it's freezing out here, it's about minus 10 degrees, the Celsius
And lots of snow and it's better to stay in the calculation on my iPad
To the DSC with Bobby eating up my side of the shipwalk
I mean, hey, man, what else would you like on a Friday night
I'm wondering how many guys are sitting there behind their computer or as you are with your iPad on the couch
And you know that you're girlfriend, your wife is near buying just like a looking at Bobby eating pictures
And I'm listening to the DSC and I'm in the chat room
I know what's going on
Hey, man, I want to tell you, I'm in a private conversation with Bobby at this moment
And hey, I want to default the sun, I would request it, I want to default it to Bobby
Okay, well, first of all, crazy character, you came in at a hundred dollars on support for the show
Which I really really appreciate and of course that gives you not only an executive producer credit for the show
But also a well, this guy call, of course, and the dedication
So I'd say, I want you to hit it, man, I got it all cute up for you
All right, so I'm gonna dedicate this song, I like big bucks to Bobby eat
And I mean, hey, man, this perfect suits are well
I believe she goes, um, I'm seeing sometimes during the city and hey, Bobby, when you're listening
I believe she will get out in about 10 minutes, she has to sleep as well
I would say, um, you know how to reach me
You're a crazy man indeed
All right, but I think
Thank you
Yeah, right, so if you're being such a douchebag, um, all these all these weeks
Well, hey, I'm happy to, to don't I just a hundred dollars in this penis, right?
No, man, oh, no, no, no, no, let me deduce it
You've been deduce and since since you're trying to get into Bobby's pants, I'll give you a little bit of karma for that
You've got karma
All right, dude, sir makes a lot coming up for you crazy, you can't have a great night take care of yourself, buddy
All right, thanks a lot
All right, take care, bye bye
Oh, my god, Becky, look at her bet
It's so big
She looks like one of those rap guys girlfriends, but you know, who understands those rap guys
They only talked to her because she looks like a total prostitute
Okay, I mean, her bet
It's just so big
I can't believe it's so round, it's like out there, I mean
Girls, what?
She just felt
I like big butts and I can't not lie
You're other rubber stitches and I
You want to go walk see with any baby waist and a round thing in your face, you get sprung
You want to pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up
You know the stats, but you're stuck
Deep in the gdc's wear out, I'm hooked and I can stop staring
Oh baby, I want to get a whip top and take your big job
I hope I try to warn me, but that but you got me
You rap a smooth skin, you say you want to get my bands
But you's me, you's me, cause you ain't that average group
I've seen a dance in
To hell with a grown man, since he's sweat
We've got to go on like a turbo flat
I'm tired of magazines, and flat, but solve a thing
To the average black man, and ask him about
She got to pack much back, so fellas
Yeah, fellas, yeah, the girlfriend got to butt out
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it
It helped me, but baby got badly
I hope I do, yeah, I hope I do
Baby's got badly, yeah, I hope I do
I like them round and big, and when I'm going to get a guy
Just can't have myself, I'm acting like an animal
Now here's my scandal, I want to get your home
And blah, blah, blah, blah
I ain't talking about playboy, but still a cold part
I made for toys, I want a real thick and juicy
So find that juicy double, make a lot to travel
Bagin' for pizza that bubble, so I'm lookin' at rock videos
Not gonna be bimbled, walkin' like hells
You gonna have them bimbled, I'll keep my women like flowjokes
I work to the fix-o system, I wanna get a witch out
I'm gonna cut so a hitch out, but I gotta be straight
When I say I wanna, to the break of dawn
I'm gonna be gotta goin' on, all the same flow
Like this song, cause it pops like a hit, quit it
And I'd rather stay in play, cause I'm long
And I'm strong, and I'm down to get the friction on
So ladies, ladies, people wanna roll my Mercedes
Turn around, check it out, even white boys got the shout
Baby got back
Baby got back, yeah baby
When I come to females, pass my way, got nothing to do with my selection
36, 24, 36
Only if she's five, three
So you girlfriend rolls the hunt, playin' workout, taste my fun
But find that ain't gotta motorin' about the hunt
My anoconda don't want none unless you got buns on
You can do side bins or sit-ups, but please don't lose that butt
Some brother wanna playin' hard roll, and take it at the bank
Go, so they toss it, and leave it, and I pull up quick to retrieve it
So Cosmos says you're fat, we're ain't down with that
Cause you're wasting small and it curves off kickin'
And I'm thinkin' my stickin' to the bean pole dames and the magazines
You ain't it, Miss Thing, give me a six-star can resist
I rap beans and rice didn't miss her
To knock a head, try to dis, cause this girl's a whole lot less
Yeah, game, but it tastes a hit-up
Yeah, pull up quick to get with them
So ladies, if the butt is round, and you wanna triple, let's go down
So I won 900 mixed a lot, and kicked them nasty thoughts
Baby got fat
Lilling a meal, but you got much fat
I miss this girl who's trying to tell me
We made a wunch of same rhythm again
So it's a love of all I know
And money will still go through
Now that we're tired, we shall be all killed
First time we saw that killing you in one
Now that we're tired, we shall be all right
No one will teach you what I want to make
Shake me all night, just let it shake me
Shake it down, break it, break it, break it, shake me
All that you said, all right, no
I know you'll be with me
Spending lots of money all right
I never read it down, out of my hand
And now that you make so thousand calls
Here's me a squeeze, catch my tip and roll
Now that we're tired, we shall be all tied
And we were second and never played
I'll see you've done it in the middle of the night
We made a wunch of same rhythm again
Shake me all night, just let it shake me
Shake it down, break it, break it, break it, shake me
All that you said, all right, just let it shake me
All right, no one will teach you what I want to make
Shake the my body, and do it all right
All night, just let it shake me right
Shake me all night, just let it shake me
Yeah, Bobby, love you too, baby
Bobby, you're in the chat room, cowbell on your radio, baby
All right, everybody can all calm down
All night, just let it shake me
Not what you were in, but I don't know where's Bobby?
Taste me a month and those snacks and just mix it up
Not boss it, I've just got an explosion of taste for all night
And my mouth right now is like out of control, but luckily
Where does it, you can still rock in America
Fuck it, let's do just that
Blow thatcier of all night
All right, let me do it all right, just let it shake me
It's crack, crack, crack, and crack, crack, crack
Oh, it's not that, boy, alright, wait a minute and there
Nothing on your house, or something up to you
I was happy when you were seen
I've got to wake up, I've got to pull around the lights, I'm talking to you
You seem right in the mirror. I'm getting dark, far away yeah
You seem right in the mirror. I'm getting far away God, far away yeah
All night, in the middle of the night, in the air
The sisters took me to the gate door
And those were just a few seconds ago
We had a week to sit with things all day
And how the sound is she makes you get away
And those got ready to go
Time's worth the free for the show
Let out our children we don't know
And I can't walk in, walking in, walking in
We can feel the fire, and the melody
Oh yeah, so high, so good to feel
fucking the melody, yeah, hi, yeah
Oh, night, in the middle of the night
We can feel the fire, and the melody, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you know.
But you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know,
you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey nah nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
I'm pretty sure when I first arrived on the scene at MTV and the mids 80s, that night
Ranger was actually the punchline of many industry jokes.
But I've learned that the arrogance of mainstream media is so far of bays that it's
often the biggest hits that people absolutely want to hear.
That's why I got no shame bitches.
I'll roll it out for you because you can still rock in America.
That's my Ranger on the Charlie.
Chainsley mood just a little bit as we roll into our third hour.
There's a little bit of back eating swing for you because you know,
you can't go back to Jersey babies.
If you are from the garden state,
what's your good jersey maybe never to go back now?
Pick it y'all.
If you are from the garden state,
if you are from the garden state,
Just if I let the girls make me mad
I take and touch it getting up a smile
And leave it, get that in ground for a little while
And make the lamp off, drink all day
She's from me in the face and say
I can't go in there, man
I take it like a jersey, ain't goin' back
Keep up like the jersey, ain't goin' back
I can go back, you gotta do me like that
Go back, you gotta do me like that
Go back, you gotta jersey, ain't goin' back
Keep up like the jersey, ain't goin' back
You're'in a way too big and gotta do me like that
Go back, you gotta do me like that
Like, don't you and the dosya
Now get losty
Don't move around, oh missed it
Don't move around, oh missed the
Flows, you can't do that.
Hey, all my friends, I'll see you on them around my booth.
And my main objective is to keep the bear with what's left left right.
And the night before, last night, something's wrong with that.
My girl, to sit your waist and release you down my phone.
Why?
Because you just do my shit.
I thought we don't want to block.
I pick up my guitar and see it ain't going back.
If you pick up my guitar and see it ain't going back.
I like that man.
It's kind of rocking that.
Can't go back to Jersey, now I get more and more radio guys, why see tweeting about this show is really outrageous. I have to tell you how cool it is.
The idea of complete lemonade, the whole idea of an open source show where you guys are basically putting it together by dropping tunes in your box sharing those with me.
I'm now at about 40 gigs worth of dropbox files, so please, I'm trying to clean up stuff from time to time. You might want to consider that.
I was actually funny. I saw, you know, I get these growl notifications. I got a note that said, do not delete.
So I guess I don't put a file in that one of their folders, do not delete.txt. It says, do not delete has been deleted.
They're like, wow, we have a lot to learn when it comes to the interface.
So this morning, you know, usually once a day, and I do this for a very particular reason, and the reason why I did it was right.
I log on to the bank account. And as you know, we have no credit cards.
Wish I could do only with cash. But of course, you have to have a debit card.
Which, ours happened to also be accepted as credit cards. Only there's no credit on it.
As you know, I'm patently on credit worthy and unhierable and all that stuff.
And I'm like, I couldn't believe my eyes. I'm like, there's like $500 ATM withdrawals in Sacramento, in woodland hills, like all over California, like what that was going on.
And yet, loan behold, someone had a cloned, I think, Mickey's card.
And somehow actually got her pin card.
The pin number, and was withdrawing money. Now I have to say luckily our bank immediately said, no problem.
We'll refund y'all the money and they have to open an investigation all that.
But they say that they will refund the money, I guess, Monday.
But it's a couple thousand dollars and like, holy crap. And these days, by the way, the kind hurts.
Although I have to say the value you guys have provided me for doing this show is exactly what I used to make for doing a four hour.
Uh, weekend shift on Z100. Now I granted there were so many commercial I didn't talk as much or play as much music.
But it's, uh, and of course there's no real adjustment for inflation. But wow. I mean, the system works. I fucking love it.
Anyway, to the whole of the debit card thing, maybe think of this song, which loan behold showed up in the Dropbox.
Your cell phone, your world, your time, your ideas, no barcode, no party, no ideas, no beers.
Your fan card, your license, your thoughts, your fears, no sim card, no disco, no photo, not here.
Your blood, your sweat, your passions, your regrets, your profits, your time off your sessions, your sex, your pills, your grass, your dudes, your laughs, your thoughts.
We won't be drunk, your soul.
You're happy, you're sad, you're here. Give us your address, your shoe size two years.
Your digits, your plans, your number, your eyes, your sketchy, your disheartened, your tears.
Your life.
Show us your children, your photos, your home.
Here.
Take credit, take insurance, take a loan.
Get a job, get a bench, get a haircut, get a suit.
Playings are lottery, play you football, play the fields, or some too.
We'll show you three, we'll show you three, we'll buy you three.
Tell me, you want to know where to sell you crap, we'll judge you.
We're gonna buy big things, we'll run the cash.
Show me, you want your soul.
You want your soul.
You want your emotions.
You're love, you're dreams, you're chapel.
You're residents, you're sweet, you're screens, you're security, you're subrionic.
You're in the sense you're society, you're slow, you're place, you're distance, you're space.
Go back to bed, America.
Your government is at control again.
Here's watch this.
Show us.
You were free to do SME-Tell you you were free to do SME- Tell Y'all
Ta-da!
Guys there's Mahers.
Here's takeaway, k-holared for kk7, Kgcv here's some rock
We're not commercial, we're commercial, we're not scary.
Not to press, buy a video life.
They're trying to call me for a tough year.
So, here's popcorn, here's magazine.
Here's milkshake, here's blue jeans, here's petty barbeque.
Here's long pictures, here's flipper, here's gay stock cap.
There's long pictures, video game, here's cool.
A lot of here's tin, though, and here's two turtins.
Here's collagen, and here's all my nails.
We're lost together.
Now, right now, all we need from people, if you can't be part of a medical team or a search and
recipe team, we just need cash.
I know a lot of people want to send blankets or water, just send you cash.
Watch this.
Shut up.
Go back to bed, America.
Here's American Guardians.
Here's 56 channels of it.
Watch these picturing retards, baby, and fuck their skulls together.
And congratulate you on living in the land of freedom.
Here you go, America.
You are free.
You're too as my turn.
You're too.
You're too free.
You're so.
We want your soul.
We want your soul
No strings, no dropouts, no games
No leftists, no lunatics, no opinions
No opinions, no way
No thinkers, no teachers, no facts
No freaks, no skaters, no tweakers
No drugs, no fun
Here's popcorn, here's magazines, here's music
Here's music, here's music, here's music
Here's popcorn, here's music, here's music, here's music
There we dare me, there we dare me, there we dare me
There we do, there we we long and some emotional
You know it's just a courtesy here to me we need a...
option of the song, we need it with
OrrezM Pardon me, here's some cardacent's name
Here's some
Extra extra extra, you know we need to put that in there
So updated quotes from the president who's laughing
Tellin' you and they never have to take off your shoes
Arthas mayonnaise
On the skype's right now another one over support
for daily source code 854 coming in at double nickels on the dime 55 dollars and 10 cents
the one only sir Kelly spawnberg sir Kelly in the morning to you. In the morning to you
and everyone out there and all boots on the ground. Yeah and the ships at sea exactly.
Hey, man, so are you in now you're in Canada aren't you? Yes, we're going to get
my nation frozen north. Send them all your oil. That's right. It's and thank you so
much for being our source of foreign oil. We're coming to kick your ass soon enough.
Yes, we will look forward to our new masters. Yes. Now, do you have the lovely
Dame Andrea there as well? I'm here. Yeah, she's right here beside me. Yeah, but you see
and see, you were kind enough to turn on the camera, but I'm like, I'm like crying
in my neck and I'm trying to get a good look. Is she off screen on purpose? Is that
what she's done there? Hey, how are you doing, girl? Hell yeah, it's time to get up north.
Ah, you crazy kid. Nice, nice apple t-shirt, by the way, they're so Kelly. You work for
the Uber Lords? Somewhat, yes, we work for an oil field service company side by side here
in our office, yes. Excellent. So what now is it really cold up north there right now?
Or is that just a myth? That's about minus seven degrees Celsius here. So it's a nice
warm day today. Yeah, holy crap. You know, I actually sat outside my t-shirt and the
people's Republic of Southern California this morning was so nice. So listen to our song that we
requested because we're on our way to Hawaii on Monday. Oh, that's so nice. Is this a vacation
or work or what? For a vacation and we're taking all our kids with us, so it's going to be quite
a pack. Okay, now which island are you going to? To Maui. Oh, man, that's so beautiful. You'll
really love it there. How many kids you guys got? Three between us were a blended family plus
taking one more friends kid along with us too. Holy crap. God bless you, man. That's a,
are you going to get any rest of those of vacation? Well, they're teenagers. So they don't
want nothing to do with us anyway. So that's right. Right, right, right, yeah, yeah, I know what
you mean. Mine is a teenager no more, but the pain is still there. She's gone from 19 to 20. I was like,
oh my god, it never stops. So circaling in demand, we really appreciate your support for the show.
Double Nichols on the dime, of course, a code for being a no agenda minute man and minute woman,
I presume. And that's very, very nice. I really appreciate you doing that. And that's how long
you're going to be on vacation. You're going to be able to get the no agenda show while you're there?
Yes, we should be able to stream it. We'll be there for a week. So there's Wi-Fi in the condo. So I think we're
excellent. Excellent. All right. Well, you requested a song, which you were kind enough to put in the
drop box. So I didn't have to, so I didn't have to go and find it. You want to set it up for me? We'll play it.
Yes, being that we're Canadians going to the way the hit a way by the young Canadians seem
appropriate. All right. You guys have a great time, okay? Thanks a lot. Thanks again for all the
support. I'll see you. And enjoy your tune. All right.
And for the fun, we're going to fucking Las Vegas. No one in the sun, we're stuck with it,
we're out there for the fun, running from the rain, passing down the river. And you like the rich,
and for the fun, we're here. We're coming to the air, seven, four, and seven, and you
chat to the moon, we're going to summer, save our money. So I think we're going to fucking
our way, and we're going to fucking our way, and we're going to fucking our way, and we're going to
fucking the rain, passing down the river. And we're going to fucking our way, and we're going to
the second best thing you can do by yourself. And morning, morning,
we're going to be on fire as soon as we arrive.
You skin makes you cry
You float like a feather
In a beautiful world
I wish I was special
You're so very special
But I'm a tree
I'm alone
What the hell about you?
I don't belong here
It's okay
I wanna have to show
I wanna have to fight it
I want you to know this
But I'm not around
You're so very special
I wish I was special
But I'm a tree
I'm alone
What the hell about you?
I don't belong here
It's okay
You're so very special
I wanna have to fight it
What the hell about you?
Whatever you want
Just love my special
Excuse me, I was very special
I wish I was special
I wanna have to fight it
I feel like I belong here
With my friends, Chuckleheads, all in the chat room
Boots on the ground, ships at sea
And the human resources, charged up and ready to go
All pretty much waiting for one thing
Comic strip
And come on in my European Union correspondent friend
Comic strip blogger, Yeho
Hello Adam
Hi Erlin, astronaut Eshol
No man, I don't do that anymore
I wish I was
Here is CSB, you always say the correspondent
Yes, so Adam
Don't hate me please
But WikiLeaks indeed reveals some interesting stuff
Like recent races of some EU commissioners
Now this is the whole thing about WikiLeaks
And I get a lot of E-MailC, a lot of conversation going on
Of course on the know agenda show, we assert that WikiLeaks
Definitely a front for the CIA or some other agency
And they leaked stuff when appropriate for someone's agenda
That's not to discount what's in the memos
But it's also not really new
A lot of this stuff we've actually discussed on the show
And besides that, 3 million people had access to these cables
Because they were not marked top secret, they were confidential
And there's different levels of confidentiality
3 million people in the police state of Gitmo Nation
United States had access to it
So it's not like it's a huge secret
And
I'll let you finish
From West EU towards East EU
But one important thing is this is in this quote
Europeans may agree or disagree with US policy
What Europeans admire is that US is ready to carry out the policies
It thinks best
No matter what the rest of the world thinks
Well, I think that's actually a very sad statement
I don't know what your take on it on the whole thing is
But to me that means we're so docile
We've been floored in it with so much crap in the water
And there's spraying so much crap in the air
We're like, whatever. Yeah, dude, we just rock and kick ass
Yeah, we'll do it. Yeah, we'll go along with that no problem
So what of course is not the end of quote
What of course is not possible in you because some countries are mortgages
And other less cases, cautious and opinion
It's not the same concept like USA
Well, no, it's not the same because let me think
What's the difference? Oh, yeah, you don't even get the fake vote
It's for your president of Gitmonation Europe
It's like you don't need to know democratic vote
At least we get the illusion that we're allowed to do that
But USA, USA, I'm a kind of policy of divide in the concs
In European Union, so you're too bit fucking annoying
Other than by the way, stop smoking, matey
No, no, I will eventually, but it's not time yet
No, quiet. Oh, that was it, you
Oh, comic strip blogger, you know what, ma'am
Despite all your misguidants, I really do love you
And maybe the song give you a little jolt
It's better than the WikiLeaks Trust me
Even looks like freedom to me
Expressions of liberty
Wonning our America to be
A responsible agenda for me
Didn't know I was a communist
But wanting to share the wealth
It doesn't take an economist
To measure the cost of health
And what I believe in
Looks like ever to me
Won human fame
Where everybody's got enough to eat
It's something I want to cover to feed
Didn't know I was a level of terrorist
For Darren to speak my mind
This becoming more precarious
For failing to toe the line
In what I believe in
Sounds like freedom to me
Like the sons of liberty
In 1773
Dumping 45 tons of tea
The norm was in the minority
All people who love the earth
I hope that there comes a priority
Before I get any worse
And what I believe in
Looks like ever to me
Where angels take the shape of a tree
Giving us clear air to breathe
From the river to the mountain to the stream
The no I hated my country
But acknowledging the truth
This was despicable prophecy ring
At the expense of our youth
In what I believe in
Looks like ever to me
All of your men are seen
Living as community
And rather too long
I know it's just a song
But if the whole world sang alone
How much longer would it be this way
She was living in a single room with three other individuals
One of them was a male and the other two were females
Not only knows what they were up to and there
And furthermore Susan I wouldn't be the least bit surprised to learn
That all four of them are betually smoked marijuana cigarettes
Refers
I smoke to drugs in the morning
I smoke to drugs in the night
I smoke to drugs in the afternoon
It makes me feel alright
I smoke to drugs in the night
This life.
I don't care about nothing, man.
Roll another plant.
Eee.
Oh, be careful.
La la la la la, la la, la l, la la.
La la la, la la, la la, la la, la la, la la la.
Okay, you may sing along a few ways.
I was gonna clean my room until I got high
I was gonna get up and find the room, but then I got high
I was gonna go to class before I got high
Come on, y'all
I could've cheated and I could've passed
But I got high
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
I'm taking a next semester
And I know why
Because I got high
I was gonna go to class before I got high
I was gonna go to work
But then I got high
I just got a new promotion
But I got high
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
I was selling dope
And I know why
Because I got high
I was gonna go to class before I got high
Uh, uh, uh
I was gonna pay my child support
But then I got high
No, you wait
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
And I know why
Uh, uh, uh, uh
Because I got high
No, no, no, no, no
I wasn't gonna run from the cops
But I was high
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
I was gonna pull right over and stop
But I was high
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Because I got high
La, la, la, la, la
I was gonna pay my car
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, you, I did not got high
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
I never told you I was spuing away
And I know why
Oh, yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey
Because I got high
La, la, la, la, la
I'm gonna make love to you
I'm gonna sing
I was gonna need you pussy
Now I'm jacking out
I'm gonna sing
Cause I lost my cage
Why?
Because I got hurt
They say what say what say what say what no
I'm sleeping on this spot
Walkin' I know I
Why doing it?
Hey!
Cause I got hurt
Because I got hurt
Latter,atter,atter
I'm gonna stop singin' if snow
Because I'm hard
And I never take good I'm singin' this home
Bingo
Cause I'm hurt
And if I don't want to
Don't want to sell one cup
I don't know why
Yeah, hey, cause I'm high
Cause I'm high
Are you really high on me at the
La, la, la, la, la, la, la
He really is high
Shoot, shoot, shoot, be the one
Get jaguated, skip it, be the
Don't bring it back, bring it back, bring it back
You, you, you, you, you
Say what, say what
Cause I'm high
You, you, you, you, you
My name is Afroman
And I'm from East Palm there
East Palm over there
We ain't, I'd be smoking
East Palm is hey
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Excellent deliver
I don't believe in Hitler
That's what I say
Oh my goodness
So all of you skin skin
Please give me more hand
It's cool
You a bro,
NO NO NO NO NO
Hold on, hey, I owe you
Sometimes double, you
We gon' see
I'm not in these motherfucking ours
Let's put our
Neil Love ot chicken
I throw Matt
World Biotch!
Yeah, Biotch!
Yeah, because they got high.
Drop the cowbell down there.
Hey, all right everybody.
Hey, what are we doing?
Oh, we still got plenty of time left to play some tunes here.
And I'm thinking maybe we need to crank it up just a little bit.
I think before we get into the typical behavior that happens around this moment in the show
when GX2 gets all cranky, maybe we'll do this for him.
What are you guys starting outside my bedroom, guys?
Mike?
What's wrong with you?
Oh!
Oh, very funny.
I was busy thinking it's very clever to know between being a people on the door.
What?
Yeah?
But you just get out the way, please.
I won't get into my bedroom.
Huh?
You know exactly to a story?
What?
I don't like it.
I won't stand on the convention and never stood on the way.
That would be a thiever.
But it will look okay.
Five pounds is getting to my own bedroom.
Ha!
What are you done?
Turn it into a villain.
Ha!
Can't help it, can't help it, can't help it.
Can't help it, can't help it.
A programming note for y'all tomorrow's starting at 9 a.m.
Gitmonation Westtime, the open source daily source code will commence.
We'll be relaying it here on the stream at noagendastream.com.
Baby, when you don't turn, you can go through the disco.
And get most slave and GX2 on a cast of thousands.
We'll be bringing you the open source daily source code.
We'll be relaying it here on the stream at noagendastream.
playing the songs you've just never hear anywhere else on the radio that is the new
radicals and where the kids in America with kind of an abrupt end there well I guess that's
what you get from the Dropbox that of course the Kim Wild Classic let's just keep that rolling
for a moment sorry about that yeah like I brought the song as interruptors Dropbox as interruptors
and then for the week I'm a rock and spread that came off the street I'm trying to kick the piece but I gotta keep up
gotta keep work for these lovely all right beat and I'm set to put it higher ground I'm on my head in the sky
so I let I can't come down because I've been in every town across the nation there should be no stuff
what's going on there, what's going on there, yeah what's going on
This right here is as high as it gets
Somebody liked it
The hell?
Can't the real distance
They've gone a step
So get full force
Don't you yell at me
Have to check
Come on, don't you?
Am I custom best rates?
It came for me
I'm the best thing
You can't keep the trap
Because I smoke that the less
They look
They're back of tired
I get your voice
Don't follow me
To the town
How can you be in front of me
You can't breath
I hate no has to
We can't touch all the medals
I couldn't
Until one thing
So we better pass it
As tonight
We're in fire
Grezer
Prazer
Come on
You take
Hey
Hurry toSenator
Come on
I don't say go, I don't crazy, I don't mind it
It's in the state, don't fire, go higher
Cause when I'm late for the fire, there's so much broken
Make the whole city rise, there's the fighter
And they can all hold well, lift it
One back, and they take the land with a mission
There's no way you can stand this position
You can't dig that heat, get up, about the kitchen
The field the hustle, see we hit in the road
You'll never stop it, you ain't got the muscle
We're got the full of tall, cold boy, this is the show
We've got a cure, blow the stage up, we out the door
Sometimes we all need to escape
Some of we fall off track, you get your mind right and make this dance
I made a fight, put my true heart to kill
Look at you, you feel the ball, the people will need that bill
The town's gonna die, I'll be the heart to kill
You'll be the head of the muscle
The town's gonna die, I'll be the head of the muscle
The world's gonna die, I'll be the head of the muscle
The world's gonna die, I'll be the heart to kill
Once again, the message is in the music
You really got to listen for carefully, but it's there, propagate it
Our formula is this
We go out, we're here people in the mouth.
Come on, say it with me now.
Waters.
You know what you are?
Shut up, sleigh.
Because if you don't speak, you know, sleigh.
Why are you just a sleigh?
I do what they tell you to do.
Black Crow has got an answer.
She flew by Friday, 3rd December 2010.
Blue's too close at the break it down.
A mother said I don't know how to fall this time.
I act to less than the face of your feet.
I never want to let me just say it please.
You want to be here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You want to be me as you do now.
You don't think like a girl, baby.
Please, let me go take the law.
Pull the tension to rise above.
But baby, climb both of us in the air.
But that is to be the miracle.
You want to be here.
But that is not good.
I can stand away.
No, no, no, no.
You want to be me as you do now.
You don't just think like a sleigh, baby.
Please, let me go.
You want to be me as you do now.
But that is not good.
You don't just think like a sleigh, baby.
You want to be me as you do now.
But that is not good.
I will be my friend.
four-scored episode, eight, five, four,
your football Friday, she and he, baby.
I gotta tell you, you know, I've done many,
many live gigs around,
get my nation, particularly,
and get my nation lowlands.
And one of the jobs of the DJ is to keep
the crowd kinda quiet, you know,
when they're acting up, and I'm seeing,
we got a fight brewing here in the chat room.
It's like, we got Marcus Cows on one hand,
and CSB on the other, I'm getting a little worried.
I don't know if I should tone it down a bit,
so we can all just kinda cool off, chill out.
Or if I should hit your heart,
I'll choose for the latter.
I haven't played any in nine inch nails in a while.
I've got money, I'll do anything for you.
I've got money, just tell me what you want me to do.
I've got money, now me, I've got so long.
If I can have money, don't wanna!
I can set hands full once,
that I'll know you!
Ask me how to say my name?
No, it can't!
Live hall!
Live hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall!
Live hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall hall!
I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop
I'll tell you for the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Don't forget to let me go
Ferrari
OK broken money's the smoking full of joy
If God money's that concerned
But I last kept  sick of my Mum endured
For God money let's go dancing on the backs of the rules
At God money's not good
No you can't take it
Know ya can't take it.
SO
Oh, I have died, can you give me time?
So tell me for who I'm interested?
You're going to get what you deserve
So tell me what you deserve
Oh, I have to go
And I'm dying to get you close
But my soul, my soul
And I'm going to get you close
And I'm dying to get you close
Now, I'm dying to get you close
Without dance, and the whole door, to the gang came through, fit me
Where did all this Mark Duries come from?
I don't think that out that you these just won
From someone tell me how to give me some
On the floor in a car on a seat at the bar wherever I go
That's where they are
It's my nose
Now go get it now
I'm nose my nose
It's my nose
I'm going to be a bad boy right now
Feel me as dying to hang out
I know you know what I'm talking about
I've got a feeling you can show me how
On a bus, on a train, on a boat, on a plane
I'm falling in love
What's your name?
It's my nose
Now go get it now
I'm nose my nose
It's keeping in love
I'm going to be a bad boy
I know you know what I'm talking about
It's my nose
I'm going to be a bad boy
I'm not going to be a bad man
I don't think that I could choose just one
Well, it'll be smart girls come from
Someone tell me how to get me slow
It's not a great need for not really
Which one do I want here with me?
They're all smart girls
They're being tied up and tied to you
And I don't understand how you make me lose my mind
I like my girls
Never get enough of those my girls
They're being leveled
They're all smart girls
Now, now class
Class, I want you to pay attention
I want now come on
Come extra, I want you to go over there
And sit at your desk, I want you to sit on one side
Marcus
Marcus couch, I want you to sit over there
Now, boys, now separate
Now, I'm be friendly now, okay
We need a little bit of quiet
And niceness in our chat room
This has just gone too far
Remember now, this is a friendly place
It is your daily source code
So maybe if I just change the music
It'll help y'all calm down
Because y'all be fucked up, you know
Come on people, can we all just kill y'all
Money
Get away
Get a good job with more
Pay your own kid
Money
It's against
Grab that cash with both hands
And make a stretch
Look hard, can we learn
For a start and dream
Think about me a football
Money
Get back
I'm on right, Jack, keep your hands off my
Stay
Money
It's a hit
But don't give me that
You're good, you're good, you're good
I'm in the hot pot
Feel the first glass drum set
I think I need a little ear chat
Oh well
Yes
It's a crime
Carefully
But don't take the slice of my pie
Money
I'm willing so they sing
There's the moon of all the old two days
For the few as clear as it's most impressive in the universe
We've entered into the lounge portion of the show where we help you meet music and children from other lands
This guy's name is Frank Bennett, which I'm sure is a mashup of Frank Sinatra and Tony Bennett
And throw in some tinfoil and I think we've actually calmed everyone down for a minute there
I kinda dig that man, reminds me of the whole anchor stuff that he's been doing and of course of the infamous Richard Cheese
Now let's do one of those only let's do an original because we got stormy weather ahead, my friends
That's right, the ships had seen, we'll have a tough time
There's no one, there's no sun up in the sky
Tell me whether, since my man and I together
Keeps raining all the time
Life is there
And as we everywhere, stormy weather
Since my man and I together
Keeps raining all the time
When he went away, the blues came in and met me
And if he stays away, oh, I can't hear it
All I do is pray that all the buzz
Gonna let me walk in the sun once more
And go on, all I had a life is gone
Stormy weather, since my man and I together
Keeps raining all the time
But time, keeps raining all the time
Stormy weather, since my man and I together
Keeps raining all the time
The time, keeps raining all the time
Stormy weather, since my man and I together
Keeps raining all the time
Sitting at home with my dick on heart
So I got the black book for a freak to call
Picked up the telephone and dialed the seven digits set
Yo this RC baby, are you down with it
I arrived at her house, knocked on the door
Not having no idea what the night had in store
I'm like a dog and he and three without warning
I haven't ever tied for sex because me so horny
Oh, me so horny, oh, me so horny
Girls always ask me why I fuck so much, I say
What's wrong baby dog, where the quick one at?
You can say I'm desperate even call me perverted
But you say I'm a dog when I leave you fucked and deserted
Your dad will be disgusted when he sees your pussy
Pusted, your mama will be so mad if she knew I got that ass
I'm a freaking hate, a dog without warning
My appetite is sex because me so horny
Oh, me so horny, oh, me so horny
The horn section so horny, oh, me so horny
Me love you long time
You said it yourself you like it like I do
Put your lips on my neck and suck my asshole too
I'm a freaking hate, a dog without warning
My appetite is sex because me so horny
Oh, me so horny, oh, me so horny
Adam coming, Adam coming
I'm going to have myself a real good time
I'm feeling like I have a world
I'm getting excited
I'm so horny, oh, me so horny
The horn section so horny, oh, me so horny
I'm going to have myself a real good time
I should stop living through this guy like a tiger
But if I am the laws of morality
I'm racing a, passing by like letting it get diver
I'm going to go, go, go
There's no stopping me
I'm running through a sky
Doener degrees whether call me fucking tight
I'm travelling with speed o Mat, do another thing
I think it's super sonic night out of you
Stop me now
I'm having such a good time
I'm having a boy
Stop me now
Do you wanna have a good time
Just give me a call
Stop me now
I love you
I'm a rabbit ship
Or my way to Mars
On a collision course
I am a satellite
I'm out of control
I have a sense of human-readed to reload
Lying at a bomb
But got a war
Oh oh oh oh
It's blood
I'm burning through the sky
Do I have to decrease
I spotted call me Mr. Farren
High
I'm traveling under the speed of light
I'm having a super sonic night out of you
Stop me now
Do you wanna have a good time
I'm having a good time
Just give me a call
Stop me now
Oh oh oh
It's blood
I'm burning through the sky
Do I have to decrease
I spotted call me Mr. Farren
High
I love you
I'm having a super sonic night out of you
Stop me now
I'm having such a good time
I'm having a boy
Stop me now
Do you wanna have a good time
Go to the sky
Just give me a call
Stop me now
Go to the sky
I'm having a good time
Don't want to stop at all
Did I have to die?
Did I die?
Alright, wait a minute, I need some cowbell.
We've been in our cars, we've planned to start out in the street.
Though we didn't have much money, we barely made enough to survive.
But when we got a lot of space, we got baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby.
Walk in the land of everybody, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby,
Live it on, oked music that we weren't, we got that thing, we were missing when we got the challenge, we got that again. We in the fair and the world, this a
Walk through the wrong thing, everybody is waiting and can't Everything is OK, isn't it alright to buy a new career?
her music
I came by
in partial
old
life
Beata
Take it to the space one night
It's more for me to go, but tellin' it all
Suppose I think this man can't decide
Oh, man, I really can't make a trust
You're gone, gone, right expectations
Where are you, you wanna cry, you don't need me
Oh, I get it, I'm running over me
Everybody's waiting at them
It's a pain in life, let's do the same
It's a pain in life
You know, it's really hard to do that when you only have two arms
And you've got to, I hold the cowbell, you've got to bang it
The cowbell, it is
You've got to control the board
And I've got to have my cigarette
It's like all three things you're wanted to become very difficult
Sometimes I move this whistle to the beat, I'm sorry about that
Boston, this little bit of band stopped on the Boston
The Daily Source code
85 400 in the homestretch right now
As we are willing to hour three
On your poo or Friday
Bring it on home
I know that for the breath, the true
That's the feeling, the two men, you're the only one I want to
I see your face at the depth of a dream
I'll be with you baby, see you around
Please support me, you're the only one
I see your face at the depth of a dream
I'll be with you baby, see you around
Please support me, you're the only one I want to be with
Make me an offer, but I can't refuse to make me respect to my own man.
It's time for my last time in the end and for my life.
So like it or not, you'll take a long time.
It was your life, keeping my love in your world.
I told him it all or night because that's why I am.
Be women's I'll make...
Keep in mind not to beg for a lie.
We're having this only a horny man.
Every dives can it be all the horny ones.
I don't mind, and maybe I'm all I need
Because what I am, I'm all of you alone
You're doing good, you're doing good, you're doing good
You're doing good, you're doing good
I don't mind, and maybe I'm all I need
Nothing like a word from big Greek crank in the background
I've laid it for you, that's right
Who call am I?
I've laid sticks, that's right
I have no shame whatsoever
Because I know that deep down secretly
That's exactly what you wanted to hear
Alright, let's just bring it back to a decade
close to where we are today, shall?
Heads that be talking
We should get a kind of into the groove even GX2 or like slippery people
GX2 or like slippery people