this is a no-agenda stream and daily source code special report as reported I believe
live during one of the most recent daily source codes the no-agenda official no-agenda
porn princess and of course adult film star Bobby Eden has promised through her twitter
account blow jobs to every twitter follower should the Netherlands win the world cup
now from what i understand uh... the uh... the western media has been uh...
vigilantly pursuing Bobby
uh... together uh... on for an interview to talk about this and uh...
bobby Eden has chosen uh... the no-agenda stream and daily source code audience
to do the only and exclusive interview about this promise and so
i'm very proud to welcome uh... Bobby Eden to uh... to the stream bobby how you
do on
very good how are you died i'm great at first question most importantly what are you
wearing right now
nothing
I know you're lying to me i know you're lying to me
Bobby what's going on tell me what's happening this is like a huge media storm
i know it's fantastic
and
well as you said
accraments to give them a free blow job all my twitter followers do you have
exactly on your twitter account
i think thirty thousand thirty one thousand
i'm very so in one day twenty five thousand so that's like uh... three every
second Bobby
i don't know how you're going to do that now you you actually
if i remember your tweet properly you promised that a number of your uh... associates
and colleagues are going to help you out with this uh... endeavor who else is in on the
scheme with you
the secret and the secret
so they're all all in
so we're a team bj
team bj
bj
and that would be a
dressed in orange as you pay off this uh... this wonderful dead of yours
of course with my nice orange and dress
oh lovely now
what if the net ones doesn't win i mean you're obviously you know you're trying to
help the team orange win by uh... by motivating everybody what
what if they don't win then what happens
well done
probably nobody gets a free blow job
then it really sucks
so big time actually won't suck is it is it's what you're saying uh... that would
be horrible okay so we too we all have to attend to root for uh...
yes of course for me
so there is actually
no chance they're going to lose
the winning bobby where uh... where will uh... we'll be able to collect uh... our
prize uh... come uh... well after the weekend i guess
after we can numb they i will tell you everything we're to collect it
and so uh... we just to keep an eye on your on your twitter feed i guess
and of course
man i'm so excited about this you know and uh... miss Mickey miss Mickey also
wants to blow job by the way
oh really
yeah you kidding she's what she's been from
something else for Mickey
okay
uh... uh... nice
uh...
as long as i can take pictures
so Bobby you're still in the Netherlands
yeah you're still in the Netherlands right now
yes i still
and
because you're
uh... the third week of July we'll end this two
live two weeks of July i'm leaving uh...
for my tour
from going to make more people happy
so tell me about the tour where will this take you
uh... i'm first going to the stage has a nice holiday
and meeting of course we're speaking
and then and we'll be doing shows in Finland
Germany
Holland
a France
and while the whole tour continues
but we'll do a list
time
no i was going to ask if you're going to do any uh... shows in the united states uh...
anything while you're here is that just pure vacation
yes
purification
what uh...
what exactly do you want to meet up with you
yes and i'll make it easy and i'm like hell yeah
gone away
what uh... what exactly uh... can the fans expect from one of your shows
well uh... on the most shows i do have a list of you think that
what i'm doing a bit of very good friend of mine so we do let's be in
shows
uh... nice
and we do everything
and uh... we do signage and they can take pictures with us so
that's a bit of a
yeah it's a beautiful thing
hey how do you do
new movies coming out uh... soon or did anything that's uh... that shot that still
has to be released or you have any plans
yes everything will come on on my new sides bobby either live dot com
oh
so i've been shooting
a shooting and shooting
but there's nothing else it with my new books on video so
that's the new boob's right yeah
so are these your own productions or these uh... yes
okay you know have you ever worked for vivid entertainment
no no i have so many uh... many crossings for them
but i never uh... no i never did something for them
no because you know the house that that were there were in now here in the uh...
hollywood hills the hilltop watch tower
crackpot command center apparently has been featured in many vivid entertainment
productions i'm just trying to find out which ones and i was you know
had the only diffid ones or the other one still because maybe i've done something
i mean your house already i know it bobby of you come by like hey i know this place
i know i've been over here
and maybe and i don't know if it's specifically vivid the neighbors weren't that clear about
it but uh... well because it's always secretly there
extremely extremely
well uh... and then they always say
please just park the car somewhere
and park the park all
all the inside secrets to the adult film industry
everybody i love it well uh... we certainly look forward to a welcoming you here to the
uh... to the studio in a couple of weeks time when you're on your holiday
uh... and maybe we'll uh... maybe we can do a little uh... interview from the hot tub
about here on the deck
of course
i'm so much lucky back
and
well of course
are you kidding yeah i've been working out i've got them on this program
you know
yeah i've had on the three by it's a long story but it's a
three months and then i get a special prize it's uh... i'll tell you when you're here
oh yeah
i'm curious
and you might be curious now
so Bobby uh... well uh... are you
ideas and any special preparations or any exercises you're doing uh... to get ready for
you're in training my job
alright well we will certainly be rooting for a team orange for the nevelins uh... i've
changed my stance now i've the go orange all the way
and uh... on the monday i guess we'll figure out exactly where and how we can collect uh...
once you uh... post this either on uh... on your twitter
which is uh... at bobby eating uh... or uh... bobby in live dot com is that or dot
and out what is it yet dot com dot com
bobby it's been a pleasure talking to you as always and uh... well i i hope you uh...
hope you make it through uh... next week it's it's going to be a rough one
just go for the next team
the greats bobby eating everybody right here i know you stream dot com and daily source
code dot com thank you