Delta Sierra Charlie 827
We're 16 months to 7 minutes and showing 5 9s of time turns
The 21st century of radio stars here
We are the most deepest in being alive
I know it's gonna strike out
Fantastic, it's a sugary
Come on, feel the no-hoids
Girls, rock your forehead
We're getting wild, wild, wild, wild
So you think I gotta be fine
I tell you honey
I don't know why
So you think my singing's out inside
It makes me money
I don't know why
In it more
I don't know
So come on, feel the no-hoids
Girls, rock your voice
We're getting wild, wild, wild, wild
So I feel the no-hoids
Girls, rock your voice
We're getting wild, wild, wild, wild
So you think I gotta be fine
I don't know why
In it more
I don't know
So come on, feel the no-hoids
Girls, rock your voice
We're getting wild, wild, wild, wild
So you think I gotta be fine
Girls, rock your voice
We're getting wild, wild, wild, wild
So you think I gotta be fine
I don't know why
Why you think we are the reason time
Yes you know better
I don't know why
I don't have my
So you say I'm gonna turn in mine
I will beat your fear
I don't have my
And more I don't
Come on, feel the noise
It's a Friday
You're a Friday
You're a Thursday
I'm a Quad so recover
You're a Friday
I'm a Friday
You're a You're a Friday
You're a Friday
Are you going to work tonight?
один tonight
A gentleman
I AM 1
My child
Here's the full還
Deli's horsepower must electromagnet
We've got the cube and hurricane on the base with quiet right
My buddy Ruby similar to us, who is hangar with it
Last night, at the Golden God's Award, I'll talk to you guys that later on.
Gotta make a check at the pool and a foreign store in the chat room.
I mean, this place is great for what?
No agenda.com is where you can join in the party and of course, no agenda stream.com.
We've blasted to your live every footballer's flighting.
From the hilltop, watch tower, pack my command center.
We're landing in California.
I must be worried to be able to say,
I'm a day like I'm dead.
I've met a group to me on a fire.
I'm the sunlight of tears.
When I'm out to get out of the corner,
I'm going to get out of the corner.
It's been me my good night and never hurt.
Oh, it's over, I can't believe it.
I've set my meals, kids, don't worry.
It's not that much, I'm going to play it guitars a day.
When I'm out to get out of the corner,
I'm going to get out of the corner.
I'm going to act like I'm getting out of the corner.
I'm going up to get out of the corner.
Oh man, I gotta tell you, I'm loving life here in Southern California, Lenny Gravitz, put it to words and music just perfectly.
It is quick and time, everybody, it is Friday, it is the 9th of April 2010.
It's the football Friday, the show that's about everything, and then again it's about completely nothing.
Just about having a party on your iPod, your iPhone, your Android, G-Phone, or maybe a blackberry, or just on your computer at work.
Why you might even be addressing for people live somewhere?
Drink it out, turn it on.
Something we used to call radio, and now it's live in no genderstream.com.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah love, cool, cool, like, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, for it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah,, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, that yeah,
I want to be in a counterkill and so on
I never miss it
I want to shake the whole thing
Look at it on the one to three
I never be, I never tell
No, I don't play for me
It's not time, it's time
It's so filled with love
I'm going to win it for all I want to do
I can't see the time
Turn up the radio
I can't hear the music, it needs to move
I want to be in a counterkill and so on
Turn up the radio
I need a new music, it needs to move
Let's get the official pronunciation right
It's off the graph
Turn up the radio
I want to thank everyone who has contributed to the show
By sending in tracks
Marcus got your assistant very last minute
I'll see if I can work that way
I got so much music lined up for today's show
It's unbelievable
And some old friends returning to the show
And of course all this is brought to you
By the sustaining producers of the knowledge of the stream
At no origin of stream.com you can find them all listed there
I'll talk about that later
But of course first we have to celebrate the fact that is the end of the week
One, two, three
Come out and turn it off
It's great and tight
Let's go home, screw the buzz
Okay, one more before you break it down, okay?
Find Dutch Group, do we uncover us?
I'll find out my find Dutch Group
I don't mind coverage man as long as they've done
Just as to the song, present and famous
I've got this on and now to talk
I've been like a silver thread
I've been summoning beauty in love
I've been as was her name
She's got it
Your baby, she's got it
No, I'm your Venus
I'm your fire at your desire
I'm your Venus
When this were a crystal eyes
Making everything else mad
Black is the dark in the night
She was going no one else had
She's got it
Your baby, she's got it
I'm your Venus
I'm your fire at your desire
I'm your Searl
I'm your Venus
I'm your fire at your desire
I'm your Searl
I'm your Venus
I'm your fire at your desire
Oh yeah, I've got to get that out of my system.
Now we had a great light last night going to golden gods awards at the Nokia LA Live theater
by invitation of my good friend Rudy Sarzo had seen and we actually figured it out 20 years
Christina wasn't even born the last time we saw each other. Of course we talked about Rudy a couple
years ago on the daily source code when he released his book off the rails about his life on the road
with with Randy Rhodes and the book is still selling it's say you can check I think it's a Rudy
Sarzo dot com anyway hooked us up got us some passes into the event I haven't had a laminated
all area access pass in many years my friends it was good one of those again and it was great there
were so many people there who I who I remembered recognized and they actually remembered me
see Alice Cooper was there running James Dio just tons tons of awesome talent of course it was one of
those TV shows that was not done live to tape or or broadcast live so the show itself and it
looked great on television I'm sure but it really sucks when you got like guys all cranked up and ready
to go you got slash on stage and he's bringing people out and then they have to wait for the cameras
to reset and just all the energy gets sucked out of the room I'm pretty sure they're going to have
to put in crowd shots of people being very happy because there was a lot of like what what's going on
but backstage was was where it was really happening and the best part of it all is they had
goody bags from hustler yeah interesting stuff in the goody bag I'll say hey welcome back a good
friend of the Charlie who didn't even know we were back on the air he's done tons of stuff
in the past years he's from the Netherlands and his name is Raymond we call him Ray for short
and he put together a little ditty to celebrate the return of the Charlie onto the airwaves
oh wait a minute hello yeah come on in come in juicy hi is this the deadly source code
hope it's time to be a part of us again someday I want my dears and welcome back welcome back
welcome back welcome back hey Adam it's nice to hear you again the source code I must say
I really miss you man so first of all congratulations with your new born you and I'm glad
everything worked out fine for you and your loved ones like I said before life is too short to
not leave the life you want to live no we'll know the crossroads of the life unless they dare to take
the exit so it's a new spring it's a new life and I'm feeling good okay before I start
new episode of Ray on the Charlie I've got to admit something let me think okay actually I'm not
that good in English really thanks for all the chocolates I'm from the Netherlands and English is not
my mother language so I kind of do a lot of prep before I can record a new Ray on the Charlie
I actually got to write this scripts and use some Google translations before I can build these
episodes let me tell you a little story before I was allowed to do my English exam when I was in
high school back in 1990 I had to score a 9 I think that's an 8 in America but I had to score a 9
on my English to do the actual exam something I've never could have done without okay still the essay
out of my teacher's office well that's out of my system I remembered after the test I went into
the teacher's office to check the results of the test and the teacher was sitting behind his
desk and told me I scored a one a D and I thought to myself 13 possible why is this man
messing with my test I knew already I made one mistake on purpose so it would not stand
in afterwards he called me into his office and told me I scored a 9 and I could go to the exam
he was only testing me I can ask oh anyway you've opened up Adam found that you're new you
you're new life and a lovely girlfriend and I failed to answer your openness with this little
confession from my best so a new start of the source code I've thrilled and excited but I first got
some catching up to do I'm listening for the last five hours to the last five episodes of the Charlie
I really have to pay more attention and monitor my Twitter because then I had known you started
these new shows already a month ago Adam it's good to have you back I'll do chuckleheads reunited
on the chuck to hide to make you for me take care I love you bro okay thank you so much my friend good
to have you back on the show and it looked like the chat room is hot and I'm heating up no
agenda chat.com we continue with a nice mashout
tonight I'm a lot to be the captain tonight I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to be
I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do
I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do
I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do but I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do I'm a lot to do
Take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it.
Come by and I give you two precise, this is my last reaction, come by and I give you two, next, come by and, come by and I give you three sides, okay three sides, ultra-decisball, this is my last reaction,
Come on, man, Digest Molly really knows how to mess up doesn't he? Digest Molly, root boy, resort, you can find links to that track and all the other songs played on the Charlie and the show notes of DailySourceCoat.com.
Well, we bring the art of old school radio back to your iPod, your iPhone, whatever the hell you use and differences make. That's the beauty of it.
It works everywhere. Soon you'll just turn on your car radio. It would be like, oh, there it is. It's stream and no agenda stream.com.
I'm pretty excited to tell you, Monday, the, the creamy as we call her, the shvarkenheimer, but it owners my daughter will be coming over for two weeks, so I'm going to pick her up at the airport. Unfortunately, because I booked this ticket for her, I think in October, October, November. She has to fly in the San Francisco, so I'm going to go to San Francisco, pick her up, bring her into Los Angeles.
And I think she's going to have a pretty good time. I am praying, of course, for good weather. I can just imagine her sitting here with the clouds going overhead and saying, why does all the bad stuff always have to happen to me?
That's going to be great. Maybe I'll get her on their show. She used to come on the source code for time to time.
It's this pod save, it's the lingus in the morning sun.
In the morning sun, I rolled a fat blood just to wake me up. Sometimes I find it hard to understand the way it can.
From your point of view, you'll find this true, and you'll just throw your eyes, but in your mind you'll see, it's not all that she thought it was.
Because I wonder what I can sometimes every time you come around and tell me all the things you do.
The things that change out the ways you're present to us, they'd say that message is not yet true.
And the morning sun, I rolled a fat blood just to wake me up. Sometimes I find it hard to understand the way it can.
Because I wonder what I can sometimes every time you come around and tell me all the things you do.
The things that change out the ways you're present to us, they'd say that message is not yet true.
From the positive music network, these days known as musicalley.com, the link is in the morning sun here on the football Friday for the resource code episode 827 plus funny last night.
We were hanging out at that golden god's award show.
And I could feel like some eyes in the back of my neck and then Mickey said, I think this guy wants to talk to you and turn around.
And this is a big rocker, he's got the leather zone, he's got his tats, he's got a really long hair and a couple of guys.
Actually, I'd seen these guys around.
I don't really recognize him. Oh, maybe I do him, not sure.
And the guy says, and by the way, I get the sweetest handshake from him just like really soft and he's like, hey man, I'm Jesse from rock sugar.
Like, oh, I love you guys.
Of course, they do live mashups and I'm still waiting for their CD to arrive in the mail.
I tried playing a couple of their tracks off of the YouTube clips, but it just sucks too bad on the stream, there's no quality.
So it was great, you know, it was really, I love the fact that I'd played him on the source code, but maybe two weeks ago.
And you hook up the world as vast, but in a way, it's kind of small and I really like that.
And it's basically, it's the magic of the internet, it brings us all together.
Now this one was submitted to adamaccurry.com.
It's, uh, I think it's fun, save everything they have in Album yet.
I like it, I find dragons, don't you?
Don't you, don't you want to party?
Leave all the bullshit at the time.
Drink up, so you don't have to think I know.
You're just falling in your door.
We open half our time, running around for you, my mind.
We spend the other time.
We've added that some rain just to get flat by.
Just to get back.
Don't you, don't you want to be famous?
Right things like you don't even care.
And everywhere you go, have everybody stop and stand by now.
We open half our time, running around for you, my mind.
We spend the other time.
We've added that some rain just to get back.
Just to get back.
Don't you, don't you want to know with things?
And see if that's a matter of the harsh?
With every word you say, you tell it to people's words that are not born.
You say, no way, no time to stop.
We open half our time, running around for you, my mind.
We spend the other time.
We've added that some rain just to get flat by.
We've added that some rain just to get back.
Just to get back.
I like it.
I find dragons.
Don't you want to party?
I believe it's pot safe.
Although maybe not officially listen on the pot safe, using that word.
I dig it.
Very nice.
So we have an official celebrity in the chat room.
A lot of you, of course, listen to the show on your iPod or some other portable device.
It says it wasn't tended originally when we put this podcasting thing together.
What's kind of new though is the idea of putting, or for me, at least, it's not new and general.
Producing the show live, putting it on the stream.
We got a lot of shows running at noagendastream.com.
Of course, the noagenda show that I do with John C. Dvorak tomorrow morning.
In the morning, we'll do another, I'm sorry, Sunday morning.
We'll do another early service edition.
Then there's the Dvorak Horowitz unplugged show.
There's a daily source code.
We're looking for a couple more.
And we're slowly building it up.
It is nice to see that at any given moment, it's actually going up a little bit.
There's probably about, I'd say 90 people listening to the stream, which doesn't seem like a lot.
But when you take any consideration that they can listen live, you can just check in, sample it wherever you are.
Or if you want to get any of those shows as a podcast, it's cool.
But the live part, for some reason I really like it.
I'm a radio guy.
I've been a DJ really all my life.
I've been anything.
It's that.
And we used to have something called, what was it?
Oh, yeah, telephone.
And people would call up during the show.
And they'd say, hey, I do a man play this song for me.
And now I've got people in this chatroom from around the world.
And I'm watching him talk with each other and
yapping back and forth.
And it's all live.
And I'm getting actual, not just interesting info and feedback, but in pulses.
And in the chatroom today is, someone who I've never met, only virtually speaking,
Bobby Eden, who is a well-known porn star.
And I say that with the utmost respect and humility.
Because you know me and porn.
I encourage it.
I think it's absolutely awesome.
And she checked it.
It's awesome to have a diverse crowd checking in at noaginachat.com.
Time to break it down.
This is kind of where, you know, if you're getting ready to go out, you might want to start getting dressed
and stand in front of the mirror, check yourself out.
Kind of get into the swing of things.
For me, it's perfect here in the sunshine of Southern California.
Exactly that cool breeze is kind of blowing up from the valley.
It's beautiful.
Chicago beginnings.
When I was with you, it doesn't matter where we are.
Oh, and when you're in, I'm with you, that's all that matters.
Time passes much too quickly.
When we're together laughing, I wish I could sing it to you.
Oh, no, I wish I could sing it to you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, if I ask you, if I ask you, if I ask you, if I ask you, I ask you for
We've been trying to sign which one
I should try to put him to earth
Oh no, you can try to put him to earth
Oh no, no, no, no, no
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no
It must be our facility
Sun..
Oh
Yeah, that's all that I'm thinking
Oh, what I want to feel better
Oh, that I'm thinking
Oh, that's just a stop, yeah
I got to get you in a matter of power
Got to get you next to me
Oh, that I'm thinking
Oh, that's just a stop
Oh, that's funny
Mickey's outside there
Enjoying the sun and she's listening to the show
I'm from Noah gender
I think a pocket Noah gender
I phone app is like
Hey, say hi to Bobby for me
I'm practicing
I think Bobby's coming to Los Angeles and the summer
Definitely get her on the show
Talk to her about her life
Oh, that I'm thinking
Yeah, that's just a stop
Yeah, that I'm thinking
Oh, that I'm thinking
How do you love me, Jimmy?
For those of you who are near to the show, you're kind of slowly getting back into the swing of things.
We talk about technology, we talk about stuff going on in my life.
We talk about things from outer space.
There's been a lot of activity in that room lately.
On Fridays, we do the Fubar Friday edition, which is basically just a bunch of good music,
meant to lift your spirits, make you feel good about life.
And I tell you, when I hear this from Chicago, which Ray hooked me up with,
it's the seven-minute version of the beginning.
I can't wait for my shit to get here from London.
I miss my cowbell along with my compressors, my limitters, my disorders, my mixer.
Hell, I'm even waiting for my nickname to show up, you know, like right,
motorcycle, trophies, my t-shirts, my uniform that I wore in a rack.
But it's been weird without my stuff, but the cowbell.
That's really the one I'm waiting for the most.
Imagine what I could do with this.
So we're a minor that this program is completely commercial-free,
as is everything at knowageindustream.com.
You can support this program and others by showing your support in donating,
go to devourac.org slash n-a-s that's November,
Alpha Sierra, and you can become a sustaining producer of knowageindustream.com.
Here's a guy who I used to play a lot of back in the day.
Jersey Todd sent me a couple of his tracks just to remind me of him.
And I think we'll get Jersey Todd back on the show soon enough.
So why you?
Were the great message getting out live with all the little things?
Please, Tom, I'm a boy as he serves up such songs.
You gotta see it, man.
And boy, you're Jimmy, but Jack, with your doing a cash beer with being rich.
So go with Southern Rock.
He plays guitar like he comes his hair, so smooth.
He's the dog in the band.
May I see him, man.
Get him.
Get out the house out in the street.
I need to tag you though.
Get off, catch him.
I need all life for style.
I'm not like you leave him.
That made him bad.
Just wake him even.
Live a little.
Love a lot.
Come on, come on, get out.
Live a little.
Love a lot.
Come on, come on, get out.
Live a little.
Get out and walk and roll for you in the rocking chair
99% of life is
Yep, just be there
Yep, I won't hide my memory
Give it all
Get out
Get out of the house,!)
You're selling the street on your divorce
Get off the couch, get off the line
If you don't like post out
1991, but I can leave it
You might've been alive
Just make it even easier
We don't have the same speed
I need to tell you
Get off the couch
Get off my pillow night
First hell
Just laugh it about just waiting
Even live a little
But right
Take a little chance
Don't let you go
I love the lyrics
Get off the line
Feel like you
Yeah
Grab it
Let it blow
Love it like
And
I just wanted to mention
I got another celebrity in
In the chat room
Angie B
The sexy soul treat
Tulsa tones of Angie B
It was nice this
Yeah, so many people say
Oh, why don't you do video
And turn on the webcam
Like no way
I want you guys to be
Imagine where I am right now
In my hilltop
Watch Tower
Crackpot Command Center
I want you to be imagining
People are in the chat room
And all they've got is words
They don't see anything
And they're talking to each other
And they're imagining
What their own environments are like
And this theater of the mind
It's you know
You can read a book
That might be a good idea
From time to time
I encourage it highly
But also this type of
Just imagination
It does actually
Help fire
Synapses in your brain
It does something to you
And you will feel much better for it
And
Seeing as
The chat is such an important part
These live shows
I encourage everybody to bring a couple
Friends in
It's really easy to hop on
As you go to
Actually, if you go to
No agenda chat.com
But you can get to it
From other places
Well
And
Bobby Eden, please
Feel free to bring some
Your friends next time as well
Well
The light's
Now
I am an
And you can't stop
And I can't stop
Don't know what I want
But I know how to get it
I want to destroy
I'll survive
Wanna play
Yeah
And I can
Now
Don't
But
And I can't
Farther
You can't
Yeah
It's coming some time
I'm an
I can't
I can't stop
Trafficking
I can't
Traffling
As I've been
I can't
Fly
Wanna play
Yeah
And I can't
I can't
Fly
Keep
You
I can't
Fly
I'm running wasted, go watch everyone
I has the best prize of rest
I miss the enemy, I miss
And I can't survive
I'm running wasted, go watch everyone
I have the best prize of rest
I miss the enemy, I miss
And I can't survive
I miss the enemy
I miss the enemy, I miss the enemy
I have the best prize of rest
I miss the enemy
And now that comes out and I'd say
I wanna play
Yeah, I wanna play
And I wanna play
I have a game in the UK, sex pistols
I'm the football fried, not only a very appropriate for a fried edition of the chuck
But also because we lost a great one yesterday
Manager, legendary manager of the sex pistols
Malcolm McLaren, passed away, it was 64
I don't think anyone really knew how ill he was
And to me, it came as a shock, you know, like 64 crap man, that's young, that sucks.
And of course, he was legendary in the London scene, he lived with Vivian Westwood.
I started a lot of the amazing fashion trends in the 70s, and he will be missed not just
for the work that he's done, but for who he was.
And luckily, he does leave legacy behind, and he lives on in his own, by carousely through
songs like this from the Sex Pistol.
So, Rest in Peace, Malcolm McLaren.
They say good fences, make good neighbors, for you, my friend, this might be true.
But you still gotta play, boys, I'm a little too slow, I'm sorry.
Sayin' hello to my little friend, Alan and Gary, I'm a very source call.
I got that TV in the corner, and that's their greatest dream, and I'm a little
slow.
They poison your mind, my child, with their fear and their guilt and the wounds.
They teach you that you're just a number, as they program you in school.
So, by the time you're out in the world on your own, you've been trained not to buy
your own, you've been trained not to buy your own, you've been trained not to buy
your own, you've been trained not to buy your own, you've been trained not to buy your own,
you've been trained not to buy your own, you've been trained not to buy your own, you've been trained not to buy your own,
you've been trained not to buy your own, you've been trained not to buy your own,
you've been trained not to buy your own,