Delta share Charlie eight four nine are the snafu side of the edition
I got air, fling that out of me, and it won't, I got more
Then I could ask for, I don't have to run around
I don't have to stay out all night, because I got me a sweet, a sweet love and warm hand
It's your note, just how to treat me right
For my baby, that she's all right
For my baby, that's clean outside, don't you know that she's
She's so kind of wonderful
She's so kind of wonderful, yes she is
She's so kind of wonderful, yes, yes, yes
When I hold all in my arm, you know she sets me so long back
Ooh, and the baby kisses me
My heart becomes feelin' this eye out
When she repelore the novel around me
About to pass me out of my man
Yeah, give my baby kisses me
She's been up and down my spine
For my baby, that she's all right
For my baby, that's clean outside
Don't you know that she is
She's so kind of wonderful
She's so kind of wonderful, yes she is
You know, yeah she's so kind of wonderful
We'll kill the killer with death
I'm talking talking about my babies
I'm kind of a wonderful talking about my baby
I'm singing about my baby
I'm standing on the bow
I'm playing about my baby
I'm being accompanied by my baby
I'm sitting on the bow
Falling to the morning to everybody
It is the daily source code episode 8 sword
9le
The start from Saturday
This year has changed
It has been kind of eased
Into things don't makeuyors bleed
Right off the bat
seems like not just myself, but a couple of people in the household as well as some of the
chuckle heads at the chat, you know, agenda chat.net where the party is always happening during
the live sessions are a little bit under the weather. What is it? Perhaps it's the crap that
have been country like we got shit weather in the hilltop watchtower crackpot commander today
people I tell you.
Don't regret it, you could guess yes, yes.
I was waiting, you got to feel scared in the head.
I was waiting for you, we'll stand by and promise my faith.
Well, it's all the way up, but it's the death, it's all the way up, but it's all the way up,
okay, we can't catch it, it's not just death.
Oh
I was round, I walked off theencies, I stuck down to
Now I'm not a man for a day
I feel down
Some of the things that I've called me today
Damn, yeah, I'm proud
I don't feel down, but I'm still afraid
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm proud
We'll fight, fight, fight, fight
Where the hell that you saw?
Where, who is that?
Where you hidden
I, with you, yes, more
I hope you change yourself
Can't break
What's the gas
Come to get red
Can't break
I got a house full of chips here, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course, she lives here, I've got
at Chrissy Curry who has been out with the flu on the couch for two days, and then special guest
appearance by Miss Molly Wood, who came by last night, and we had a nice dinner, and we all
hung out, and let me just tell you one thing, there's been plenty of jacuzzi work going on here,
the head of the crew, the second best thing you can do by yourself, and morning, step by
all of you guys are here, I got a house full of chips here, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course,
I got a house full of chips here, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course,
I got a house full of chips here, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course,
I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course, I got a house full of chips here, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course,
I got a house full of chips here, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course, I got the lovely Miss Mickey of course,
I was always thinking to myself, it's so amazing how the pharmaceutical company, of course
I didn't think of them as pharmaceutical companies, but how the drug companies are always
advertising, claritan, and all kinds of anti-conjusted and congested stuff, and flu medicine,
and always at the right time, just when I had the flu, and it's been pretty bad for the
fast week or so, and now it seems that everybody has it, I mean, you just got to think
that even early on, I knew that there was some kind of conspiratorial behavior going on
between all of these companies, doing all this weird shit, anyway, got to get your flu shot
everybody, right?
She was, and then I left the place to become a man, and I never thought I'd see her again,
and I even failed, remember in her name, but the other night, and the studio fit me,
she can suddenly walk in through the window, and she said it now, in my mind again
I can live for another thousand years when I see the eyes of Jenny,
because I can't say that to another place, another time, and I remember in her name,
but when I see the eyes of Jenny, if that may take me to where she knows how far the
place of mine, she's so me, she's almost a twenty-five, and through some struggle,
and some strategy is pretty, ooh, like shit was, it's not the color,
not the size, yes it's the promise, and those eyes and makes it pretty, through like shit was,
and then I left the place to become a man, I don't know if I'll ever see her again,
but I'll always be, remember in her name, because the other night, and the studio fit me,
she can suddenly walk in through the window, and she said it now, in my mind again
I can live for another thousand years when I see the eyes of Jenny,
because I can't say that to another place, another time, and I remember in her name,
I remember in her name, and I remember in her name, and I remember in her name,
and I remember in her name, and I remember in her name, and I remember in her name,
and I remember, thank you very much, Ray, who will be dropping by later with Ray on the Charlie episode 44,
I have not listened to it, of course, because, well, that's the big surprise, he rolls out the soundtrack to my life.
And I think we've turned yet another corner with a daily source coverage, of course, started off actually as a really just a test broadcast for
The engineers out there making receivers better known as podcast aggregators now we've
morphed into this three to three and a half hour show every single at least once a
week.
I'm pretty much once a week and it used to be me pulling stuff off of not actually it
was a pod safe music and then it was independent music and then it was iTunes music
and now with the advent of of Dropbox being added to the mix it's fantastic.
I've really like in this you guys have shared all these Dropboxes with me and I literally
have just watched the songs come in throughout the week and I'm like okay I can
remember to play that and you are actually controlling the program and it's
entirety now so if you want to please share your Dropbox with me and don't
fill it up too full okay and I'll just pick the ones to go together well and we'll
make something that kind of brings what's back the Arctic radio.
Don't give me no reason why don't stop it now keep it coming up keep it coming up don't stop
it now don't stop no don't stop it now stop keep it coming up keep it coming up
don't stop it now stop it now stop it now stop it now stop it now stop it now stop it
don't fill it up just let me drop don't stop it now don't try me on just to turn
we all don't stop it now keep it coming up keep it coming up don't stop it now stop
don't stop it now stop keep it coming up keep it coming up don't stop it now stop
don't stop it now stop it now stop don't tell me that ain't no more don't stop
don't turn me down just close you don't stop it now keep it coming up
oh yeah
come in love keep it coming up don't stop it now stop don't stop it now stop
don't stop it now stop keep it coming up keep it coming up don't stop
don't stop it now stop it now don't stop it now stop keep it coming up keep it coming up
I have been driving around Los Angeles quite a bit actually, I've been looking for apartments
with Christina, I run a couple errands, now that I have a car actually it's nice, of course
we have the soft 9 or 3 from 1999 and with one headlight kind of falling off, the lights
that perpetually remain on, but it's a convertible, it's a good point, so I'm listening
to a lot of radio because it has a decent sound, decent, I'll not say great, but that's
a decent sound system, and oh the radio sucks, so bad, it's like unless you're into
really into hip hop and the real mainstream stuff which I'm kind of not, although I
find it gets myself listening to it for like 20 minutes on it, and then it just starts
to repeat, like wow, the radio has become so incredibly shit, it's so bad, I was gonna
go somewhere with this, I'm not quite sure, I'm still a little fuzzy in the head, that's essentially
what's happening here, but let me collect my thoughts on that, let me just play a couple
more songs before I can really break it down and talk to you guys, now what's cool about
this Dropbox thing is some people are doing exactly what I hope they would do, I like
Citizen X and they're dropping songs, but they're also dropping little note in, so there's
a Citizen X readme.txt file and her shared folder, and hold on a second, would you please
let me, don't Skype me on, I'm doing the show, it's not a good idea, yeah, I was gonna relate
this to the music business, how that is changing as well, of course Prince who has refused to
be with any mainstream, big record label for a long time, has been looking at alternative
sources of distribution, although he seems to be kind of against any type of internet distribution
in general, although I have yet to hear directly out of his mouth other than through some
interview that was done and I think it was, I wonder if he's the telegraph, I think it was the
same paper where he actually released a CD, because this is what certainly in the United Kingdom
where in Gitmonation East where the newspapers are still kind of a cultural thing and they
really go out and try and get news, I'm not gonna say they actually do a great job of it, but they
have relatively large distribution and Prince decided to release his latest album exclusively in
Gitmo East through, I think it was the telegraph, I'm sure the chatroom will correct me if I'm wrong
and Citizen X did a great thing here and she ripped the CD for me and she put a couple of the
tunes into her Dropbox and I kind of like this one which I want to share with you, this is old school
company, listen to the lyrics, let's think this song, get a kick out of it,
show me what, this is my song, I'm not here yet, I look here y'all, flop hat hot pants and go
my downs, fake brills, to the side, look out, if you're also new, wow, you need some old school
company, it's about a better picture, it's a sex group, and old school is better day, we got your
song in the love family, through the documentary, it's all just a little up to it, I haven't
thought that we can't believe it, everybody talking about hot time, like I just thought it
destined it, people I know they've been struggling, at least it seems that way, back
cats on Wall Street, they got a bailout, why somebody else got to wait, 700 billion
but my old neighbor who ain't nothing changed but the date, listen, everyone's a new, wow,
you need some old school company, it's about a better picture, it's a sex group, and old school
is better day, we got your song in the love family, through the documentary, it's all just a little up to it,
we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we
Got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, that was it, we got it, we got it, we got it all, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, and we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it give it, we got it, we got it, we got it, yes, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, we got it, yeah, we got it, we got it, we got
It's raining, your state of man
Got you kidding to the seams on the flesh
But, bør ua
Itx'n't you get your paper right
Rock your
Call me old fashionable back in the day
Was the no shuttles inside
GOT THAT mommy a day
BABY
It's a has cool
We need it
BABY
Slooot
sexy
BABY
Freedom
I'm gonna take a-hah-hah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
I'm ready, okay?
Power to the people.
Target your speakers!
Target your loudspeakers!
Get it.
The new mini-apple sound.
Honey Colletia, drop the needle round.
I'll scoops from the name.
I'll scoops from the name of the day.
I'll hide what you do.
See that another like me for this chocolate box.
You've got a dance for me baby.
You want to see me rock.
Call the government name and tell them we got to be free.
Valentino tonight, but I'm busy.
Tell your mama 77, Beverly Park.
It's better for time.
You got the old school company y'all dancing in the dark.
I don't mind.
Put this thing over your feet.
Go back to one and just move your feet.
Just your friends.
Sprints in the mini-apple the sound.
We think beep beep.
I'll scoops from the name of the day.
I dare motherfuckers of jeans.
As with most print songs.
You got to kind of get into it and get used to it.
When you hear that guitar whale, it's like, oh yeah, that's him.
That's a man for Minneapolis.
And he's got so much the right idea.
The man is a prophet and a poet.
The white house is black.
We got to take the radio back.
Fuck yeah.
I'm not quite sure if he means it in the same way that we do.
But yeah, we got to take the radio back.
Instead of actually going to go around it.
And we're just always created our own radio here.
You know, that app phone you've gotten your hand right now.
That is the new radio.
Now, only prints will get on board with the program.
And understand that we need to really build up shows like this.
Streams like a Noah gender screen.
And the automobile companies need to start putting that crap into their cars.
It's a stupid serious XM.
You just wait till those guys have to finance another one of those satellites.
It has to go on.
It's probably another two years before they have to shoot another one in the space.
And they will be out of money.
Then what?
Where's a couple of boneheads can kind of get it together and put it up.
Because I'm not that pretty decent.
Of course completely illegally.
No rights paid here.
But I've got proof that this type of system does so records.
That all is fair in love.
And one of the things I'll be happy with my mistake is that you're made.
She has a ball or two.
And I'm telling you to use it.
So you don't have it in another way.
All of you.
Fuck all of you.
We're here.
All of you.
Fuck all of you.
We're here to drop.
Okay, inadvertently I've lifted a bit of the veil behind how it works here.
You see, I've set up another improvement to the system where I now have my, what is it?
The fader fox, MIDI controller, mixer, panel thingy.
I've added that to the mix along with the new iPad control panel for Ableton Live.
It's a lot of gobbledy goof for people who don't give a crap work.
So I was actually testing a combination of a jingle and a song together and I kept doing it over and over thinking that that was outside of the broadcast.
Of course you guys heard most of that.
The combination of a lovely meal last night with Miss Mickey and Molly would where we had an amazing discussion.
I have to say it was it was pretty analogous to almost like a no agenda except there was two chicks and they were beaten up on me pretty hard.
I have to say I was not really losing but they had a real shut up slave thing about them and they were probably right.
And then also my dinner showed up and it was this link we need with white truffle and I just decided to really shut up and just enjoy that really be quiet.
But of course you know we had a drink or two and I got up early this morning and the weather is it's completely sucked in here.
It's been shit for two days and I just the whole my head is fuzzy everything is like, what's going on? Where am I?
I'm truly the second best thing in the universe.
But it's something that I must believe in and it's there when I look in your eyes.
Lovers in the air in the whisper of the tree.
Lovers in the air in the thunder of the sea.
And I don't know if I'm just drinking it.
Don't know if I feel safe.
But if something that I must believe in and it's there when I call out my name.
Lovers in the air.
And I don't know if I'm just drinking it.
And the day is nearly done.
Don't know if I see it true.
But it's something that I must believe in and it's there when I look in your eyes.
Lovers in the air.
And I don't know if I'm just drinking it.
Don't know if I'm just drinking it.
But if something that I must believe in and it's there when I look in your eyes.
Lovers in the air.
Oh yes.
The human resources are getting all up in the chat room.
No agenda chat dot net.
Half of course thinking, hey, where's the songs that make my ears bleed, man?
It's a snafu Saturday.
Remember, it's only just hit 12 o'clock here.
It was a long week, a lot of stuff, a lot of work.
And then you sit down for three hours show.
You got to kind of ease into what you can't just be rolling out the crap right off the bat.
By the way, I do like when you guys delete songs from your shared dropboxes.
They actually move out of my dropbox as well.
That's phenomenal.
Cool.
Clean the shit up that I've played already.
That the wheel falls down.
I'm trying to figure out where it all went wrong.
It's day in another industry.
All my soul crush and dizzy.
Got to get back into the room.
Little bird on your shoulder.
Sign up for a million songs.
Might be soon be far along.
Got to get back into the back yard.
It'll look a bit better.
Get out of the room.
Get along.
Get back into the room.
Get on the right yard.
Got to keep back into the room.
Olive in the walls.
Head on to our roof, head on to our trash town.
And then before the sauna,
Give way the go up first.
Got to get that in the room.
Oh, I can't see.
It's just a dream and when you live here
You just have to live in a long gone
Little girl, I know she'll never say ever before
It's only for you
Yeah, good thing, good action
Get on the right track
Take it long
Yeah, back, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, well that's
Nice, found in the Dropbox, and something I never would have played otherwise.
Get back Jack here in the Daily Source Code episode 8-4-Niner on the Snathoo Saturday for October
16th, 2010, man, where's the time gone?
It's going so quickly.
You know, if I showed any of my old radio guys to set up that we have together, they would
shit themselves.
They would poop in their pants, because I've also got this growl note of, growl notification
set up.
So when something is added or deleted, apparently I didn't know that deleted from the Dropbox,
it tells me that.
And here we go, and I could create all the coconuts, and I'm not your Daddy MP3 was removed
from the Dropbox.
This is perfect.
They would kill themselves over a setup like this, where all I have to do is I'm just
the glue.
I'm sitting in between all the stuff, and I'm just trying to play all the things you guys
are dropping into the box.
It works out perfectly.
I love this.
I totally love it.
You know, sometimes there are bands that are way ahead of their time with the message.
And I have to point out the George Michael actually was calling out Tony Blair as George
Bush's monkey, monkey boy sitting on his lap, sucking his shlong, and people ridiculed
him for it.
They laughed, and said, oh, he's lost his way.
And of course, he actually did kind of lose his way, a little bit too much of the of the
refer.
I think it just served time for that.
But I think the guy was on a lot of, he'd saw what was happening, and maybe that's
why he just couldn't handle it, and he started smoking himself into oblivion.
Know what that's about.
But I was checking through the Dropbox, I don't know who's this came from, but wow,
if you would remember the video for this song, which was actually from a British television
show called Spitting Image with this Spitting Image, where they had pretty life-like,
characterized puppets or puppets, or, yeah, some kind of combination of that.
It was a satirical television show of political world leaders, see, I think it was Reagan
in this one.
Margaret Thatcher was in this one, a couple others, and the song, well, it was just fantastic.
Of course, you recognize that drum beat immediately is that of Phil Collins, if Genesis
landed the fuse on deadly source code, eight, four, nine are.
I'm stitching the thousand dreams, fit on it by a million screens,
back in here and marching feet, moving into the street, and did you read the news
two days, they still didn't do it down our way, but I can see the fire still light.
But in into the night, there's too many things, too many people, we can't do many problems.
I'm not much loved in a crowd, I can't see it, it's just what I don't think it would have.
Who this is the world leader, and these are hands together, you think let's start trying
to make it a very swallow to be in.
Who Superman, where are you now, where everything's the most amount, for men to steal,
and we're not power, losing control by the hour, this is the time, this is the place
so we're not a future, but there's so much love to around,
and we're not a future, this is the world leader, and these are hands together,
you think let's start trying to make it a very swallow to be in.
I'm not much loved in a crowd, I can't see it, it's just what I don't think it would have.
I won't be coming home tonight, my generation will put it right, we're not just making promises,
but we don't, we never keep, we never keep, we never, there's too many people making too many problems,
and I'm not much loved in a crowd, I can't see it, it's just what I don't think it would have.
I just started to connect a couple dots, while I was giving me that whole wrap about George Michael,
so George Michael, who I think is an excellent songwriter, may I write a lot about loves and
sacks and stuff like that, but he's, he's prolific, he's a poet, I was one of the best songwriters of
the 80s and 90s, completely ridiculed, he's now become a big joke in the United Kingdom,
he's a big joke over here too, people say, oh, he's like wham, he wrote a lot of great,
you know, somebody please drop a couple of George Michael's solo songs into the Dropbox,
he wrote some really, really good stuff, I don't care what you say, completely vilified,
completely ridiculed in the United Kingdom, but Phil Collins, who also called out the governments,
also ridiculed in the United Kingdom, I don't know if you know about Nanny Gate,
but this guy, you know, he people, Phil Collins become a big joke in the United Kingdom,
still love the world over, but in the United Kingdom where I actually called out the government
in songs like this with Genesis, completely ridiculed, we go figure, now you know why,
I just like to call myself a crack pot up front, so they just leave me alone, it's much easier
that way, believe it or not, that is the sound of an invasion, yes that is the sound created by
the musical invasion of America by the world's hottest recording group, a try and a cool quest quest quest,
they are not conformists to such a great degree that don't seem members ever dress alike,
and many educators consider their popularity resulted from their becoming symbols of teenage rebellion.
They certainly are ricking in a lot of good, free and American money and gathering
efforts of thousands of teenage fans in the process.
Can I kick it?
That's what I love, I love what flat soul is what we're above, if you disus people
even think of, we'll nip up a dog and give a big shove, this with a real if it's like a
strong club, like a box of positives, it's a plus love, as a child floss, high like a dog.
How do you say a try a cool quest quest quest?
Can I kick it?
Well, you got the title by now.