Delta Sierra Charlie 831.
We're 16 months to 7 months and showing five lines of time turns.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We're not in the city.
We're in the middle of life.
I know it's in the stranded.
I'm testing.
It's very scary.
We're ready to see.
I'm ready.
Yeah.
Me.
Okay.
All right fellas.
Let's go.
Yeah.
It's a full fire front.
It's quick and tight.
All right.
It's fun and so.
Really like the one thing.
It's interesting.
Right.
We're getting so scared.
I like to tell you everything.
I see.
Oh.
What do you mean?
It's a fight.
It's a matter of fact.
Size.
It's red.
It's fun.
And the girl in the cold.
It's no one ignore.
She thinks she's the passionate one.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's like lightning.
Everybody goes by a thing.
It's a music one soothing.
It's the old story through me.
Yeah.
It's a matter of fact.
It's a kind of tell it to about split.
And the girl in the cold.
It's a fight.
I've already made it until the right level.
I've made it.
It's a matter of sisteries.
Two male and males.
Come back to fridge, crack, break your nails and leave.
How does that sound?
There's no music at all,
addictive music.
At the Mass, the back of the fridge and crack with your raises.
At some sky!
Now, let's go!
The color is good as everyone's wanted!
You can give you with a week!
Wake up right!
Come on!
Yeah!
This is fascinating.
Look at this!
The water 지en.
It's 8 squats on 9 dips.
I was born in the edge of you
I was born in the jakim...
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it
Got the 11 official Friday night dance parties with those of you on the given a kao SAD things and in the low lands, maybe you just getting started down there down under, it is a beautiful day.
Once again a Friday and it's good to gotta fire it!
This is the SUC coming to you from the hill top Watch Tower at Captain and Centre it is a Hollywood showroom, II'm an UV88
Relangement score, dual wear names?
Don't know what it is, but just feel like grab it a whole bunch of tracks of a bytunes that fell right.
Because it's been a rollercoaster ride on me.
How you been? Let us know at knowaginachat.com.
What you mean comes here about me, I'll be alone.
That's as you know it may be, tell me, your troubles will die out.
Give me everything inside and out of this.
Lost strange, so real and hard.
Think of the tender things that we're working on.
Switching, it may pull us apart.
Wanna laugh, get it in your heart, baby.
Don't you forget about me.
Don't don't don't don't don't don't you forget about me.
Don't you stand above me.
Look my way, wherever long it is for you.
Make it for you, don't don't don't don't don't don't.
Will you recognize me?
Come on, make it for one more life.
Make it for you, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't.
Say we're alone.
Don't you try to pretend it's not you.
Will you recognize me?
Come on, make it for you, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don
don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't love me, yeah I'll call you, come on.
And when you walk on the street
All you walk on is
When you walk on the street
My favorite part of the record coming up
And the tension mouse
Turn on your radios
Twist the knob up to it
I told you I was in a really easy mood today
Simple mind
Don't you forget about me
Interesting to watch
Everyone, yep and away
The party at no agenda chat.com
Talking about license fees
Hey listen
You can't get a license fee for this
You can't make many money on this
I'm doing this for us
Just so we have a good time
They want to take away my music
They want to take away your music
Screw it
I made all these fuckers millions of dollars
The first time around
I think they owe me I can share with a couple of my closest friends
All right
Time to show up and play a more hands
Remember this one
I'm telling you
I too made a bundle off of me
Is you
Seems to be that life is imitating our days
As the bank buildings burning grease
We're nearing the final countdown
Who will be next?
Portugal, Spain, the United Kingdom
The Netherlands
We're leaving together
Let's still get scared
And maybe we'll go back
To burn the truth there
I guess there's no one to leave
We'll leave it right
We'll never be saved again
It's the final countdown
The final countdown
Oh, the hell is going to be the seedless
And still we stand tall
To bury the seedless
And welcome, a star
With so many light secrets to go
And these could be found
I saw what we had before
Oh, the final countdown
The final countdown
Oh, the hell
It's the final countdown
The final countdown
Oh, the hell
It's the final countdown
We'll leave it together
Well, we know what I'm doing these days
We gotta worry
Or kinda wonder what joy the boys are doing
What they look like
You're, and it is indeed the final countdown
If you're listening to the stream right now
No agenda stream.com on this Friday
Or maybe Saturday wherever you are
What the hell you're doing if you're working
You gotta quit, it is Friday
I've played this song on the last show we did
That we shared together
Got so many comments about it
So you gotta roll it out for you one more time
On the Super Friday
Kicks major F and S
Thank you Marcus God for bringing to me
One less reason favorite cover
Daily stores go to eat free one
But I said it wrong to me
You're much more free
Don't my fingers make break
I'm just kidding
Let you go
Don't know why I believed you
Not with and promise you made me
Just yesterday
You made me
Not with and promise you made me
Just yesterday
You made me
Just the point we'll find out
Take me out
Just the point
I'll always love you
Take the me out
I'll be okay with me
Just the point we'll find out
I'll love you
And I need you
I'll always love you
Take the me out
I'll be okay with me
Just the point I'll find out
I'll go now
Take the my shore
Till my heart stops on earth
I'll never know what's inspiring
I'll be okay with me
Just the point I'll find out
Oh yeah
Just gonna reel tough days today
Technology wise
Now I'm sauna table cripped out
Earlier everything went down
Television telephone
And the Internet
Triple Play
Triple fail as someone said in the chat room earlier
Got a lot of that so in one less reason favorite color on the football front finish of the Charlie
Yeah, maybe you can tell I I watched them moving the other day
I would be disappointed when they find out the love that song
Yeah, I watched movie the other day called pirate radio, which of course historically is very
Incorrect it's about the pirate ships off in the north sea who broadcast to
Mainland Europe in the United Kingdom in the sixties and early seventies
I and although at historically was really incorrect there was some pretty good acting the DJ stuff was yeah, it was okay
But it really did spark a fire in me once again, you know these I ran my own pirate radio days
Which came right after that and I'm like yeah, the stuff that we're doing here on the daily source code
It's kind of like pirate radio it really is and by the way back in the day
They don't have to worry about Askab be am I and all that crap
I'm not gonna worry about it now either I paid for the songs I paid a dollar 29 fridge of these tracks. I hope you enjoy it
And it's good to be here and all of these old friends of the Charlie back calling in again saying hi
Listen to this old friend who's back
Adam here from Portland here. Yeah, hey man long time no talk
There was a tradition in the old in the old DSC where people would sign off their voice comments with like
items or or little tag praises
That came about from the show and I wanted to start that back and I'm gonna start right now by signing off this message with I love your man
No, homo big hair. Hope you win
Folder and a new one for TSC part two here in the morning
Indeed
Thanks for coming back in my brother
Good to hear from you
Good to see you doing well, and I love those short messages
They were really worth for me
You show us everything you've got
You keep on dancing now
It's hot
You drop us wow
We'll drop you crazy
You say while we go for a spin
The one is just begun to let you in
You drop us wow
We'll drop you crazy
You keep on shouting you keep on shouting
I
All night
And what the every day
I want to rock and roll
All night
And what the every day
Yeah people saying you'll be mine for a while
You're looking fancy and I like your smile
You try to smile
We'll drop you crazy
Yeah
You show us everything you've got
We'll believe that's what I'm not
And you drop us wow
We'll drop you crazy
You keep on shouting you keep on shouting
I want to rock and roll all night
I want to, yes
The ride to the airways is landed and he's sounding good to me.
This is the Daily Source Code with Adam Curry.
Alright, it's the Trifectown.
Played this one for the candy man up there in Finland.
I know he gets off on this.
Death.
Crank it up.
Talk to him on dance where you got some rush on your fiery radio.
I'm the stream.
No one's in the stream dark time with a full body of the Daily Source Code.
Be careful day with the friendly voice,
I can't tell you not enough truth to him.
Played that so much so we lose and I'm the magic you took me to your moment.
I want you way in the open room.
You never imagined you'd get to your fingers.
But this baby never lingers on the mountain top.
I'm taking your hands on the top.
You never imagined you'd get to your fingers.
I wish I could see you
It's all the parts were written on the step of your wall
Got them all
I know that goes from where the sound of salesman
Salesman
Truly the spirit of radio rush
On the source code for all you chuckle head that appreciate it
And we had to kind of a football weekman who is weird
Right after Thursdays
There's no agenda the Marcus tanks
Dow Jones dropped over a thousand points
And of course we have some thoughts just to why that happened
We'll be talking about that in the morning on Sunday during the early service
But while that was
Apparently it started with some
Trader in Chicago
And I would say you want to look more towards the high frequency trades
And some malicious code that was out there
Or first I'll be spewing my theories on you during no agenda
But let's talk about Chicago back in the day
And talk about it still
When I'm a name of football
Trader make that turn his own
And he called his place for
With the forces of the law
I hit my mom
I would raise the night Chicago die
Brother one and I'd be the one
Brother what if I'd be the one
hrough you
I hit my mom
Run the night Chicago die
Brother one and I'd be the one
Brother what if I'd be the one
Under the sound of the battle
Listen to the oldies
to the last of the hook and to end it up all the time
through a shouting in the street on the sound of running feet
and asked some more said about a hundred clubs
I did I heard my mom cry
I did pray that I should go cry
Brother what a night is really was
I heard my mom cry
I heard praying that I should go cry
Brother what a night is people so
Then there was no sound at all
Brother what a night is really was
Brother what a night is building
Brother what a night is people so
Brother what a night is
It's one of the very first forty-fives I ever owned.
Paper lace.
I can't believe that was the night, too.
The day of Chicago died.
Remember when songs had a story?
And they were like three minutes long?
Yeah, back in the day.
That's right.
From the seventies to the eighties and back again,
down today's football are Friday.
You can't get much more yanky due to the song than this.
Jenner Jenner can I turn to?
You can't miss something.
I can hold onto.
I know you're playing fine like the other people.
So you made me number all the way.
And I got to know.
I managed to make you my wish.
Then I don't change all the time.
But they've been found by the United States.
Seven five three hundred.
Six seven five three hundred.
Six seven nine three hundred.
Jenner Jenner.
You're the girl for me.
You don't know me but you think I'm so happy.
I tried to call you before, but I love my name.
I try how you've made me turn, but I want to see you.
Jenner can't hold onto.
I just make you my wish.
Then I don't change all the time.
But they've been found by the United States.
Seven five three hundred.
Six seven five three hundred.
I've got to know.
I got to know it all the way.
I've got to know it all the way.
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby AstraZoni Francisco sweetheart and these doctor just baby baby baby baby baby Honey baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby babies baby baby baby baby baby상 diabetes baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby babies baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby strony baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
And of course, as George Carlin would say, my shit is my stuff, but of course, your stuff is your shit.
When it's mine, it's stuff and when it's yours, it's shit.
And I remember Miss Mickey had to pay almost $2,000 for some bullshit scam that customers pulls to inspect her stuff.
By the way, nothing was inspected as far as we can tell.
And I only have to pay $85.
I love it.
I guess they didn't see the Japanese machine gun that I'm smuggling into the country.
I'm hoping they didn't pull it out.
I'm hoping it's still in the box labeled Guitar.
Because I plan on mountain that sucker right here on the deck of the Hilltop Watch Tower Crackpot Command Center.
Oh, yeah.
The only thing I'm looking for now is a magazine.
If anyone has a magazine for an LMG 99, I'm in the market.
So I was very sad yesterday.
A lot of you probably saw the blog post.
I made Apple rejected my iPhone app for the second time.
I wish they would just test the whole thing out and not just at the first thing they don't like stop and then reject it.
It would be so much nicer if they did everything.
And because of some network hiccup or something else.
I didn't get through and I was really bummed out.
I do highly appreciate everyone posting comments at curry.com and sending the emails and suggestions.
I do kind of have a plan now.
I'll be resimitting it probably this evening.
And it may get rejected again, but there's a longer term strategy to fix it once and for all.
But I'm still not angry at them because they're right.
If it failed, it failed.
And if that was a network hiccup, then there should be something that tells the user at least what's going on and helps them out.
And so I've got to work on that.
But man was I was I bummed out.
So I immediately went to the latest iPad app that I have called big oven.
If you've never seen this thing, it's awesome.
And it really works well on the iPad.
It's one of those apps that just really is made for a big screen.
Cookbook, essentially, with the community, builds it on the back end.
Think of a website.
It's probably big oven.com.
And made me some spicy, maple salmon.
Let me tell you.
Your pilot of the airways is becoming quite a cook.
Just when you thought it couldn't get any hooky or yes, he flows it out.
There's another one that we remember from the 80s.
I've always wanted to know a girl named Ilyne.
Because we all know the joke, but boy, I would've loved her, said it.
So I've got to work on that.
And so I've got to work on that.
Now I have to work on that.
So I've got to work on that.
Okay.
Come on, come on, Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on... come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come nower, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on come on, coming on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
I live all I smell to me, I'm the small one
I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know
I don't go to me, I don't take the sauce code, I don't go to you
I can't get crazy sauce
I don't go to you
I live all I know, I live all I know, now I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, I live all I know, how I live all I know I live all, I live all I know
I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I
won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up again, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, Give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won't give up, I won
I'll be jealous, I'll give up, I'll be dead
I'll be dead, I'll be dead
But believe it, it's not me, believe it
Please believe it, I'll be dead
So you're my great value, I hate you
Soon, maybe I know what it actually is
But people who tried to follow me
And steal me and pull me apart
Nobody ever beat me down
Charlie agreed with B.n.T. at no original chat.com
Come, yes, this is slap-dissing.
It's slap-dissing.
Say, I know now, I am a bad movie references.
Right out to the pepper is higher ground
on the football front edition of the Daily Source Code,
which has brought to you completely commercial-free
by the sustaining producers at the No Agenda Stream.
If you'd like to support the show, go to devouract.org-n-a-s.
November, Alpha, Shira, and show your love.
And of course, we'll put you on the page there.
It's one of the sustaining producers of the stream,
as we continue to feed it with more and more
great programming for you live 24 hours a day.
And of course, special thanks to everyone
who contributes to the show by sending an ideas, tracks to play.
And as seems to happen, almost every single week,
my good buddy Ray is going to give us a rundown
on what's been happening in get-mown-nation lowlands.
All we want is night is rain.
Game ons, hark, no.
We've got to be a part of us against the name of the game.
Hey Adam, got to tell you, man.
The Dutch population is afraid.
We are scared.
You know, it's a strange week for us in the Netherlands.
After Queen's Day, where everybody's extra-versed and happy,
this last week, we thought a lot about the Second World War.
On May 4th at 8 p.m., Dutch people will take two minutes
of silence to remember the victims of the Second World War,
gave their lives for our freedom.
At 20-hundred hours, my country is still
and frozen for two minutes.
Mr. Renne, nice to see you all this.
Now the time and news are up to done.
Thousands of interested people at the National Remembrance Day
at the Dam Square in Amsterdam started to panic
after the two minutes of silence.
The blasts were here and in the confusion,
many of them started to run away from the scene.
Eventually, they appeared to be a combination of incidents.
First, there was a homeless drunken guy named Adam.
Oh, really?
No.
That's really true.
I started to yell something.
You know, it's not a series of incidents.
It's a co-incidence.
I think not.
By the way, if you haven't seen it yet,
go out and have to post this in the show notes.
A daily source code.com.
Princess Maxima, the lovely Argentinian beauty
who will be our future queen in the Gitmonation Lowlands.
In a nice little video montage,
there where she is actually pushing a kid,
holding flowers out of her way,
as she runs away.
Literally pushing this kid to the ground.
Get out of the way, slave!
After that, someone saw a man walking away
from the suitcase, which was left behind.
There also was someone who had become a well.
These all happened.
At the same time, exactly after the two minutes of silence,
hundreds of people started to move
or run away from the crowd.
You could see the panicking in their eyes.
Immediately, the Dutch queen was evacuated
from the dance square.
There were soldiers with rifles
and lots of lots of police officers.
With their hand on their gun.
Of course, a lot of people were crying
and panicking because they didn't know what was going on.
A couple of minutes later,
the queen came back to the dance square,
to finish the official memorial.
Well, there you have it, my friend.
Now you see how dense we are.
You know?
Nothing is as reassuring as the words.
The queen is back.
The generation that lived through the second world war
dies slowly.
It also increases the fear
that the war will be forgotten over time.
Well, that's probably what's going to happen.
History has proven that.
And then the next day, on May the 5th,
we celebrate our freedom.
It's liberty day in the Netherlands,
with lots of musical performances
on several liberty pop concerts all over the country.
So, it was a week full of national bonding here.
So, just one more thing before I wrap it up.
Yesterday, the results came out
of the final investigation into the cause of the plane crash
into an open field near the airport's shiphole in the Netherlands.
The main problem was the altitude that didn't work.
The Turkish Airlines crew did not respond
that adequately enough.
And the air traffic control in the Netherlands
was not entirely in her instructions.
But the report also said that the cause of the crash
at the shiphole last year was the coincidence.
9 people were killed and 18 injured.
Turkish Airlines disagrees with parts of the report
and denies two specific conclusions.
First, the Turkish claims that the fact that the device
is not stable enough would have been
at an altitude of 1,000 feet
not a factor in the cause of this accident.
The council said that the device, according to his information,
should make a new start.
Furthermore, Turkish Airlines disagrees
with the conclusion of the board
that a recovery process after a warning was given
was not well executed.
According to the company, the equipment
responded properly.
The second attempt by the crew was successful
but too late.
So, that's it for this week, Adam.
How's your work going?
3 and 3.
Is that working for you?
That's all for now.
My fellow Chocolates.
I wish you a very nice weekend.
Talk to you later.
You know?
It is so funny.
You asked me to find this.
And all that great.
I'm a realist.
I've been working my best.
I've spent an hour on the treadmill this morning.
I didn't go to school.
Oh yeah.
I've never looked at me.
So let's do work.
It all means don't say,
I malice the real,
When the housemates grab the clothes,
then get these spaces with me.
I'd want to live in life like that.
I want to be dysmerised,
Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills,
Lennon and Beverly Hills, Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon.
Beverly Hills.
Lennon and Beverly Hills.
Lennon.
Beverly Hills.