Delta Sierra Charlie 830.
We've 16 noises to 7 minutes and showing 5 rounds of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We're not in the state.
We've been dreaming of life.
I know you're in the strip down.
I'm just kidding.
Hey, come here.
C'mon.
That's right, everybody.
It's a group of our friends.
Daily source codec was sold in 3-0.
We're always as quick as time.
Noisyinestream.com was with the parties.
There's no agenda chat.com.
Are you ready?
He lived in the jungle when he was born the King.
His great strength made him a lot of effort, been.
No creature crossed his path that lived for long.
His name, so let it tell us what it can't call.
He was never an issue.
I was great, but jungle's shopping is this magic way.
His eyes were muscle, there's the other three.
This temple was big and wide as it could be.
Come on, Zombie!
Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie!
Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie!
He didn't notice somebody. He spoke sometimes but hardly.
When women heard his love call, he was still beginning to die.
One day while Kong was sleeping on his back,
a surrender starts, lunch the sneaker time.
They fought, first come with down, then up again.
The fight went off, no one knew what would win.
How reached and seized the muscle with both hands.
Then summoned all the strength and his command.
He stretched the creatures mouth to the split.
Then locked the child again to play with him.
He didn't notice hearing chest and left around.
Five miles away they heard his running sound.
Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie! Come on, Zombie!
Come on, Zombie! He didn't notice somebody.
He's focused on his blood hardly
One woman heard his love call
But he was too big and too tired
From everyone he knew he got rid of his pants
Will it fail to give it?
He corrected
Nobody across this path and left alone
His name, something to tell this was King Kong
Call somebody
Today's Daily Short is called Eén 3-0
This is the Fuji Bar Friday so we are taking it to the esteem
That is the Jimmy CasterBunge
With King Kong, thanks to Rade
Mister Prrap let me prep out on the show
Doing quite a while we're here for late ron
Right now we gotta get the weekend started
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick
quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick process shoot, quick, quick quick, quick, quick, quick, successful, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick
I think of all the education that I've had, but that I don't want was never quite like this.
I think of all the education that I've had, but that I don't want was quite like this.
It just makes you want to do live show with lots of tunes.
It's just too long for me, I just don't get a chance to listen to the whole thing.
I do find something about you that is very enjoyable.
Anyway, we really glad you do what you do.
Did you get that flash frame thing I sent you, I saw that terrible flash frame with the influencer thing on it.
You helped me get laid and now I have a film set out of it.
I hope you win, love you, mate it.
I hope you win, mate it.
I hope you win.