I gotta do a brand new day, it's now
Come on, baby, you look up the motion
I know you're with the like it if you give it a chance now
My little bit is here, look and do it with ease
It's easy, I love you, baby, it's easy
So come on, come on, do it a lot of attention with ease
You've got to swing it out, it's now
Come on, come on, do it a lot of attention
Come on, baby, you look up the motion
Well, let's make it change now
I know you're with the like it if you give it a chance now
Come on, baby, you look up the motion
I know you're with the like it is now
Come on, do it a lot of attention
Come on, baby, you look up the motion
Now get in the line
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Thanks for filling up the hard drive everybody. It's highly appreciated. It really helps when I'm doing other stuff
Just to see the all the tracks slipping in
Continuously
Think we got uh, I want to do something different today
Maybe instead of just the
All drop box all requests perhaps we even do a dedication type of Charlie. I I did hook up the Skype to the system
Maybe we can have people call in
Dedicate their songs and that'll play it for it
See we can get a little more involved
If you're listening now at the stream no agenda stream.com the party is always on in the chat room
No agenda chat dot net today stores code snap through Saturday for the 23rd of October
Who hunts friends
body
When it takes you
You can't sleep
You can't eat
There's no doubt
You're in deep
You're from this chains
You can't breathe
I'm not a kiss
As I can be
Oh
You like to think that you're into the snow
Oh, yeah
Of course we'll do the truth
I say yeah
Can't be anything
You don't have to face the truth
You're too too close to the side
You can't breathe
Running at
Different speed
Your heart beats
Double time
And the kiss
You'll be mine
No one's right and right
You can't be seen
But with me I'm alone
And I'm you great
For this song
And for you
You don't mind
Can you do
Oh, you like to think that you're into the snow
Oh, yeah
Of course we'll do the truth
I say yeah
Can't be anything
You're going to have to face the truth
You're too too close
My ears will be torn
Take to love
Take it to love
My ears will be torn
Can't be anything
But like some odd
But you're not home
You're all weird
You're heart sweeps
And keep your mind
And go to kiss
And you'll be mine
Oh, you like to think that you're into the snow
Oh, yeah
Just goes away
Through the truth I say yeah
Can't be anything
You're going to have to face the truth
Take it to love
I'm kind of doing a little rain dance here at the Hiltop Watch Tower
Crackhot Command Center trying to play as many sunny songs as possible
Because we have had nothing but crap weather for the past
We're going to have it's just been total shit
That's why we need a little bit of cowbell
No one I'm saying yo
Thank you Marcus Couch
Told me loving the dropbox
Is kiss
Caught and duck the love
You need my love
Take the most so bad
You're not the only one I've ever had
And if I say I want to set you free
Don't you know you'll be a miss or free
They call me
They call me duck to love
I'm kind of doing a little rain dance here at the Hiltop Watch Tower
And if I say I want to set you free
Don't you know you'll be a miss or free
Even though I'm full of sin
In the old days
Let me in
You let me through this walking
You can't do all
You need my love and touch alone
It's true
So enter please
Get on your knees
There are no bills there are no fees
They may I know what the problem is
The first step of your illness
I can't see
So come, sweetheart
They call me duck to love
I'm kind of doing a little rain dance here at the Hiltop Watch Tower
Let me in
They call me duck to love
I'm kind of doing a little rain dance here at the Hiltop Watch Tower
We'll save the world up right now
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh true.
uh
I gotta pop my soul off on a coroner to get completely ready for this show and then I've got an idea
They don't want to talk to you guys about kiss
They call me back the love on the snap food Saturday
The second best thing
I'm just in the morning
Here come the gestures, one, two, three
It's so far from my fantasy
I've heard the music, and I let the sea the ground
Dancing in my eyes, and I'm singing along
Yeah
Here come the gestures, one, two, three
Your mother's calling but you're having fun
You found your dancing home in your nightclub
Put your letter together, you see the loud
It's so far from my heart
I can hope fantasy
I can only dream
It's so far from my heart
I can only fantasy
I can only dream
It's so far from my heart
Put out the spotlight, one, two, three
There music, so far from my heart
I can only dream
It's so far from my heart
I'm thinking Marcus Couch just moved in with me
I am bringing your MP3 collection with you, my friend
That company rock and roll fantasy
I'm the Charlie episode eight five zero
Is the sun tries to peek through
Just a little bit here at the Hilltop Watch Tower
It's a track spot command center in Gipmonation West
Alright, here's what I'd like to do
If you've got a drop box you've shared
And you've got some tunes in there
You'd like to share with the group
I hop into the chat room with no agenda chat.net
And give me your Skype name, I'll call you
And we'll do a dedication on the air
Alright
I'm hungry, I'm hungry
You don't have to read my mind
To know what I have in mind
Honey, you wanna know
Now you move so fine
Let me lay it all the light
I wanna know what you're doing
End of the show
Now it's time to give you
We can make a secret running through
Just me and you
That's all you're loving like you never do
That's why I hop into the chat room
You'd like to share with the group
I gotta say that over hungry
Come on baby, do you want to dance
I hop into the chat room
Gip it feels alright
Maybe you can stay alright
Shall I live you my key?
What you got to give me a sign
Oh no, so kind of sign
Tell me, are you hot mama
You sure love that way to me
Are you losing now
Will you be ready when I call your love?
Is my timing right
It'll save your love for me tonight
Yeah, I hop into the chat room
Check it and see
Feeling free my burning inside of me
Come on baby, do you want to dance
I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot
Now it's up to you
Can we make a secret run at blue
Oh, you won't do
You'll have to get away from you no
Where I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm cold, I'm cold to see
Got to feel that over hundred free
Come on baby, do you want to dance
I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot
I think I need to revise my statement there about how I'm going to do these
dedications and Paulins on the show.
Here's what you do.
I'd like you to drop a note into your drop box that you shared with me, hopefully.
We have enough of them and this enough to get through the show.
Drop a note in there with a song you'd like to request and your Skype name so that I can get back to you.
We can put you on the show. How does that sound?
Adam Curry.
I'm gonna watch it go away.
You take their right. Come on.
Even Sean John.
The things are small.
They use small heard.
But not me.
I'm just wonderland Marsh.
I work in outputting up
Archie sticks using my mouth,
Doesn't have gone speed and worse
I'm right now, I'm running out
I'm getting out
To the city, we can see
I'll be here to be
Now is where all the people are so messed up
I'll be right now
I'm not afraid to be gone
As I'm here, I'm not afraid to share time
I'm not worried I'm making you
At the time, I'm not afraid to be tired
I come to make you so late
So much larger than yours
At the time, I'm gonna wash it
Rowling in time
That's not opinion, that's science
And science is one core at the edge of the 14-year-old
All my life is one big adventure
Always through our days
With a shoulder from the heart through the day
I heard it makes like a magic ring
This will wipe below for my big advantage
And whatever will be taken
I'm not afraid to be tired
I'm not afraid I'm making you
At the time, I'm not afraid to be tired
I've got to make you so late
So much larger than mine
That's not opinion, that's science
And science is one core at the edge of the 14-year-old
All my life is one big adventure
My heart is not afraid to be tired
I'm not afraid to be tired
My fingers are not afraid to be tired
My heart is not afraid to be tired
I've got to make you so late
At the time, I'm not afraid to be tired
My heart is not afraid to be tired
I'm not afraid to be tired
Yeah
From the crack box to the bus
Yeah, freezing your shizzle
Yeah, keeps me out in Don't be tired
Keeps me out in Don't be tired
Don't be tired
One, one
Shut up, stay
Fuck all of you, we're here to rock
Hey, don't be tired
Yeah, hey
Hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey
From the crack box to the bus
Yeah, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey
Hey
Somebody turn around and shout it, play that fucking news and wipe it all
Play that fucking music race
Play that fucking news and wipe it all
Lay down the bug and play that fucking news and cheer you up
To die, yeah
Whoa, to die
Gonna play some of that fucking music race
First it wasn't easy
Changing life and roll with my eyes
I think we're getting shaky
I thought I'd have to leave it behind
Oh, but now it's so much better, it's so much better
I'm fucking out and out of your way
But I've never used that feeling
You know I'm home
But how all of them are less empty
Yeah, yeah, yeah
When you know I've been saying it and moving to the room
And just wait, it hit me
Someone turn around and shout it, play that fucking news and wipe it all
Play that fucking news and wipe it all
Lay down the bug and play that fucking music to your die
I must have been 1976, 1977
It was the high school dance
I was like, whoa
I was the first time I actually hit the dance floor
Y'all, oh, yeah, if you can believe that
At one point actually did that way back in the day
Some more cowbell for you
Top in about your clothes
It's a cry in the cinema
A painted pony let the spin in wheels spin
You got no man, yeah
You got no home
Still wheels, all alone
Top in about your clothes and yeah
You never learn
Light up painted pony let the spin in wheels spin
Did you find the dire acting sign on the straight and narrow highway
I want your mind to reflect this line
Just let it shine
Within your mind and show you
The colors that are ruined
Someone on his way can drive you
Spin in wheels spin in the crew
Top on your top both of the river side
Capture painted pony on the spin in wheels
Don't worry, I want my great, great
Don't worry, great, great, great
Don't worry, great, great, great, great
Don't worry, great, great
Great, great, great, great, great, great
Go for the dribbling
Go soft Go on yourself
Go on with toe
Yes it let go
Go hand out
Go fast It won't give me the edge
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, it's called the last bit of the song was, let's see what I'm looking for.
Ah, fucked up.
Yeah, never really liked it.
I liked the song.
I like, uh, blood sweat and tears spin wheel, but I just never really got this last part.
Why the hell would they do that?
All right, it's, uh, well, we're in the middle of a nice cowbell set, everybody.
And yeah, yeah, well, yeah, yeah, thank you to enlite men for putting that together.
And Nicely categorizing the Dropbox works, well, creedons born on the buying thing.
Now we're now in Japan in our heart
I'll start it through my dad and me
My Papa said so I won't let the man get done
You oughta thought of me
I'll forget you
I'll always be gentle now
Now I'll go in no more than fall
I'll run up through the back of your face
And I can still hear how long I'll fall
Can't take some down I'll do there
Trace some down I'll do there
On all of you
We're shall we fight go to fail
All of us are cage and cage
We're shatter way up that's free
We're up to the two and all down I'm new Holly
On all of you
I'll run up through the back of your face
And I can still hear how long I'll fall
Can't take some down I'll do there
Trace some down I'll do there
On all of you
All of you
And in particular right now, we're talking about the cowbell.
That's what it's all about.
Gotta have me some cowbell.
I gotta get down to Guitar Center and get me a new one.
Because my husband is completely footballer.
It's not from Saturday.
B.S.C. eight five zero.
I'm in a gentle ballroom, queen, and I'm here with us.
I'm just trying to take it up, stay as far as I ride.
But she had to pee me right out, close that shoulder.
Because I just came saying to drink out my mind.
B.S. three...
Outira don't wanna say he ain't no yore instead.
I have to put a lot of some kind of a fun
The lady had this shit covered me
Roll this
She blew my nose and then she blew my mouth
It's a ho-ho-ho
It's a ho-ho-ho-ho
Give it, give it, give it, give it the ho-ho-ho
Give it all right
Give it, give it, give it, and give it the ho-ho-ho-ho
Come on, get on and don't play
Give me a hit, give me a hit
Give me a hit, go on and don't play
Come on, come on and don't play
Give me a hit, give me a hit
Give me a hit, go on and don't play
Stones in the hunk, talk woman
Oh boy, it's happened again
Listen to the email, here it is
This is what always happens
Dear Adam, you've used up to 90% of the allocated traffic in your account
This notices for account ID number, blah, blah, blah
User name, blah, blah, blah
Once your bandwidth is completely used up your account
We'll be in activate automatically
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no
I will have to buy some extra traffic
To get through the show
Now I'll get my style
Surprise, surprise
So you rock your eyes
We have a news soon
Yes, so cool, where's eyes
We need a fight, yeah
There will still be a fight
But to get it the rises
Has one cries
That's a mall we know now
We're rock your eyes
The birds, but up to your star
We'll be so high
Who falls a low west
Soon as we go
Has a bridge to the floor
And make sure the song
Deforestation and souls
Dear Adam, you've used up to 90% of the allocated traffic in your account
We'll be in activate automatically
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no
Deforestation and souls
So, I'll play the hand roll
A tight, the middle
Clean the two holes
The glow rotates
From the old, the old
Beauty has teapot
The reached the souls
Narrow eyes, stars are there
Still holding the holes
Do up before and before
And when we come close
To the contrary
They can't stay alone
They call it road rock
But it's a deep unshreener soul
These fish hair are so
My hair
A deep fish hair are so
Oh no, no, no, no, no
Deforestation and souls
We plan everything
With a color of skin on the skin
We're in like sweat
Tox there it is
And soon as we begin
And when I play the frame of thought there are it
Again, you've since got to do with the villains
It's not where you're from
It's can they use it
The stuff you brought
And that we are given
A piece of the mind
Connect with the rhythm
The special soul
Yeah, yeah, yeah
This we share the soul
And it's time
What do you shit and so
I'll cook the wrong breakfast
I once tasted was shared
And so
At the emotions the lack that aren't running
What I'd sayower and a Auf
What I said
But I lost what I said
Love and me pass
But all lies
All lies
All right, all right, all right, all right
Deep we share the song
And deep we share the song
May not be entirely familiar to some of the US based Charlie and Chuckle heads up there
Dutch band Urban Dam Squat, the deeper shade of soul
I wonder what those guys are up to these days
Everything's huge hit back in the day
Fucking awesome, I like it the same time
And really has their shit together
Okay, we've up the band width
So we can continue the program, not a problem
Remember if you want to dedicate something on the air here in the Charlie
We're doing Skype calls, just drop a little note in your Dropbox
Share that with me and I'll get around to you eventually
I think I'll try
I'll do my absolute best
Gotta tell you guys have an eclectic taste
Really loving it though
Remember these cats?
Known as the BIOS?
Shhh
He went on a shoot
And he got
Told you and football he got
Walk you finger
Shhh
Go, go, go, go
He said, I know you
You know me
One thing I can tell you is you got to be free
Come together
Right now
Over me
Shhh
He back in touch
He got
All this gun would be cut
Oh no, sad boy he won
Spiral cracker
He got feet
Down below his knee
Hold you in his arm
Share you can't feel his disease
Come together
Right now
Over me
Shhh
Right
You roll the ghost and he got Ellie wanted, he got Marty wanted, he wanted, he wanted more, you'll filter, he said, one, one, one, one is three
Got to be good looking, got to be so hard to see, come together, right now, all of me
We'll sing as we'll never see that on iTunes, we'll sing as we'll never see that on iTunes
I guess we might as well share it here on the Charminer, kind of the place where we've been doing that lately
You know, I have been touring again, I just can't help myself with the idea, hopping on the screen once a day and doing something non-musical
It's just been so much amazing shit that's coming out these days
And I didn't last night with a couple of nice folks here in LA, we are not alone
That's for damn sure, I can wow, just do something short 30 minutes a day
But that can't happen until I find a freaking intern or someone to help me with the editing of the big app shows
That takes up a lot of time, in fact it's like a sinkhole of time is what it is
Yeah, so I've got the lovely Miss Christina here who was staying the night before she goes back down the hill
And let me just see if she's there
Yeah, so she shows me this picture
She was hanging out yesterday, it's not very far, let me see Marilyn Manson, people got that
Yeah, she gets around, I'm just sitting here, growing cobwebs
Meanwhile, the kid is having a rock and sound
So this is one of those falsely labeled songs, it's not the temptations, it's his love, tender, and version
What's great about it though, is it is a live version
You love this song, every time I turn around I'm back in love again with you
Sounds like they got some clobbies, some wood they're knocking on
And maybe a cowbell or two, right?
Leave on Charlie eight, five, zero
Here it's time, I'll find you, we're out for a minute
Here we come, I'll find you, I'll find you
I'll get out of the hole, I'll find you
I might be alone
Here we come, I'll find you, I'll find you
Sometimes I just don't need you
You'll find me, when I look at me, when we're tired, I'll find you
I'll find you, I'll get out of the hole, I'll get out of the hole
Now I'll find you, when you put your arms around me
I feel so sad, it's fine
I hope to love you forever, yeah
I just can't, I think it's fine
Yeah, let's have a happy one, let's have a baby
I'll find you, I'll get out of the hole, I'll find you
I'll find you, I'll find you
I'll find you, I'll get out of the hole, I'll get out of the hole
Now I'll find you, I'll find you
I'll find you, I'll find you
I'll get out of the hole, I'll get out of the hole
Now I'll find you, I'll find you
I'll find you, I'll find you
You go for it
Just something you'll have to go back
I can't stop to go and love a little bit
Yeah, it's time for fun
Oh, look at me
If it's time to turn around
I just wanna love you
Yeah, it's time to fight
Yeah, yeah
You lies in fights, you fight
Yeah, it's time to fight
Oh, seriously
I'm not
I'm not here
Just don't leave me
I am
I'm not here
Oh, feel so stupid
I can't love again
Can't stop to go back
Yeah, it's time to fight
I'm not here
Oh, c-d
I'm sitting
I personally love together
I've never heard this version though.
Thank you so much for dropping that off in the Dropbox.
Getting requests in every minute or so with new Dropboxes to share.
Down to 40 gigs available on the hard drive here.
So we'll see just how far we get.
And I think it's time to get the party cranked up just a little bit.
I'm curious.
Fuck all of you.
We're here to rock.
I'm like...
Turn down your speaker.
I'm on it.
When I'm with you baby, I go on my roof.
I just can't get enough.
If I'm with you baby, I live with you.
I just can't get enough, I just can't see things.
Get it, I'm off.
You want to get a walk around the street
I just can't get enough
Every time I think you do, I know we have to meet
It's getting hard, it's a pretty low
And I just can't seem to get enough
I just can't get enough
I just can't get enough. I just can't get enough. I just can't get enough, I just can't get enough.
I just can't get enough, I just can't get enough.
And we break, you just shot in love for me.
I just can't get enough. I just can't get enough.
Just like we're rainbow, you know you set free.
And I just can't get enough, and I just can't get enough
You're laughing too hard, you're laughing too hard
And I just can't seem to get you apart
I just can't get enough, and I just can't get enough
Just can't get enough, and I just can't get enough
But I just can't get enough, and I just can't get enough
Lookin' true, I can't get enough
Yeah, that takes me back as well. The best mode just can't get enough in the daily source
code episode eight five zero coming to you from the Hilltop Watch Tower Crackpot Command Center.
As promised, I'm going to do some dedications today on the air try something new. I think
we have a knowledge and a chat dot net regular on yellow jackets in the morning.
Hey, in the morning man. How are you? Good. Yeah. Where are you actually from? St. John's new
from land Canada most Easterly city in North America. Lovely. I did. And when I was listening to you
just a second ago, you had a police scanner on in the background. Yeah, there's a house fire up the
street. You're a true nerd. You're sitting there listening to police scanner. Absolutely. I got the
source code on next to me and everything. Awesome. Awesome. All right. What can we play for you here on the
eight five zero? Hey, so Don Henley dirty laundry to all the media types out there that's
love taking up the dirt. All right. The real dirt, of course, scrambled bracelets and the
like important things. Excellent. All right. Yellow jacket. Thanks for the request man. It's on
for you right now. Okay. Thanks. Take it easy now. In the morning.
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I
mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean, I mean I mean I mean I mean I mean...
You can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl
You can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find a girl, you can't find the guy, you can't now hide the girl, you can't find the girl, you can't find someone, coming back right now so let's not go on and run back together and run again if we try to make a call over each single call, nothing gonna happen with you today
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, like yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, there yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love
kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, killed my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill my love, kill
have worked for me.
It really did.
And it's nice to put a voice to, you know,
line scrolling by on my IRCC.
Terminal here.
And no more people really are at.
So here's a deal.
If you have a dedication, have a request.
All you gotta do is drop a little text file into your
shared Dropbox folder.
With your Skype name.
And whatever details you want to get me.
So I can add you as a contact and bring it on the air.
I really like that.
I think that's the, well, actually, back from I was in the,
in London.
I think we did it a couple times.
But never really with that kind of success.
You've got it all hooked up.
So the sound is actually fairly decent.
All right, let's do that.
Totally digging that.
Thank you, Ella Jack, if you request Don Henley's dirty laundry.
Certainly one of my favorite Don Henley tunes.
The guy, well, if you've never heard of stuff,
he's got a couple of very cool tunes.
Inside job being one of my favorites without a doubt.
How about one of the ugliest guys in show business?
I mean, the guy's awesome.
He's got a big hit.
At the week there.
Joe Jackson's stepping out on the Charlie.
The miss the cross.
The window hides the land.
But nothing has the color of the lines.
That shine.
Electricity is so fun.
Look at dry roads.
So tired of all the darkness in a light.
With no more angry words to say could come alive.
Get into a car and drive.
To the other side.
Stand in my mouth.
To the light.
To the dark.
To the wind.
Are young again in all before our time.
We'll leave the TV and the radio.
We'll be fine.
Don't you want a wonderful fight.
Stand here now tonight.
To the light.
Baby, to be my heart, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise,
the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, and the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise, to the rise
miss them even this stuff stepping out on daily source code episode 850.
Now, when it comes to bringing back the art of radio globally, there's a couple things
that we do here on the daily source code if you're new to the program, it seems like
the audience does appear to be growing again over the years.
We definitely play songs that you probably never would or ever will here on commercial
radio mainly because they're just too damn long and we need to get some commercials
in there.
So it's 12-inch?
Yeah, I got my 12-inch right here for you.
Have not heard this version in many, many years, snippet to your driver's seat on the
chart.
You're doing all right, little driving on the Saturday night, you come up
man, gonna die in the day and the way.
And I miss me, show it smile for people as you need, I'm trouble is trying to get out
of the way you look in the light.
News and blue, the news and blue, I don't wait to get to you.
You're doing all right, little driving on the Saturday night, you come up man, gonna die in
the day and the way you look in the light.
the night, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man
and you come up man
and you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light
and you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light,
you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you come up man, gonna die in the light, you bring it over to me, aaway?
I know I said this on a previous episode.
But it's so freaking surreal to have you guys actually producing the show that dropping tracks
into your box totally loving really really works and cuts down on the workload for the
disco jacket.
It's exactly the way it should be.
The only song I could ever really handle from Al Jerobe but I've always really really
like the roof garden on the daily source code episode 850 and now a rather famous name on the
skype someone who you of course if you're ever in the chat room and no dinner chat
done that will recognize we welcome gx2 I yeah hey man yeah I can hear you find now how
you doing great okay not too bad not too bad man so where are we calling you gx2 you
calling me about 40 miles west London do you ever sleep you're always in the chat room
uh... no no never never
gx2 of course uh... world renowned for his amazing mixes that he does uh... for no agenda
uh... they you got a family man because it seems like you just spend all your time
working on stuff
i i fit that in with the family as well
so yeah it's 24
24 by seven
yeah they actually know what you're doing in the and they're okay well yeah yeah yeah
there i ask what you do in real life gx2
uh... i'm a gc computer programmer
excellent what particular language
jupel
yeah yes
another jupel
we could have known we could have known so uh... well i just want to say i want to reiterate
we really appreciate everything you've done for no agenda love having you in the chat room
you've been dropping some uh...
some great tunes into the drop box that's awesome and uh... you have an interesting
request the song that uh... i haven't heard uh... in a while i doubt that if anyone
has really heard this song
yeah i don't think anybody because i think
because you were kind of saying that you know this stuff is in play done radio and i thought
i kind of drop one in
that nobody's ever heard before
and this one is uh... the mike florist pop so orchestra doing princess nineteen ninety nine
and i kind of nineteen forty's franks natural way i love it and i really
different yeah i'm sure everyone on the stream is going to love it as well
it's very different
is that what we call something that sucks these days it's very different
that not really no no it's just it's just different it won't get played on the radio
it's just different no absolutely absolutely different that's all all right we're
we're going to listen to it right now gx2 thanks again man thanks for
for sharing this with us and yes he man yeah anytime it's my pleasure i love it
okay take care all right in the morning to you all right in the morning to you
but you've never really had a doubt i don't believe that anybody
means the way i do about you
and all you go is the lead is where i'm winding
and all the lives that like the way you're winding you know actually i just
realize that uh we had that wonderful uh that wonderful setup and then uh i
actually uh dropped in the wrong song so hold on a second let me
correct that immediately i'm uh that really sucks uh how come i can't find it now why
is it not showing up for some reason uh this is also mike florist pop
except it's exactly the wrong song all right let's uh let's try this uh let's try this
hold on a second see this shit wouldn't happen on real radio no because there's
little professional here we go
but when i woke this morning i thought it was a judgment day
the sky was our purple all the people running everywhere
the trying to run away destruction but me i didn't even care
but since you don't use your body over it's all the time
tonight i'm gonna party like it's nineteen nine
well it didn't come to party don't bother nothing at my door
got a line in my pocket and baby he's ready to roll
everybody's got a bum we can all die here the day
before i let that happen don't have that smile like the way
i said you 000 000 a body over it's all the time
tonight i'm gonna party like it's nineteen nine
welcome to the new wilds generation everybody the reason my voice sounds so
clear is because there's no cracking my brain and i'm also using a microphone
to tell us now i'd like to take this off choosy to thank you all for coming to
our little end of the millennium party so just relax let your head down and if you
can't let your head down then just take it off mmm
i said 000 000 a body over it's all the time
tonight i'm gonna party like it's nineteen nine
well i'm going down to your health best street yeah
i'm gonna walk so sexy
why am i from my head to my toe i'm going down i'm what year is it
oh we got there eventually didn't we awesome i really like that my
flowers pops we're gonna party like it's nineteen ninety nine thank you very much
june x two for bringing that all the way home to us sorry about little cock up there
shit does happen you see i know you're not real man because i'm loaded okay
i've had some experience in that area besides that whole rap of yours is
bold anyway good evil it's all the same crap rock and roll the only thing that counts
dig hard ass blistering awesome heavy metal rock and roll you say
oh
What the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck have you got?
What the fuck aren't you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
Wait a sec.
Look at creatures.
Stop, wait a sec.
Stop.
Look at you.
You.
The fuck.
Lopin.
Why the fuck?
look at me.
Fuck.
You.
I.
You know, right now, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, both of you know, you know, you know, are you, who are you, who are you, is your great
Turn down your fingers!
It's the start somewhere.
It is the start sometime.
What better place than here?
What better time than now?
Ha!
Don't let down!
You can't let down!
You're not let down!
Stop!
Don't let down
Nah, either.
Oh, no.
This ship met a in the fort I'd be alive.
And see what's back.
The profusibly died here.
Trying to get right.
You're the land of the world
In your pennies
I'm the land of the world
You're the land of the world
Your land of the world
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh.
Oh, let's go try the game!
The power's taking the right!
Yeah.
Come here like that.
Uh.
Yeah.
Huh.
Yeah, that's what I'm fucking talking about.
The fleets of the Stone Age, a song for the dead,
thank you very much Raymond Quart, our buddy from Norway,
dropping that in his box here on the daily source code episode 850.
Yeah, all right, we got more Skype requests coming up in just a minute.
People are going to go down to get Monation Kiwi next.
So, stay tuned as we roll out.
Something just a little more mainstream after Queens, the Stone Age and Rage against the machine.
It's chilly trappers, blood, sugar, sex magic, I'm Charlie, the snap of the Saturday.
Okay, people are going to be young men.
So, I'm not alone, do what you know.
Well done, little boy.
Come and buy me a star gun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
People are going to stay on the daily source code episode 850.
So, I'm just kidding my shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stay right here.
Is shit talking dirty.
Get to me, sweets with Mr. Macbook.
May the suck my kiss.
Let's make it the seed, y'all know where to want to be.
It's forever, my world that comes here.
I need you really.
You want my girl to be a seed.
Oh baby, just for you.
I'm still in a different world with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, I'm just kidding my shit.
Get to me, I'm just kidding my shit.
You know where to go.
It's time.
Oh, I'm just kidding my shit.
Oh baby, do you know where to be?
You know where to be.
It's me, you get it, man.
So, my kiss.
Get me, people, right now.
Stay right here.
Is shit talking dirty.
Get to me, sweets with Mr. Macbook.
May the suck my kiss.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Shit, oh man.
You know where to be.
You know who to be.
As we are well into the second half of the show
On the snafu Saturday
Yeah, it is the what are we here today the 23rd of October
Snafu Saturday we roll out songs that you never hear on the radio never have heard him probably never will hear him and we're going to get
Monation Kiwi where we've got a Kiwi Chris on the line Kiwi. How you doing man?
Oh, hold on a second for some reason. Are you there?
Yeah, I'm here man. Okay. There you go. Hey buddy. How are you? I'm good man. Excellent. This is it. This is really going off. This is fantastic
Yeah, it's working. Hey listen. Are you anywhere in your Christ church and all the earthquake machine activity
We're in the north island. So about four hours drive away. I've had a number of friends from down that way
They're still going on man. They're up to about four and a half thousand shakes since the big one
Yeah, what's up with that? I mean, is this like a normal occurrence for there or is this completely new?
Now, this is completely new for them. They yeah, this they've never had a earthquake on this particular fault
But it's been really going off. They've been getting fours almost every day
And this still you know, a liquefaction where the sand comes up through the ground and people's houses are being
Absolutely fine basic like that's that's crazy man because you know, what does the ministry of true saying?
What is the new saying about what what this is all about? There's a I mean no one predicted this that geologists could know it
It just all of sudden appears out of thin air
Yeah, just seemed just seemed to happen and
It caught everyone by surprise the geologist and the and the tectomic guys are just going off the planet as far as excitement goes
You know, there's probably stains all over their house, but they got word big time
But some know that I'm in the government's doing a pretty good job of managing it. Obviously everyone down there's under stress and strain
But some I think it's coming out okay by the sounds of it. Well, I find it fascinating
What do you guys have oil or something? There must be something going on there might be some value in damn hills
Yeah, the probably is but we haven't been told about it
Well Chris we certainly hope that you stay safe but it sounds like you're far enough away from the fault line that nothing should happen
How big is New Zealand actually in in in in area?
Oh, it's probably about the same size as England I suppose and
Then we've got about four million four and a five million people I suppose
Yeah, it's a pretty cool place to live. It's just a long way to get to anywhere
She know when I visited you in San Francisco
You know it's a 12-hour flight from here and it's well with you know spending some time
Once you get out of the country. I don't know if you noticed when we met because we met twice in the office
The media office, but I was walking down second street. I'm just strolling along just minding mill business all of a sudden
I can feel like someone behind me and then someone calls out money and you're not a small guy
You're like you're like a six six-foot tall or something like a
Always you know, I have this idea like someone's gonna sneak up one day and give me two to the head and I'll be it
It was tempting
All right Chris, so you got some real kiwi music for us for the show
Yeah, this is this is an old one
I managed to dig it out of my eye because somewhere it was that this was about the same time as David Bowie was sort of hitting a stride
And it was a kiwi band that
Sort of put something together and it sounds pretty good really and something you definitely would never hear on the radio
Certainly not and get monation proper
Up on the on the upside of the of the globe
Yeah, absolutely not all right. You want to tell us what it is
It's the thing called space folks and it was out on the street was the name of it
It was I think there was a fair bit of acid being taken at the time
How the good old days good times
All right Chris, thank you so much man and Steve safe down there and check in from time the time
Letters know what's going on okay
All right in the morning to you
Who's
Wrong
I'm a boy who tried to follow her, trying to she aspires
She's out how long the street, out of the street
But she talks to everyone she needs, out of the street
She needs no roots, she tells you she's right, she knows
I'm on the street, out of the street
And she talks to everyone she needs, out of the street
She tells you she's right, she knows she's wrong
I'm on the street, out of the street
I try to get myself out of the street, she tells you she's right, she knows
I'm on the street, out of the street, out of the street
I'll show off the street, I'll show off the street
She tells me she's right, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it, she does it,
it's gentle, that's a rose fellae can conquer anyone
It's time to take a stand
Brothers and sisters, the world
We've got to let them roll
We can't do it alone, we can't let no more
We can't do it alone, we can't do it alone
We can't do it alone
We can't do it alone, we can't do it
We can't do it alone, we can't do it alone
We can't do it alone