Delta Sierra Charlie 853, the Black Friday Edition, please stand.
Police and gentlemen, please rise for your get-ownation, national anthem.
In the morning get-ownation, we are all charged to be.
You've been resources and servants in all lands and all ships and sea.
From the east to west down north to the lowlands and beyond.
We are happy and distracted, slaves.
Here are hidden foundations on.
We are all here!
We're 16 months and 7 months in showing five rounds of time.
The 25th century of radio starts here.
We're here to meet our lives on no gender stricter.
On casting, here's the Battle of Korea.
You've been waiting for five long days.
Passing time and so many waves right here.
Just waiting.
Just waiting, baby.
We're all here to meet our lives.
We're all here to meet our lives on no gender stricter.
Tell them it's going to be our rock and roll.
Rock and roll, yeah.
Trace your watch.
Let's get the time.
Passing time and so many waves right here.
We're all here to meet our lives on no gender stricter.
Rock and roll, yeah.
Tell them it's going to be our rock and roll, yeah.
You're waiting five on ding.
We'll make what's just a little bit more.
It's going to be our rock and roll.
We can't it is officially quick and time.
Everybody does the daily search code episode.
It's five, three, it's good.
Black Friday, four, our mission crew.
The second best thing you can do by yourself.
In the morning.
Chatroom all filled up with human resources.
Your charts are ready to go just the way their government loves them.
You know we're going to chat about that.
We're alive.
You know we're going to scream.com, everybody.
Rock and roll, yeah.
Rock and roll, yeah, yeah.
Give it away, give it away, give it away, give it away, give it away
Like you need women in my ability
There's no doubt I know right, you're the killing team
Come and check it up, I'm the killing team
That's where the lotta helllockin' more
Fin't the fear of beating, mama, mama
Don't mind my good until i'm dead
No call no time which is coming soon
Feel it, then, not for the vote
And make trigger my previous gun
Does Totally light the death
For the dribbled blunt to be a gun
And keep your world not-led, can't shed your fuck
And dies and never go back
Come on, everybody down to defend
Forever way, keep Rushway, give Rushway
Now, give Rushway,送 Rushway
Keep Rushway, give Rushway
Give it away, give it away, give it away, now
끄 caval, keep your low, oh boy
asy
What I got you got to give it to ya, byman
Why the catch you got to give it to ya, byman
Why the catch you got to give it to ya, die
And turn your two zititz in again, win me now
Meow, tell you
Why the catch you got to give it to ya, byman
Yes
What the catch you gotta clean it put it in you
What I catch you gotta get it put it in you
You know with the feeling that's done
Can't see you
Oh my god, that's not a word I've been trying to
Can't find my sky and be the winds up
Don't break it, that's nothing up
I don't remember if I ever run a keep it like the clouds
Give it away, give it away, give it away
Give it away, give it away now
Give it away now
Give it away, give it away, give it away
That's the first choolio consort radio program
It's the bringing here the radio
Globally
And we truly are worldwide, I'm the stream, no one's just stream.com.
Should the track first get the wheel now?
It's a black Friday with fleas of shopping and strap-a-gams,
and these United States of Gitmo Nation, of course.
We are slaves who are disobedient.
We're not going to go out and fight with crowds.
We're going to hang out with the ride pods, our iPhones, our speaker systems,
and we're going to share some music together the way it used to play.
Time to rock it up a little bit.
Just a little bit of ear bleeding music.
I think we deserve that.
To wake up from the coma toast steak from the turkey yesterday.
Now, never thought I'd feel this way.
I wanted to believe.
The founders are starting in their grace.
And what we've come to be.
The tactics act is for your freedom and civil liberties.
Robert King's never reading war.
For coming by darling late.
You can fool people some of the time.
But you can't fool me.
The cost is because you can't defend itself.
So you're going to focus like me.
We'll bring it on and we prefer it straight.
And stop lies in the sea.
But be aware we know your game.
I know what you can't defend.
Where do you think this will lead?
You like us and can't have them here.
Who opened your eyes and see?
I doubt to buy a group of folks.
A criminal's in the sea.
Don't let them intimidate you.
Here is how they feed.
No matter what they throw away.
We must defend them and see.
Where do you think this will lead?
They're building a kill and a shame.
Where do you think this is gonna lead?
Where do you think this will lead?
Somewhere spectral care is coming.
The moment this impacts, I think the point is the moment you have encountered.
That guess our sight out there, so will Gary.
But, how the time this image can just make Death OUT.
So, we can't control the security of axis.
Everyone now knows!
It will go through the edge of the darkness of the war twice!
Go through the darkness of the darkness
You know you'd almost be thinking that those guys listen to the show to the Noah
agenda show the sons of liberty and false flag you heard it here on the daily source code
where up to episode 853 near future a crisis approaching that unnerves me and causes me to
tremble from my country corporations are in throned and corruption in high places will follow
the money power will prolong its reign by working on the prejudices of the people until all wealth
is aggregated in the hands of a few and the republic is destroyed Abraham Lincoln
fuck yeah hey whoever went out and propagated the formula on the president Barack Obama
congratulations great job formula is this we go out we hit people in the mouth
yeah 12 stitches I want a little bit too literally perhaps say it with me now
I think we need something to lift our spirits something to help us get up get out of our lazy bed
and about the ankle seems to do the trick for me I think it's trick the fan that you find
in Turkey and that's the shit that makes you completely calm and cozy
step to baby she goes out every night to the moon on his light and she sleeps all day
to come on I get up and we'll see you in a game I drag you out
I get up I get up get up your life is in bed before I can't breathe and step to baby I don't care anymore
you can sleep on the floor I just knocking you out so come on I get up I won't say you're the game
I drag you out
I get up get up get up get up your life is in bed get up get up your life is in bed get up get up
get out get up get up get up get up get up get up get up I know a lot of you only want to hear
bleeding stuff we must do it for work right now but I think it's kind of a special one
and that's my spirit get out your lazy bed that's right and five three is the episode
oh geez GX2's already in the chat room bitch and about disco duck now there will be no disco duck
in the show ever I'm sorry if we just can't do that I had a really great thanks giving yes I
hope those of you in get monation proper had similar experience had the the kid over the cup cake my
little cream cream sickle Christina came by and well it was just it was a complete lovely family
experience where she was even helping cooking she made a fantastic two layered chocolate cake
and I took care of all of the cooking outside of the cake for the first time I really had to
go all out and in fact I spent about 30 minutes with John after the show on Thursday discussing
exactly how to make candy jams and I did use his recipe with the bourbon and I'll tell you not only
did it work and taste great we got kind of hammered which was pretty awesome just the three of us
not bad till let's see if we can kind of awaken stretch a little bit in the full box
get me a track drop on the drop box send me the invite jams right here right now on the Charlie
where as life has a baby
When it's in the world, the change
The blame come from mine
Diffin' the thing
And mess your soul
I was alive in a way
In a way, in a way
Like you're right now
I'm alive in a way
In a way, in a way
I was alive in a way
Right in a way, in a way
Right now, there is no other place I want to be
Right here, right now, but you know where I go from here to here
Right here, right now, there is no other place I want to be
I must say there's only two things that can make a dad, the happiest
One is when your kid says, I love this food you're cooked, can I have some more?
And I have to say the other one is when the kid's laughing at your jokes
It was happening all the once you asked today
I mean, I'm on cloud nine here, I'm telling you
Not only that, but wow, did you see the pictures?
I don't know if I think she may have put him on her Facebook or tweeted them
Oh boy, she got a lot of, a lot of pleasure out of me fisting the turkey
As she calls it, as I was jamming the stuffing deep down into the bird
It's one of these songs you can only play once a year
Because the titles completely appropriated and black Friday
I collect everything I want, and before my friends find out of it on the road
When black Friday calls you know it's got to be
Don't let it fall
Yeah
When you cry, cry, come
I fly down to my swell girl
Gonna strike all the big red words
You're my little black boy
Don't do just what I need
Don't wear no shots in you
When nothing goes over me, all the time goes
When black Friday calls you know it's got to be on that road
You know I will
Yeah
When black Friday calls you know it's got to be on that road
I'm gonna take myself a hold
Gonna lay down in the middle of a set of spots on my shoulders
Don't let the world pass by me
Gosh, this ship don't say goodbye
And if you don't come, it's gonna fall
When black Friday calls you know it's got to be on that road
Now I guess I'll take my hand
You know for 20 years I was not only did I not cook
I was not allowed to cook long story, trust me, though
And it's so amazing that if you just indulge me for a second
If I can tell you when we have your turkey
We had your mashed potatoes, your candy gums, your Brussels sprouts
You're a corn on the cob
All time perfectly and not a single thing
Was cooked with reference to a recipe book
Now my mom used to cook all the time I'll tell you
And when I'm in the kitchen this weird thing happens
It's like she's almost sitting on my shoulder
And she's like guiding me
I swear to god, I know it sounds kind of like
Who's out there, but it's really true
It's like, oh no, it's over there, sniff the spices
And like, yeah, I'll put some of this time, yeah, that'll be good
How about a little bit of trying the family stone
Shall we all try and get that a dance to the music
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it
All we need is a drama
But people only need a beat, yeah
I'm gonna add a little good talk
And make it easier to move your beat
You might like to hear my organ
I'll sit right now
Let me out, yeah, yeah, yeah
If I could hear the whole song
Sit the air on the ground
Yeah
Isn't it me?
Sit the air, call the message that's heard
All the square's heard
That's not opinion, that's science
The science is one cold, how did they do the 14-inch drama
It's been a great interest
I've been following this open source daily source code
The project that the human resources had been putting together
It's really quite fascinating how we've wired
I'll say we, but they've wired Dropbox to a stream
I'd really like to figure out how we can have that shit automatically switch over
Maybe do some real programming
We can still repeat no agenda and daily source code
And then in between have all of that stuff rocket
I'm liking it
And then of course we need to have some more interaction
That's something I gotta do
I think we have come up with something amazing
Go, go, kill me, Thunderbird's already dead
Gotta focus on that, just come on the way
Oh, look out
Put your white blood in the light
Everybody in this trees
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep
Go, Thunderbird's
This is a journey into a sun
Study on the funnest side
Study on funnest side
You play Russian the way
Keep this frequency clear
Study on funnest side
studied on funnest side
Register on funnest side
The beast was beast beast, the beast was their cults.
Essentially, if we're talking about here is mashups of the beasty boys and the Beatles,
the Beatles and the Beatles and the Beatles.
The Beatles and the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the
The Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles
the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles
The Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, The Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, The Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, the Beatles, The Beatles, the Beatles, The beat, the beat, the beat.
And that's kind of intense, I had no idea that D.J.P.C.
Years, I guess he used my voice in the beginning of that.
I don't know if that's a recording of something else, but it's fucking cool, I like it.
That's the, our little middle finger to Steve Jobs.
Yeah, hey, nice to have Steve.
First we killed Michael, then we released an album of his work that he never would have wanted to release.
And then we put the Beatles in iTunes.
Okay.
Tell me that ain't connected.
That's no coincidence.
Alright, this is what you want to crank it up, see if it goes to 11.
You've got a trickle of blood rolling out of your ears with me.
It's super massive, black hole.
You've got a lot of blood.
You said you're still in my way.
I've got your hands are empty.
You've got a lot of blood.
You said you're still in my way.
I thought I was a fool for no one
I thought baby, I'm a fool for you
Yeah, I'll call you, I'll be soon
Yeah, I'll help you, I'll tell you
I'll be soon, I'll be soon
Say that a matter of time
Say that do that
Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back
up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up,
Yeah, kind of reverberates to the entire body down to the bones, doesn't it?
What radio station do they play this song on?
Please just tell me that.
I've been feeling I'm not going to find very many at all.
Again, it's...
So we've got a really big figure out, is that open source Dave your source code?
That's where you can basically put a radio station together.
There was songs you'd never hear anyway, or anywhere.
And boy, do I love looking at these drop boxes?
This is from Adam Hanson's drop box, he's in Toledo, Ohio.
He dropped a couple of interest in tracks in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go, go, go with a smile.
Keep bustin'.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah every dream at night
music
number
all
or
not
next
Hi
Who's going?
I'm trying to avoid all this but I can't
I just gotta know
We're gonna try to let this together
Stop
Rest
Who is that?
Kiki Vale
She's great
Oh yeah
Yeah
I wanna fight that body
Oh yeah
Yeah
Oh no
That might be
Oh yeah
Yeah
He's out there right now
Right
Oh yeah
Yeah
Oh no
Every dance with the down on the dance line
I always ask that of all my friends
I just like this sound
Yeah
Hey
In person
Oh
Hey
hey Jackie, there's lots of Robin in the computer
Hisا
How need genanimous, genanimous
Viroode
And I'm a
좀
I'm
I'm a
model
I'M ALRAD
Yeah, remember when French was in that kind of house he punky vibe and he did the soundtrack
to Batman?
Well, that was it, my friends, there you go.
That must have been 80's, right?
Please tell me it was a long, long time ago.
By the way, speaking of 80's, last night we watched a classic movie on DVD, Christine had
brought this one over.
It's the three heathers.
Oh my god, I can't believe how young they all were.
Christian Slater, Shannon Doherty, Heather was, what the hell was her name?
Winona writer?
Oh man, it was like, and of course, all of a sudden, I've never seen it.
Remember, that's where the ultimate phrase comes from right at the beginning of the movie.
Ah, fuck me gently with a chain saw.
Brand new Michael Jackson, RIP, being raped after being killed.
That's the way they work with a woman that I did.
It's breaking news.
Listen to the lyrics.
They're shoving it in our face, that's how arrogant these fuckers are.
Everybody want in my piece of Michael Jackson.
The more it's talking the more some Michael Jackson.
They're just when you thought he was dying.
He wants to give it a kid.
They can put around the world today.
He want to write my bitch away.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
You just want to read it again.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
You just want to feel it again.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.'
Oh yeah, oh yeah yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
ijing behinding watching the attention my old Jackson
man, you all understood that if fall because of my old Jackson.
I'm with the rest of the story like it's so happen
You turn your back on the love and you can't get it again
No matter what you just want to read it again
No matter what you just want to feel it again
I just want to read it all with all the love
I always have all the major things to do
I'm with my crazy girl
I just can't go
I'm just just breaking
I'm thinking of you
It's just crazy
I can't do
My education is always hard
I'm feeling like you're thinking of
I'm with my crazy girl
I just can't go
You're so crazy
I can't do
I just can't do
I'm with the new stars today
They say we crazy
Every day
You're so crazy
You're more Disney
My education is always hard
I can't do
I'm feeling like you're thinking of
I'm with my crazy girl
I just can't go
You're so crazy
I can't do
My education is always hard
I'm with my crazy girl
I'll bring all my crazy cars out of charge, and all the crazy things
I've been in a little distance, crazy in a little distance
I've been in a little distance
Move with me inside this strange world of the twelve-inch twos in twos
Where nothing is as it seems, seems seems
Where everything has its place, space and there's a place
So everything, everything, everything
And anything, come out
Let me take you on a tour of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of
the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the twerוס of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the tweros of the
Now, our favorite, the funky guitar.
Building thoughts, the funky percussion.
Building thoughts.