Delta Sierra Charlie, 8-3-2 the Snapfoo Saturday Edition.
We'll 16-0 in Sysad minutes, ensuring 5-9's up-time turn.
The 21st century of radio stars here.
We don't need us.
We can't hear the meaning of life.
I know it's in the strength I care.
I'm testing.
It's Adam Curry.
Well, I'm half-blotted.
Can't get to see.
I gotta pay the level of a hundred free.
Come on, baby.
You're doing all the best.
I'm half-blotted.
You don't have to read my mind.
To know what I have in mind.
Honey, you don't know.
Now you move so fine.
Let me lay it on the line.
I want to know what you're doing.
And to the show.
Now it's up to you.
We can make a secret running through.
Just me and you.
That's going to love it like you never do.
That's why I'm half-blotted.
Can't get to see.
I gotta pay the level of a hundred free.
Come on, baby.
You're doing all the best.
I'm half-blotted.
It feels alright.
Maybe you can't stay all night.
Shall I leave you my key?
What you've got to give me the sign?
Oh no, I've got the sign.
Tell me, are you half-mom?
You sure look that way to me.
Are you moving now?
Will you be ready when I call your love?
Is my timing right?
It's like you're love me tonight.
Yeah, I'm half-blotted.
Can't get to see.
Feel a bit of burning inside of me.
Come baby, you're doing all the best.
I'm half-blotted.
Say hello to my little friend.
I'm a carry.
I'm a daily source call.
I'm half-blotted.
Now it's up to you.
Can we make a secret run?
Yeah, we'll make a secret run, yeah, we'll make a secret run.
Now it's up to you.
You'll have to get away from you, no?
I'm half-blotted.
Can't get to see.
Gotta be, though, a hundred and three.
Come home baby, you're doing all the best.
Hot blood and hot blood and every night
Oh yeah, hot blood and you're looking so tight
Hot blood and I can tell that you're alive
Hot blood and hot blood and hot blood
Hot blood and I, it's day of source code episode 832
Coming to you from the hilltop watch tower crackpot command center
And the people's Republic of Southern California
This is of course a snap-oocider edition
So a little bit lower key than a football Friday, but still
Enough tunes to keep your rockers
Small jeans, genius, my cough, I've seen it
Strong out of lasers, slash back lasers
Ain't all your razors while pulling the waders
Talking about non-roll, your kin's no way
New y'all so go go and everything tastes nice
All in a greening
Get back to it
Ging, genius, my cough, I've seen it
Strong out of lasers, slash back lasers
Oh
It's like a man, but smiles like a reptile
She loved him, she loved him
But just more short while
Stretching the sand, let's go and his hand
To set the easy addition
Sales you nutrition, keep on your den-herfer
Making a bummed web
All the greenies
The ginger in it lives on his back
The ginger in it loves Jesus' accent
His hands ain't as he spins on him all
The ginger in it lets us out go
Away from him
Swish him while grinding
Can't drive his mouth full
Like summoning an author and sleeping and capture
Gosh, you still calm
A lot swim endarl
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.Image, we didn't
I have now hooked up the old rack as everything arrived from the United Kingdom up David.
Taken home.
Yeah, so I spent most of yesterday, hooking everything up, no longer am I running through
all the digital stuff that crunches the sound and is so incredibly dangerous because when
the Mac crashes, then you can lose pretty much everything.
Although this is technically still a test and we've got a couple of people in the chat room who
already agreed to record the stream just in case the recording messes up.
And I need a backup of the show, at least it'll be available.
So my stuff arrived from the United Kingdom earlier this week.
It arrived in lots of boxes.
It was packed without a lot of love as you can perhaps imagine if you know some of the
backstory.
The shit was literally just thrown into boxes and the worst part was the wires.
When you have a studio and you got a rack full of gear, there's a lot of patch cables,
power cables and it was just basically one big bunch of spaghetti.
Miss Mickey spent about an hour and a half last night with me untangling everything.
And I kept going, oh yes, this is a great find.
This is an awesome cable.
Yeah, this is exactly the one I need.
And of course you never really have enough and you know your brain is just overloaded
thinking about how to set it up so that everything works and I need to
know what's known as a mix minus through Skype.
So I can talk to John in the morning and do that perfectly and have it here everything
except himself.
No echoes.
For those of you who have done any type of broadcasting or podcasting, you know what I'm
talking about.
And of course, I have like four or five microphones.
My favorite one, the high LPR 40 was broken.
I hooked it up and I just couldn't figure out why the sound was all crappy.
And then eventually I just did a direct input into the mix and like, oh okay, this thing
just shit the bed probably because of the way it was packed or the lack of packing for
that reason.
And I got it all hooked up last night.
I will be taking some more pictures explaining exactly what I've got.
I've got quite a nice little chain of stuff.
What was funny though, so I had it all hooked up around 1130 p.m.
This Mickey had gone off to bed.
And I was just working on it and said, why am I supposed to try and figure out
some of the stream stuff and see if I can get everything to work.
But this time I'd popped open a gray goose.
And as most of you all know, I'm not really a drinker.
I'm certainly an amateur.
So I drink a glass and I am completely hammered.
And I'm on the stream is like six people listening.
I think Void Zero was in the chat room in Mr. Oil.
And I was just playing songs.
And if anyone ever recorded that, it could be used against me.
Oh boy.
So I needless to say, I'm hurting just a little bit this morning.
But I do want to bring you a full on food bars, full on snafu Saturday.
And of course, as a part of what arrived in the boxes from London
is not just my gear, not just my wires.
But, haha.
Yes, you'll recognize that, don't you?
So I think we need to celebrate the facts that the cowbell is back.
Are you ready?
It means more cowbell!
We'll be able to fly.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
And of course, it's a good year for the cowbell.
So I don't want you to be myself,
Show me your hands really yet
I'll do it together and it'll hurt us too
Show me your hands
For it has been a long day
I've heard of your words
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ohot, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I
I don't like it, I don't get it, I don't like it, I don't like it, I just don't, I just don't like it, no donne high- specified
Really good!
Hahaha
Wooу opa
All right, that felt good, and by the way, that will be more Cowbell8eron in the program, I promise you that,
I have more Cow Ball songs that have been sent to me for the Sn Ahora through Saturday addition of DailySource mouth of Code Episode 832
at noagendastream.com the party
Is it no agendachief.com
Oh, let's chill out with a little bit of ELO.
You do believe, you are in higher and higher, baby.
It's a living thing.
It's a terrible thing to lose.
It's a given thing.
What a terrible thing to lose.
I can't believe this is what you could see from your worst day.
I'm taken, I'm alive.
I'm moving in life and you live back in time to the first day.
I'm taken, I'm taken.
You, I'm just with the side.
Don't you do it, don't you do it.
Higher and higher, baby.
It's a living thing.
It's a terrible thing to lose.
It's a given thing.
What a terrible thing to lose.
Oh, let's chill out with a little bit of ELO.
It's a given thing.
It's a terrible thing to lose.
What a terrible thing to lose.
I had kind of been epiphany while I was setting everything up yesterday.
Last night really.
God, it sounds so good.
It's almost like when you are listening to MP3's most of your life.
And then all of a sudden you hear a CD on a real good sound system.
Better yet you hear someone playing live.
You're like, oh, that's what I've been missing all this time.
I don't know, it's just like all of a sudden everything's opened up.
The song sound better and everything,
who knows, maybe it was the Grey Goose, I don't know.
Wow.
It's interesting to see what's happening this morning.
Let's turn on the news.
Let's get an overview of what's happening in the world.
And not really getting an overview of what's happening in the world.
All I see is basically two things.
One, everybody in Europe has two implement austerity measures.
austerity, I think is a different word for slave.
And of course, there's still this golf oil thing going on.
I'm pretty sure we'll talk about that in the morning tomorrow for early morning service.
But wow, and this is something I won't bring up on the show tomorrow.
But it seems like the stuff that we've been talking about.
Certainly for the past two, maybe no, actually two and a half almost three years.
That finally, they're getting their way.
And looks like the banks are going to have total control of everything.
Total control of all governments, all political decisions that are made.
And we're, I feel like we're moving towards the, and
God, we've talked about it so much.
Towards the, you know, the one world bank solution, which of course is no different from the one world government.
And that'll be very interesting to see what happens.
I just been watching the euro, man.
It was like 135 a couple weeks ago.
Now it's like 126, 127 things just tankin.
Was it now 700 billion euros has to be set aside in a separate fund for all the problems that are expected.
I'm sure it's going to be 10 times that.
And well, this can only lead to one thing.
That is the complete removal of money as we know it.
And we'll all be using debit cards and credit cards and all kinds of weird stuff.
And we'll be paying carbon taxes probably directly to the banks.
And it was Sammy Hagar, who sang about this a while ago when he was in Montrose number those guys.
It's by the way, is another cowbell song.
But I'll lay back a little bit on that.
It's called Paper Money.
It's on the source code A32.
Play a game of a rich boy.
I buy everything I can.
My main role is a fun thing.
I'm a wealthy man.
A million dollars of note is right there in my hand.
And I can't stand the thing.
Well, it's all that I've got.
Take away all my silver love.
Take away all my gold.
And hand me a stack of paper.
Paper money.
Paper money, don't hold on.
Well, you're acting so you don't remember.
We're all used to be.
Now, what man he likes of the money?
And the man holds a key.
A million dollars of note is right there in my hand.
I can't stand the thing.
Well, it's all that I've got.
Take away all my silver love.
Take away all my gold.
And hand me a stack of paper.
Paper money, paper money, don't hold on.
Paper money, don't hold on.
My car costs me 15 grand.
So I'm saying I got a deal.
Now, the dollar got a thousand pounds of junk.
Ten dollars worth of steel.
A million dollars of note is right there in my hand.
And I can't stand the thing.
Well, it's all that I've got.
Sorry.
Take away all my silver love.
Take away all my gold.
And me a stack of paper.
But paper money, paper money, don't hold on.
Paper money, don't hold on.
Paper paper money, don't hold on.
it's two of my favorite bands, it's I-Fight Dragons doing a cover of Weezer, a Y-Bother.
They somehow turned, I thought that most of this rack gear is equipment pretty much
was dual voltage so that it would do both 220, where I use most of it, and 110 volts.
Only one of them actually was dual voltage, so I took a trip out to fries yesterday, which
was really nice.
For those of you who don't know, fries is without a doubt the nerd heaven of electronics,
computers, and gear, and I was able to acquire a step up converter.
I knew that you could convert down from 220 to 110 volts, but I didn't know that there
were such reasonably affordable transformers available for a step up from 110 to 220.
And so actually the way it works now is there's one chord going into the wall out
left that goes into this thousand watt transformer, and then it's plugged straight into
that, is a UK plug, one of those crazy ones, the big three-prong monster with the fuse in it,
and then that goes into a strip, a UK strip, and from there on out, it's pretty much a
cheap, more nation-east, baby.
The bottom of the airways is landed, and he's sounding good to me.
This is the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Oh yeah, the message.
Change your pace, the source code.
Oh, Adam, let's start the dance.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah and okay just makzak and
Oh, that's a good one.
All's in make sure that I move down
The heart of the blood is in your head
You can take back to the bank
Go team our search and rescue team
We just need cash. I know a lot of people want to send blankets or water
Just in your cash
I'm talking to you. Get up and shout.
There's no hate in the name. Hey, watch your whole night out.
I'm talking to the music.
Oh, I got it. Tell me about you. Hey.
Oh. Hey, shout.
Oh, baby.
In 1965, Vietnam seemed like just another foreign war, but it wasn't.
It was different many ways, and so were those who did the fighting.
In World War II, the average age of the combat soldier was 26.
In Vietnam, he was 19.
Not not not 19.
I haven't just fighting in the past two weeks.
I knew it today, 25 miles from West to Saigon.
I was really sure what was going on.
In Vietnam, the combat soldier typically served at 12 months or a duty.
But the exposed hostile fire almost every day.
Like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like
like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like that.
This is the story of men who are victims of war.
They also have a combat in Vietnam.
According to a veteran's administration's study, half of the Vietnam combat veterans suffer
from what psychiatrists call post-traumatic stress disorder, many vets complain of alienation, rage,
or guilt, some succumb to suicidal thoughts.
This is one legacy of the Vietnam War.
They fought the longest war in American history.
None of them received a hero's welcome.
This is the story of men who are victims of war.
Almost 800,000 men are still fighting the Vietnam War.
Quite amazing how little we have learned since the song came out in the early 80s.
Paul Hardcastle, one of the plethora of mixes available of the track boy.
What a super smash that was.
I love watching the chat room to see the conversation that goes on during every single song.
The music can say so much, it can mean so much.
That was the fallout from the Vietnam War.
Long of course, but now is outdated because the wars we are fighting now in Iraq and Afghanistan are by definition now.
The longest wars the United States has ever fought.
Of course, no one really knows why we're there.
We're still trying to figure that one out.
It's a big game.
There's a lot of players.
We are not players in that game.
Of course, the average age of the Vietnam is probably 18 and not 19.
Just to show you how, as time progresses, things actually go backwards.
Tomorrow night, we'll be the final episode of the Pacific on HBO.
I don't know if you've been following that or not.
I have my grandfather was in the state, was the tenant commander in the Navy and the South Pacific.
I think in this final episode we're going to see exactly the same thing.
Traumatic, you know, post-traumatic stress disorder.
No jobs, people being people who fought under the guise of freedom.
Who were brainwashed into doing that and did it for no other motives than purely patriotic.
Are just shunned.
We're seeing now record number of veterans from Iraq and Afghanistan committing suicide.
Six thousand in this past year alone.
Six thousand.
Sometimes things are so wrong.
And then again, when I look at myself, I think cranky.
I got nothing to complain about.
And all you have to do is listen to a song like that and think to yourself,
shit.
Life's pretty good for me.
In fact, it's been pretty good to me so far.
Count my blessings every morning.
I wake up.
And I actually open my eyes and I'm awake and I'm still alive.
It's nice and sunny and Southern California.
We got Joe Walsh on the Charlie.
Eight, three, two.
One, two, three.
Two, three.
Two,三.
Two, six, four.
One, two.
Two, three.
One, two, three.
one, two, three.
Two, three.
One, two, three.
Who's at the scene of the crime, life's been good to me
So long
My mother, right?
It was 185
I lost my license
Now I don't drive
I have a little road
Right in the back
I left the doors
In the case I'm attacked
Now I keep records
My fans they can't wait
They run me letters
Tell me I'm great
So I got me an office
Go records on the wall
Just leave a message
Maybe I'll call
Lucky I'll stay in a deal
Who's at the end
I can't complain
Let's enter
Now I still do
Life's been good to me
So long
I can't complain
I won't complain
Well, I can't complain
I can't complain
See, you never hear that party either, because then have to break for commercial halfway
through.
A flock of whale ass, I think there's more on this, ah, that dude was smoking something good
wasn't he?
Oh man, ah, I love him, ah, I hold on a second, this is another, ah, this is actually
coming from a video that I found online, actually so I think someone sent this to me, it's
a great piece by the fantastic George Carlin who, ah, unfortunately is no longer with
us.
Oh man, did that guy have a lot of shit straight, did he know exactly what was going on?
And this I think is from an interview where he talks about, well, people like, certainly
like me and maybe like you.
You know, if I had to say to you, what is the answer?
I would say massive bloodshed, I really would.
I don't really, honestly, deep down, believe in political action.
I think the system contracts and expands as it wants to, it accommodates these changes.
I think the civil rights movement was an accommodation on the part of the, those who own
the country.
I think they see where their self-interest lies.
They see a certain amount of freedom seems good, an illusion of liberty, give these people,
give these people a voting day every year so that they'll have the illusion of meaningless
choice.
Meaningless choice that we go, like slaves and say, George, I voted, they, the limits
of debate in this country are established before the debate even begins and everyone else
is marginalized and made to see me there to become units or some sort of disloyal person
a cook.
There's a word and now it's conspiracy, they've made that, something that should not
be even entertained for a minute that powerful people might get together and have a plan.
Doesn't happen, you're a cook, you're a conspiracy buff.
So the only way you cure that death bloodshed, I don't advocate it, but I see that it's
really the only answer.
And of course, in your words.
Yeah.
And I think Greece is, under that, I think they've figured it out.
Unfortunately, I heard another bomb went off in Greece this morning, we're going to see
a lot more crap coming down, but at least we've got the tunes, we've got each other,
and we're all connected virtually speaking.
If you're listening to this show on podcast version, which of course is great, because
you can skip forward and track you don't want to hear, might crap, you don't want to
listen to, but the coolest way is to do it live.
And if you're listening now, no agenda stream.com, check into the chat, no agenda chat.com,
good conversation happening there, meanwhile Michael Murphy.
He comes down, yellow mountain, on a dark, flat land she writes, on a pony she
in wild fire, when the world went by her side, on a comb of rest her night.
Oh, they say she died one winter, when there came a killing frost, and the pony
she named wild fire busted down a stall, and a Blizzard he was lost, she ran calling wild fire,
she ran calling wild fire, she ran calling wild fire, by the dark as a moon, I planted
her hair, but there came an early snow, there's been a hoot out here and by my winter now,
for six nights in a row, she's coming from me and no, and the wild fire will be riding wild
weather riding wild fire will be riding wild fire on wild fire, we're gonna ride her, we're gonna leave
her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna leave her, we're gonna
go ahead of funny, I've got a number of command line windows open here on the dual monitor, I always log in to noagendachat.com, of course, I have a Twitter window, and also because I'm always interested in what they're talking about over there, the Twit Chat, if you look at this, actually I'll take a picture right now. So, they're talking about gadgets over there on Twitter, I see, Olivia, I see, Perez, Hilton saying,
And of course the real conversation is happening at no agenda chat dot com boy, there's a lot of craziness
You know, it's so easy for us to just put our heads in the sand nothing about it think about the coolest new gadget or
What does he joy be hard talk about the other day. Oh, yes porn for women
And what am I saying that that's actually pretty good topic
Comic strip
Oh, yes, how are we doing in the European Union my friend?
Oh, Adam. Yes, what he box is carry is so this is be he is picking a European Union correspondent
Yes, Ireland so Ireland Spain and Greece are cutting spending and the euro currency that seems to be safe
Well, it's not really cutting spending. It's making the people pay for
I believe at least stealing the money
Taking government money putting into projects that nobody needed and we're failing
And Adam, do you remember this ribbon throw up a lot of back?
Yes, we talked about this this of course the new one now is Russia and
And Germany bypassing Poland. Yes, aware of it. Well, apart from the Soviet Russia invading Poland at the same time as
In 1989 from the East it also invaded Estonia and we're taking a stonial
The stonial is a high-tech small country. This is joining you occur in the next year in January
So Estonia is a neighbor of Finland and
Finns were going and are going to Estonia for many many years for cookies and blogs
I think and I'm not kidding
So you see Adam you are is not lost yet
You're right. No, there's still good stuff happening in Europe. Obviously in Estonia
Maybe John and I should do a little road trip
Time to crank up the moon a little bit
Forsells out of that depressing thoughts
With a little bit of funky Miller
Make up to yourself who say good back touch me deep inside
Baby, I hope it's not fair
You can count on me when it's a friend you need
All the same
I hope it all goes well
Now be good to yourself every day and every night
This is a summer girl to be in the band of children
Be true to one another till your dying day
Near the sunshine down your way
Yeah
You know the times we have been far from bad
And I hope it come together once again
But until that day
You just say good back
I'll remember you till the very end
Be true to yourself
Every day and every night
It's a summer girl to be in the band of children
Be true to one another till your dying day
Near the sunshine down your way
Baby, I hope it all goes well
Keep going to your safe every day and every night
This is a summer girl to be in the band of children
Be true to one another
Until your dying day
Near the sunshine down your way
You can count on me when it's a summer girl to be in the band of children
Be true to one another till your dying day
Near the sunshine down your way
Funky fucking Miller
Be true to yourself on the Charlie episode
A 32 the snuff from Saturday edition
And hour and five minutes into the show
And still plenty of tracks to go
And we got great on the Charlie coming up
I'd say about another half hour if you don't mind hanging out
Theujenestream.com and the party's on
Marriage and the chat
This is a summer girl to be in the band of children
Be true to yourself on the Charlie episode
A 32 the snuff from Saturday edition
And still plenty of tracks to go
Funky fucking Miller
It's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's my
great life, it's my life, I must find it, it's my life, it's my life, it's everything I hear, it's my life, a life, a perfume, everything I hold on, thee, behold.
ilation
had faced
where to be
and the real name
Dr. Dicks
here
In this
we're beyond
three
You go to a quest
dangerous
To the winds
HIM
Baroque
Dokes
Demons
Music
I set free, set you up, set that down, teach me how to leave my room
I think that you're gonna lose you
All the night in all the mixed web without looking back
No matter how good you are to be
Remember to throw the train...
Know he you're dead, or...
Let's not start thinking
You're gonna feel better
Burn, burn, burn to wake
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh.
Charlie, a three, two.
Woo, nice to fade out, ladies.
Hey, Space Shuttle, Atlantis launched yesterday.
And I was just watching some, what is it, NASA channel.
Now, it's the thing of myself, is that crazy
that we walked on the moon in the 60s.
I mean, I'm talking 40 years ago, more than 40 years ago.
And the Space Shuttle, of course, was that 70s, late 70s, maybe.
This is technology from 30, 30 plus years ago.
And we haven't been able to do anything else.
And I just look at how personal computers, integrated circuits,
chips, how everything is advanced, the power of technology
that we now hold in our hands.
He got to think to yourself, isn't there more
that they've got, maybe they're holding back on us?
What did they just release the secret manual of the black bird?
The X was at X 57, whatever, that stealth aircraft
that flies at triple supersonic speeds.
I mean, that thing's also from the 50s.
You can't tell me that we haven't discovered something.
Did technology just stop there in travel?
Hmm.
These are the things I think about.
But after the gray goose, I really don't
lay awake thinking about it.
All we want is that it's ready.
Today, my fellow Czechoslovans.
All we've got is that we are part of a second Sunday
for Raymond Hachdord.
Africa Airlines Flight 8771 took off from Johannesburg Airport
on Tuesday night.
The Airbus A330 had 104 souls on board.
Around 6am local time, as the plane approached the triple
international airport in Libya, disaster struck.
I wasn't intended to make a dot episode every week, but it seems
the incidents that affect the nettle ends is increasing.
Maybe you can imagine I'm a little band-out.
Today's after the accident in Libya, it's still not clear what caused
the crash of the airplane in the north of Africa.
Local authorities said that no direct attack was called, and a technical fault
unlikely.
Despite of the hasty statement of the Libyan authorities immediately after
the disaster, that it certainly was not an act of terror, experts are not so
certain about that.
Apparently the jet crashed about 400 meters from the nearest public road to
the crash night that was some distance, and it was inside the secure perimeter
of the airport, which explains why there were no ground injuries.
According to aviation experts, can and shoot a terrorist attack on the Airbus
certainly not be excluded.
By the way, there also was no sign of volcanic ash in the air.
A nine-year-old boy who is a Dutch citizen is the sole survivor of the deadly plane crash.
The child identified as Rubin from Asso suffered multiple fractures in his lower limbs,
and on the wind and operation at the Elkadra Hospital in Tripoli.
The miracle boy is central to the worldwide coverage of this disaster that killed 92 passengers,
and 11 crew members.
Many foreign media reported extensively about the miracle that the boy managed to survive the crash.
The Airbus jet carrying 104 people is crashed.
It was trying to land a Tripoli international airport as pretty close to the city.
Experts say that they are not allowed to enter the world.
There are a lot of people who are not allowed to enter the world.
Though an 1-year-old passenger, a nine-year-old young,
he believed to be a fan.
According to the Dutch government, he was heard to cry Holland, Holland, several times.
Now, Dutch authorities, from the embassy of Tripoli, have seen the child,
and the hospital in Tripoli has confirmed to CNN that he isn't in 80-year-old Dutch citizen.
His name is Rubin Ben Assoom.
The delegation which includes politicians and the Air Actives investigators has flown to Tripoli.
Here in Tilburg, in the south of the Netherlands, this street is building behind me.
This was the home of Rubin Ben Assoom.
Rubin's aunt and uncle have arrived in Tripoli and have been to see him in hospital.
When he does eventually go home to Holland, it will be without the people who were closest to him.
His survival may be a miracle, but it is one overshadowed by grief.
The death toll around his accident is 103, including 70 people from the Netherlands.
A total Dutch family of five people cut and wore to ferry last minute before the plane took off.
It's just one of the sad stories.
So you probably can imagine this bonding thing in the Netherlands is not over yet.
Many Dutch cities are plunged into moring.
His nine-year-old Rubin lost his parents and brother on a plane crash.
He's such a young boy with already such a heavy load on his shoulders.
So that's helpful now, my fellow chocolates, take care and enjoy the weekends in the morning to you.
Yeah, Raymond, well, thanks for blowing me out.
Yeah, that whole story is pretty weird.
I'm not quite sure what's going on with it.
No one's talking about the cause of the crash, which apparently the aircraft was relatively new.
It was an airbus now, of course we know that there's a war going on between Boeing and airbus, but still it happened in Tripoli,
which is another interesting data point to think about.
The skies were clear, apparently there was no weather, but no one's talking about the cause of the crash.
It's all about the miracle boy, which I find strange, but I haven't really been able to find anything to,
you know, anything at all really.
There's a couple of things coming in on email, just want to check.
What is this?
The commencement of the University of North Dakota, where, who are Secretary of Homeland Security
will be speaking there?
I don't, okay.
Watch the live video.
Janet de Palatano and North Dakota, what's she doing there?
All right, so that's not working.
What else do I have here on email?
Gotta, oh, adult Madonna, the band erotic aversion.
Apparently worth playing on the daily source code.
Well, let's just have a listen for a second here.
Hold on, this is coming in from the web, so it could suck.
I'll be watching the video, and you guys listen.
Ooh, all right, nice.
Oh, this is pretty hot.
I'll have to put this link into the show notes.
No, let's be honest.
Yeah.
Of course, why would it work?
All right, interesting experiment.
Let's get rid of that then.
Let's just end that.
Ah, this was by request.
Courtsmith, by the way, is on Twitter.
Okay, she hadn't seen him yet.
Oh, I'll do my best.
He is the headline.
Says you're pretty to choose.
The second piece of my new shoes.
I want to think that I'm trying to do.
Say it.
Someone in the Senate leaves off the wall.
Who is the first one?
Someone in the streets.
Someone in the streets, someone in the streets.
Something man in the nations.
Someone in the streets.
Somebody in the streets.
Something man in the streets.
Someone in the streets.
People in line.
Nobody Erfolg.
I listen.
I know, but according to my students,
The sins of love, the sins of love
The signs, the sins of love, the sins of love
The signs, the sins, the blood of peace
The sins, the sins of love
The signs, the sins of love
We'll take the money
Everymore
We'll pay the money
We'll save the money
Everymore
We'll pay the money
The sea is the sun, the sea is the moon
The sun is the sea is the moon
The sea is the sun
The sea is the sun, the sea is the moon
To be a state where we should go to the news of the primary and the left-chain,
the right-and-thousand-coust, and we'll give you the victory now,
I love us so much, remember me, who love you, smile as, love us Thank you so much,
We repeat the same thing to them
We sing the love of the stars we saw
And the seeds we love
And to me
The politics of me
We sing the love of the stars
They're out on tour apparently
I didn't know that
If they come through a Los Angeles
I will definitely go check them out
Love those guys
Cheers from fears
With their beat-alask
Sewing the seeds of love
They said cursemith these days
Big Twitter hound
Scrolling through the chat room
Mr. Oil has an interesting
Well, the theory I would say
But connection about the
The Polish plane that crashed
400 meters from the runway
As did the AAA plane
And yeah, I wouldn't mind seeing a passenger list
I totally agree
I think there's too much focus on the Dutch passengers
Who else was on the aircraft
Of course, really the question
Yeah, quick update on the iPhone app
I recompiled
Got a little bit of help
Thank you very much for the chucklehead to pitch in
Made some changes
Which I can undo remotely
By the way, once the app is in
But I need to get it past the Apple review team
I put it in Sunday
Almost a week ago
And it's still waiting for review
Which is a little disconcerting
It's never taken this long for to get into the review process
It's just waiting for review
So it's like, you know, just twiddling my thumbs
It's frustrating to say the least
But I hope once it does hit review
And maybe it'll happen on Monday
I don't think they do any reviews over the weekend
I hope that this coming week
It'll finally be released
Oh, wouldn't that be nice
So an appropriate song to play
Since I was denied
Refused
Might as well play refused
Didn't even know these guys existed
But I love this track
It's called new noise
And you can find it the iTunes store
How twist it is that?
Let's rock it on the Charlie
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no真的 won't take that good shit and I'll throw it away at that game right now so he
Come on, come on, come to your base
We're back to the ocean
Come on, come to your base
You'll see fire
Turn it up, turn it up, turn it up
Turn it up, turn it up
Come to your base
Bring your eyes on the sky
And you can increase your man
Bring your tongue to the cover of the actual
Look, look, look, look, look
We're back to the ocean
Come on, Come to your base
Hey!
Down!
Where's mine?
Rolls down!
It's a piece of work.
Hey!
It's a song like the noise.
Money, money, it's a piece of work.
And put the camp in the car.
I can feel the spirit better and more to listen.
Just because it's a single voice.
You're the noise.
You're on to the camp, you're on.
We've got loads of lessons.
We've got lots.
We've got……
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
what's in the place i do, delinquent and the, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, really great, yeah, yeah, kinda that into dress, yeah that's the cab as you always want being that in your rep or then on your backs
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, oh yeah yeah, I what you like, I know those咮 quick guys whatever is great like they all!
Let's get it, let's recover.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah now you better that club, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah I won't, so for that thing, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,' OK gonna go down to that halto though, the no light on you,
right, hey, hey, hey, hey, no light on me, that
I just been great though, I love the snap-o-side on the show.
This is actually another cowbell, but I'll let you imagine the sound of that.
Fins losing.
Boys, I've been back in town.
Guess who just got back today?
They're why I'm not boys that have been away.
Haven't changed yet much to say.
But man, I still think I'm catch a great.
They were asking if you were around.
How you was where you could be found.
Told them you were living down town.
Traveling all the old men crazy.
I was like a town.
You know that chick that used to dance a lot?
Every night you'd be all the floor shaking like you'd got.
Man, when I tell you she was cool, she was red hot.
I mean she was steaming.
And that time over at Johnny's place.
Well, this chick got up and she slept Johnny's face.
There we just fell about the place.
If that chick don't wanna know together.
The boys are back in town.
Boys are back in town.
I see.
I show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show you show show show you show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show Show show Show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show Show show show show show show show show show shows show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show show
Try the night they'll be dressed to kill
Down that dinner as far as we're out
The drink won't blow as blood will smell
And if the fire's one of fate you better let on
That you rocked in the gun, I've left it out my face
It's all for night to get longer, it won't be long
Won't be long, too, so my gun
Now that the fire's here again
The burning town won't blow as blood will smell
Oh, it's a bacon town
The burns are burned and the town
The burns are burned and the town won't blow as blood will smell
The burns are burnt and the town won't blow as blood will smell
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh yes, the boys are back in town, and I'm about to skip out of town.
At least I'll off the stream for a while and I'll blow the show of course.
You know the way the setup is now.
It's so easy to put your flip the switch, turn everything on.
I don't have to, you know, reboot the machine and set up all the virtual routing anymore.
I can pretty much go on the stream anytime I want.
And I just made wind up doing that.
I love it, and particularly with the feedback loop that we've got with the chat room at
noagendachat.com, it really makes a lot of fun.
So who knows, maybe I'll do another late night show.
As I started on the show off today, I said that I was spinning the tunes late at night
while completely hammered.
And I'm paying for it this morning.
Busy week coming up.
First of all, we have episode 200 tomorrow in the morning of the Noagenda show.
That'll be on the stream around 9 o'clock, get one nation west time.
And somewhere John and I are going to produce somehow the 200.5 show, which will be for
donors only.
I'm not quite sure when we're going to do it.
I'm scheduled to fly to San Francisco Monday and not coming back until Wednesday
night.
So I'll have to see how we do that or where we do it or when we do it.
Now of course tomorrow will be the first time where hopefully John will be of reasonable
quality as I now have a separate computer set up for Skype and I've got everything running
through the old school analog mixing board.
And it's going to be busy.
I got a board meeting on Tuesday, holy crap.
Anyway, what I did not hear anyone complain about is the sound.
So I guess the sound is good.
I guess everyone likes the way it sounds.
I'm sure I'll be receiving some feedback after the recording.
The podcast has released, which will be probably within the next hour.
Let me know if you think there's anything we should adjust.
And well, play one more song for you.
This is actually the kind of song where you want to get close into the microphone.
Breathe heavily.
This is Michael Franks, who has done some amazing songs.
This is one of my favorites.
It's when it's like alls.
When it's like a cause, the Prophet speaks with slight cause.
The secret leaks, the sky falls.
The day has stopped.
The war is won.
The battle is lost.
When slight cause, it's 13 takes.
When slight cause, the summer breaks.
The sky falls.
The rain begins.
And on the box, some beyond swims.
To instantly meet me from the icy after the shark.
I feel each time that's like home.
When you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when
you know that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, whenever you hear the sound, when you hear a sound, you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear what that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, and when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hearing that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, you hear that, when you hear that, how you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that,
Gloy, teeth on her arm
Man, the test is found
Man, the test was found
Let's dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance
dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance
dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance
tomorrow for the early morning service of No Agenda in the morning, until then, live your life with passion, and as as long as it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medial presentation, stick it in your ear.