Delta Sierra Charlie eight four zero.
With 16 minutes to 7 minutes,
ensuring five lines of time.
Turn.
The 25th century of radio starts here.
We are being lost.
Keep increasing in the alive.
I know a gender strip.
I'm fantastic.
Here's Adam Curry.
Hey, hello to my little friend.
Adam Curry, another baby source quote.
That's right, everybody.
It is officially quick and time.
It's the deadliest source quote you've ever tried.
It is the end of the month.
It's quick and time.
If they do you, I saw you again.
Today, I have to turn my heart away.
Smile like this, son.
Jesus will raise you.
If Jesus never leaves.
If you lie, smile like this.
I feel like you're not involved in it.
You can't be helped.
You can't live like this.
It's no good job.
Barocker.
Let's go to time, we will come all the way up to you
You've never fought with me, yeah
All right, you're the right, no wrong
Serious souls can be
Whisk the game
And if you're real, then don't do it to it
You better leave up something to me
You better go to time, we'll come all the way
Ooh, barracuda
Serious souls, you're the right, no wrong
Serious souls can be my new
I think they're doing their best too
All right, you're the right, no wrong
Serious souls can be my new
Serious souls
Real souls don't do it to it
You better leave up something to me
You better go to time, we'll come all the way
Ooh, barracuda
Serious souls can be my new
I gotta tell you, there's nothing like banging the Wilson sisters out on a Friday afternoon
Barracuda kicking off the resource code episode 840
is the Fubar Friday edition of the Charlie, everybody's on the box.
Your radio's a restarted.
We sent out the bat signal on the pocket no agenda.
We're live on the stream at noagendastream.com.
Of course, the party as usual is taking place at noagendachat.com.
If you have a chance drop on bites, we'll always get into a lot of trouble eventually.
And thank you so much for the submissions.
The list is lengthy today.
Not quite sure if I can make it into three hours because, well, I'll tell you later, I'm busy
boy getting ready to get the hell out of the country.
This is Stores.
It's a roll on a Friday.
Get the shelter bagin'.
Shut down.
Plan that.
With the Charlie.
Eight.
Four.
Zero.
One go on up.
Four.
Sit down.
Love.
Land Keep.
Five go on up.
Fifa's.
Four.
Five.
Fifa's.
He's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he
he's got a shadow, he's got an shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow, he's got a shadow
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, right now, right now yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
When I know it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need
it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need it, when I need all that.
Bring him back the honor video, bring it to your smartphone, your iPhone, your Android phone, your Blackberry, your stream and internet radios.
Lay the tune just for you.
I am hyped up today, I'm so happy.
I got my caffeine, got my nicotine, got my aspirin, I'm ready to blow your mind.
You're right, hips, easy to live in.
This is a thing I've never known before, it's called Easy Living.
This is a place I've never seen before, and I've been forgiven.
Easy Living, and I've been forgiven since you've tried the last place in my heart.
This is a thing I've never seen before, it's called Easy Living.
So disown yourself face.
This is a weird thing I've never seen before, it's called Easy Living, and I've been forgiven since you've tried the last place in my heart.
This is a thing I've never seen before, it's called Easy Living.
It's called Easy Living.
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be
let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let' be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be,
Well, the New Orleans order is structurally brings down the entire economy,
screws us to high hell of heaven and back again, as long as we can keep the Wi-Fi up and
operating, we've got easy living, you're right, he's on the Charlie episode,
a 40-foot-year-old football Friday, coming to you from the hilltop watch tower
crackpot command sends in the People's Republic of Southern California in the morning to
y'all, taking it down to get my nation lowlands, again most of this by request just
sent in an email, you guys know what I want to play, that's for sure, so now we're on the
same frequency, like this one from the hearing.
Hey, I big time the fear's like me, they're shaking, it doesn't matter,
I say it's falling, I hear a shout, maybe it's raining, that's too fast,
shadows dance, I am the morning, you're not gonna blow away I'm the feeling of
the gain, the love, the love
I'm not A love, you scream, you're not When the solace of one beats off the floor,
For another shot, we got the feeling and a feeling of pride
When the lady smiles, she holds me in her hand
That's a matter of fact, she could always let me down
The lady smiles, I can't resist her cold
As a matter of fact, I don't exist at all
As a matter of fact, she is leaving away
My friends tell me, she used to be still so much a pair of dice
I guess you've heard it all before
Before an angel, that has got to hear my size
I'm not always need some more
And I'm not in
Yeah, I love it
She's not nothing to me, it's me
It's every time we meet the girl, this shaking
It doesn't matter of course, it's falling
I hear a shadow, maybe it's raining
That's your faster, she'll go dancing
Together we're alive
My better lover came out of love
Oh, I
My better lover is gonna come out
When the balls know how much I've got
But I'm in a feeling of pride
When the lady smiles, she holds me in her hand
When I'm in a battle of fact, she could always let me down
I can't resist her job
As a matter of fact, I don't resist at all
She's been a better lover, she holds me in
Yeah, I love it
My better lover is gonna come out of love
When the lady smiles, she holds me in her hand
Soft Load
When the lady smiles, she gives meantes
meer
Brien
What's wrong with me?
smiles. I got some pretty exciting news. I want to talk about today, which we will get to obviously
last week, progress through today's Charlie episode 8-4-0 and a whole crap lot of awesome
tunes that you sent in, which I can't wait to play. I'm going to be talking about some
latest developments right here on the Charlie.
I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be
talking about some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about some of the
things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing,
and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about
some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing,
about some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing,
and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about
some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing,
and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing, and I'm going to be talking about some of the things that I've been doing,
J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J
J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J
J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J-J, K
I don't want to see, I don't want to see
You're the right, I don't think we were all
You're the right, I don't want to see you
Oh man, where's those guys, fuck up?
Damn, front the roses, you just don't hear that shit
I don't know anyone anymore, this is nuts
Paradise City, G&R, on the Charlie
The wilder's of the airways is landed, and he's sounding good to me
This is the Daily Source Code, with Adam Curry
Don't call it a comeback, I've been here for years
I'm rockin' my feet, what's up with the fear?
Raking the tears, rain down like a blind soul
Let's until a beast go boom, it's bulging
Overpowering, over the competition, outpowering, wreckage down
And when I try these lyrics that I make you call the cops
Don't you dare stare, you better move
Don't ever come here, be till the rest that I all get sliced in dice
Competence is taken over the points, hunger to Jack you out
I'm gonna knock you out, want to say knock you out
I'm gonna knock you out, let him speak, knock you out
I'm gonna knock you out, Mun device knocked you out
Don't you call it a day shackle, I'm gonna rip this land
I'm gonna take this city, baby world, my sole
Just get warm, just like my mom and I think
Call some kisses, watch me fast, just read like a skull
That's what I hate being with, why do you risk with me?
The man he acts like gold, and when I pull out my game again
Then they got their mind, don't blouse
Can you like me now, the rainbow will not allow
I'm blasting, I'm blasting, kind of like shit
So you can say I'm tapped in, oh English to my mind
And I came up with a monkey rhyme
I'm coming up with a monkey rhyme
Now I'm saying knock it down
I'm gonna knock it down
W Thu' Даty, knock it down
Yo am, now knock it down
TIME TO Say knock it down
I'm gonna knock you down
Now I'm saying knock you down
Come on, I don't think you should hide
Come on I don't think you should hide
Yeah, it's for real, to make it I feel real, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh oh, oh, so great, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, constrained, I don't maradingHero I am so excited with it, ah-pa it, ah-pa-pa't-pa-pa-pa'pa'pa'pa'pa, ah-pa-pa'pa'pa tappll-pa
Man is in the parking area now.
Oh.
Man is in the parking area for the runs.
Man is up here.
Man is in the parking area already.
Man and Hillary happen to get theily records on
that the jackets that they threw up,-
Ass, you can't drive me for何 part of the design.
Oh!
"...facing the wetroy45, ready groundbreaking Smash Bros.]
Man is in the first corner running!
Two for the price of one here on the daily source code. I kind of like that. It was a little intense little twisted LL cool Jay and Dexy's midnight runners a DJ lobster dust mash up
Haven't played one of those in a long time happy to have him back in on the show. So I've been in a crazy mad out of control rush the past two weeks.
Yeah, I guess it's now officially what is it's the third week since we've been together my friends crap all on so sorry, but all that's going to change very soon.
First of all, I had the the pod daughter over for two weeks, which was great to have her here. Of course, when you have the kid in the house and she's got no wheels you function partially as
Show for banker chef, you know, all things in one, but oh man, it was so much fun to have her here. She's doing so well and particularly with her writing stuff, which I'm very excited about. But that of course preoccupied me then we went off to San Francisco. She wanted to see some of her friends up there up north and I went along of course to check in on the folks at the media office to see how things are going.
I've been busted my ass on the big app show in the next few weeks will be more news about that, but basically an episode every single day and you know what, it's a lot of work.
I was laughing people like, oh, you should do an episode of this, an episode of that. It's you know, I forget sometimes I make it look easy, but when you're doing it all yourself, I'm basically doing the work of four people, but in order to make it actually work, I've got to
be kind of small and slim right now. And so I had to pre-produce a whole bunch of stuff because Miss Mickey and I are leaving tomorrow for the Netherlands and Tiles.
I think it's a Dutch and Tiles or Netherlands and Tiles. I'm not sure.
Friend of mine from my past has built a house there and said, hey, once you guys come on down and stay for a little bit, you know, the house is built so that we won't even bump into each other.
So I'm looking very much, we're looking forward to that. So that means that there will not be a show next week, but upon my return, there might be more than a show a week.
And I will tell you all about it after this.
Got to get you into the right mood for the news, you know, a little bit of B3 Hammond with man for man.
Everybody is building ships and boats, some of the buildings, many boats, some of the top and down boats.
Everybody is in the space and we're going to land more. We're going to get to see everybody going to charge a show.
Come on without. Come on with it. You're not seen nothing like the mighty wind. Come on without. Come on with it.
You're not seen nothing like the mighty wind.
Let me do what I want to do, a lot much of a sweep.
Come on with it. You're not seen nothing like the mighty wind. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it.
You're not seen nothing like the mighty wind. Come on without. Come on with it. You're not seen nothing like the mighty wind.
Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it.
Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come
with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it.
Come on. with it. Come with it. Come with it. Come on with it. Come out with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on. Come with it. Come on with it. Come. With it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on. Come on with it. Come on. Let's do it. Let's do it. Come on. Let's do it. Come on, let's do it. Come along with it. Come on with it. Come with it. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on with it. Come with it. Come on with it. Come on with it. Come on. Ready. Come with it. Come on with it. Come with it. Take a car. Come on. Come on. Come with it.
Let me do what I want to do, like my sugar sweet, but you're meant to use a makin' taste,
ain't my company, nobody can get no sleep, so I want to let the ones go, but we need to move it to everybody gonna wanna do,
come on without, come on with it, you're not seeing nothing like the mighty man, come on without,
come on with it, you're not seeing nothing like the mighty man, come on without,
come on with it, you're not seeing nothing like the mighty man, come on with it,
welcome home, welcome home, hahaha, ah, they're my exercise for today, Matt Romands Earthzban,
the mighty queen, of course, about queen the Eschimo, so you know that for the past two and
a half years John and I have been new in No agenda, no agenda show dot com and of course that is expanded entre
quite an amazing project and we believe that we can actually do that well, I don't know full time
we have other interests, but we can certainly devote more time to it. My main problem has
been for the past five years, I've been President of Mio. And I'm about to perform an
aerobatic trick in the business world that is known as the Slow Exit, which essentially
means I stay connected to the company as a, what do you call it, Consultant? And I actually
will, and I do consult with the company, but I will have no more managerial duties or really
much to do with the company other than shepherding it where I can and of course promoting it
where I can. That does have some consequences. The main one is I'll stop receiving a salary.
Of course, that money is better purpose or repurposed towards someone who actually can
help and participate and my partner Ron Bloom will be assuming the duties that I had and he'll
be bringing in some other people to take care of that so that I can focus on three main things,
which is of course this program, Daily Source Code, which of course is no agenda and the big
app show, but I'm going to have to hustle. That's for sure. Unless I get lucky and sell the aircraft,
it's going to get tied after a while. So I'll be counting on your support. Primarily the
the main thing you can do is help promote no agenda, get more people to listen, more people to support
the show, as well as the big app show. That's really the main things. And of course the other
consequence that it has is I'm free. Yes, I'm completely a free man to do what I want. I love it.
The feeling is astounding, amazing. I'd recommend it highly with everybody. It's kind of scary.
Fuck, that's part of the joy. And I noticed Marcus Couch sent in the perfect song to celebrate
atomic time to rain and free. I couldn't put with that a page, nothing other on the wall.
Right, the cup of tires games we play, I'm not afraid to get on and on.
Right, and every corset had to pay the time and not to freedom.
Oh...
Right...
Nothing more they'll have a day but they'll depend on our blood, we step from inside
I'm not afraid
I'm not aware of stuff to me
I'm not afraid to let you know
I'm not afraid
I'm not who I used to make
I'm not afraid to let you know
My understanding, behind theに
I take a breath
It's been really hard to let sing old
And I will teach you a tune
No back on the inside
But not free
But now it's supposed to make
But not free to let you own
But not me
If you made
But not free to let you own
But not free, but you own
Back home inside
Try it out
I'm going to let's miss
Look, try to save me
I'll be a better night
Just to let it go
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Chatroom, of course, buzzing with questions
Happy to answer them
But it's pretty simple
It's not that crazy
Founding partners do this
From time to time
I've probably two years past my due date
And the amazing thing, you know, when you
When you, while they say proverbially
When you close a door
Another one opens
Oh my god
So many things have happened
And just the past week alone
So many exciting things
No change in my pocket yet
But I hooked up with the director extraordinaire
He like Rob
He's actually got a movie coming out
The end of August
And we're working on a project
Which I think will blow your socks off
I'm very excited about that
Just tons of stuff
All potential of course
You make your own luck
And luck has always thought of the intersection
Between preparation
An opportunity
And that's where I plan to be
Sweet berries ready for your ghosts
You're not different than you
Ghosts are now waiting for you
Are you dreaming
Dreaming in the night
Dreaming all right
You're waiting for me
When we fly
When we go
Do we fly
So many berries ready for your ghosts
No different than you
Ghosts are now waiting for you
Are you
Sweet berries ready for your ghosts
No different than you
Ghosts are now waiting for you
Are you dreaming
Dreaming in the night
Dreaming all right
You're waiting for me
When we fly
When we go
Do we fly
So many berries ready for your ghosts
No different than you
Ghosts are now waiting for you
Are you dreaming in the night
Dreaming in the night
Number of listening to is 840 live at nogenoustreme.com and of course on the podcast of
dailysourcecode.com, fun to see the chat room coming up with all kinds of business
I can use for all of these.
Whoa, yeah, but it's okay.
I've got three businesses already, you know, and the big app show is a real business.
What I need there is I need 10 times the amount of viewers, I got about 150,000 now integrating
I adds into that soon, but I just need more people, I make blog posts, send me the URL,
I need to get some viral love going there, that's really what'll make that happen because
people who have the app absolutely adore it, just needs more exposure, and I'll be working
on that as well, more news after we play some guest here, when the band was singing,
she could snorkeling, snorkeling, and I tried to do the dailysourcecode, she smiled while we were
scrolling, and I knew that I was rolling, and I told her I'd be bored of the new.
It's not the magic, it's not the music, it's not the moonlight, I don't know where I'd love
like this before, about 10 years time ago, when the band was singing, shaking all over
up, when the band was singing, shaking all over
up, and I'll make people choose illusion, we did the one, two, three, and I'll rock and bear a boost
way too, once you don't know, I won't hurt her even though I might disobey her, got to tell
my best body the new, it's not the magic, it's not the music, it's not the moonlight, I don't know
where I'd be gone, it's not the magic, it's not the time before, about 10 years ago,
when the band was singing, shaking all over, when the band was singing, shaking all over
up, it's not the music, it's not the moonlight, I don't know where I'd be gone, it's not the moonlight, I don't know
how I'd be gone, like this before, about 10 years time ago, when the band was singing, shaking all over
up, when the band was singing, shaking all over, when the band was singing, shaking all over,
I'm out there plugging the crap out of the big app show, you can do the same by linking to
bigappshow.com for the iPhone challenge, it might even persuade you to get an iPhone, I've actually
started working on a Android version of it, which has been an interesting little challenge,
man, when you just feel the Android, using a droid for development, it just feels a little
wonky, it really is the difference between a PC and a Mac, but now there you go, what can you
do? So one of the things I'm doing was actually I got helped out by one of our
no agenda listeners, I don't know if she's in the chat room, sit us an X, and she actually
sent in an audio comment to tell you all about what's going on. Hello, Anna, my name is Barbara,
Barbara, I'm probably known me better as a citizen X, and I wanted to say thank you for
committing to do the interview with Carrie Holsman, I'm really looking forward to it, it's going
to be a great opportunity for you, it's a live chat, but also a Colin Show. So I'm trying to promote
the show so that your fans can actually Colin and perhaps talk to you, I think that's going
to be a great opportunity for them, but also I know how busy you are, I know you could have
said no, but I just wanted to say thank you, personally thank you for saying yes, and for appearing
at Computer America on the 30th, looking forward to it, can't wait, I would like to say in the
morning, but in this instance it's in the evening. Yeah, I love you, mean it. See you soon. Okay,
sit us next there, I don't know why you're thanking me, I'm thanking you for hooking me up, it's great,
it's a thing is a national radio show, it's on a lot of AM stations around the country that starts
at 7 o'clock this evening, Pacific Standard Time, and I'm actually contemplating streaming my
end of it live, which would be kind of fun. So that is tonight, I check your local listings,
I guess, to find out where it's on. And thank you very much, Barbara, for hooking me up with that
opportunity, I really love it. To me, it's like, hey, get the work out. Oh god, damn, it's just funky.
It's really rocks my boat, boss gags, chill out, I'm Friday afternoon with my friends and no
agenda chat.com, so we stream out to the new radios around the world, bring it back to the
arc of the radio, so load down on the charming.
Good to say, it's a treat, you've done it all down.
Nothing you can't handle, nothing you ain't got. Put your money on the table, drive it up and
up. Turn on that old love life, turn to make it do you have the same old school bargain, got you
when it is fair. But get on back and down, raise your saddle, turn it all down.
Come back and listen.
Look, don't yell, don't yell,
You ain't got to be so bad, got to be so cold
This doggy dog is just a show that I get no
Got to have a joke with this, just for that
But this runger with the dumplings raw just ain't where it's at
You're gonna come back around to say it's at you
You're telling all the damn
Got you thinking like that boy
Got to have a joke with this, just for that
You're gonna come back around to say it's at you
And that's it, just for that
I don't want to want to go
Got you, baby
Let it go, baby
And share it with me
I don't want to want to go
I don't want to go
I think California kid and the chat room
I know it's in the chat.com nailed it
This is totally top down, cruising around
Your Lincoln Continental
A Hollywood Boulevard
With a low down
Nice
Yeah, I got to find me a cheapest car
car too.
That's scary shit, man.
He's like, all right, I'll drop my responsibility, drop the paycheck.
Of course, I've got the Delta Shara as like some meager form of insurance policy, back
and everything up.
Can always sell it for 50 grand.
I know I can find a microphone for that, but that would be a, I would be kind of a shame
wouldn't it.
No worries.
Going to be the race to poverty and starvation, or can we make something out of these
lemons, eh?
I see nothing but upside, that's for sure.
By request, came in a couple of times through email in the chat room, Lighthouse,
one five fine morning on the Charming.
One five morning girl, I'll wake up, watch it from my eyes, what's on it, feel a sunshine,
then I know I'll be your lies, where there's long as you love me go far.
You're on that moment when I wake up, see a face inside a cloud, see a smile inside a window,
here your voices out of crowd calling come with me baby and the fly.
Yeah, the fly, yeah, the fly, yeah, the fly.
And on that morning when I wake up, we'll go outside and live our dreams, but by can we stay to start us,
when little dogs are stuffed in the wind, and everywhere they go, we'll laugh and sing, but this is morning good night,
and all the universe was smart on us, because they know that I love this fact right.
Yeah, the fly, yeah, the fly, yeah, the fly.
And on that morning when I wake up, we'll go outside and live our dreams, but by can we stay to start us,
Oh, yeah, we'll fly to the north, we'll fly to the shore
If you wear it, we'll become our home
Oh, yeah, we'll do it way more
Here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly
Here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, yeah we fly, here we fly, here the fly, here we fly, here, we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here's we fly, here we fly, here we fly, there we fly, here we fly, there we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here, fly, here we fly, there we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here, we fly, here we fly, here we fly, there you fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, now you fly, there you fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, there we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we fly, here we
I'm just leaving, I'm amazing.
You've been with me at the castle, at the cottage.
You've been with me through the passing of my mom,
through a divorce, a new life.
It's great.
And I'm amazed at how many of you are actually friends
that I know a lot about as well.
It's nice.
I can love that.
Particularly when I look outside,
when I see the sun shining in Southern California,
they can do myself, hey, you know what?
The government doesn't know in the sun.
Yet, here's a guy who started off pot safe
and is doing okay for himself.
It's now an iTunes.
I love this track, Bob Gendry, upside down on 840.
Now, I've been talking in my ass lately
when I'm waking, well, my tongue is tight.
I've been thinking I should leave,
instead of waiting for her when the time is right.
I've backed the bags under my eyes,
well, I've seen enough to know what it's like.
It's turning me up.
I've turned me up.
I've turned me white again.
I'm done wrong now.
I've been walking in my sleep when I'm waking up
Well, my legs are tight
I've been thinking I should breathe, put the window up
It's a marathon
I've been dreaming I could fly it
Well, I'm free enough, but I'm still way down
It's turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking at the inside out
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just stick around
I was able to hide every bruised on my body too now
Until now
I've been afraid to just walk out
And you know where to stop me now
It's turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking at the inside out
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
When everything's breaking me down
Looking at the inside out
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just stick around
I was able to hide every bruised on my body too now
Until now
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When those rules got changed somehow
I was able to hide every bruised on my body too
I was able to hide every bruised on my body
Until now
Upside down
Bob Gentry on the Charlie
By the way, if you go to know agenda
Entertainment.com
That's where you can find the playlist
With associated links to iTunes
For all the songs played on the show
And of course, you can just sound hounded
Or shazam that shit that always seems to work
And for one hit to another
You know, remember when you heard this song
All the time on the radio
And that of course, it just went away
Because the guy's name is Bruce Hornsby
And that Bruce Hornsby JC
It's kind of the way the music business works these days
Luckily, we've got radios in our pockets now
With our smartphones
Turn up your speakers
For the way it is
Still in line, looking time waiting for all of their day
Stay kept by our job
Man, it's so surreal
He's biased, he keeps falling ladies eyes
Just for funny sets
Get a job
That's just the way it is
Some things I've never seen
How but don't you believe that
Say it in my, you can't go without this cold
You don't look like they do
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that way
That you really think about it
Before you make a move
Just a stitch
Let's just the way it is
Some things I've never seen
How but don't you believe that
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that way
That you really think about it
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that you really think about it
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that they really think about it
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that way
That you really think about it
Say, hell man, how can you standin that way
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that way
If I really think about it
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that they really think about it
Say, hell man, how can you stand the thing that we really think about it
Super talented guy and just incredibly nice.
I've actually mismicked it to me a total solid.
She's having all of my old pictures framed and she had them all scanned in and actually put
up two pictures of on my flicker account the other day.
One with me and Rundian C and the Leastie boys and me with Tina Turner and a lot more
to come.
I think I've got some Bruce Hornsby pictures somewhere, so I actually find them.
It's interesting when you announce something like this, like my aerobatic move, the
soft exit.
All of a sudden, all the songs in the world just sound so relevant.
Like, oh yeah, that one kind of fits the mood too, doesn't it?
Oh this is crazy!
My last one, Jeopardy!
Is it ready?
You can not be found, what can I do?
What I believe in you, you're running me around
You can change it as I want it
I'm taking any way you like
It's a slayer, not the funer
You never know what it's gonna start
I love you, Jeffery
Baby
Don't get you
Don't get fun enough
It's way that then you think
Or it's the use
I'll save your mind now
It's hanging on the bed
Don't let go
While I'm hanging on
Cos I did, I'm hanging on too long
It's so hard to keep all alone
I know you're not that strong
Yeah, yeah
I love you, Jeffery
Baby
Don't let go
Want I'll pay And I'll go softer
Pay And I'll be strong
It's summer, to be more low
I know you knocked that strump
Yeah, yeah, Oh the cigarettes
Name it
Ooo woo woo woo woo
hello certificate
Name it
Baby, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I
love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love
I'm just an average man with an average life
I'm from nine to five
Hey, hell, I paid the price
I want you to be left alone
In my average home
But why do I always feel
I get mad in the twilight soon
And I always feel like
Somebody's watching me
And I love your price
And I go, I always feel like
Somebody's watching me
Tell me, is it just a dream?
When I'm a criminal
I've been through a real time
People call me on the phone
Trying to avoid me
Look at the people who don't really see me
When I'm a criminal
When I'm in the shower
I'm afraid to watch my hair
Because I'm out of a mind
And there's someone standing there
People say I'm crazy
Just a little touch
But maybe I wouldn't mind me
I'll fight for you
But that's why
I always feel like
Somebody's watching me
And I love your price
And I go, I always feel like
Somebody's watching me
Who's playing tricks only
Whatever
Anything
You can imagine
And I don't feel safe
And I don't know what I'm up
And I wonder who's watching me now
The ARL
I love this feel
Somebody's watching me
And I look no better, oh I always be loving somebody's one to me
Tell me you're just a dream boy
I always be loving somebody's one to me
And I look no better, oh I always be loving somebody's one to me
And I look no better, oh I always be loved
We might stay
I gotta spit out
So I just want to meet
Get out of my privacy
I gotta spit out
So I just want to meet
I just want to meet
I gotta see a light
So I just want to meet
Oh
I gotta see light
So I just want to meet
Rockwell
Michael Jackson back in it up
Somebody's watching me on the Charlie
Interesting conversation going on in the
The chat room
So funny
Comics are bloggers in there
Trying to calculate how much time
It takes to do the big app show
Oh yeah
So there are three minutes each
So by the way
It's not five a week
It's seven a week
Yeah that's 21 minutes
Yeah that's how long it takes
Yeah that's right
There's nothing else involved
No editing
No setup
Ha ha ha
Shmuck
I don't agree
I'm a real good
And it was coming through my heart
And it was coming there was looking there was candy
Orange long dog glasses with wine up to a yard
And somebody grabbed it through me out of my chair
So before you could eat you got a dance like Fred or the star
You know I can dance, you know I can dance
I am a man of the road, a hobo
By name I don't seek entertainment
But if it's all the same to you then yes I will try my hand
If you raise hungry at me that I show you when I'm the star
I'll wait a minute
Yeah
Of course I can dance, of course I can dance
I'm sure I can dance, I'm sure I can dance
I'm a dance, I really hit the floor
I feel good, I'm a dance
I did a two-step quicks that manner
I'm the popper to the bass wall
Excuse me, Mike
It's a left-g står
I married down my taxi-do
Next week I come and back for mobile
I had a chance
Or I am także
Lord and my dance in the floor
I need to stand as what I need, stand for the cowbell, a little clip there for when
I'm smoking, and then it would be just perfect, I've almost got everything I need here
in the Hilltop Watchtower's crackpot command studios, took for the naked chicks in the hot tub,
got I hate being alone on a Friday, when I think about you, think about love, I don't live without you and your love,
if I had those golden drains of my yesterday, I would have left you in the heaven, but feel it, I am in on the way, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it,
feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel
feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it
feeling it, feel it, feel it, Feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it
Do I make it look like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it
It's like it's like that's like it's like it'll make a porcelain and it's like you're sorry.
I love this type.
Oh man, I wish I could participate in an alcoholic beverage right now, but I still
got a computer America coming up in about four hours from now, so I'll have to keep
me.
You know, me, I'm such a lightweight, a roll over immediately.
Now, bad company.
Going through the archives of stuff I have tagged for the Charlie.
Oh, by the way, a programming note for those of you who didn't know already, no agenda
2, 2, 2 will be broadcast tomorrow, tomorrow morning at 9 a.m. in the morning, seeing
his miss Mickey and I leave Saturday afternoon, and we have an extra what John would call
an evergreen show lined up for Thursday.
Should I not be able to connect with him from the Netherlands and Tiles, but I'm thinking
it'll work out.
I mean, internet is pretty much everywhere these days, so I shouldn't be too much for
problem.
So anyway, going through the archives, I find a ray on the chart, which we have not shared yet,
so let's roll out Ray.
Hey, this week, the was the release of an English magazine, Inspire, which is something
like a club magazine for terrorists, made by an al-Qaeda big week from Yemen, and
our al-Avlaki.
The magazine focus on radical Muslims in Europe and North America, and it includes a manual
for making bombs at home.
On the magazine's hit list, art, the names of the Danish cartoonist, Kurt Vestigart,
author Salman Rushdie, Ayyan Hirshi Ali, and the Dutch politician, Kurt Wilders.
Kurt Wilders is the frontman of the Dutch Freedom Party, and was the big winner of the Dutch
Military Elections held on June 9, 2010.
He's threatened with debt by al-Qaeda after he announced his new big plans for the Western
Modern World on Thursday.
This week he announced that he's building an international umbrella organization for
organizations and individuals, as the PVV, fight for freedom and against Islam.
He strives to present the so-called international freedom aliens at the end of this year,
together with sympathizers in the United States, Canada, United Kingdom, Germany, and
France.
Builders says that he's working with prominent persons on the Eva, but does not name names.
The intention is that, at the end of this year, a presentation of the Eva website is launched.
In the meantime, the Spanish government has expressed the Moroccan authorities its concern
about the release of Christians from the North African country.
Since March this year, Morocco expelled 130 Christians for alleged conversion drive.
The newspaper L.I.E. reported that the Spanish ambassador has asked the Morocco Rabbit government
for a clarification.
Spain wants Morocco to respect the international obligations in the area for religious freedom.
Also seven people from the Netherlands who gave shelter to orphans in Morocco are deported
because they sometimes read from the Bible that told children about Jesus.
Looking about freedom of religion, I got to call my friends from the Y.
You know, the worldwide movement of more than 45 million members from under 24 federations
affiliated through the world aliens of Y.M.C.A.S.
Otherwise, the dust will never settle down.
I really need some positive vibe now on the Charlie.
The soundtrack to my life.
Maybe something like, ah, a good soundtrack from your life.
I.M.C.A. is a song by the village people, which became a hit in 1979.
The song reached number one on the U.S. charge and reached number one in the UK around
the same time, becoming the group's biggest hit ever.
Taken at Vage Value, its lyrics extols the rituals of the young man's Christian association.
Gonna wish y'all a very nice weekend.
Bye bye now.
I.M.C.A.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S
S.S.S.
S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.
S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.
S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.
S.S.S.S.S.S.S.
S.S.S.
S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S
S S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.N.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S...S-S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S...S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S. type.S.S.S.S.S.S.
That old analogue, nothing sounds quite like it doesn't.
Listen to it.
Oh yeah.
You never heard that part on the radio.
That's for sure.
Rod Stewart handbags in the glad rags.
Sound the daily source code.
And let me bring in a little bit of slapback bass from herby flowers.
Who's that?
He plays along with Lou Reed on walk on the wild side.
Hi.
Hollywood came from Miami at Bill A.
Hitchhack to way across USA.
Pluster eyebrows on the way, shaved her legs and then he was as she should says he'd be.
Take a walk on the wild side.
Said, hey honey, take a walk on the wild side.
Candy came from out on the island.
In the back room she was everybody's darling.
But she never lost her head,
even when she was given head, she says hey babe.
Take a walk on the wild side.
Said hey babe, take a walk on the wild side.
And the colored girls go, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, thingy a wirklich.
Little Joe, never once gave it away.
Everybody had to pay and pay.
A hustle here and a hustle there.
New York City is the place where they said he'd be.
Take a walk on the wild side.
I said, hey, Joe, take a walk on the wild side.
Oh Lord, hey, Joe, just give me.
Look at the smoke.
It's all gone, it's all gone, I came in.
Take a walk on the wild side.
Baby, take a walk on the wild side, all right.
Huh.
Jackie is just speeding away.
Thought she was Jim Dean for a day.
Then I guess she had to crash.
All the young would have helped that fish that said he'd be.
Take a walk on the wild side.
Say hey honey.
Take a walk on the wild side and the color girls say.
Take a walk on the wild side.
Say hey honey.
I would be remiss if I did not mention to you that this program is listener supported.
And I appreciate it if you donate to the cause support the show.
No agenda.
You can go to no agenda show.com.
Daily source code.com.
Of course, devorac.org slash NA is where you can sign up for multiple ways to support.
The stream, the show, the show as well.
And tomorrow in the morning will be doing another no agenda show.
And I think that once I get back and into the swing of things after I take my cheap holiday.
And there's nothing cheaper than staying at a friend's house.
Let me tell you.
We'll be kicking it large.
And hopefully ratcheting up some of the episodes of the Charlie.
Although I have to say really all that pent up energy and bring it all into one day into one
Fubar Friday or sometimes the snafu Saturday really does work.
It's like a big release.
It's like one big money shot.
And boys, the money shot is just that.
Okay.
Time to turn up the speakers.
Teer axe, bang it, gong it at home.
Let's do it.
Get back to my bag.
I love you.
You do these feet down there.
But just in the week, you got the tune to the hydra for you.
You do these feet, you're my girl.
Get it all.
When you're feeling nothing cold, you're going to hurt.
Can't time it's going to heal.
She did do like a car out here.
We're going to hunt team with that cute little money girls.
Can't do these with your man girl.
Get it all.
We're here with you.
All, we got the blue shoes and the strawberry and it messes.
You've ruined the world out here.
We've got real black or collar.
We've got a hug him time to tell hate her.
Taking a dirty için to the molta.
Get your finger down, get your finger down, get your finger down, get your finger down, get your finger down, get your finger down
Now I wish I had it
We can do this, we can't stand on the back of the other door
If you do it, it's me and I'll be here
We can't dance with a walk, but it doesn't take a time to stand on the back of the other door
If you do it, it's me and your mind goes
Get your finger down, get your finger down, get your finger down, get your finger down
You
Littery sitting here laughing to myself
I've got this command line Twitter client
So the Twitter's just kind of scroll on by I must have
Follow this feed London erotic awhile ago
It came out with four tweets in a row
There we go. I really lovely girl ready for action in London 24
In your hotel alone call Paris for a great time
754-3-489-602
UK's most intimate and lovely female goddess Sandra Buena Vista
No to boo seriously hot posh Totti
Phone fuck 35 years old and live your dreams with me
I'm subscribed to the wrong feed apparently
I need to get the one for Los Angeles Southern California
This is no good
T-Rex on the Charlie bank and gone get it on as we roll our little bit of Bob O'Reilly
The who stuck in a teenage wasteland
Feels
A little mushy in here on this teenage wasteland
How about you
Crank it up
You'll need it
Make your ears bleed
Get out of the morning
I hear you in the field
I'll fall for my medium
I get my back here to hold out in the air
I don't need to fight
To prove my pride
I don't need to be focused on the other hand
Don't cry
Don't reach your eyes
It's all in today's wasteland
Be-be-be-be-be.
They're all wasted!
I always thought this is a weird part of the stuff.
The Hoopaparale on the resource code A4, zero of the Fubar Friday edition.
Nice to see that Bunk is announced.
That the Noagenda challenge coins have now raised over two and a half thousand dollars for the show, which is great.
Yay, we can eat moment love it.
Noagendafans.com as we can find out more.
And then one of those songs you never hear on the radio.
How about some queen live?
The audience participation on this song is phone-chilling.
Track from Live A has a murdered film for 20 years.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room with Radio Gaga.
And watch your cry-only friend.
To see that everything I've had to know, I heard on my radio.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room with those songs.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room with Radio Gaga.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room.
The radio clap-a-long on the chat room with Radio Gaga.
The radio clap-a-long performing in the chat room to get recorded.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room is just on the chat room with Radio Gaga.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room.
The radio clap-a-long in the chat room with Radio Gaga.
fashion things.
This of course is the new sound of radio.
I am Adam Curry, your daddy, or the radio.
And I think that we have let him suffer long enough.
Comic strip.
Come on in, CSB.
Hello, Adam Inception Curry.
Here is CSB, your CEO, correspondent.
Yes.
So, after long debate, CEO has finally decided what to do with genetically modified organisms,
fought and planned.
Go put it in the snacks.
It's good to taste each country.
We'll be able in CEO to decide whether they want to grow genetically modified stuff or not.
Right.
There will be no over all you love for that.
So, for example, lovers of genetically engineering, like Czech Republic and Spain, will be
extending the genetic ropes.
But haters of genetically engineering could modify the food, like Australia or Italy,
will be forbidding it.
But there's one tiny question.
What about the wings and animals that are carrying the genetically modified plants and seeds?
Yeah, they're tasty.
I think soon all food on this stupid planet called Earth will be genetically modified.
Whether you want it or not, it's a manifest destiny.
Sorry.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, what are you talking about CSB?
This has already happened.
There's nothing you eat that doesn't contain some genetically modified crap.
Yeah, it's nice, nice little tasty GM modified snacks courtesy of.
Yeah.
Back to lobster dices.
And the mash-up.
The blue me away when I heard it.
Stone Temple pilot versus Miley Cyrus on the Charlie.
You know I just stand.
Yeah, what it is.
That makes it take.
But you wish it did.
Yeah, always taking yes.
What a rip.
I say yes.
It just moves out every time.
It's the only do.
What?
I talked about when I was my friend just hanging out.
Maybe about the insides, too.
Oh, what to say?
What to do?
That way when you make the game, baby, you can never look.
So, we're such a pity that I don't know that.
I'm a pity real pity that I don't know that.
Oh, my flesh is a pity, yeah.
You know that I don't know that.
So, we're such a pity that I don't know that.
It was no.
It was a deal.
When I'm with my son.
Now we do.
Yeah, always taking yes.
Mother, it was never gotten going.
Yeah, it was a new year.
No, my now.
If you were my boy.
So, it's happy to meet you.
If I make the call.
Yeah, always taking yes.
So, we're such a pity that I don't know that.
We're such a pity that I don't know that.
Maybe about the insides, too.
So, we're such a pity real pity that I don't know that.
Oh, my flesh is a pity, yeah.
You know that I don't know that.
So, we're such a pity that I don't know that.
Oh, my now.
I'm a pity real pity that I don't know that.
Yeah, always taking yes.
You know that I don't know that.
Oh, my now.
What I say is,
It's come with a closer.
And what I can tell you is, don't you?
So, we're such a pity that I don't know that.
I'm a pity real pity that I don't know that.
Oh, my flesh is a pity, yeah.
You know that I don't know that.
So, we're such a pity that I don't know that.
The little girl you're in touch with.
We're going to come on with.
If you never let's say,
To watch your say, yes.
Yeah, it works for me.
Of course, we've got up to one guy to be able to make that kind of mess.
DJ Lops to does check Monday, DJ Lops to does.
God, come, Stone Temple Pilots of Miley Cyrus.
Yeah, that's like Batman and Robin.
Film and Louise, all built into one.
Be beautiful.
Oh, I was going to tell you about Big App Show.
I don't think I mentioned this,
but I've actually been working on something very cool.
A friend of mine who actually was my agent in Hollywood 20 years ago.
Super agent Lesher.
He, he's a big fan of the app.
Should we call me up tonight?
I got an idea.
He talks because I got an idea at him.
Is it a really good idea?
So, what's up, super agent?
He says, well, I think I can get all kinds of celebrities to promote their apps.
And they can do episodes for you.
Oh, yeah.
That's actually a pretty good idea.
Guess who's coming in.
After I get back from vacation to promote his app.
Oh, yes.
The man who some call God himself.
To present an episode of the Big App Show.
The one and only.
David Hasselhoff.
Oh, yes.
The app man will be the hoff.
I gotta tell you, I have been excited about things, but that kind of,
just takes the gamut.
Kind of close on the charting episode,
eight, four days to football Friday.
Mr. Jones.
He's done a new episode down.
He's done a this yellow hair rommet.
He just strikes on the competition.
We're black here.
We make our dance music.
He dances while his father plays.
So, she's starting beautiful.
And I want something beautiful.
I don't show beautiful.
So come here for some of his dancing tomorrow.
Shout-out-out-out-out-out-out-out-out-out-out-out-out.
One song there.
Cure with me up.
Show me some of his Spanish dance.
He has me a bottle.
Best of the Jones.
Because I want to be someone who believes
Yes, to show them me Tell each other
It's every chance I'll be standing in the room
It's just looking at you I'll know you should look at me
Smiling in the bright light
Come out through hysteria
And we're everybody in love you
You could never be lonely
While I'm awake in my picture
Bring myself through red black and red
All of the beautiful colors are very, very meaningful
Every now and then my favorite colors
I feel so symbolic yesterday
And my new Picasso
Now I'm by myself for a break
It's all I'm playing in this country
Look at you in the future
Now we're standing in the room
It's just looking at you
I'll know you should look at me
Smiling in the bright light
Come out through hysteria
And we're everybody in love me
I'll never be lonely
I'll never be alone
And everybody won't pass this count
I'll never be fit, fit stars, ever
We got different reasons for that
Leaving me
Because I'm so free, man, anything
And I just want to be someone
Jumping in, jumping in, jumping in
Yes, that you'll let me
I'm storming out for your body
Now it's just looking at you
I'll never be lonely
She's a fool of you
Man, it's got to be somebody
Me, I'll be by you
Mr. Joe Bush, he was someone
Just to let him off
He went in, everybody
Love you
I saw you
Just about what gives you
To me
Mr. Joe
Damn it
I knew I'd score a big with that news
About the half on the big app show
If you don't know what the big app show is
If you've got an iPhone or iPad
You can go to
Bigappshow.com or search for it in the app store
I might as well spill the beans
On a couple other silver tays
You're scheduled to appear in their own app
So any Duke, poker player, extraordinaire
And I think on the weekend of the 13th
One of the wrestlers of the WWE
Oh yeah, I don't mess around man
When I sit out to make the
The MTV of apps, I mean it
Now I've got to figure out how to make some money with it
Love a lot of fun at the meantime
My dad's boys, please be
From the brains going to the balls
You know what happens, don't you?
Ha ha ha
Me and the boys went out for a ride
Typical attitude
We are all tied
Come in and out on the 7th level
Oh, roll, roll, roll, roll
I see all the 747
Turn it up, turn it around
If you've got me, it's about my own
But it's just in my mind
Nothing can stop us, nothing at all
Find a try, the ball, roll
I see all the 9th level
Nothing can stop us, nothing at all
Find a try, the ball, roll
I see all the 9th level
You know, you're just another joke
I've got a ball, shout out to my Chris
I see all the 9th level
Ooh, ooh, ooh
I see all the 747
Turn it up, turn it around
You get the best thing out on the ground
You get the ball, roll
Nothing can stop us, nothing at all
Find a try, the ball, roll
I see all the 9th level
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait
Its always my dream
You're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too
loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud, you're too loud
No blood in the brain.
It's all about extender now, man.
Oh, yeah, full bar indeed.
Where's it going now?
Just bring it on hold.
In the morning.
Would she Mann, you won't let her see if you're done with you.
Breathe in and resist it out and fill out you made a concrete.
Okay, yeah.
Oh, low ether, and maybe here I'll see your little better.
Sleep it down a bit.
Good morning, also.
Think you guys are better, good morning.
This is a dream for me, too.
Ooh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, okay oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
the hustle and the bust, land and the crowd from Galaz.
Well then, I love you there, and see you here to enjoy being here by
all earths on his we know me, now a heroly
in the past where he owned Geekle, oh man, yeah, yeah, yeah of the
earths on his right, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah Yeah vibe like that song to it's like made, in gosh there's, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah oh yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah. yeah
Even though one's all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right,
all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all next, this
Well, jam, even flow off the trolley.
Perfect, who are funny too?
Oh, that would be fun.
That would be fun.
I'm sorry, you can tell me Adam and Curry are coming.
Get him in for the football we'll be doing in two weeks time.
I can't stay with you for the typical...
What?
I can't stay with you for the typical three hours that I'd like to do
because I just got some stuff to do before.
These seven-to-all computer-american shows.
Then they got a trap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, man.
About the house room, blue.
No.
Perfect for no agenda for tomorrow morning.
Come home one Friday.
Had a ton of land, lady, I'd have lost my job.
Oh, right.
It's George Sturgut.
Yeah.
She said that to come front me.
Long as I get my money next Friday.
It should get your blood boiling.
Now that it's Friday, come out and get the rent.
And I put the aura away.
Thank you, boss.
So I go through the lane, lady.
I think you'll let me slide.
I have to rent for it on my other next day.
I don't know.
So, so let me slide it on, you know, people.
I know it's what I come home in the evening.
She got nothing nice to say to me.
But for five years, she was so nice.
No, what you will love her, David.
I come home one particular evening.
The lady said you got the rent money yet.
I said, no.
Can't find no job.
They've only got no money to pay the rent.
She said that, I don't believe you're trying to find no job.
Said I knew today was standing on a corner.
They never get to post.
I said, but I'm tired.
I've been walking on day.
She said, that don't be fun, me.
Long as I get my money next Friday.
Now I try to come out and never rent.
And I put the aura away.
So I go down the streets.
And I'm a good friend, Stiles.
As I look, man.
I'm out of those, you know.
And I'll stay with you, maybe a couple days.
You said, oh, let me kill her as my wife.
To come out of the house, I can see this face.
I know it was no.
Said, I don't know, man.
She got a money, no.
I said, I know.
Everybody's funny.
Now you put it too.
So I go back home, man.
I'll tell the little lady.
I got a job.
I'm gonna pay the rent.
She said, yeah.
I said, oh yeah.
And then she was so nice.
So I go in my room, pack up my things and I go.
I'll slip on out the back door.
Down the streets, I go.
She are hollowing about the front rent.
She'll be lucky getting her back rent.
She ain't gonna get another.
So I stop in a local bar, you know, people.
I'm going to the bar.
I'll rent my code.
I'll call the bartender.
So look, man.
Come down here.
You got down there.
So what you want?
The one verb and the one sky.
The one here.
When I ain't seen my baby since I don't know when.
I've been drinking bourbon whiskey.
I've got you and Jim.
Gonna get high man.
I'm gonna get a lose.
Need me a triple shot of attitude.
I'm gonna get drunk.
I don't fear.
I want one verb and the one sky.
I need one verb and the one sky.
One fear.
But I'm sitting now.
At the bar.
I'm being drunk.
I'm feeling mellow.
I'm taking bourbon.
I'm taking a stat.
I'm taking beer.
I'm going down a bar.
So look, man.
Come down here.
So what you want?
The one verb and the one sky.
The one here.
I ain't seen my baby since I don't know when.
I've got to get a drink, man.
I'm gonna get a get a get a get a get a get a get.
I'm gonna get high man.
I ain't had enough.
Need me a triple shot of attitude.
I'm gonna get drunk.
So listen right here.
I want one verb and the one sky.
I'm gonna get one verb and the one sky.
I'm being drunk.
But I'm okay.
I'm gonna get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a get a
a get a get a get a get a
Express mine back baby
You
Ned
Sit down
Slowly
I'm playing a high
You know when your mouth is getting dry
You're playing a high
Look down the bar
I'll see you in my butt tonight
I'll sell you a man
Come down here
You got down there
So it's my dish time
I'll sell you a man
I would sign this
You sit the clock on the wall
It's futile
I lay as close
About the hall
So it's what you need
One verb and one shot
One beer
I ain't seen my favorite since the lie on a week
Gotta get drunk, man
So I can't even speak
Gonna get high, man
Listen to me
One drinking and up jacket
Better making free
Gonna get drunk, I'm gonna make it real clear
I'll run, run, burn, run
You've got to one beer
One beer, one beer
One fat beer
I know a lot of people listen to the show
All working out on the treadmill
And I think that is exactly the type of song
That gives you the rhythm
The role that you need
When you're trying to drop a few pounds
Oh by the way
My daughter was here
And she said that
Yes, I do qualify
As having passed the three by three challenge
So you'll get news on that
After we're back
On vacation
Though yeah
Oh yeah
I win
Trust me
Door third good, one bourbon
One scotch, one beer on the Charlie's seven minutes and 42 seconds of goodness now on
With Metallica
Oh yeah
Yeah
I can't remember anything
Can't tell if this is true or clear
Deep down inside, I'll feel the screen
This terrible silence stopped in May
Now that the war is through with me
I'm waking up again, I'll see
That there's not much left in me
Nothing is real but paid it now
Oh, my breath is how it is, oh dear
Oh please God wait me
Back in the womb it's much to real
And it's not that I must feel
But can't look forward to it, dear
Look to the time when I'll live
Better to do this thing to me
Just like a war time now
Oh dear
Tight to the shins and make me be
Cut this life apart from me
Oh, my breath is how it is, oh dear
Oh please God wait me
Now the world is gone
I'm just one
Oh, God help me
Oh, my breath is how it is, oh dear
Oh please God help me
In visiting me, all I see, absolutely all I can do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do
I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I
can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can not do, I can
forget my very first Metallica experience on the North Pole and Tukti-Yuk-Tuk-North
West Territories with the Molson Ice Polar Beach Challenge, where we actually cybercasted
live from the North Pole, we had Veruca Salt, whole, Courtney Love completely smashed,
diving into the crowd and Metallica. 500 prize winners, that was it, it was the most outrageous
experience I've ever had when it comes to rock and now I want you all to put your hands
on your iPhone, your smartphone, your blackberry, your android, I want you to squeeze it, I want
you to lift your eyes up to the hills and I want you to pray to the gods of rock to come
down and give us the stairway to heaven.
There's a lady who shone, all it glitters is gold,
and she's buying the stairway to heaven, when she gets there she knows, you can start our
close with the word she can get what she can.
And she's buying the stairway to heaven, there's a sign on the wall, but she wants to wish you
what, because you know sometimes words help me in the dream by the road, there's a song
bird who sings sometimes all of words help me in the dream.
There's a lady who shone, all it glitters is gold, and she's buying the stairway to heaven
and she's buying the stairway to heaven, there's a lady who shone, all it glitters is gold,
and she's buying the stairway to heaven, there's a lady who shone,
all it glitters is gold, and she's buying the stairway to heaven, there's a lady who shone,
all it glitters is gold, and she's buying the stairway to heaven,
there's a lady who shone, all it glitters is gold, and she's buying the stairway to heaven,
there's a lady who shone, there's a lady who shone, there's a lady who shone,
there's a lady who shone, there's a lady who shone,
Sing us the song, you're the piano band, sing us the song tonight
Well we're out in the mood for a melody, and you've got us feeling alright
Everybody was wasted, get ready to sing along
Chatteru, it's a little crowd for a sad day, and the bad at your lips being smile
Because he knows that it's me, they've been coming to see, to forget about life
And the piano sounds like a tunnel, and the microphone smells like a beer
And they sit at the bar, and put bread in my jar and say, man, what are you doing here?
We're out in the mood for a melody, and you've got us feeling alright
Absolutely, the perfect song to get wasted by, and you know me, Mr. Lightweight, one rolling rock, we'll do it to me
How did we almost get to three hours again? I was supposed to cut out in here early, this is like nuts
I want to thank Ray for sending this one into me, I have not played this song in the radio in New Years
But nuts about it when I was in high school, couldn't help singing it, even though the lyrics kind of weird when you're a guy, love unlimited
I'm so glad that I'm a woman
It's nice, you know, in the morning when you wake up
As you comb your hair and put on your makeup, it's too lyrical, you know what I mean
Just use the chocolate cake, and you can make it even way
I'm so glad that I'm a woman, and no one will trade, I'm the one that made it all
You're the lifeline of mankind, and now it's a time for me
I know I've got me in the cold
In the lifeline of mankind
And now it's my time
Yes now it's my time
So yeah I know I've got me in the cold
In the lifeline of mankind
And now it's my time
Yes now it's my time
So yeah I know I've got me in the cold
In the lifeline of mankind
And now it's my time
Yes now it's my time
So yeah I know I've got me in the cold
In the lifeline of mankind
And now it's my time
So yeah I know I've got me in the cold
In the lifeline of mankind
Love and limited I'm so glad I'm a woman
And it is now time for music appreciation
Moment on the David Source Code
Every footballer Friday we try to educate you
I'm music from the past here is a definite blast
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh
oh, oh, oh, oh
Well
I've got one of the chains
She's got one of the chains
And I've got to see the lyrics
I've got to see the lyrics
Well, I know she's marked you this
I do the food in my heart, my love
My beauty beauty, she's all right
She's got just one of the chains
She's got one of the chains
And I've got to see the really great
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
The amazing Jackie Wilson on the Debbie Horse Code
Just part of your food for a Friday musical appreciating education
Uh
Reça Chance
2 more songs than I'm out of here
I've really have got to
Uh
Get prepared for vacation entrading for the show tonight
the night. Computer America 7 p.m. Get Monash and West. My coast to coast.
This is brand name. You've got another hand round. She serves them with whiskey and wine.
Sears are surrounded. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound. You're a pound.
You still watch it, I've been told, let's say you're the story
You can feel a ship or a ride
Just some, it's for you, Jim Lauren
But here I'm always told, true love was mine
But there's hope, there's hope, there's hope, there's hope, there's hope
And I, when the bars close down, ran into walks through a sighting town
Love's a man, it's not a run, she's still getting here in the same
She has a ship right up there, you'll find your ride
What a good way, you and me, set your mind, my love, my love, my lady
Is the same, it is, you and me, you and my girl
What a good way, you and me, you and me
Looking glass, how many times I've said that?
Looking glass, brandy, you're a fine girl, what a good way if you would be
Okay, boy, wait a minute, let me just check you
A little trickle of blood coming out of my ear from earlier when we played
Some of the harder stuff
So it looks like we just about made three hours after all, I'm not quite sure how we do it
But I can't stop, I'm just enjoying it so much
This show is of course, listen to support it
Please go to devorac.org slash NA
And, excuse me, verb
Who thoughts in sale?
And support the show, it'll be much more important now than ever before
As you can imagine, if you've been listening throughout the entire program
Looks like David source code along with no agenda will be highlighted on iTunes
In the next coming weeks, the guys called in and said that they were, there's a new team over there
Which is great, so that's very cool
And make sure you listen to computer America, the seeding starting at 7 o'clock
Getmonation Westtime tomorrow morning, 9 a.m. in the morning is when we do episode 2, 2, 2 of no agenda
And please, if you go to no agenda entertainment.com
Consider picking up any of the songs that you really like
This folks over there putting together a playlist with iTunes, links of all the songs
Played on these long extended Fubar Friday Charles
So that does wrap up episode 84840 of the Daily Source Code
The I'm Free Fubar Edition was produced with the help of hundreds of chuckleheads worldwide
Rebirthing the art of radio globally
May I live to be 100, each of you to be 100 in a day, so I never have to see my friends pass away
Until next time, live your life with passion
And as long as it lasts, enjoy your freedom
There are places I remember for my life
Though some have changed, some forever
Not for better, some have gone
And some remain, all these places
Had a moment with lovers and friends
I still can recall
Some are dead, and some are living
In my life, I will love them all
But above these friends and lovers
There is no nobody that can lose with you
I and these memories, blues and meaning
When I think of love
As something new, I know I know
I'm never as affection for people and things
And before I know I love and stuff
And take a welcome in my heart
I love you more
I know I'm never as affection for people and things
And before I know I know
I have to stop and think about them
In my life, I will love you more