Delta-Share Charlie 835.
We're 16 minutes and seven.
We've been sharing five lines of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
The only loss.
It's getting me alive.
I know it's going to strip down.
Fantastic.
It's a battle curry.
I can warn everybody in this time once again
for the Charlie Daily Source Code 835
coming to you from the Hilltop Watch Tower
Crackpot Command Center.
It's a snap-hoo Saturday.
It's a beautiful day to be in the park.
Saturday.
Here on the park.
I think it was the father July.
Saturday.
Here on the park.
I think it was the father July.
People can't see.
People laughing.
A man selling ice cream.
Singing a tell you song.
You look like crazy.
Nothing can't you take it.
I guess I can.
And I've been waiting such a long time.
Saturday.
I know the day.
Here on the park.
I think it was the father July.
I know the day.
Here on the park.
I think it was the father July.
People can't really smell it.
A man selling ice cream.
Singing for a song.
You look like crazy.
of songs, which you see, what would you call those things? Oh yeah, records. And just kind
of throw them into one big bin, which we call folders these days. And I'm just a role
and I'm out as the feeling comes to me and on and in. It's one sprawl you chuckle
there. You're my best friend.
I feel they saw true and really love you, oh, oh, you're my best friend.
You make me lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay,
lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay, lay.
Oh, you're my best friend
Ooh, you make me live
You're my friend
Oh, you're my best friend
Ooh, you make me live
You're my best friend
Freddie Mercury Queen, you're my best friend
On the full bar
We visited, which we call the Snaphu
Snaphu Saturday, everybody in the morning to you
Coming to you at noagendastream.com
If you're listening and you have any opportunity to get to a computer
The real party for the shows at noagendachat.com
That's where we, well it seems like we're talking about football today
I'm not, I'm definitely not in a world cup kind of mood
That's for sure
But that's where we eventually get into some kind of interactive thing
Where people start throwing songs out and then they just kind of flow
And usually these shows can last anywhere from an hour to two hours
We'll see that we come up with today
But my physical max is definitely two hours
And my physical tolerance has been kind of low for the past week and a half
I got really sick about 10 days ago
With some kind of virus
And I think a whole bunch of things came out at once
You'll know that it was Thursday a week ago
That I was actually quite sick while we're doing noagenda
So it was two shows ago
And after that I just kind of collapsed
And I couldn't wake up, I had to sleep, just continuously
I had no energy
Most of my bodily fluids were draining quite rapidly
I'll spare you the details of that
And of course that's not just because of a physical health issue
There's some other things going on
And one in general
Which for those of you who've been listening to this program for
Well 834 episodes by now you might have caught one or two
And for those of you who have listened to
209 or some of the episodes of Noagenda
You know that there's one major life choice that I have to make
And it's been bugging me for probably about five years now
And a combination of things last Thursday
Set off a perfect storm
Like a spark in a Tinder box
And it doesn't really matter
How what where for what reason
That'll all matter later after I've made my choices
And maybe then we can talk about it more in depth
And that'll be something we definitely will discuss on the daily source code
Just right now it's not prudent and not fair to a number of people to do that
But I lost my shit
And I embarrassed myself
And I upset a lot of people, interestingly enough
Not so much the recipient of my shit lossage
Luckily because Johnson to work is my friend
He is my best friend
And confidant and colleague
But actually you guys for those of you who are crossovers
Between chuckle heads and
And producers of the Noagenda show
And I'm really sorry about that
So no apology I give here is going to make any difference
The words matter and actions matter
But I feel really bad
And then I realize what it is
It's something that has to change within my own life
Something that I've been
Struggling with for quite a long time
And actually all of this will have a very positive outcome
Because it's finally given me the strength to do what I need to do
So I'm actually quite excited about it
And I'd like to celebrate that with some feedback
It always helps a little bit
Maybe if we just kick some jams out really really hard
You'll understand how I'm feeling right now
You'll understand how I'm feeling
You'll understand how I'm telling
You'll understand how I'm honestly feeling
You'll understand how I'm feeling
You'll understand how I'm though
Play for me
Do I say I'm not your girl?
I don't like that, but you're in the way
If you want to call, then I would love
And you think I would stay, I'd say I had you needed for
Three days, three days, any more
Yes, this is
I don't like that, but you're in the way
Yeah, yeah, for those of you wondering who that is, that's news, hyper music
I mean those guys are really good, and hit me every single time right in the gut
As do calls like this, I love receiving emails
And voice recordings from chuckleheads who've been around and to hear them come around and come back
This is the stuff that I'm remembering now, why I do it, why I do what I do, why I should do more of what I'm really good at
And less of what I really have no passion for
I don't like that, but I don't like that, I don't like that, I don't like that
I don't like that, I don't like that, I don't like that, I don't like that
It was a neat thing because you became almost a human aggregator for me
On top of the great daily conversation and the insight into just another human beings life
It was always interesting to see the music you were pulling
And the promos that you were playing, because that really started to get me expanding my horizons
And other podcasts, things like Catholic Insider, Don and Drew, the bitterest pill with Dan Klass
Even radio adventures with Dr. Floyd and G-Wiz, I don't know, I have one point
I was up to 48 or 50 podcasts that I was trying to listen to
But at least I had an hour and a half long commute that now
I got about seven minutes, so it's a little bit of a different model for me as well
But great to hear that you're alive and well and back on the wagon
I guess you could say, all right, but have yourself a great day today
And I will be listening to you soon. Thanks, man, I really appreciate it
You know, when I hear that list of names and I hear
And there's a couple of people from the old days in the chat room, Mark is couch
Who is still hanging in there with the scenes he now, I think it's just celebrated five years
You know, things turned out much differently, then I had hope they would back in the day
Much much differently
And I think if anything, probably the name podcast is what killed the whole idea
And that in the fact that it turns out you really can't measure shit on the internet
You know, and that most of everything online where money is being
I was reading today in the Wall Street Journal, I was reading Facebook
Has revenues of had revenues last year of eight hundred million dollars
Eight hundred million dollars and I'm thinking of myself this can't be from people clicking on banners
You know, in the chat room, no Jenna chat.com, could you please raise your hand if you've ever clicked on a banner on Facebook
You know, she has sure there's some revenue to be made from displaying a banner
But really, I mean really, where is this coming from?
I mean, the way I see it, people are being forced to watch advertising and click on things
In order to get virtual money to play addictive games like Farmville
You know, I just don't see it being a really happy advertising medium
And is advertising really still viable the way
This conversation's been it's the same when we've had for the past six years nothing has changed
Nothing has changed, just the deals are bigger
And there's the flow, let's put it that way, is more sophisticated
But really, how real is it? This is real
This, this what we're doing right here with the people
Feeding back in real time ideas going back and forth and value for value
I'm really, I'm really into that and if my value is much lower than I need for my lifestyle then so be it
But value for value really works for me
And right now the value I'm getting out of just doing this show
And being able to share my thoughts for as far as I can share them at this moment
To be continued
It's, uh, it feels good, it really does
Let me play this one for you
Now this is not for you to lean on me, but it's for me to lean on you
I'll need some of that in the next couple of weeks
Classic bill where there's on this NAFU Saturday, DSC 835
I'll roll, roll, roll, roll if we are white
We know that they're always tomorrow
Lean on me, when you're not strong
And I'll be your friend
I'll have you carry on for it won't be long
Till I'm going to need somebody to lean on
Please swallow your pride
If I have faith, you need to borrow for no one can feel
Don't love me on me
That you won't let you
You're just called on the brother when you need a hand
We all need somebody to lean on
I just make a problem that you understand
We all need somebody to lean on me
When you're not strong and I'll be your friend
I'll help you carry on for it won't be long
Till I'm going to need somebody to lean on
You just called on the brother when you need a hand
We all need somebody to lean on
I just make a problem that you understand
You're just called on the brother when you need a hand
We all need somebody to lean on
We'll be all need somebody to lean on
Oh, yes. Here's the feeling that I want.
The feeling that is brewing inside me and bubbling up.
I'm free.
I'm free. I'm free.
I'm waiting for you to follow me.
I told you that it takes to reach the highest high.
You'd love to see the things that's so good.
But you've been so many times before my shyness points into the door.
Oh, no one had the guts to leave the temple.
I'm free. I'm free.
I'm free. I'm free. I'm free.
I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free.
I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free.
I'm free
And I'm waiting for you to follow me
I can't recall
Don't try to read into it, don't try to figure out the riddles, just go with the flow of the messages in the music
By the way, how's the microphone sounded today?
The gear is working so nicely, I think I can do my nails while I'm doing the show is working really well
I'm free
I can't recall
Don't try to read into it, don't try to figure out the riddles, just go with the flow of the messages in the music
By the way, how's the microphone sounded today?
The gear is working so nicely, I think I can do my nails while I'm doing the show is working really well
And if I stand, I'll just let them burn their eyes on you
And if I shine, don't let it change the thing that you do
I can't recall
Don't try to read into it, don't try to figure out the riddles, just go with the flow of the messages in the music
It's a little bit of cowbell here for you
I think it was wasny I can the chat room
Somehow I don't think it's the real Steve wasny
I requested Santana, Sambapati
Oh my god
One last time you heard that on the radio
In regards to the Howard Stern interview I did the other day
Beginning of the week
Obviously the reasons for that appearance was not to just promote anything
But let's be honest
If we ever want to see anything become of the new freedom that we have
That we essentially kind of stumbled into
And you know as the band with became available
Six, seven years ago was inevitable
Inevitable that we would start broadcasting on the internet
I remember the very first time I saw the internet
And when I witnessed it when it was still a command line
Based we didn't have the worldwide web
We had something called go for and you use programs like links
To get the stuff and we had news groups instead of chat rooms
Well we had IRC actually which is still one of those things
It just hangs around and we're still using it today
The main thing was was to plant the seed of digital broadcasting
Because that's really what has changed
When I look at the wonderful apps that have been made by people for no agenda
Like pocket no agenda
There's at least four or five of them
There's Android apps, there's even a version of an app for the Blackberry
And something that I think is becoming available on Nokia phones
But really streaming it's everywhere you know you can listen to it in your car
The idea of time shifting is just beautiful
I mean hey we used to make mix tapes for each other
Remember those days you loved the girl you had a crush honor
You made a mix tape you know that wasn't like live stuff
For later was for a for enjoyment in a different scenario
All of this stuff has now come together and we can do it all
Of course there's there's been some significant hurdles along the way
And there still are everything I'm doing here technically is illegal by playing these songs
Now I am buying them from iTunes and essentially I'm playing them for you know a couple of my friends
That is a significant hurdle but it's a risk I'm willing to take because this is what the art is about
There still is an Academy of Radio Arts and Sciences
Art and Sciences
It's not just something that comes out of a computer or a playlist or a pre-programmed or done by callout research
It's something that has to do with the weather with feelings with mood
And it is digital broadcasting there's no difference how it gets to you as long as it gets to you
The real issue is how do you sustain it and that's when my value for value comes in
Anyway, here's one that was sent in by one of the listeners one of the chuckle heads
Kind of liked it it was again messaging the music big reset button in the sky
I think the artist is ring or ring not too sure
Jam though
I can remember the moment we first met
But you and I were as close as in your bed
We haven't worked but we'll love to face this
Where they were
The same old love we had
To the start of all
Can we start again
Do you remember the time you said you'd be in the bed?
What would it come to the animals and yet?
We broke the same old, do you feel the stream?
Do you feel it's time to turn the page?
We're together
What if we go
Can we start again?
Do you remember the time you said you'd be in the bed?
We broke the same old, do you feel the stream?
I really like that.
The big reset button in the sky.
Yeah, I'm about to push that one for sure.
And just reading along with the chat room, no agenda chat.com, which is where the party
always is.
When we hit, I roll out the daily source code.
This is episode number 835, by the way.
As we march towards 1,000 episodes, we'll hit 900 first.
That's the Snapfoo Saturday edition.
It's clear to me that I haven't been really, well, I haven't been clear about my offered
to Howard Stern.
It's, of course, it's sincere offer.
It's real easy.
I mean, anyone can do the math.
You brought in 2 million new listeners to a serious satellite radio who pay, at the time
I think they were paying 12 or 13 dollars.
That's probably around 10 bucks or maybe you can get a, I think he's packaged in.
So let's say it's even 10.
So if you get, if you can pull those 2 million over or a million of them over and you get
another million from around the world, and the guy is bootlegged and pired it everywhere,
and people really want to hear his content, the numbers are very easy to do.
And you do it through an iPhone app and an Android app, and you encrypt the stream or whatever
you have to do so that at least there's some exclusivity for it.
And I think people will be more than happy to pay for it.
It is the value for value than I'm talking about.
Now, that's whatever you find valuable.
But really what is going on is, and this is something I did learn from Dave Weiner.
There's always a shift between centralization and decentralization, and right now everything
is moving away from centralized networks into smaller decentralized groups.
That's just the way it works.
This will happen to Facebook too, by the way.
The minute someone comes out with some kind of program or protocol or something that allows
you to share things with people by selection, because that's really what the private, what
people think privacy is, you know, I don't want my boss to see this picture.
I don't want my mom to read this particular post.
I want to give certain access to people, the minute that's available, everyone will shift
to that.
I mean, it always happens.
It always goes back and forth, and right now I think we're in a tectonic shift away
from centralized networks, particularly in media, and we're moving towards decentralization.
We have smaller groups and these are self-sustaining groups.
And then smaller groups will work together at arms length and get things done.
That is almost a natural law, and I'm almost 46.
I now can see it happening in cycles over and over again.
And we are becoming more dependent upon each other, not upon big networks.
And this is the same thing with the governments.
You know, the government is desperately trying to centralize everything, and people are going
to naturally push away from that and want to decentralize.
Now, of course, we're going to need guns and stuff like that to protect our decentralized
networks, but that's a detail.
And I can see it, it's so clear to me, and I'm very excited about it, and that's where
I want to be.
I want to be at the center of what is really happening.
And that's what I mean when I say I have to make choices and changes so that I can feel
happy.
Cranky, how much longer do I have to live?
Who the fuck knows, right?
I didn't want to hit that one.
What I meant was this one.
The bottom of the airways is landed, and he's sounding good to me.
This is the day he saw Scott, with Adam Curry.
It's staring at Mike.
Yeah, we got feet tickets to the brand bank on turnip, and it's Monday night at Pacific
College.
They're going to all the way to a few where I want to answer to the question, mainly when
it's hard to be rich.
I can just call this a simple one, right before I see what's in there.
Give us a ring, ding, ding.
It's a beautiful day.
Yeah, Todd, this is the last one.
Ring, a ding, a ding, a ding, a ding.
And one goes to the brand bank tickets, man.
What do you think?
Time.
This is Mike.
I woke up again this morning with a son and my eyes on Mike.
Came over with a script surprise.
I'm my beautiful story with a twist.
I came over for you.
While I'm here to get your ass out of bed.
It's good.
I was waiting on the way.
But I didn't think nothing.
So we didn't know nothing.
And I'm sick.
What my hell am I?
You went drinking in a lake at any place.
I thought the feet are full of flavor.
The pain that wouldn't leave us if I didn't make it.
I'm the perfect one.
And the girls are busking up and down.
We're around 10 dead events again.
I run out of the teeth for acceptance.
It's just me and everything.
They were doing great.
We were working all the way.
They're right.
But we didn't know nothing.
So we didn't know nothing.
And I'll say, you're my hell am I?
You went drinking in a lake at any place.
But my mind, my mind, my mind.
My mind, my mind, my mind.
Yeah, I'm dead.
I'm in full my drinking in a lake at any place.
And I'm drinking in a lake at any place.
Yeah, I'm the perfect one.
So we're around 10 dead events.
We're so manly I want to take care of it.
And other men say, you're my worstie.
But you can say, you're my bitch, you're my the boss.
I'm about to find my human rights in the book.
And wait, time to say, which thing we got to talk about.
We found a good solution.
And I get that something.
So I have to want my hell am I.
We're bringing in a lake at 20 speed.
I got the feeling full on the answer.
But I'm hate and we'll be late.
It's the bottom of the lake at 20 speed.
It's the edge of the hole.
I'm going to make a hole in the hole.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll lay.
Hell lay.
So I have to want my hell am I.
We're bringing in a lake at 20 speed.
It's the right.
Am I?
Yeah, it's my first feeling.
I never heard of it before.
Yeah, exactly. I love that song. I've never heard of it before.
Brandven 3000 drinking in LA. Yeah, it's I dig it. It's really nice.
All right, I'll be honest. You caught me. I was rolling up a smoke and song ended.
If you're digging the songs that you're hearing on this snap-oos Saturday edition of the Daily
Source code, I recommend getting sound-hound, which I think is available for Android and the iPhone
or shazam on the iPhone and shazamming the shit out of these songs and then go buy them on iTunes.
That way you'll support the artist or at least the infrastructure that or artist is a part of,
which is the way it should work. And if you want to support this show and the no agenda stream,
please become a sustaining producer. You can find details of no agenda stream.com and you can
donate directly at devorac.org slash n-a-s november alpha c-era.
As I guarantee you one thing, you can buy this song on iTunes, but you will never hear it on the radio.
There's no way that at you.
These are laps this day.
Loading really looking for a busy evening night.
P Cocking
It's suggesting
I can't get it all air
It's been done to the opposite
Feel like I'm not in a mess of what I've had
I'm not in a mess of what I've had
I'm almost done to the opposite
Oh yeah
I'm a footmaid on the ground
I can't see them anymore
Come on YouTube, let's just give these motherfuckers on
'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd trade
Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Yeah
Sheiile
Not not comfort than all heaven's dough
Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh
Oh, Yeah
Not not comfort than all heaven's dough
THE FAMILY
Oh can you still write in it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
You'd love to see it, yeah!
We got one for!
Hey, let'sK breach.
Hang on, okay, man.
No, I don't have to Matter!
Let's fight up with your face!
Whoa!
We went crazy!
No, I don't have to Matter anymore!
Whoo-ooooh-ee-ah-hoo!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no one good dreams.
We will lead you.
Thank you!
Good night!
Greetings!
Oh, he's got one.
and
That's a reason why you don't hear songs like that anymore on the radio and that's because
it's 13 minutes long and there would have to be at least two commercial breaks in that
amount of time.
So it's impossible.
And of course, if you're listening to this in the podcast version of the Digital Broadcast
and it's too long for you, all you have to do is just press that fast forward button
that's some interesting technology we invented.
Eric, who's Portland?
Hey, Eric, did you see that story about George Allen Reckers?
He was currently with a male prostitute, but the guy's an anti-gay activist and he's the
Baptist Minister.
Yeah.
He's a critic.
Remind me of that song, Missionary Man.
That's your rhythmic song.
Hey, can you spin that up for us?
Absolutely.
My favorite.
I was born an original singer.
I was born from original sin.
And did I had a dollar bill for all the things I've done?
There'd be a mountain and a money pile up to my chin.
My mother told me good, my mother told me strong she said the truth to yourself
that it can't go wrong.
But there's just one thing that you must understand.
You can forward your brother.
Don't mess with a mission or a man.
He's got gun on the side.
He's got the scenes and the puzzles like enough from behind.
Like I looked from those five books.
He's a man with a mission, got a serious smile.
There was a woman in the jungle and a monkey on a tree.
The mission or a man he was following me.
He said stop what you're doing.
Get down upon your knees.
Have a message for you.
Get your head up to leave, leave, leave, leave.
Leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave
leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave
leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, there leave, leave, whatever, leave, go, leave, leave, leave, leave, leaving, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, let, leave, left, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leaving, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, they leave, left, left, leave, leave, no, there leave, leave, leave, Leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, there leave, leave if they leave, there leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave that leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
You lie right to my face
You spent me to believe in it
You said you'd rather walk away
Let me fall to peace
Because I know it would fail
The salty catastrophe
A major betrayal
But getting disaster
You're walking on water
Struggling long as I dream
And I'll give you a chance
From me to you
I'll give you a chance
To be free like I can see
In your eyes
And all I ever believe in
The lost in your heart
Feel it in my hand
See it in your eyes
And all the times you say
You tired of this place
You're so sick of my face
But I should wait around on you
And I know that's your world show
Sometimes we are just me
Softens to believe
Something so much more than you
Something so much more
Because I know it would fail
The salty catastrophe
A major betrayal
But getting disaster
You're walking on water
Struggling long as I dream
And I'll give you a chance
From me to you
I'll give you a chance
I'll give you one death
From me to you
And I know that's your world show
There's not ever lightning
And all the times you say
You're walking on water
Can't see
I'll give you a chance
And all the times you say
You're so sick of my face
I'll give you a chance
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, I don't have any other, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
And all I ever need is nothing, all I feel is, I can't see it in your eyes, I see it in your eyes,
A walk you on happy day, is a walk you on happy day
One last reason brought to you by Chucklehead Supreme Marcus Kauch
in this one's by request from whom the chat room had like you'd to start spinning out some song ideas
no agenda chat.com if you're listening on this stream beaten grab it and that for that
I'm mad just smoking weed in the street without cops harassed, I imagine going in the court with no trap, life's down cruising blue by homo waters, no well fence supporters, more cops set away, we raise our daughters, thieves and shorter nights of colder, feeling like life is over, he's next strike like the cobra, the world's hot, my son got not, evidently as elementary, they want us all going eventually, true for now to stay more plain, knowledge of copes, come without the cops, we don't have the top dollars,
imagine everybody flashing, fashion this on and close, lacing its click up with diamond rolls, your people told they don't go for votes, global scores, through going through a magic law at no end recovery, just a source for the mind, I take a glimpse in time watched the Flet Streep, the world has mine and I ruled worldwide, imagine that.
I tree on my son, I looked a lionabola be that McDonnell, as if I was a gotta.
If you could be mine, we both shine
If I rule the world
Still living for today
And these last days and two
Let us be paradise, like relaxing
Black, latino, and Anglo-Saxon
The morning it's changed the range
Cast, Lord, drop us your bags
Free of glass, brand new whips to craft
That we laugh in the ill-a-pat
The villa houses for the crew
How we do, trees for breakfast
Diamond sexists have been stretched
So many kids of depression make me vision
The better living, type of place to raise kids
And opening us to the lies
History is too fast, but I'm as wise as the whole out
Plus the gold child seeing things
Like I was controlling, click bowling
Trick in six inches on kicks and still holding
Tricks to the power, it's not civilized if he savages
Give me one shot, I turn, try, fight to lavish
Political prisoners set me free, stress free
No one released, purple in the threes and jettees
Fill the wind breeze and west in these
I think her better sky can't make it
The cities and reverse things, the williest
It's sound foul whenever you roll
I mean to go downtown, I don't believe
I can't be selling out of consent until I feel
I don't know the world, imagine that
I feel like my son
I love him, I love him, I don't pay that
The act I'm in, it's yours
To the beat, if you could be mine, we won't shine
If I don't know the world
Still living for today, it's me, it's me
I want right up to my son
And in hand hand
We won't write up to our son
We won't land land
Hand in hand hand
We won't write up to our son
We won't land land
You let it hit the story, how the thugs live and where we
Duck down and car seats, heaps, man and Toby
Running from the jakey
I've got for pigs, he's on a break, a million states
Go down, out of shit
Wait, I had the little man, we can't be with
Trying to get loose, flip the A-Stack
Man and keep the gap with your cock camera
Making moves and then laying a back and forth
Scremmer
Because you can have all the chips
Be poor or rich, still nobody wanna nigger have a shit
If I prove the world and everything in it
Skies the limit, I push the Q45 and finish
It wouldn't be no such thing as jealousy's a beef felony
Strictly living longevity to the destiny I thought I'd never see
But reality struck, better find out before your times out
But don't forget
If I lose the world
Imagine that
I've free all my son
I love them, I don't pay that
Black donans' vows
Could it be if you could be my people shy
If I lose the world
Still living for today and these last days of time
I've managed to narrow
I've free all my son
I love them, I don't pay that
Black donans' vows
Could it be if you could be my people shy
If I lose the world
Still living for today and these last days of time
I've free all my son
I love them, I don't pay that
Black donans' vows
If I lose the world
That's nice
And Lauren Hill on the locals there
If I lose the world
That would be the title of
Hey, we are well into the second hour of this Saturday
Snaphoo Saturday just in the Daily Source Code
It is episode 835 time for our friend from
An undisclosed location in Europe
Comic strip
Come on in my friend
In the morning to you Adam
No, in the morning to you
Here is CSB
Your impassioned eocrets funded
So Adam, I must say
Since early that I have nothing against
Further eau enlargement
And the enlargement in fact
Including penis enlargement
So I don't mind
Terrike joining eau
And in fact I want also you crane
And Russia to become full eau
Members
Absolutely
Well then all up
Yeah
Some eau countries are against
So Terrike for example
It's why I think already 30 years to join eau
And now
Eau is American sinister minister Robert Gates
Blames eau for the latest shift in the Terrike's body
I want to say only one fucking thing about it
If you say once two once eau
To accept the record then why the fact
USA is not giving visa free movement to visa free
With a way to
To Turks
Trying to say
What?
It's cant
And by the way
How is the Mickey doing?
She's fine
Squeeze her back from me
You
Sometimes I just wonder
To the fucking comic shit blogger talking about
Jack
I went out through
Right
And I never went back
Like a river
That's all no work's wrong
Like a fool
I'll turn it and I just get wrong
Everybody's got a hungry heart
But everybody's got a hungry heart
Everybody's got a heart
But everybody's got a heart
And a hungry heart
But everybody's got a hungry heart
I only heard once two twice
You had a good stop
Falling, getting stomachs
You fell and struggled with A sugar
We took a  as we grew to death
Oh
Now here I am
But it's got a hungry heart
Everybody's got a hungry heart
Play out their money and you put your heart
Killing the limits of nobody says
Nobody's like to feel the heart
Everybody's got a hungry heart
I wish it's still kind of sounded like that
You know, it's just, I love that tune
First spring, staying hungry heart
Snapples, Saturday, and the Daily Source Code episode
835 coming to you from the Hilltop Watch Tower
Crackpot Command Center
And I just need to play one more song that kind of makes you feel
You know, like we're back in the 70s
Yeah, that's it, that's why I need it
Despite the way it's a song that features my good friends
Already IP, Dan Hartman on a bass
The mountain is high, the valley is cold
And you're confused on the square floor
So I'm from here to give you a head
And lead you into the promise
And come on and take a free ride
Here you go
Come on and take a free ride
Come on to take a free ride
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, go on and come on, come on, come, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on , come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Now that missed that guy, man, what's up?
That's the Edgar Winger group, Dan Hartman, as I said, on the fretless bass, first
man he was in.
Good friend, passed away in late 80s.
Crap.
Free ride on the daily source code and since she's back at the watch tower,
it might as well play her favorite song of all time.
This one's for Miss Mickey.
Divinals.
Can you do the video for me all playing the song?
Yeah, oh yeah baby, show it to me man.
I love myself.
I want you to love me.
And I feel good.
I search myself.
I want you to find me.
I forget myself.
I want you to remind me.
I don't know anybody else.
But I think it feels too much to watch myself.
I don't know.
You're the one who makes me come on in.
You're the son who makes me shine.
When you're in, I'm always laughing.
I want to make you mine.
I close my eyes and see you before me.
Like I would die if you were to ignore me.
I couldn't say just too much.
I adore you.
I can't get along with me.
I do anything for you.
I want anybody else.
But I think it feels too much to watch myself.
I don't know anybody else.
I don't know.
I'm not here.
I love myself.
I want you to love me.
When I feel it, I'm just with all of me.
I search myself.
I want you to find me.
I won't get my set.
I want you to ignore me.
I don't know anybody else.
But I think it feels too much to watch myself.
I don't know.
I want you.
I don't know anyone else.
I want you to think it feels too much to watch myself.
I don't know anybody else.
I don't know anyone else.
But I think it feels too much to watch myself.
Okay, babe, you can stop now.
I can't even spit under the desk anymore.
It's horrible.
The vinyl's not touched myself on the snap of the saturday.
It's not the deadly source code loam out for you.
And now we're getting in request.
Now the chat room is really heating up and starting to throw out some tunes.
We got about 25 minutes left because Miss Mickey and I have a playday later on today.
We've got some stuff to do, don't we?
And snubbing your business, what it will be.
So when it comes to songs that you can request, you hit my hot buttons for this one.
Don't tip a thief for the devil.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a man of wealth and taste.
I've been around for a long long years.
So many amazes.
So many.
I was around when Jesus cried at his moment.
So many amazes.
Hope you guessed my name!
Oh yeah!
I want buzzing you with the nature of my game!
Oh yes!
I want to clean why you can't bear to clean
Boba tenta gates!
Boba God save me!
I shot it out!
Who killed the candidates?
Where and after all?
It wasn't you ever!
Let me please introduce Boba,
I'm a man of wealth and taste!
An island transport for those
who can't kill before they reach Boba!
This is the mint juice!
Hope you guessed my name!
Oh yeah!
I want buzzing you with nature of my game!
I can't bear to clean me!
Somebody saved me!
Question what did you want to do?
I want to get the candidates from Boba Doc!
If you guys would want to leave we can go cheating!
Uh huh huh huh!
Don't you can't fight me!
Oh yes!
What you got in my eyes?
The nature of my gaze
Just as every encounter is a cremateur
And all the sinners say
As he tends to say, you just call me
Lose a book because I've been here the sun
The risk of rain
So if you meet me
Have some currency
Have some sympathy
Has some taste
You know you're well-versed
Violet him
Or I'll nail you
Soak the waste
Yeah
There's a me too
Hope you get my name
Yeah
But what?
What's the use of nature of my gaze
Yeah
Me too
Get that
Oh yeah
Get out of there
Yeah
Look
Come on
Help me
Outweigh
Hand it
I'm giving the Janeiro
Outweigh
I'm not
Zoe
I'm going
Simply for the demo, please give it to you for what's my name.
Still a lot of the World Cup Soccer Talks going on in the chat room and origin in chat.com.
And just like to point one thing out to you, like most organized sports,
the thing is rigged, the game is fixed.
Do your research, the shit is not real people.
I'm telling you, they're throwing the games.
It's all about money, you fools.
Go ahead, look at the German officials from 2006.
Look at the FIFA scandals. You're falling for it.
It's a secret queen.
We're now around big boys.
We're around Louisiana way.
We've been zwischening faded.
What a Sickman queen.
You're tossing up a plan, sir!
We've been outside all my world,
And the men glued were to get wrecked
And, you, boy, are youhalten now?
We've been provin Harry for years.
It's cold, but I think it's cold
And we'll see it, it's weak
It's cold, but I think it's weak
It's weak, but I think it's weak
I just don't have no more cowbell for you.
The song is over.
What can I say?
We're cranking it live for the hills of one star.
It's right behind the man set up.
One great day guy after another.
It's Jimmy.
There must be some kind of way out of here.
Say that chocolate to the thief.
There's too much confusion.
I can't get no relief.
It's the smear there.
The drape are white.
Plum and dig my earth.
Nine will level out of nine.
Nobody up it is worth.
No reason to get excited.
But they kind of spoke.
They are many here.
I'm longer.
No reason to get excited.
But they kind of spoke.
They are many here.
I'm longer.
Who's through the life of this by the tone?
But you will not be in through that.
And this is not a fate.
So that is the top post in hell.
But I was given away.
I was given away.
Take that to the bank.
The size of the show up and take advantage of people's goodwill and generosity.
We're all along the watch tower.
Princess kept up you.
While all the women came and went.
But the servants too.
We're looking for outside in the contestant.
So I can't get it wrong.
To ride a small adventure.
We can't get away.
Man, this shit still sounds good.
Years later, doesn't it?
Sounds just fantastic.
Keep away in the chat room.
You want something fresh.
You want something new.
Stick this in your air bitch.
I can't get away.
But it's nothing that we're falling down for now
It's a real story, nothing at all
No one is mine, no one is mine
Just a little bit, I can't understand
Oh no, it's a little bit, I can't understand
Oh no, it's a $40, no one is mine
I know, it's a promising amount
Oh no, it's a $40, no one's mine
I know, it's a $40, no one is mine
Oh no, it's a little bit, I can't understand
Wow, it's a real story, nothing at all
From all over the night
There's no no worries from all over the night
There's no reason we finally know more now
There's no longer starting to be no more
From all over the night
Another Marcus Count's check-in-head supreme
Cream pie tasty snafu treats
Disturb sacred lie on the snafu Saturday
And someone out there said Van Hayland
I think I can't comply
Yeah, yeah
I live my life like this
To tomorrow
And all I've got
I ever feel
He's not on me
So I'll be gone by road
Yeah, so I'm living at our place like you
Ooh yeah
I'm running with the net
Oh
Running with the net
Turn your back
I love the sympholy
It's so simple
When I jumped out of the road
I got no love
No love is for real
And got nobody
Waiting in her room
Burning wings of death
I tell you I love you
I want to tell you I love you
Running with the devil
You know, I've had the ship all night
For life, what's so simple
No, when I jumped out of the road
I got no love
No love is for real
And got nobody
Waiting in her room
Burning wings of death
I tell you I love you
Running with the devil
I want to tell you
I want to tell you I love you
Running with the devil
I don't got nobody
Waiting in her room
Burning wings of death
I tell you I love you
Running with the devil
running with the devil
Let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what
what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here
let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look at what's going on here, let's take a look
it's like a kick up the pieces, that's right, well, as I said, we do about 2 hours, 1, 2, 6, 0 on the Saturday, snap through Saturday or finish with the source code
I've got to play it, I'm going to get the hell out of it, I can't wait, I'm going to sit
in here my job, but I've got to give you that visual, right?
Alright, I'm going to leave you with one more song somewhere in the past eight and a half
hundred episodes, I'm sure that we've discussed the fact that around the 30s, the musical
scale was detuned from 432kHz, which is really the most natural fabanucci-like frequency
range that you want, that your body wants to hear music to.
And one of my chuckleheads out there sent me a detune version, I don't know if it's originally
done this way, or detuned in post-production of this body rate song, and I think if you
really just close your eyes for a second and just relax and really let the music come over
you, you'll feel how it is absolutely affecting your entire psyche.
Turn down the lights, turn down the bed, turn down these voices inside my head,
lay down with me, tell me no lies, just hold me close, don't patronize, don't patronize,
cause I can't make you love me if you don't, you can make your heart feel something
that it won't hear in the dark, in these final hours, I will let it in my heart,
but you won't, no you won't, cause I can't make you love me,
if you don't, I close my eyes, that I won't see, the love you don't feel
when you're holding me, want it will come, and I'll do what's right, just give me to that,
give up this fight, and I will give up this fight, cause I can't make you love me if you don't,
you can make your heart feel something that it won't hear in the dark, in these final hours,
I will let it in my heart, but I'll feel the power, but you won't, no you won't,
cause I can't make you love me if you don't,