Are you ready to be full barred?
Delta Shara Charlie 825!
We've 16 months to 7 minutes and showing 5 rounds of time.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
We are being lost.
We're getting me alive.
I know it's gonna strip down her.
I'm casting kiss for Adam Curry.
That's right, everybody!
It's pregnant time.
This is the first Friday only and everywhere on the chart.
Come on, Chuckle Hans.
Are you ready to get to use it?
We can start it right when you came to the right place, my friends.
We must pack up our boat, see me in town.
Down around San Francisco.
And the boats that ride them all, not the day.
The roundabout day at home.
We brought up a town of Spain.
And the battle where they came.
Where you coming up, try to make a roundabout roll.
Where are you trying to go?
We'll be the yellow pizza.
No, they look awesome.
They're all the talk of the town.
When I got to kiss the fan, they ran in the sun.
Don't fall in now.
They say they're the follows in vain.
And they're Ms. Morgan's again.
When talking back to China, do that roll.
Take a blow.
We feel great.
There's new theme, you're gonnaal a smoow in you,
She and my family, but I'll be the same of my sons
You can't even hear them yet, I'm sick and lie
And go and get some power of the world
Small state, people don't seem to care
There's this key for nothing to the key
Say hello to my little friend, I'm carry, I'm a big sister's girl
Don't be brothers, take it out the full fire Friday for this heat 25
And after so number that he source code, let's keep it rock and we got to wake up
We got to get ready for the weekend, Margarse couch and no original chat.com
Thank you for this time, my friend
As any slows your life, cause it's all you want for it man
We lose the change like a hurricane, I'm coming to watch a way to stay
Can you smell a remuneration in the air?
I can't live with you like a sea, I won't live in the world that you made for me
Can you smell a remuneration, you won't keep me down, can you hear me now?
I'm leaving the line for single day that you told me
When you're so mad, time to decide when we live your way in the kingdom
With a freedom, steal the way around, take it deep for the night
But I'll fight to keep on, it seems to me if I got one thing and it splats
We lose the change like a hurricane, I'm coming to watch a way to stay
Can you smell a remuneration in the air?
I can't live with you like a sea, I won't live in the world that you made for me
Can you smell a remuneration, you won't keep me down, can you hear me now?
I'm leaving the line for single day that you told me
When you're so mad, time to decide when we live your way in the kingdom
With a freedom, steal the way around, take it deep for the night
But I'll fight to keep on, it seems to me if I got one thing and it splats
Can you smell a remuneration in the air?
I'm leaving the line for single day that you told me
When you're so mad, time to decide when we live your way in the kingdom
Can you hear me now?
I'm leaving the line for single day that you told me
When you're so mad, time to decide when we live your way in the kingdom
I've heard a loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud
loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud louder loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud loud
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, or oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh all, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh,
One, two, three
It's the shadow of the shadow
The shadow of the shadow of the shadow
It's the witch
Partner
The man certainly does live up to his name
Doesn't he part?
he bad maching gun shelter
On the charlighted 825
Quite a slow behavior of now
Call me time
For those of you that know
Easy sir
Hearer
You receiving us as we are
Why?
It's so much like the old days of pirate radio. I just love it so much. Hey, so sorry for those of you who are waiting for the live show
Which of course takes place at no agenda stream.com and normally I try to get it on around 12, 31 o'clock
My entire week has been not what I expected it to be. Some things went very smoothly
But kind of all stacks up in the very end there. It just got delayed including a late phone call from a
Get-monation lowlands is all good though
Maybe I should tell you right off the bat. I'm in a very good mood
I'm not sure if it's because of the conversation we've had about it here on the chalk
I don't know if that at any influence whatsoever
I don't believe she listens, but I had a fantastic conversation with Patricia
Soon to be ex-wife
Let's see that was or early. Yeah very early on this week
We had a long conversation like two hours
We had a lot of it was about our daughter Christina it was civilized
She said hey, you know what these lawyers their bastards can we just like we agree on everything don't we and I said yeah
But you know the lawyers have been dragging it out and everything every time they they write something
I got a respond and then just stealing your money like of course
I didn't say I told you so because that would not have been appropriate
I felt like saying it, but I said you know like I kind of predicted and
So we just went down the list here's we agree upon she said could you could you please just write that up?
That's America. Can't you like can't stuff be taken care of pretty quickly? I said yeah, absolutely
Is real simple? I'll send you a document one pageer will make it real easy and we're we kind of agree on everything
That's what the crazy thing is and she wants to move on and and of course
I want to move on and there's always that little thing that marriage thing that's hangin in there oops looks like
We just lost the the stream. Oh, okay, maybe it's back. I hope it's back at least
You may have to may have to refresh
Those of you on the pocket no agenda app or one of the many other
No agenda applications for iPhone for Android for Blackberry. There's also
No agenda stream dot mobile
And I will before I forget we also have the daily stores code torrents
Which I promised I would promote at dot com Dave
dot com slash ds see all of that in the show notes, of course
Anyway back to the story at hand. We had a great conversation
It was like amazing. You know, it was like it was civil and it was like what and
Just I was just about an hour ago. I just sat down getting ready to do the show and Patricia called me
We had a couple of things to go over mainly about Christina, but again, it was all it was like hello
It was civilized. It was nice. It's like so one puts something in the water and it all it all just kind of fixed itself and
I can't tell you how happy that makes me
Yes, applause, please for two people being able to figure their shit out. I love it
a
Bit of Canadian whole school music for you have by request from some of our friends from a North
This is deep water
I'm Richard Clapton
Oh, there we go
We used to go down to the beach in the night
Far from last night's in the promenade life
While I was like a room man, just a riddest way
I do fucks across the sweet crusty
Speakin' to be with a gentle head in
So I'm not down to under there
Deep water
I'm cold out of me
It's cold
If I made over my head
I'd be the left to know
Ooh
Deep water
And deep water
He closed down the door to the truck of the room
And I came back up and just like the door
Hosted a scatter over the stairs
Nobody reads us alone by the chaos
Jacks are a top with a reach 21 home
So really just ain't my eyes due to fall
Deep water
I'm cold out of me
It's cold
If I made over my head
I'd be the left to know
Deep water
And deep water
And deep air
The same heat's been with me
It's now in a pump-each road
I'm so drunk the car won't go
A crazy ask keep looking out to see
Someday drive the cruise and rail
We stayed our own back to town
What do they expect to find?
Short sailing between my mind
Deep water, mine caught up in its floor
If all made over my head
I feel that it's unknown
And deep water
Deep water, I feel that it's unknown
And deep water, I feel that it's unknown
I feel that it's unknown
Honestly, I hadn't really heard of this track before
Or the artist, but apparently as I said, it's a pretty old school stuff from the
Yeah, back in the day from Canada
What do we learn the other day? What do we call them?
Well, yeah, the next one is with sweaters
We learn how to know a gender
Well, bring it on guys
This is kind of stuff you're making up there
I love it
Awesome
Deep water
All you charcoal heads out there, up north
So I had a pretty full week, actually
Mainly consisted of being up in San Francisco
Monday and Tuesday
Up at the old, at the old
Meavio HQ, also did an episode of cranky geeks
I do want to talk about that later
Particularly because of course, we're at the iPad
Launch today and tomorrow
I guess today, officially, but tomorrow everyone gets it
And whatever
So we'll talk about that
But probably one of the most exciting things
I think I told you I had to take the Delta Sierra
My aircraft down to San Jose for its annual
And Wednesday was literally the last day
I could legally fly under its old
It's old annual
And if you don't do that then you're grounded
And you can't fly where you could fly of course
But you could get arrested
By the air cops
But more importantly, your insurance would be invalidated
So not a good thing
So I'd captain Dave come up because of course
I hadn't flown in the airspace
Well, flew a little bit with him in the new
Sessna 210
No, 206, I'm sorry, but the glass cockpit was just amazing
But the last time I had flown the Delta Sierra since
Wow, probably eight or nine months
And it'd been sitting in the hangar at Oakland
For a good five or six months
Battery was dead
So I had to have the battery replaced
The battery would actually wouldn't even charge anymore
And it was kind of like, wow, you know, here's my old friend, my old pal
My old girl
You know, so got her primed and put a little bit of oil on the
On the heads and on the plugs and made sure everything was all ready to go
And she started right up and she was rare to go
And it was relatively short flight
Only I was at like 22 minutes from Oakland to San Jose
But it was really nice, and you know, and of course when you
Haven't flown an aircraft for a while and it's been just sitting around
Which is probably the worst thing you can do for a
For any airplane
Particularly one that, you know, it's not a brand new one
Although the engine has only had 500 hours and it's, you know, the cats me out
This, you know, it's still in mechanics and it's metal
And you know, who knows what can happen
So we took off runway 33 with a little bit of tailwind actually
So took a little bit longer to get airborne
But perfect left the gear down
Just in case, you know, if we need to go back
We don't want to have to be dealing with lowering the landing gear
Let's just leave the gear down for a couple of minutes
And then as we were ready to make our turn out to the right
And you know, raise the gear, work fine, flew over the mountains
Beautiful, I discovered something amazing
I have a, for those of you who care, I have a
A mode S transponder which just just before I left it became law all throughout Europe
Which is the transponder is basically this box that receives a signal from the ground radar stations
And then it actually pings back and says, yeah, I'm receiving your radar
But in the United States, if it's properly implemented, it also will alert you to traffic
So the ATC actually said, okay, you've got a assessor, you know, 11 o'clock
He's about 700 feet below us, so no problem
And the guy basically flew around underneath us
And all it's on here, ding ding traffic traffic
I'm like, what?
I look at Captain Dave and like, dude, I didn't know there was any traffic
Warning system in the plane, I've had it for a couple of years
And of course, that only works if everything is properly implemented
And I think in class Bravo and Delta airspace in the U.S.
That is implemented certainly in the Bay Area
It's implemented properly, so that was very cool and quite surprising
Made a greaser of a landing, just slid onto the runway
So she's going to get her annual and then of course, I'm going to have to say goodbye to her
And I've noticed something very interesting
I'm not like Jones and the fly like I used to be
You know, I was like, oh, weekend, I'm going to go somewhere
In the fly, of course, I was never a guy who would just fly around the airfield
Or go get a $20 hamburger as we say
But I'd always want a destination
And I don't really have a destination
And I have to say that Los Angeles, San Francisco
I mean, you just can't beat Burbank Airport to Oakland with Southwest
I mean, it's just too way too convenient
Certainly with the speeds the Delta share has
Or anything that doesn't fly at 25,000 feet
So when the TSA is even nice at these smaller airports
It's quite enjoyable experience
But I think that a lot of it was me just seeking my freedom
And the plane somehow was in escape, you know, just to go up and spread my wings
And essentially, you know, be with the elements
And to some degree, fight the elements, you know, it was something I really needed
And I feel so different now
And Mickey actually said, you know, this is probably what's going on
Said, oh, you're so right
You know, it was my liberator, my liberator
My liberator, my liberation machine
And I feel so liberated right now
I don't really really need it
I will get back into flying
I might even pick up rotary again
We have so many helicopters going by the house
Because we're near the 101 and of course you want to fly over the
The highway in general and also the highest point behind us of the
of the high tension wires is embedded in the hill
And of course as a rotary pilot, don't speak of the devil
Here comes one
As a rotary pilot, you always want to fly over the highest pole
And not, you know, just to stay away from the wires
But anyway, it was great to fly
And to this day I'll say, you know, if it wasn't
For all the other things, I actually do and better at
I wouldn't mind a life of aviation
It's really nice, there's so many nice people in aviation
You get to do, you know, hang out and just, you know, kick tires
And talk airplanes and get your hands greasy and I kind of love it
Whoa!
He made friends of once and a half
No right time
And a black grip on
So people like it, it's a wake up of the fastest guy
And not
Wake up people
Wake up
The media has been shooting our slides for years
But it's like no one can
Be a condition in the brain
What's in the desktop in the audience
Where's the sweat?
The government makes it so hot
A minute to pass the bed
I don't want to pass the sweat
I don't want to play
I'm bored of run
I've been uniting my town
You look for some nerve
A sweat, VVA off the sun
And real, so what we do first is hear it
I ain't psyche, I can see the future
But I don't like it
This was after those who've been burned
I don't want to find this
Wake up people
Wake up
Hey
We come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we
come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come,
we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we, come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, we come, We come, we come, we come, we come let's take in a couple minutes to adjust to the accent, get into the vibe but it's an excellent song, DVA featuring Black The Ripper wake up there is also a YouTube video which is outstanding.
This is coming from the London Underground, which I was brought to my attention.
It's actually a damn good documentary about London pirate radio.
It's about 15 minutes.
I'll make sure I put a link to it in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Crosspostsuititcurry.com.
It's really quite a vibe going on.
And although I think that a lot, you know, in the UK, get my nation east as we say,
people still really listen to the radio or the wireless.
And of course, there's a lot of bull crap on.
But in London, there is an, there must be 70 or 80 pirate stations at any given time with a limited reach.
And they've gotten quite creative.
And, you know, people still listen to a lot of radio in their cars.
And I think that that, they're kind of on the way of that we're going to get to.
It'll probably happen in the United States earlier where we've got all kinds of streaming audio
in our cars.
And I can't believe I did that.
I closed the mic to burp.
Ah, what a sense.
I missed a good sense.
A moment.
Yeah, there's, uh, it's pretty clear to me.
And to John C. Devoreck as well, that this is where it's headed.
And we're going to have thousands of micro radio stations with varying degrees of audience.
And it's all going to be streamed live.
And I think that, uh, except for China, grove and party.
Well, you know, me, I, I just can't not play some of the older non-pod safe tunes.
But we do have a lot of really good ones that were sent to me that, uh, that without a doubt,
are, uh, our pod safe.
Last night, uh, Mickey and I did something rather, uh, I would say American.
Now, of course, I'm, if anything, I feel like I'm a jersey boy.
And, uh, I remember very well moving into, uh, Montclair New Jersey, uh, technically
for Rona New Jersey, actually.
And I remember the neighbor came over, you know, the kind of the day after we moved in.
And how do you name her?
How are you doing?
And it's so important to have a good relationship with your neighbors.
Now, we're in a very interesting neighborhood up here in the Hollywood Hills.
Uh, it's not a gated community, but, um, you know, without a doubt, it's quiet.
And I said, you know, we really should just go over, uh, uh, let's just go one house at a time,
let's, you know, and because no one had said anything.
And I had the feeling that there were some weird stuff going on in this house,
which we're renting, but I think we're probably going to stay here for a long time,
because it's really, it's a phenomenal place, uh, it's within budget.
And it's, it's just exactly the kind of place we want.
Not huge, but, you know, two bedrooms, which is great, because we have a bedroom, the mommy and daddy room.
And then we have, uh, and Mickey's closet, which used to be a bedroom.
We had closet world come over and, and make it into like one of those sex in the city,
closets that chicks love.
Anyway, so let's just go over. So like, quarter to eight, you know, we go across the way, just ring the doorbell.
And, uh, nice guy opens up and they say, hi, we're Adam and Mickey,
where your neighbors, we just want to say hi, and they just introduce ourselves.
And he's like, oh, come on in. And so this is Don, who, uh, who looks, you know, not a day over,
I'd say 50, but he actually turns out to be 60.
And, uh, his partner, Jim, who was about the same age, and, you know, just typical,
great California gay guys, you know, immediately bringing out the white wine, they've got the nice
war holes in the house. But the cool thing was, we got a real rundown about the neighborhood
and what's going on. And, uh, who's who, and who not even to bother with, you know, they were
coaching big time. So here's what I learned. First of all, up the street is, uh, one of the, uh,
probably one of the, uh, lesser known and poorer Kardashians, but apparently it's not all that too bad.
There's not not too much ruckus from the, the Kardashian up the street. John legend lives right
down the street, which is cool. So I, uh, can't wait to go trick her treating and go around his place.
But most importantly, we learned a lot about this house. And, uh, my, uh, my hunch was right,
as there was kind of a weird guy in here, because I'm still getting mail from, you know, different
weird movie companies that, you know, like big deal pictures and, uh, oh, there's been a repo
man or two stop by looking to repossess the Bentley. And so I'm like, so tell me about the guy
who was here. Well, turns out this house, and I have to do my research, and you know, I will,
has been used quite a bit by vivid entertainment.
First take of a revolution son. Oh, yes. We're living in the porn palace, well known from many
interesting feature films listed a lot. This is the question that I want to ask you. I've
you heard the common color disaster. Yeah, it's clean, the troll coming in faster. Now for the reason
that it's telling you, it did the feeling that they want to troll us. We've been seeing the only
photos, they keep in secret, saying they're gunning for more trust. Don't sing right,
it ain't what to do to the rave, uh, new Johnson. It's shining down on everyone, shining down on
every phone, to the rave, uh, new Johnson, shining down on everyone, shining down on
every phone. Yeah, it's clean, the end is coming faster. What would you do on the morning after?
We got a fire that puts you calling those bastards, why do you curse us when it isn't for
the rave, for the new Johnson. It's shining down on everyone, shining down on everyone,
hmm, don't you say, isn't it, don't sin that, if anything, you're awesome, let me
go, I'm on the clouds, don't you say, isn't it, don't sin that, do we need more, we need more
true soldiers on the ground, rave, uh, new, rave, uh, new, rave, uh, new, rave, uh, new, rave,
rave, new, rave, new, rave, new, rave, new, rave, new, rave, new, rave, new on the sun.
Oh yeah, it's clear the end is coming faster.
What would you do on the morning after?
We got to find the books you call when we're just bastards, what do you curse when it isn't
true?
Oh yeah, we all are a bit of revolutions son, I believe that's how do you pronounce
it?
Love that song, and you'll see more of the revolution taking place, stream live, not just at
no agenda stream.com, but there will be many more I can just feel it.
Now sometimes I'm five years ahead of my time, but you know, it'll all catch up eventually.
So anyway, just back to the porn palace, I'm so chaffed.
I'm so happy about this, I told Mickey, I gotta do some research.
I have to find, apparently not just one or two, but quite a few movies I've been
made here.
And when I find them, I will proudly publish them so you can go and take a look at what
the hilltop watch tower looks like.
So anyway, so today is a big day, the Apple iPad has been released, and I wrote a blog
post, which is at meviotech.mevio.com.
We have kind of a cool system now, we're trying to get the whole, actually it's not
even, we don't have to put much effort into it, getting the whole company blogging,
working on, you know, just stuff for all of our channels, and everyone's really into it,
which I like.
And so I sat down and I wrote maybe a, maybe just a tad too long for a blog post, it was
somewhere in between an essay and a blog post about the iPad, my feelings about it.
And, you know, I am far from an Apple fanboy, but I totally love the Mac products and
have used them for 25 years.
And I do believe that the iPad is going to be quite a game changer and not just a gigantic
iPod touch or an iPhone without a phone.
And I'll of course I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourceco.com so you can read
that blog post.
But I really was convinced, you know, I've been working on an iPhone app, which I'm going
to wait a couple of weeks to release just until the initial iPad noise dies down a bit.
Although now the app that I've made, I will also have to make a version for the iPad.
And it actually, it'll be, although the same completely different.
And I just don't want to tell you what it is yet because when you see it, when you see
this app running on the iPhone, you're going to go, oh, of course, I can't believe no
one did that.
It's going to be free, by the way, so there's no business model behind it, but it does
fit very much in line with what I do and who I am if that gives you any clue.
So it is video heavy.
And one of the reasons why I'd really like what Apple is doing is, you know, I became a developer,
I pay by nine to nine dollars, I downloaded the SDK and it's, I was quite amazed, you know,
but what they do with X code, which is their development environment, is, you know,
you fired up and if you can kind of get over the initial shock of a lot of stuff going
on here, you find now that you can actually create an iPhone app very quickly, even
one that just says hello world and it will work, you know, so they give you like a great
experience out of the box and you have a little emulator, but you can also put it onto your
iPhone and which is, by the way, it's pretty damn cool, you know, you don't necessarily
have to go through the iTunes store approval process to develop software that you just
want to use on your own device.
I mean, you can put it on your own iPhone, you don't have to release it necessarily, excuse
me.
And there's a couple of apps that I want to develop.
Here's an example of one.
I want to have an app that just checks my followers on Twitter and whenever there's a link
that's included that I like, it will immediately file it for me in the right place through
a number of of steps that I now go through manually.
And of course, I've pretty much learned that the best way to use a computer is to tell
it what to do and take away those repetitive steps that you find yourself doing all the
time.
For instance, if I find something, I use simply tweet, you know, I click the link, the browser
fires up.
Oh, I want to save that.
So then I have to email it, I have to email it with a certain code, which then I have
to set up a filter for, sort of goes into the right mailbox, I mean, it's just a whole bunch
of steps I have to do, which you know, the iPhone app that I'll develop for myself will
make that much easier.
But I'm getting off the point here.
So in order to go through the iPhone approval process, you have to adhere to the human interface
design, what is the actual term, human design guidelines, I think, is what it is,
or human interaction guidelines.
And I think you can deviate a little bit, but in general, that's some really smart stuff.
It's like, okay, here's what people are expecting.
We've done all the research, you know, your mileage may vary, but just, you know, if
you kind of make it work like this, when you're doing certain things with, you know, here's
what people expect from a list, here's what people expect from a button, here's what people
expect to see when there's no internet connection, just all these very basic things, then
you'll get it approved.
For video, though, if you want the video to actually work on a 3G network, or as they say
cellular, because of course, you could be in a bad spot, you could have edge only, there's
a number of things that can go wrong, they ask you to adhere to the following, no more
than 10 minutes of video, which is okay, because my, although video heavy, nothing is 10 minutes
long, and no more than five megabytes in a five minute period.
Now, most of my videos are around eight megs at nice quality, and it's imperative to my app
that it has really good quality, you know, at least, so it's not fuzzy or blocky or, or really
to compress. So I have a choice to make, either, I scale stuff down and have really been messing
with the settings, you know, dropping the frame rate just a little bit, using different type
of compression settings, I can get most of it around five megs, but of course, each video,
varies and length, and so that's going to be a bit of a challenge, or, and this is what's interesting,
or you have to go to the HTTP live streaming protocol, which means you basically serve up the
equivalent of an M3U file, and then the device will actually say, okay, how much bandwidth do I have
available right now? I'll take the high bandwidth version, the medium bandwidth version, or,
and this is kind of the unfortunate part. You are obliged, if you're using the HTTP live streaming
protocol, to at least have 164 kilobit, this is what I'm streaming the audio on here today.
So imagine how that's going to be a video 164 kilobit stream, which is total crap,
and will not work at all. So although Apple is absolutely right, you're not entirely for the
application that I've been working on. So I guess what I'm going to try and do is whittle everything
down to around the five megabyte size, yeah, five megabytes in size, and probably trying
fits with some of the later videos that don't show up immediately, and hope I kind of slip
through the approval process, because I just shutter at the thought of your iPhone deciding that you
should have the 64 kilobit video version, which will be crap. They even say, you know, if you can't
get the quality all right, then you should probably just do an audio stream with a picture,
and like, now that's not going to work. So all kinds of challenges, but I think they are the
challenges put in place by Apple for the right reason, and just going through this and the
newer SDK for iPhone OS 3.2, I think it is. I'm getting really nerdy, I can't believe that.
Which is essentially applicable to the iPad. I think they're going to have some amazing things.
Actually, I was having a nice little Twitter chat with Angie B, who had read my column, and I personally
can't wait to manipulate things with my fingers. Angie, if you know what I'm talking about.
Wait a minute, so sorry, didn't mean to do that one, meant to hit this one.
Here we go.
Now, not that one either. I need something to wake up by. Yeah, come on. That's rocket.
Ha, almost forgot it was Friday, I've been talking so much. Wake up everybody.
It's your full-bar Friday, your new mission, 825.
It's your new mission.
And I said, I'm going to work, sleeping in your room.
The power was so close, there was just a bit so far.
Well, what am I to believe in? I was thinking if they were going to stand out.
That's what I guess was just an outcome of what I did.
Here's the girl, last night's the white daylight.
But what arms are ever? I try to keep forgetting what I did tonight before.
But I can't stop regretting that I slept with her before.
But I tried to share my sorrow with a bottle of booze.
Gotta get rid of yesterday's news.
There can't stop leaving nothing at all.
Yeah, why am I to stand out? Oh, why did I kiss that girl last night?
Well, the white daylight. But what arms are ever?
Yeah, why am I to stand out?
But what arms are ever?
Just a girl, last night's the white daylight.
But what arms are ever? Yeah, why am I to stand out?
Yeah, why am I to stand out?
We're special thanks to Mike UC from UC Radio, UC Radio, PodShow, UCRadioPodShow.com for sending
me a couple of tracks for the footballer Friday.
I really love that the Erotic's kids that grow and he's 71 more that I do want to share
with you.
Of course, the links to all these tracks in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Hit it, boys!
End of a raster!
Baby, baby!
Let's take a sincere red and I don't want to taste it all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
baby baby baby
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I like it
yeah it yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah nothing
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
What I don't promise you I'll drown you crazy
I'll fight it all
Tell me just what you do
What you do
I promise you
You won't
Make it all
Love me
There's no way
Oh
Oh yes
Nothing like a big sound from Vegas
And never after
Find them at myspace.com slash and never after
They might as way be one might as well be an L.A. here
This is awesome
Perfect for the football
Nice
Thanks again to Mike UC for setting those tracks over
Time in the show now where
I tell you how you can support this program
And the entire endeavor of no agenda stream.com
Which
John C. Devouric and I are really building up
We're putting a lot of effort into it
He's actually working on a couple of interviews
With some people who are interesting
That you would never hear more than a sound bite from
If that
In the mainstream media
We've got his devouric horror
It's unplugged
We've got some music shows of
Well of course take example here of the
The Daily Source Code
Which is kind of music talk
We've got his interludes and of course no agenda
If you want to support this
Then we would highly appreciate you making a donation
You can go to devouric.org slash n-a-s
November alpha Sierra
And we'll put you up as a sustaining producer
On the page there at no agenda stream.com
That said
We've traditionally had a form of business model
Here on the source code which has been
Essentially codes, marketing codes
For great discounts
Now
I definitely want to support me
Because let's face it
It's my company
There's like some people working there
Who would like to stay employed
And I'd like to share the opportunity
Because I'll make no money
Certainly not directly
From what I'm about to talk to you about
But I've been talking a lot about
Sis admins and network admins
And I have a feeling that there's a lot of you out there
Who would wow
That's a big one
Another black hawk
I have a feeling that a lot of you
Probably wouldn't mind making some extra cash
And I've got to I want to start off with five
Five Sis admins or network admins
If you want to make some extra money
I've got an idea
So please email me adamantcurry.com
Or perhaps adamantmyvio.com
Curry.com sometimes gets a little clogged up
Still although I've blown out most of the spam wattage
Put in the subject line
DSC Sis opportunity
And I'll get in touch with you
It's a very interesting way to get some extra cash
Which of course you can turn right around
And donate to no agenda stream for all I care
Or just keep it for your own hookers and blow
It's fine whatever you want to do
Now speaking of money
This morning I was watching my favorite morning television station
Yes, I do watch television mainly to find out
What drivel is being fed to us
But there's a station here in Los Angeles
Local station called KTLA
And they have kind of like a morning show
And the reason I watch it is because they always have happy news
They've got some happy going on
It's not all depressing
And there's some puppies born
And it's kind of funny
I like that
Just give me something like drively
And smiley in the morning
I also know
Michaela who I think is one of the anchors of that show
She used to be, I think I'm tech TV
In the evening on KTLA
There's
I know people from the station I've been on the show
That's unbelievable
What is going on?
Look guys, I'm not even
No agenda time, no need to fly around
So I'm watching this show this morning
And I forget the name of the actress who comes on
Let me see if I can find it here on the website
Gosh, what was her name?
Hold on a second
You would expect it to be
It was beautiful
How typical was that of me?
Not to remember her name
Anyway
Her whole pitch was to help the people in Haiti
Now if you've listened to No Agenda
Then you know that I believe this is a total
Hostile takeover of the country
We've got the Clintons in there
There's $11 billion being invested
By the United Nations and the World Bank and private investors
Essentially to turn the country into a tax haven
A casino paradise
I'm sure there's going to be a Bill Clinton Avenue
With lots of tall buildings named after him in the Hillary
And it's their scumbags, all of them
Just totally raping this country
And so you think that you donated money to
ClintonBush for Haiti.org
Well, no such organization exists
That money is shuddle directly through to the William Jefferson Clinton
William Jefferson Clinton Foundation
And George Bush's Texas Foundation
Which has like $800 million in cash
And stocks and bonds
They make all kinds of money
Off of your money
And they've been doming out the money
Clinton by his own admission
Ray is like 14 million that came in
He's only dished out 3 million to a whole bunch of other organizations
So basically it's crap
They're stealing your money
Not giving it to Haitians
And all I see on TV if you see it
You can certainly get the reports
People don't even have tents yet
It's like oh yeah
It's red tape and bull crap
They don't give a shit
They want these people to die
They want them out of the way
Like just bulldozeem
So this is a home in Haiti.org
Again, a home in Haiti.org
Which is a really good idea
Which I like a lot is buy a tent
And then this organization will make sure that it actually gets to them
Now if you look at the website
We'll see how they do it
And they actually you don't buy a tent from them
They have links to tents on amazon.com
And they give you the shipping address
Which is I believe in Atlanta
And from Atlanta they take them over to Florida
From Florida they basically have to sneak them into Haiti
And this is what these people really need
Hey, babe
This is what these people really really need
If you see they still got like sheets
And crap strung up
And there's hundreds of thousands of people homeless
And none of this money is getting to them
We have 20,000 troops on the streets in Haiti
It's a total scam
Total scam
It just pisses me off to no end
So angry about what happened here
And we've been on it the whole time
I know agenda
Just tell you this is a rip off
One devourack was a quick-to-paray me agrees
So take a look at what these guys are doing
And by a tent
And Mickey by the way we bought a bungalow tent
Yeah
Not for us
No for the people of someone in Haiti
It's for us
What?
I'll take you camping in Haiti
It could be fun
If we bought a bungalow tent
So please consider buying a tent
It's a great idea
I really like this
They also have a Twitter account
At home in Haiti
So it's at at home
At a home in Haiti
And it's www.ahomein Haiti.org
And I will also mention this
I know agenda
Which I'm sure by now has a much bigger audience
than daily source code
I should actually look at the stats
It's nice to see that
I think there was an immediate 25,000 downloads of the show
When the first one came back
I haven't looked since then
Because I really don't care
It's the people who show up who I care about
That's really what it's all about
So get those guys a look
I think they're doing a pretty good job
One more track before we go and
Turn me home
I find the frequency
It isn't what you need
It's what you have
Less than everyone
And understand
And we want to fade to away
In a power dodge
See their laughs again
And other grunts
Staying
You stay on the phone
Into my eyes
Staying in the air
You're in your eyes
It isn't how you're seen
And people's eyes
This is the spirit of our times
We've all gathered key
To a better life
To get it open to your sight
You're in your eyes
Staying in the air
You're in your life
From it to my eyes
Staying in the air
You're in your eyes
See their laughs again
Staying in the air
You're in your eyes
Jeremy Roe
I find a frequency
Repping up
Charlie 825
Super Friday Edition
Thank you everybody
No agenda chat.com for 200 news
Well it's no agenda stream.com
All the show notes and daily source code.com
Until we speak again
Which of course will be Sunday for the no agenda early morning service
And Wednesday for another Charlie as far as I can plan it until then
Leave your life with passion
And while it lasts
Enjoy your freedom
Another fine, medium presentation
Stick it in your ear