Delta share Charlie eight six four. It is April 26, 2012. I am drunk. And a perfect
time to restart the daily source code. Let me just explain for a moment. I was watching
American Idol. And they were playing songs from Queen. And regardless of whether these people
can sing or not, the fact that they take a six minute song like Bohemian Rhapsody and cut
that down to a minute and 15 seconds with some douche baggets singing it hurt me so much. And
I miss Freddie Mercury so much. I miss so many people so much for the great music they gave
us that you don't hear on the radio anymore. That is not respected. That I just wrote
down a list of 10 or 12 songs. And I figured I got to play them for you.
I was never there. You were the saddest Joe. And I did it to your goal. So if you come see me remember me
and I knew you were. You said you were bad, but I guess we were in 1991.
I'm looking for a beautiful, I'm looking for a ride, I'm looking for a body, I'm looking for a
side, I'm looking for the trees and that I'm going 65. Beware of the selfish Joe.
I'm looking for a ride, I'm looking for a ride, I'm looking for a ride, I'm looking for a ride,
I'm looking for a ride, I'm looking for a ride, I'm looking for a ride,
Now, granted David Bowie is not dead, but he's so buffed as an entire capital.
And he's not made a decent song since, so that is one of the people that I really really miss and want to share with you as I go down my list here of songs and what I'm doing literally is downloading things from Amazon's MP3 as we go along and I'll put all of these in the show notes at what's at dsc864.curry.com, new show notes for the show.
Just going to restart this program. I don't care if they send me to jail for playing licensed music because I just realize the future, the current state of the music industry is the voice American idol, all of these programs.
And I have to say, although I don't mind the voice because we got some good singers, they're raping the music. They're really, really raping it. It's not okay.
We need to hear these songs. And I miss Freddie Mercury so incredibly much. I remember when I heard when he was sick, he was supposed to come on my show and do an interview and it's not going to happen.
And by the way, it's never going to have a sworn to secrecy. It wasn't about to say anything and I had to keep that secret for like a year and a half. It's horrible.
And I grew up listening to Queen and I want to play a couple of tracks from Queen. I got a lot of other stuff on my list from people. I really, really, really miss. And this is just one that you don't hear enough of anymore.
I want to write it where I like.
I say white, I say white, I say sharp, I say him, and yours was never my scene and I don't like Star Wars.
I say wrong, say right, say God give me a choice.
I say no, I say Christ, I don't believe in Peter, but I can stand a Superman.
I want to write my bike, I want to write my bike, I want to write my bicycle.
I'm sick of races, I'll come in your way, so forget all your days all year now.
I want to learn how to feel, be running today, so look out for those beauties all year.
I want to learn how to feel, be running today, so forget all your days all year now.
was probably one of the funnest video clips never shown on American TV, a whole bunch
of beautiful girls riding on 10-speed bicycles completely naked.
Of course I was in Europe at the time that this was, actually, well, I think it was a hit
at the time, a screen with bicycle race, one more from the unbelievable, Freddie Mercury,
actually, only about six weeks after he passed, I was in Portugal, excuse me.
As I was doing a television show, which also was broadcast in Portugal, and Roger Taylor
and Brian May were in the same hotel that I was staying and I sat down with him, and these
guys were fucking destroyed, and as was everybody in the music industry, because
Freddie Mercury was such an incredible, beautiful talent, such a shy, beautiful man, and
I just want to honor him with one of my favorite queen songs of all time.
So it was time, it made up his mind to leave his dead life behind, his boss fractured him
while you'd been a big kid, to get those crazy notion, right out of your hand, Freddie
Mercury, do you think that you are, you should have escaped there, I'll keep it for a while.
We're in your wings and try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away
try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away, try away,
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Since he was small, had no luck at all.
Nothing can be as easy as you will
Now it was time
He made up his mind
This could be my last chance
His arms are set to hand
Now listen, boy
You're always dreaming
You've got no real ambition
You won't get away from all
Every bird that you live with
You are
Why can't you be happy
Have to have a roof off
To hold his friends always
And fly away
Fly away
Spread your little wings
Go in and swim together
You know they're so stupid
Let's be close your free man
Come on, girl
Come on
I was singing a long, very, very loudly where that song has funny how you remember
some of these lyrics that just stick in your head, but even though I've had almost an
entire bottle of wine, as Miss Mickey and I just decided to kind of let loose. Although I kind
of let loose, she didn't let loose so much and I was just watching this bull crap on American
handle. And I got to do a daily source code. She said, go, go, go, right now, shall I pour
you another wine? She understands so much, doesn't she? All right, so here's another guy that
I miss very, very much. And this is just the theme. I have no idea what's going to happen
in the daily source code, but I actually, here's a little secret. I recorded a daily source code,
I recorded 864 yesterday. And it was pretty much a non-musical show. Although I did have a theme
about radio and I was talking about the state of podcasting. And after I was done with it, I was like,
this is done releaseable. I just don't like what I did. I like so much the vein that I was in with,
you know, I'd add the three hour music extra vegans is a little bit too much, just physically.
It's too much for me to do and you get into it. You start repeating songs very quickly
from week to week if you're doing three hours worth. And I really just want to go based upon
feeling and convey something. And I know a lot of people are waiting for a new show. So I hope that
you take this with a little grain of salt since, as I said, it's completely based upon just
emotions of the moment needing to just play some songs really loudly, songs that I love from
people that I miss. And here's a guy that I work with many, many times throughout the years in
Montros, Switzerland where he lived. He was on my show, many times I've interviewed him a lovely
guy his name is Robert Palmer. I'm going to play two songs for you. This one never gets played.
But it is one of his prettiest, every kind of people on the source code.
Make what lives about it. Every kind of people make the world go down.
Sometimes looking for a leap in his duty to a king or two of me, protecting what he feels is right.
Fight against one with his life. There's no profit in this seat.
On a smith or that revenge doesn't not disappear.
Whether he yellow black or white, each and every man's the same inside.
Who takes every kind of people to make what lives about it.
It takes every kind of people to make the world go down.
And the new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new
new, kind, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new
takes every kind of people. By the way, we are now streaming live at no agenda stream.com.
Thank you very much. I get most laid for plug-in. I hope I didn't pre-empt anybody on the stream.
But for those of you just joining us, I'm drunk, which is saying a lot for me. That's like
three quarters of bottle of wine and I'll just catch up to speed for those of you just joining us.
Those of you listening to the podcast you already know that I was watching a recorded American
Idol and they were doing Queen songs and it just made me so angry that these great artists,
these great songs, these great musicians who I love so much and who I miss so much,
being raped in a minute and 15 seconds and whether these people are talented or not,
it doesn't matter. I just, I, I felt like I had to play some songs really,
really loudly. Songs that I love, people that I love, that I miss very, very much.
So you missed the Queen songs if you're just joining us now, but that'll be on the podcast.
One more song by Robert Palmer, who passed away. I don't know. What is it? 9 or 10 years ago now?
Another one you'll never hear on the radio.
Dr. Dr. Give me the news.
Got a bad case of loving you.
I need you to suit my head. Turn my blue heart to head.
Dr. Dr. Give me the news. I got a bad case of loving you.
No feel's gonna kill me. I got a bad case of loving you.
A pretty face, don't make no pretty heart.
I learned that, but if I'm gonna start,
you think I'm cute. A little bit shy, Mama, I ain't that kind of guy.
Dr. Dr. Give me the news. I got a bad case of loving you.
No feel's gonna kill me. I got a bad case of loving you.
Wow.
I know you like it. You like it all the time.
Tell me, Mama, but you don't stop.
Let me down. I'll twist my love to you.
Oh, it's on your lips. Shake my face.
Rock, roll. I'm got a bad bad. I'm a guy in tune.
Dr. Dr. Give me the news. I've got a bad case of loving you.
No feel's gonna kill me. I got a bad case of loving you.
Robert Palmer, Dr. Dr. Give me the news. I got a bad case of loving you.
I'm playing songs here on Daily Source Code 864 playing songs for people who have passed away.
Who I miss so much and you just don't hear enough of them anymore.
And when I hear their songs being raped on television by these fucking reality shows,
we need to hear a original stuff, you know?
I'm playing songs here on Daily Source Code 864 playing songs for people who have passed away.
All over the country, I've seen it the same. Nobody's wearing it.
I just got a game. We gotta do better. Let's try to be in it.
You know all the answers, let's go from it and throw it in.
Come on, it's taking three right, three right. Come on, it's taking three right.
Come on, it's taking three right.
Come on, it's taking three right. Come on, it's taking three right.
Not a lot of people know that is Dan Hartman playing the fretless bass with Edgar
Winter.
Come on, take a free ride.
Another guy in this so much, aides to him, man.
And in 1980, I'm going to say 1984, I was invited by Dan Hartman to come to America and
hang out in the state of his house up in Connecticut at the time he was working with
a Dutch band, the time bandits with a lead just hitting, and he had a studio at home.
And it was just such an awesome guy.
He had all these crazy tapes that he would play in the middle of the night.
He had like unedited print tapes and he was like freaking out about how good it was.
And by the way, when I was listening to it, I was freaking out too.
And then later in 87, when I moved to New York for a to work for MTV, he would come by and
we hang out and it was just an awesome, awesome guy.
And of course, everyone knows a lot of his, I'll play, I can dream about you.
I'll play that one in a minute, let me just write that down.
But this is one of my all-time favorites with the winter brothers.
So although I'm playing songs from the people I really miss, not everyone is dead.
I played David Bowie earlier.
He's not dead, but he might as well be, because he sold his entire music catalog
for $50 million in the mid 90s.
I can't blame him for doing that, but he never really has done anything again.
And I miss him.
I miss songs like this.
I'm your source code.
Small jeans, you miss my cough.
I'm sitting, strong out of lasers.
Slash back blazes.
Ain't all your lasers while pulling the waders.
Talking about non-roll.
You're can't slow at.
New York's a goal goal and everything tastes nice.
Fall in a green head.
Can't you get back off?
.</
You viennent me.
Ooh there's all these bad.
The gentle about chin is that it's the sweetest schemes he pour.
But you cheated me, let your song go.
Cool.
It's like a man, but smiles like a reptile to love him, she love him, but just for short
while scratching the sand, let go his hands, he sets these a new dish, sells you nutrition, keeps
all your dead health, making up underwear, all your greenies, the ginger, the lips on his back, the
ginger, the lips on his back, the ginger, the lips on his back, the ginger, the lips on his
back, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth
the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth. The mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth, mouth, the mouth, the mouth, the mouth
I'm trying to remember the codes to send up the bat signal and I'm pretty sure I
thought to it.
They've bowed in the gene gene I've never seen him in like 1984 and Rotterdam.
My first real big concert, well maybe it was all inosis, my first big concert, but I remember
seeing David Bowen just being like, holy fuck would just happen to me.
I can't believe what I'm seeing, and we never see the guy anymore.
Where do you hear songs like this?
Thanks to Mitt Romney's company, Bain Capital, Cleared Channel, has rolled everything
up in America to mindless pieces of crap music radio.
Total fucking shit, we're all we want to do is just place a chance, it really means something
you know what I'm saying?
Alright, here's that song by Dan Hartman, I was talking about.
The best lyrics ever written as far as I'm concerned.
Video kind of suck, but then again, I can dream about you.
No more time, we each hear the thoughts of our minds.
I know, I need the remedy to cure this all over life.
I can dream about you.
If I can't help you, I can dream about you.
You know how to hold me just like.
I can dream about you.
If I can't hold it tonight.
You know how to hold me just like.
Move inside the door.
I don't see you in the past.
I can climb in all the front.
Down here below where the street takes me lonely for you.
No, I can dream about you.
If I can't hold it tonight.
I can dream about you.
You know how to hold me just like.
I don't know how to hold it tonight.
Move inside the door.
I don't see you in the past.
I can dream about you.
You know how to hold me just like.
Move inside the door.
I don't understand it.
Can't dream about mine.
I don't know how to hold it tonight.
You know how to hold it tonight.
I can dream about you.
You know how to hold me just like.