Delta Sherry Charlie 865. I've got the post idol blues
They are with the love that in your eyes
The prick is a fun down your arms are open wide
Am I in too deep or should I swim to the shore?
Is this the real thing I don't know?
I've never been here before
I feel under in my heart
But I just can't control
And I walk away
I follow my soul
I feel under in my heart
And when it comes from I just don't know
Oh no
There's a star raging
They've been my soul
As I have it when that I just can control
As far as the side may I can't explain
Every time you touch me, my love goes up high
I've only known you for an hour or more
In the time of standing still, you'll never know
When I'm the star
I feel under in my heart
And I take my breath away
But I just can't control
I feel under in my heart
And I feel under in my heart
So I'm pretty cool
Oh...
There's a star raging
Yeah there's a star raging
Oh...
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Take me baby, I'm all yours
Don't guess what you wanted to do with my love
Yes, not let the night off and take us
Cause what's happening right now, man
Make a break us, just feel the way I do
Open up your heart now, baby, I'm coming through
I've been in my heart, I'm taking my breath away
I'm feeling far in my heart
It's a magic never been the same
That's right, it's exactly how I feel
Like I'm from the rear of my heart
Once again, we watched the DVR recording of American Idol
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, so many songs, I just like, you know, I need something I'm lifting
I need to play some real music
To music that I remember, songs that you can groove to
I got a whole emotional journey for you on this Thursday night
Coming to you from Camp Mofo here in Austin, Tayhouse
Capital of the drone star state
My name's Adam Curry, this is your daily source code
The Delta Sheriff Charlie, off to a rocky start
Nothing with the Jack Daniels can't fix
First on the tap on the old nagging there
Make sure it's still made of the same material
I'm good
If I do, I would show it
Showing you that light
Cause you love me
Then in the light I know
It's like thunder, lightning
So when you love me, it's bright now
Yeah, I love you, now
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm not super strange, it's like a little strange
Uh, I can take no train
Yeah, I begs me for your life
You're moving on middle train
Club your love
You're better
And in the land I know
It's like thunder and lightning
The way that I'm in front of you
You're mad at me, you're mad at me
Oh, baby
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Baby
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Baby, I'm shot by comfort
Ooh, baby
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, free bed, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-
-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
Since the last time we smoke here on the daily source code, which was, there was it two weeks ago.
We've had more people die.
It's just like, we lost a Beastie boy.
We lost Donna Summer, we lost us.
It's like, if this is part of getting all of this, what it means?
Is this what it comes down to?
We're gonna honor some of those folks tonight.
I've just played a couple songs and never here on the radio anymore,
because I guess they're too cool to be played.
You choose pride of the name Malaway and a daily source code.
We're gonna come and the name of our own.
We're gonna come and our own.
We're gonna come and teach us this song.
We're gonna come and we're gonna come and our own.
We're gonna come and our own.
One man lost, one empty face, one man lost, one empty face, one man lost, one empty face, one empty face.
Kill the angel, one man lost, one empty face, and one man lost, one empty face, one empty face.
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
and see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, this ass段 underway, see you in five, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you on the next video, take care, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you guys in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, so see you in the next video,!!
All right everybody crank that just a little bit we're going to get you ready for the rock and roll for your day
All right everybody crank that just a little bit we're going to get you ready for the rock and roll
Good to see everybody there tuning in live on the stream
Of course predominantly this admins are on this time a night
How you doing
Let's get it. Just take those old records home
I've been listening to him by myself
Today's music ain't got the same song
I got all time on rock and roll
Don't try to take me to a disco
You'll never even get the out of the
It didn't mean it found it live for the go
I got all time on rock and roll
Just in my little time on rock and roll
They kind of music just suits the song
I've been listening to about the days of hope
With that all time on rock and roll
I will miss the back of the days of both
We've had our whole time in Rockin' Roll
Still like that old time in Rockin' Roll
Oh yeah
That kind of music just suits us all
I will miss the back of the days of both
With that old time in Rockin' Roll
I still like that old time in Rockin' Roll
That kind of music just suits us all
I will miss the back of the days of both
With that old time in Rockin' Roll
Still like that old time in Rockin' Roll
Bob is eager to silver bullet band
Old time in Rockin' Roll
That takes me back to 1980
I think it must have been 1981
I was at Salem College in Salem, West Virginia
Playin' that on WITB
Which was an unbelievable ten watts of FM power
Blasting out to all of Salem, West Virginia
And if I remember correctly WITB stood for
Either we're in the basement or we're in to bomb hits
One or the other
But we were actually in to both by the way
Yes, listen, listen, listen, listen
This is your daily source code episode 865
Come on you
From Austin, Tayhouse, the capital of the grown star states
My name's Adam Curry
You're just conjockey on duty
Bringing you an illegal program
And you must repeat this at a three from your player
After done, otherwise I might get arrested
1957, Yohan Holtz was born in Vienna, Austria
1963, the young child was referred to as a new Mozart
1977, his alter ego takes control
Yohan is now a thousand
1982, Falcos forces first international hit
1984, with release of Yohan Roma, Falcos star
Has followed
1985, starting a new Falcos signs where manager Horst Bork
Bork introduces him to Dutch producers, Ballon Bork
Later, that's same here
They create the world white hits
The world's all video is in itself, larger than life
The world's all video, larger than life
is now a distant memory.
February 6, 1998, Dominican Republic,
exhausted after a long and restless night filled with alcohol and cocaine,
Falco awakens alone in his car.
He turns on to a main road,
where an oncoming bus approaches at 100 kilometers per hour.
paternal Chissent
What's wrong?
The sweat people are not dependent on their sauces
They've been banished
There is also our biggestised parkour of the Grand Gly savage Holy Land.
The village to the Stories of the Air configuration and that we do danger for one of the Gates.
Thank you.
I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance,
I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance, I'm gonna dance.
Baby, baby dude, you rock me, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die
Alright.
I got to run it and die!
You lost on Shi's own tree.
Your lost on Shi's one..
Do you have this for a million?
This is the amount that exists in our lives, what humans are doing towards...
Throughout Flood.
So I...
I might lose a million Blockchain.
Hold up, hold up.
Hold up, youre-
Boss,ulsar-
finite
You know, you got to be so careful when your cruise is through the way, you know, you
gotta be so careful when your cruise is through the way, you know, you gotta be so careful
when your cruise is through a Amazon, which is where I get all my MP3's from, which are honestly purchased by the way.
You gotta make sure you get the right versions.
And guarantee you, you've not heard of something fucking jack-a-fam, or Bob Fam, or Peter Fam, or Tom Fam,
because it's eight and a half minutes long. It is Falco, Rocky Amadeus.
Of course, produced by the legendary Dutch producing duo Balm and Malen.
Actually, when I met those guys, hey!
When I met those guys, it was my first introduction to show business.
Their manager at the time was this crazy fucking guy called Fritz Hirschlund.
And he managed Balm and Balm.
They were going to play another track that they wrote.
And I don't know if they produced it, but I know they wrote it.
And they had kind of basically found Falco, the side of the road, picked him up,
did a remix of this Rocky Amadeus, which is where you just heard.
And then many remixes since then.
But this is the first one they did.
And turn the guy into a worldwide sensation.
Almost overnight.
And of course, he eventually died.
I think he died of a heart failure, but I'm sure it was induced by many other things.
You know, someone just said something in the chat room and everybody.
Someone said, needle on the record, or maybe it was a tweet that I saw something.
What was that song?
Put the needle on the record.
And the drum beat goes like this.
What was that song?
If you remember that tell me, would you please?
Because I want to play that one for you.
This is another Balm and Balm track legendary music producers from the Netherlands.
This one performed by status quo.
You're in the army now, bitches.
You're on your way to a foreign land.
Now's the time to do what you can here in the army now.
Oh, oh, oh, you're in the army now.
Now you remember what the draft meant say.
Nothing could do all day but stay in the army now.
Oh, oh, you're in the army now.
You'll be the hero of the neighborhood.
Count the days till you're back.
Oh, you're in the army now.
Oh, oh, you're in the army now.
Smiling faces that you wait to land.
But side by side, it'll be over there.
And that you'll agree now.
Oh, oh, you're in the army now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, no, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Now, you're not too honest, they're put deep inside
Everything is on the table now, it's time to put it here in the lobby now
Now, you're in the lobby now, you're in the lobby now
Now, you're in the lobby now
Now, you're in the lobby now, it's time to put it here in the lobby now
Now, you're in the lobby now, you're in the lobby now
Now, you're in the lobby now, it's time to tell me about Fridge Hirschlund who is the manager
Of Bob and the ball on the road that's song in the state of school living covered you're in the army
I like it when nice to see Chuck Macamon in the chat room
Here's what he says. I remember the song going through my head as I was on patrol in Sarajevo in 1993
That's a connection to my damn her friends
This guy was nuts
He's a huge years old guy
More time
Love this oh
me
now
chilling stuff
haha
Love that
courtesy of Amazon MP3
So this years-long guy
He was a very very colorful person in the music business back in the day he was in the UK
Young out with the Seymour Hersh
of Sire records if that rings a bell and Seymour Hersh of course is actually the person who
originally signed Madonna to Sire records and made her
a household name and
I think I visited him once in the UK
I was maybe 18 or 19. It was really weird because these guy were always hanging around young boys and
I felt a little bit uncomfortable and the Seymour was it not her Seymour Stein
I'm sorry Seymour Stein
and
Went to Seymour Stein's office
and he had a fish tank
and the bottom of the fish tank he had a hundred pound note
but in the fish tank were piranhas
He's like ah go ahead man you go ahead and you just grabbed that hundred pound
I'm like ah I think I'll pass on that
But then years later maybe three, four years later I was working on MTV
I was in New Jersey
I get a call it's fridge, here's London the phone
He's like hey man I'm in Surinam
I'm here with the Rebels with Desi Bautorsa
you should Wikipedia that if you want to know what that is
he says
we need to buy this airplane
to transport some weapons out
and I need fifteen hundred dollars
I said you're calling me
yeah because you can do a Western Union
and like you know this guy I don't know
you know
he's a weird guy he did weird things in the music business
you know what I'm going to send it to you
so I send him fifty hundred bucks through Western Union
and it was maybe four or five years later
one day in the mail
three five hundred dollar Western Union
check show up
which was his repayment
I didn't pay me any interest
but he just he did repay it
and I think maybe two months later he died
he just killed over
and I always felt that that was kind of cool
you know it was kind of like the underground code
whatever this guy was into
I did a masala he did one from me back
and that's how the old boys network works
by the way thank you so much chat room
for helping remember this one
of course it was Mars and pump up the volume
I think I was in tour of these guys at one point
although this was kind of the only song they had to play
I bought the volume
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I don't think it's in this version, but that's totally sucks, I'll just do it for you.
Put the needle on the right and put the needle on the right and it's a drum beat goes like this.
Well, that was a disappointment.
Bars pump up the volume.
I got to tell you, man, I did these shows late at night.
I got the studio lights off.
All I got is the glow of the monitors here in the Camp Mofo and Austin.
And even though I'm moving on 48, moving up towards 50,
it still feels like I'm back at decibel radio.
Back at the pirate radio station, Amsterdam.
In 1980, I'm going to say 1982.
You know, that song was now yet.
That was around the first time that we were introduced to the Beastie Boys.
And of course, we lost Adam this year, just a few weeks ago.
And I was trying to think about some stories.
And although, you know, I did hang out with him in Montro one time during the Montro Rock Festival.
And this was when they were totally, totally out of their minds.
And remember they were wearing the Volkswagen emblems back in the day.
All the the rap guys had Mercedes stars.
They would steal off the Mercedes and they would wear those on chains around their neck.
And the Beastie Boys all said they burst onto the scene.
And they were wearing the Volkswagen emblems from the rip off of a beetle.
And I remember we were in Montro and they actually showed me how to remove the Volkswagen emblems.
Volkswagen emblem from a beetle.
And I think the beetle actually was turned over at one point.
And mine have been lit on fire.
I can't remember that.
But I do remember back before I met them, which I have fond memories of.
This is a song that you will never hear on the radio.
This is the first track that when we heard this for the first time,
we had an import record company in Amsterdam called Atalos Records,
ATT ALOS Atalos.
And they would get all these import crazy vinyl tracks.
And when we heard this, we played the shit out of it.
It was so awesome.
And of course it was the Beastie Boys.
The Beastie Boys.
The Most Littleale Boys.
The Beastie boys.
The Beastie Boys.
The Beasties.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got
And my mother got to call us for dinner tonight
Woo00
Woo
See you
Wow thing, I'm out
Yo, man. Cooky, pussy
Okay, no, nobody here but I
know. oh cookie guess
cookie tonight any boy man. Boy, I was
picked it out
Those cookies
You're serious, I want to talk to your man, cause he goes, all right, let me let me order one then.
Let me get one.
When you want it from any time, man, just like now we should, you know?
This should now, talking now, me.
Just gonna bitch hang up, I think you're ass bitch.
What the hell?
I love the drum fill.
He.
Watch out.
There's a beast.
He's making me it.
Then we weren't tripping balls on that shit, man.
We were like oh my god, I can't believe these guys are so awesome.
Cookie push.
Oh, this is making me itch.
Oh.
Ah, that is the Beastie Boys to me.
Now, this fight for your right stuff.
Yeah, it was great.
Of course it was.
There was nothing like the Cookie Pulse,
which reminds me of another guy
from back in the day.
And don't worry, we're gonna get a whole bunch of other stuff.
I'm just getting started here.
This is blowfly.
And he had the insight, the foresight,
the future vision to know that one day,
we would have a black president of the United States of America.
Ladies and gentlemen,
introduce in the first name,
I'm in the first black president of the United States of America.
Presenting blowfly.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And like I promised you, when I was running.
I'm gonna make sure they are chillins and every pot.
Hell, he hooks and every table.
I control peels and every purse.
And we're gonna have a hard day every motherfuckin' weeky.
Thank you.
Good morning, Mr. President, sir.
Good morning, bitch.
I'm at Ms. Clayk.
This shit's gonna be easy.
President, don't do number seven as I ask all day.
And you're bald as any motherfuckin' way.
It's like getting my hair together here.
Where's my fuckin' cocaine?
But the bitch's unmooted again.
Ms. Clayk.
Mr. President, sir?
You get your ass in here, please.
Right away, sir.
What did you do in my ship?
Are you constipated, sir?
Mitch, you know what I'm talkin' about my motherfuckin' road all.
Hell, I took you down to the bed, sir.
Oh, I'm talkin' about coke, coke-ing.
You know that white paddache that I put on your pussy when I'm getting ready to eat it?
Oh, that, sir.
It's right in front of you, sir.
Thank you. That'll be all.
Stupid bitch.
If I put you in so good, I'd fire up.
Miss, I'd get over here and get my hair together.
Ugh.
And some bitch-it.
Mr. President, sir?
Shit.
What the fuck you want now?
Mr. Jackson is here to see you.
Mr. Jackson.
Reggie Jackson, Andrew Jackson, a macro Jackson.
What, what's one?
Mr. Superfly Jackson, a the United Pimps Association.
What the fuck you want?
He wants the money you promised him for endorsing you.
I told that dumb motherfucker those assholes that Congress got on a phone frozen.
What the fuck you want from my life?
Well, he stated that payment and coke would be sufficient.
Uh, my last coke.
I'm takin' give it to the motherfuckin' get rid of it.
Just in and out shit.
I thought that shit was gon' be easy.
I got it. I got some weed here somewhere.
Here it is.
Room there a couple of joints.
Hmm.
Mr. President, sir?
Shit.
What you want now, Mr. Clay?
Mr. Paul is here to see you, sir.
Mr. Paul.
Paul Newman, Paul Reveal.
Paul Lanker.
Paul John Paul, sir.
John Paul?
What do you want?
And the weed you are currently smoking, sir.
Shit, too.
I just see what name.
I'm not gonna like this motherfuckin' shit at all.
I'll hug you ever to the motherfuckin'.
Can't sniff no coke, can't smoke no dope.
Damn, I know what I do.
Fuck this bitch again.
Miss Clay, would you come in here, please?
Night away, sir.
Come on, oh, you're leaving, pull off your clothes,
which is fire and sound.
I'm down.
I don't wanna hit it shit this morning.
Can't smoke no dope, can't smoke no dope.
Later, later, I can hear all of that shit later.
Shit this shit.
What is the red spots on your stomach?
That's what I was trying to tell you, sir.
What are they?
We see.
I went to the doctor, and he says I have hurt me.
The happys?
I resigned!
Fuckin' hurt me!
Whoa, fly, the first black president!
Oh, yeah, man.
That was the year of the base 1982, it was.
I remember it well.
And right now, a song that I've been, this is really the whole impetus for me doing this source code.
Just had to kind of get into the mood for it.
Because, you know, on the daily source code, we'd like to play songs that you will not hear on the radio.
So, ever again, because it's all been rolled up into one ball of poop.
Thank you.
I mean, Romney and being capital and clear channel sucks.
So, we still get to share stuff here that you just won't hear anywhere else.
So, we lost another great Donna Summer.
I worked with her a couple of times in a couple of shows, not on television shows, but on gigs, I guess.
And she was always, even the early days, she was in Germany.
And she had a huge career.
And in Germany, I don't know if it's still that way, back in the day, man.
You can make so much money.
Because you just keep going on and on forever.
And it was back in those days when she hooked up with Georgio Moroder, the famous producer.
And by the way, one of our producers at the Noah Genesis show, Dave King actually did the baseline for this song.
It was kind of an ode to him at the same time.
And I was even ending back in fourth of me.
He said, you know, I said, hey, man, it's so awesome that you did that baseline.
I said, I hope you got some kind of royalty for it.
Because it's going to get sold a lot now that Donna Summer has passed.
He said, no, I got paid 160 bucks.
And that was it, buy out done.
And Georgio Moroder is probably in his mid 70s now.
And he's probably enjoying the resurrection of the song.
And I'm going to play you the almost 17-minute long version of Love To Love You Baby.
With that awesome baseline that I think is the actual nucleus of the song, the music cure, if you will.
And if you don't mind, I will slip upstairs and pull myself another jack, or we get into the mood with Donna Summer.
When you're laying so close to now, it's the best of luck that you've been with me.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh
oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my Oh, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, wow, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my God, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
We have down your close to me
So the wind and set me free, set me free
He won't come
Oh, I'll turn up your baby
When you wait so close to me, there is no reason
That you wouldn't let me leave me here
Oh, I'll turn up your baby
When you wait so close to me, there is no reason
That you wouldn't let me leave me
Oh, I'll turn up your baby
Thank you very much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, good luck
thing and good luck to see you, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video,
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you for the next video, see you in the next video,
stay with me , the next one, the next one, the next one, if all of you slow you down, this actually
turns out hell fun, you will becharge the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video,
Nice and close, rumbling up against each other.
Now, this is how you pay tribute to someone like Donald Sunder.
I have a little crap that I play in on the radio.
Well, yes, rest in peace.
Fucking Facebook.
Yeah, I got a choice.
After my whole, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, if you hadn't heard it, I had a reasonable,
a conversation about Facebook on this week in tech, uh, Leo Lecourt Show.
And, uh, uh, you know, so, of course, the conversation about this went on and
more people are talking about, and you know, and the other night, if you get any
know what, I'm going to go check out Facebook, see what's on.
The only really thing I ever do on Facebook is they're going to terrorize my daughter's
friends.
Now, call them Fag, which is the definition of cyberbullying.
And, uh, and so, uh, and because I've never on Facebook, I don't get to see anything.
Because Facebook is so incredibly fucking smart that it, uh, then just basically shows
like five friends or something.
And I'm a member of the MTV alumni group.
And as about 98 people and the people who've worked at MTV over the years, so I check in
and the first thing I see is Kevin Gill, a great guy who I work with, uh, I think
878889, um, he started as a floor manager, what will we call that, uh, studio producer,
I guess.
There was some other name for it, and they don't want to become a director, it was a great
guy.
I loved working with him.
There are a lot in the beginning, um, and he died, oh man, really, this is, I'm on Facebook
and all you get is like, this, it's this person's birthday, and that person died.
And then, uh, another one of my buddies there, um, on Facebook, who I used to work with a lot
also from the MTV group, I see him and say, hey, man, how you doing?
He's like, ah, that's a good, I have a lymphoma, like the fuck this Facebook, man, it's
like, nothing, it's nothing but a big fucking downer.
It's all as good for when you're born and when you're dead.
They actually should have a status, this person's dead, you know, be good.
You should be able to change that.
Hey, I'm dead now.
Look, my Facebook profile.
And what happens is it go away, as your profile just expire eventually, and then it's, uh,
all run.
Someone should make a parody, 50 ways to leave my Facebook.
Problem is all inside your head, she said to me, the answer is easy if you take it logically.
I'd like to help you in your struggle to be free, then must be 50 ways to leave her lover.
She said it's really not my habit to untrue.
Furthermore, I hope my meaning won't be lost on this constru, but I'll repeat myself.
At the risk of being cruel, there must be 50 ways to leave your lover.
50 ways to leave your lover.
You just slip out the back, damn.
Make a new plan, stand.
You don't need to be quite wrong.
Just get yourself free.
I'm on the bus, because you don't need to discuss much.
Just drop off the key.
And slip yourself free.
Who's about to back?
Yeah.
Make a new plan, stand.
You don't need to be quite wrong.
You just listen to me.
I'm on the bus, because you don't need to discuss much.
Just drop off the key.
And get yourself free.
She said it grieves me so to see you in such pain.
I wish there was something I could do to make you smile again.
I said I appreciate that.
And would you please explain about the 50 ways?
To leave your Facebook.
She said, why don't we both just sleep on it tonight?
And I believe in the morning.
You begin to see the light.
And then she kissed me.
And I realized your property was right.
And must be 50 ways to leave your lover.
50 ways to leave your lover.
You just slip out the back, damn.
Make a new plan, stand.
You don't need to be quite wrong.
Just pitch yourself free.
Or you hop on the bus, because you don't need to discuss much.
Just drop off the key.
And get yourself free.
Just slip out the back, damn.
Make a new plan, stand.
You don't need to be quite wrong.
You just listen to me.
I'm on the bus, because you don't need to discuss much.
Just drop off the key.
And get yourself free.
So anyway, so people were posting like RIP Kevin.
Like, what are you going to do?
Are you going to post in there?
Oh, yeah, RIP.
It's like, if you post on Facebook that you miss someone,
then it's all good.
And then you feel good.
This is very, very bad.
You know, I'm going to blow that shit up.
I think about how to do that.
We got to blow that shit up.
Anyway, must have been last week, maybe 10 days ago,
there was an awesome rainstorm here in Austin.
And we got rainstorms that bring you thunder and lightning,
like little house on the prairie,
is as you've never seen a storm like this in your life before.
So awesome.
And I immediately went to Amazon started downloading thunder
and lightning and rain songs.
And I was like, ah, they would be so great.
And I waited and waited and waited.
And of course, the weather just got better.
And we just don't get enough rain here.
So what I want to do is I want to play this kind of little set
that I have of rain songs.
And you store this away.
You know, you're going to download.
You've already downloaded this obviously.
Store this show away.
And one of those days,
it's going to be raining.
It's going to be lightning.
It's going to be thunder.
It's going to be just crazy.
And you're going to pull this episode of the daily source code right out
of your MP3 player.
You say, ah, yeah, this is great.
You're going to find your loved one.
You're going to cut it up.
You're going to watch the rain.
And listen to all these songs.
I can't stand the rain.
That I just can't stand, I can't stand the world
Well, with the pins out of hope
When it's time you stay, yeah
I only have that sort of sweet memory
It's like a window, you ain't got nothing to say
I can't stand the rain, it gets my window
Rain, back, swimming, we said
I can't stand the rain
It's my window, oh, oh, oh
Because he's not here with me
I can't stand the rain
It's my window, oh, oh, oh
Because he's not here with me
I can't stand the rain
It's my window, oh, oh, oh
Because he's not here with me
I can't stand the rain, it gets my window
You ain't got nothing to say
I can't stand the rain
That's my window, oh, oh
I'm behind the waves, back in the day
Your kneestorms are made
And we're just talking about rain
You know, thunderstorms and rain
These days, of course, rain stands for the Devil
That's what Rihanna sings about
But that's the whole of their story
If you were for Lehman Bay
So for this guy, man, I love this fucking song.
Oh, Bruno Mars.
There's some more feet out of my door.
It will rain.
Great, too.
Because it would take a whole lot of my dedication.
To realize what we used to have,
We don't have it anymore.
There's no relation that could save me.
No matter how long my knees are on the floor.
Oh, so keep in mind, all the sacrifices I've made.
And we feel by my side.
Keep it from walking up the door.
Because they'll be no side like.
Since I knew you'd be better.
There'll be no face, guys.
If I lose you pain, man.
Because like the clouds, my eyes will do the same.
If you walk away, everything it'll rain.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'll never be your lifeless favorite.
Oh, you daddy, daddy, now look at me in the eye.
Oh, I was in that truth.
I'd be doing the same thing.
See my goals, my little girl.
Walking with that trouble somewhere.
But that just the fight I'm solving.
They get understated.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
You watch me change the mind.
Yeah, but you watch, I try, I try, I try, I try, I try, I try, I try.
I make up this broken pieces, tell me, didn't it?
I don't make a vibe.
You're selling yourself like.
If I lose you pain, man.
They'll be no face, guys.
Because like the clouds, my eyes will do the same.
If you walk away, everything will rain.
If you'll wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, I'm talking to say, go back.
Oh, I'm talking to this broken pieces, tell me, didn't it?
I don't make a vibe.
You're selling yourself like.
If I lose you pain, man.
They'll be no face, guys.
Because like the clouds, my eyes will do the same.
You walk away, everything will rain.
If I lose you pain, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ah, I don't often play new songs on a daily source code.
But this is just such an unbelievable track.
Bruno Mars, it will rain, and this is Daddy's source code episode 865 coming to you from a
virtual theater of rain. Well, I just want you to imagine that
Stark outside
We've got
Brain coming down
Been here a little bit of thunder very very slightly in the background there
Some lightning flashes and the temptation slowly come on
We're ending three play and they know
The girl is found another and gone away
With her with my future my life is still with bloom
So day after day I still locked up in my room
I know to you in nights I'm strained but I wish you wouldn't rain
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
But everyone knows that I'm in it's supposed to cry listen
I got a cry
Cause crying
There's the pain
Oh yeah, even though I'm feeling sad
Words could never explain I just wish it would rain
Oh, let it rain rain rain rain
But it rain
Oh yeah
Let it rain
Oh
The end they out my tears they face faster gets to when they'll pay
My ass such disguise
That's literally for rain cause ain't the fine my tears love
And no one will ever know that I'm crying crying
Why I'm going outside
To the world I'm San Mateus and refuse to explain
Oh, I wish it would rain
Let it rain
I need to wait and spare tears my ass
Oh, let it rain
Oh
Tentations
On your Charlie I wish you would rain
Will as you knew to the program so we used to call it Charlie and those you were listening or chuckle heads
This is our rain block that we're playing for you today and
This guy I kind of like
Country dude for you here on the source code
Something sexy about the rain
This name is Kenny Chesley
That as it came from and now
Feels like kisses on my skin
She's better arms and spun around
And a summer island storm
In a field of sugar cane
She taught me how to show me what
Something sexy about the rain
And sometimes it rained all night
And everything she did was perfect
And everywhere we were was right
We love like there was no tomorrow
That suddenly tomorrow okay
It was raining at the airport
You kept all raining on the plane
She allowed me for a season
But my heart won't ever be the same
Even now her loves the reason
Something sexy about the rain
And sometimes when it's pouring down
I feel her kisses on my skin
It's better arms and spun around
And let that summer island storm
It may like a hurricane
It's like she's right here whispering
Something sexy about the rain
I'll own me back to the city
And I'll pick you in my mind
She's still young and she's still pretty
Even after all this time
There's something sexy about the rain
She said as it came pouring down
It feels like kisses on my skin
She's better arms and spun around
And let that summer island storm
And I feel she became
She dumped me out and shown me on
Something sexy about the rain
She dumped me out and she's still alive
There's something sexy about the rain
Something sexy about the rain
Feels like kisses on my skin
For longer term chuckle hedge you'll know that I am a sucker for an ever song
And when Miss Mickey and I did our hotpockets 2008 to her and that was pretty much the only thing you could hear
On the radio across this great land of ours
As country stations
I'm playing various degrees of commercial versions of country, but I like this one. Can you
Something sexy about the rain and
And of course if we're gonna play some rain songs
We can't leave out the legendary Diner Washington
I'll just like a dying in the
That's it and
In rain
To every word of love I heard you whisper
The rain drop seemed to play our sweet refrain
Those springs had to meet it's still set down
Ooh that's a time
In rain
To every word of love I heard you whisper
The rain drop seemed to play a sweet refrain
Oh spring is here to meet it's still set down
I'm going to go back to September
In the rain
I sat that's September
And that's what you tune into the show for Les Jim
For a musical education to give you stuff that you would never hear otherwise to expose you
To music that is just out there and you never hear on the radio anymore
Diner Washington September in the rain and when you hear the rain clattering against the street
Hence the
Maybe it's asphalt but it could be cobblestones I think cobblestones we better and you just want to wish
Look to you and you want to go
Go to the garden, give them a hand, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm singing in the rain, you're singing in the rain
What a glorious feel, and I'm happy again
I'm laughing at clouds, so dark up above the sun's in my heart
And I'm ready for love, let the storm make clouds change
Everyone from the place
Come on with a rain I've a smile on my face
I want to down the lane with a happy refrain just singing singing in the rain
Dancing in the rain
I'm happy again
I'm singing in the rain
Do you want to jump or jump on me?
Be yea
Do you want me to jump on me?
Dying a whole year
I'm dancing and singing in the rain.
As a movie, you gotta check out our Netflix, an American in Paris, Jean Kelly, I'm singing
in the rain.
It's a staple, we all know, but do you ever hear that song anymore?
I don't think so.
Coming for some time, when it's all the same, it'll rain suddenly, I know, shining down
the water, I won't know, have you ever seen a rain, I won't know, have you ever seen a rain,
I'll bend down the thing, if the day is before, so this cold rain is hot, I know, been that
people hold my hand, you forever home, go, you said fast and slow, hot, no, it can't stop, I won't know,
I won't know, have you ever seen a rain, I won't know, have you ever seen a rain, I'll bend down the thing,
I won't know, have you ever seen a rain, I won't know, have you ever seen a rain, I won't know, have you ever seen a rain,
I won't know, have you ever seen a rain, I'll bend down the thing, I just love the chatter
with this hour of the night, people trying to guess what song is going to be next,
clear water revival, have you ever seen the rain, and yes, I have a couple that I'm going to bring in the
you wouldn't expect, but I will not play it's raining men, I don't think so, that's the shit you
here on top 40 radio, no, no, no, this is the kind of stuff you wouldn't expect, taking you back to the
early A's baby, aren't you's Jones with the rain?
I saw you again, again in rain, you were holding hands in love, there would be a say,
so soon you turn me, the world will see this night, the rain brought you to this my way in the bay,
don't think to my body, I would never be the same, and yes, I have you ever seen a rain,
you were holding hands in love, there would be a say,
and yes, I have you ever seen a rain, you were holding hands in love, there would be a say,
so soon you turn me, the world will see this night, the rain, you were holding hands in love,
there would be a say, and yes, I have you ever seen a rain, you were holding hands in love,
my first impulse was to run up on you, to a ramble, we bought the jammy and flat glass both of you,
I didn't want to mess up this 30-700 dollar links at home, so instead I chill,
chill, now it's the bank, took out every dime, and then with the cans from all those credit cards,
all your charge counts, I stuck in on every piece of jewelry, I have a bunch, that's right, everything,
everything, if flat with none, I don't want you to be going to don't look in that closet,
because you ain't got nothing, everything you came here with is packed up and put you in the cash
that's right, what was you thinking about, what is trying to prove, this is what the chose,
I can get soups, Gucci handbag, blues diamonds, I can give you things that couldn't even pronounce,
and I can't be in that weather vise, because you're still young, that's right, you're still young,
I hope you learn a valuable lesson from all this, that's right bitch, you know,
I'm gonna find somebody like me one of these days, I'm still there, you know what I mean, people talk like that,
you know what that attic can't come with, I'm supposed to be shooting a crump kick, I saw you with,
I just missed, I swear, seller rabbit tricks are made for kids, no tricks are made for kids,
you said you had it, I can't flick without the milk, I'm torn just Jones, in the rain,
and yeah, okay, damn Andrea, because I love you so much,
I don't really have it when it rains, I'm only happy when it's complicated,
I know I know you can't appreciate it, I know they have it when it rains,
yeah, know I love it when the news is bad, oh why it gets so good, it feels so sad,
I know they have it when it rains,
oh like I'm measured it down, oh like I'm measured it down, oh like I'm measured it down,
oh like I'm measured it down, oh like I'm measured it down,
I'm only happy when it rains
I feel comfortable to control it all
I don't feel as if it's outside the sun
I don't wanna be with my hands
I miss my limit though
I'm only comfortable to control it all
I don't feel as if it's outside the sun
I'm only happy when it rains
You get the message that I'm trying to
When I complain about me and you
I'm only happy when it rains
You get the message that I'm trying to do
I think they played the very first public gig at like an MTV video musical wars and they
were on, I think that was one of those weird shows where they didn't, where they had the
VMAs in New York, and garbage was like, they were on the balcony or something.
I kind of recall both the entrance to, maybe the entrance to Radio City Music Hall,
surely, what's her name again, Shirley Manson, I'd say it's kind of hot, I don't like
her, that's for day of injury, a garbage, I'm only happy when it rains, now here's
what he didn't expect, I knew I'd get you, with what those one-head wonders, blind
melon, remember them, remember that guy used to piss on the audience from time to time, yeah
not much of a career after that, it's not good when you treat your customers that way,
but here's no right on the source code, I like to say it's pretty plain, I like watching
the buttons gather in, and all I can do is just bother deep for two, and speak my point of view
but it's not saying, it's not saying, I just want someone to say me, I'll always be there
when you and me, yeah, you know I like to keep my cheeks dry today, so stay with me
and I'll have it made, and I don't understand why I sleep all day, then I start to complain
and I don't understand why I sleep all day, then I don't understand why I sleep all day, then I don't understand why I sleep all day
but it's a great escape, escape, escape, escape, escape
I'm all I can say is that my life is pretty plain, you know, like my point of view
but it's not saying, it's not saying, I just want someone to say me, I'll always be there when you and me, yeah, you know I like to keep my cheeks dry today
I don't understand why I sleep all day, scared I don't understand why I sleep all day, then I don't understand what I'm saying
You want to learn running around like a bumblebee?
I think it's for a lot of us.
No rain, blind melon here.
And you did a source code episode 865.
Yeah, we got a rain thing going on.
I don't know.
I just kind of felt like it is.
Nine minutes to one AM here in Austin, Texas.
I'm Adam Curry.
You're a rainy DJ on duty with an original.
That, of course, you can't leave out of a rain set.
Strolling alone, country roads with my baby.
It stops to rain, it begins to pour.
Without an umbrella, we're so too to skin.
I feel a shiver on up my spine.
I feel the warmth of her hand in my hand.
I heal after in the rain.
Walking hand in hand with the one I love.
How I love the rainy day that my happy way.
I feel inside.
After a while, we run under a tree.
I turn to her and she kisses me.
There with the beat of the rain on the leaves.
So fresh she breeze and I close my eyes.
Sharing I love under stormy skies.
Ooh, how do you laugh during the rain?
Walking hand in hand with the one I love.
Ooh, how I love the rainy day that my happy way.
I feel inside.
I feel the warmth of her hand in my hand.
I heal after in the rain.
Walking hand in hand with the one I love.
How I love the rainy day that my happy way.
I feel inside.
I heal after in the rain.
Walking hand in hand with the one I love.
How I love the rainy day that my happy way.
I feel inside.
You may think this is like totally lame and I'm plainly strong.
Believe me, this is good for you.
I saw we were watching the final episode of American Idol.
By the way, I think it's cool that that Philip Phillips guy won.
Because he was definitely the most talented.
But you know, then they get the stuff that they play today.
Rihanna comes out with a total Illuminati pyramid all seeing eyeball crabs,
zombified pieces, shit.
Like, you know, this is the kind of stuff.
It will actually lift your heart.
Believe me, it will make you feel really, really good.
Particularly if, I mean, I know.
I know.
This is really stretching, but I just couldn't resist it.
Listen to all the falling rain.
Telling me just what if you like me.
I wish that if we could go and let me cry and bend.
And let me be alone again.
The only girl I care about has gone away.
Looking for a brand new start.
But a little touch in the window when she left that day.
Along with her, she took my heart.
Rain, please tell me not as I seem fair.
For her to steal my heart away when she don't care.
I can't love another way by heart somewhere far away.
The only girl I care about has gone away.
Looking for a brand new start.
But a little touch in the window when she left that day.
Along with her, she took my heart.
Rain, won't you tell her not as I look or so.
Please ask the sun to set her heart up low.
Rain and her heart and let the love be new start to grow.
All right, 10 points for the says there in the chat room.
You got to write the cascades.
About the time I was born, listen to the rhythm of the falling rain.
That song of course translated into at least 50 different languages.
Every single country in the world has a version of that song.
It was such a hit back in the day.
Way before the interwebs.
All right, let's wrap up this rain block that we have here with a sad song.
But again, a real song.
I've seen fire and I've seen rain James Taylor on your source code.
Just yesterday morning they let me know you were gone.
Suzanne the plans they made put an end to you.
I walked out this morning and I wrote down this song.
I just can't remember who to send it to.
I've seen fire and I've seen rain.
I've seen sunny days that I thought would never end.
I've seen lonely times when I could not find a friend.
But I always thought that I'd see you again.
Won't you look down upon me Jesus.
You gotta help me make a stand.
You just got to see me through another day.
My body's aching and my time is at hand.
I won't make it any other way.
I've seen fire and I've seen rain.
I've seen sunny days that I thought would never end.
I've seen lonely times when I could not find a friend.
But I always thought that I'd see you again.
I've been looking my mind to many as a time.
My back turns all the sun.
Don't notice when the cold wind blows.
It'll turn your head around.
Well it's hours the time on a telephone line.
To talk about things that come.
Sweet dreams and flying machines in pieces on the ground.
Well I've seen fire and I've seen rain.
I've seen sunny days that I thought would never end.
I've seen lonely times when I could not find a friend.
But I always thought that I'd see you baby.
One more time again and now.
I've seen you one more time again.
It's just a few things coming my way this time around.
Many different interpretations of what this song is about.
But I asked James Taylor about her once.
He said he wrote it after coming out of a very deep depression.
So that's what we used to do back in the day.
You'd be depressed and then you feel really crappy about things that happen in your life.
And you know either you write a song about it or you find someone who would written a song.
You'd play that song and you'd feel better and it could lift your spirits.
And these days you know we just take a pill.
Like a riddle.
Not really.
I don't know.
They don't want it.
They eventually will make you kill yourself.
So there you go.
All right.
I'm going to wind this now.
I'm drunk now by the way.
I've had three glasses of Jack hefty glasses of mine.
And that's just shock glasses of a real glasses.
I did want to pay tribute to Robin Gibb and actually,
while I'm at it, Maurice Gibb and Andy Gibb.
Three of the Gibb brothers gone.
Barry Gibb still left over.
And the you know, I've been paying it a little bit of attention to mainstream media.
How they've been portraying it.
And it's talk about the BG's about the disco.
It's like that's so much bull crap.
If you really know your music history, these guys wrote so many amazing songs.
And they really did emerge on the scene back in the days of the kinks of the Beatles,
the Rolling Stones.
And they've always gotten a really bad rap.
But of course, that's how mainstream works.
You know, you do a couple songs.
And they really only did a couple songs for Saturday Night Fever.
And also they're the disco kings.
And I know that they personally were very frustrated by it because
I met them several times when they had their one album out.
What's the name of the song? You win again?
Which was a huge number one hit everywhere.
They were one of my shows.
And I remember they were like, you know, they didn't come out and say it as such.
But I knew that they were very, they was like, you know, like fuck that.
And Robin was a very, very cool guy.
It's total geek, by the way.
He had the geekiest watches.
And he was into all kinds of technology shit.
And it's just been bad luck for this family.
It's just been really, really sad.
So I wanted to play a song from the BGs.
Who, of course, their music goes back to the very early 60s.
This is one of my all-time favorite BG songs.
I started a joke.
It started the whole, well, crying.
I didn't see.
I'm the chill for the mean.
Oh, no.
I started to cry.
Which started the whole, well, laughing.
Oh, it might at least be.
And the chill for me.
Oh, it looked like the skies.
Running my hands over my eyes.
And I fell out of bed.
I'd seen my head from things that I said.
Until I finally died.
Which started the whole, well, living.
Oh, it might at least be.
I'm the chill for the mean.
I looked at the skies.
Running my hands over my eyes.
And I fell out of bed.
I'd seen my head from things that I said.
Until I finally died.
Which started the whole, well, living.
Oh, it might at least be.
That the chill for me.
Almost here, the warble in the 45 on the record player when they digitized this.
Can't you?
Maybe it was the real, the real, the BG's.
I started a joke here on your daily source code episode eight, six, five.
I hope you're enjoying the show.
It's been a weird one.
But I mean, that kind of mood.
I'm going to be 48 on September 3rd.
And I'm so fucking happy.
I'm alive.
And I feel good.
I'm healthy.
And this is, I was not going to John about this.
John, see the Vorac.
I think it was off air.
It's like, you know, you get older and just people are dropping around you.
And it's like, what the hell, man?
I mean, why am I so lucky? Why do I get to stay around?
And I really don't care.
I'm just happy I'm here.
And I'm going to share as much of that love that I get from the music with you guys as I can.
This is one of my favorite songs.
I love this woman.
Chuck a con through the fire.
I look in your eyes and I can see.
There's nothing interesting.
You're not trusting your heart to anyone.
You tell me you're going to play it smart.
We're through before we start.
But I believe that we've only just begun.
When it's this good, there's not something more.
I want you so I'm ready to go.
Through the fire, to the limit to the war.
For Chuck to be with you, I gladly lift you all.
Through the fire, whatever I lay.
For Chuck to lie to you, I take it all the way.
Right down to the wall, even through the fire.
I know you're afraid of what you feel.
It's still any time to feel.
And I can put you lonely, let me drive.
You touch me and something in the room.
For I could have been you.
I'm not a baby to kiss the green goodbye.
When is this sweet, there's no say no.
I need you so I'm ready to go.
Through the fire, to the limit to the war.
For Chuck to be with you, I gladly lift you all.
Through the fire, whatever I lay.
For Chuck to lie to you, I gladly lift you all the way.
Right down to the wall, even through the fire.
Through the fire, to the limit to the war.
For Chuck to be with you, I gladly lift you all.
Through the limit to the war.
Through the fire, to the limit to the war.
For Chuck to be with you, I gladly lift you all.
Through the limit to the limit to the war.
All right, to know how songs bring back memories, right?
I think I was 20 years old.
It was in the tiny, tiny apartment of a grown-man to Esther.
An Esther, ah, Esther Tollin.
She was the lead singer of the Novo band.
Oh, man, it's coming back to me now.
It was like a one-hit wonder band, the Novo band.
They had a, what's the name that's song?
Let's see, like, a soap and book of knowledge.
Let's go dancing.
And I'd been on television for maybe six months or so.
And it was an Utrecht.
And as she'd been on the show, and then she was doing a gig somewhere with the band,
with the Novo band, never heard from again.
And she said, yeah, you should come and watch us or watch the show.
And I went down and, and I remember that.
I was, I was like completely smitten about her, completely.
When back to her apartment, and we were making out just,
I got to, I got to play the song for it.
She played this song.
Chaka Khan through the fire.
And it was like this, one of those magical moments.
Ah, 30 years ago.
Alright, now let's fast forward to 2012.
I promise I play this one for my lovely Miss Mickey,
the woman who I will marry on July 16th.
This was for you, baby.
Her absolute, one and only favorite Neil Diamond track.
Jack on the rocks, or love on the rocks.
Love on the rocks.
He knows the price.
This for me a drink, and I tell you some lies.
And nothing to lose, so you're just seeing the blues.
All the time.
Gave you my heart, give you my soul.
He left me alone here with nothing to hold.
Yesterday's gone.
Now all I want is a smile.
First they say they want you.
They have really lead you.
Suddenly you've planned you're out there.
Walking in the stars.
And when they know they have you.
And they really have you.
Nothing you can do or say.
You got to leave just get away.
We all know the song.
You need what you need.
You can say what you want.
Not much you can do when the feeling is gone.
Maybe it blew skies above.
But it's cool when you lose on the rocks.
First they say they want you.
They have really lead you.
Suddenly you've planned you're out there.
Walking in the stars.
And when they know they have you.
And they really have you.
Nothing you can do or say.
You got to leave just get away.
We all know the song.
Love on the rocks.
They know big surprise.
Just pull me a dream.
Yesterday's gone.
And all I wanted is a smile.
I think all the jazz singer,
on Netflix will watch that.
That'll get her in the mood.
You'll diamond love on the rocks.
He's going on tour.
He's starting in a week or so.
All right.
Let's see what time is it now.
115.
And I'm kind of keeling over.
It's been a very long day.
We got the no agenda show this morning.
Which means I usually get a very, very early.
Of course, after going to bed very late.
Because that's usually how it works.
Reading government legislation.
All kinds of other stuff like that.
But I'm so happy.
I was able to share a couple of good tunes with this.
And buddies in the chat room, no agenda street.com.
Where you can always hear some kind of crazy ass show going on.
Thank you.
Get most laid for.
Connecting me into the live sort stream.
Thanks.
Everybody in the chat room who was hanging out and keeping me company.
I'm going to play one last song.
It's one of those long ones.
It's a live version.
It's eight minutes.
A little over eight minutes.
And there's just one.
One part in this song that gets me every single time.
And I'll be singing it really, really loudly.
I won't come back after it though.
Because nothing like your mom is saying,
I know why you ain't going to sing that song, girl.
But I'm talking about.
Ready, right?
Tonight is the night.
And if you haven't had your night tonight,
I want you to go and find your love one on half that night.
So they come out and share.
And all the love.
Because you know you can make love.
Like no one else.
You don't have a real good chance.
That's right.
We have it, man.
Is that all right with you?
That's all right, Betty.
Thank you so much.
Now, this is a tune that I compose.
And it's called tonight is the night.
See you soon, everybody.
That you make me a walk.
A source code.
I never intended recording this song.
It was a personal point.
That isn't till the day that my producer happened to throw through the pages of my notebook.
He came across the words, and he said,
We've got to do something with these words.
It's happening every day.
And people want to hear about it, Betty.
You see, it's the story of a young girl making love for the very first time.
Now, when I finally got a melody, I took it home and I played it for my mother.
And I got to tell you a little bit about my mother.
You see, I come from one of those pretty large families.
And I'm the baby of the family.
And you know, you never grow up to your mother.
I never forget the way she looked at me when I played it for her.
She said, I like the music.
You know, baby, the melody is really nice.
But I know you're not going to sing that song.
But we've used the right home by the beginning.
And if it came one of my biggest records too,
So I want you to do this for me if you will.
Everybody, think back to your very first time.
Now give it a little while longer, because I know some of you have to think back a little bit further than others.
Come on now, I want you to play catch up.
And I don't want you waiting till I get to get some of my songs to hear.
Oh yeah, now, remember?
Now, whether it was good, or you just smiled and it was good.
All the other hand, if it was not so good, here's my stone.
Tonight is the night, that you make me your warm mind.
You said to be gentle with me, and I hope you'll be happy.
I'm nervous, and I'm trembling.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.
I'm trying hard to relax, but I just can't keep still.
No, I can't give you a car to stand.
I won't play bigger than for all my senses, man.
But I know so little about what love is.
I just can't help acting like a child.
Like I can't do my job, hand your ring in my bed.
Hope you're not impatient after waiting until they're long.
Oh, hold me up with my silly hands.
And we're both holding up to no right or wrong.
Tonight is the night, that you make me your warm mind.
You said to be gentle with me, and I hope you'll be happy.
I'm nervous, and I'm trembling.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.
I'm trying hard to relax, but I just can't keep still.
No, I can't give you a car to stand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.
And I can't just do it what we are doing.
Not only will I never really die, but my whole family relationship, it'll all be ruined.
But we're both holding up to no right or wrong.
Oh, hold me up with my silly hands.
And we're both holding up to no right or wrong.
And I hope you're not impatient after waiting until they're long.
Tonight is the night, that you make me your warm mind.
You said to be gentle with me, and I hope you'll be happy.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.
And I hope you'll be happy.
Oh, hold me up with my silly hands.
And we're both holding up to no right or wrong.
And I hope you'll be happy.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.
Oh, hold me up with my silly hands.
And I hope you'll be happy.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.
Oh, hold me up with my silly hands.
And I hope you'll be happy.
I'm waiting for you to walk in.