Delta Sherry Charlie 866.
This is the Lunar Edition.
Hola.
Super Nano Yenshi.
One, two, three.
I'm the man.
I am the man.
Just a moon and a country possesses strange powers.
Or is it all just a moon a safe place?
16.
16 minutes and seven minutes ensuring five lines of time.
Turn.
The 21st century of radio starts here.
The only loss of thinking can't fear me.
Oh, my.
I know it's in the three dots.
I'm a f**kastic.
It's a new curry.
Let's take a bath to the moon, baby.
I'm sitting around with you.
How I'm craving you.
Oh, yeah.
Everett's have a naked eye.
Oh, my.
I'll be right here if you see me there.
In my eyes, I'll need you here.
Don't ask why.
I'll never disappear.
Why is it every day that I feel the pain?
Yeah.
Let's take a trip to the stars far away.
I will never stay with you.
I'll stay bringing to the dead.
My pain is caused by my pressure.
My pain is cause by my pressure.
I use it every day, and then I'll feel the pain
Now, yeah
Now
No
I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you
I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you,
I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you,
We pray for silence
We keep from making our nights
Bad news is calling
These return to kill the light
And when these families love people
They're silly and wrong
Can you hear me?
Fucking the moon
Ha ha ha
replicated
Do tell me
Maybe the movie is crazy
Goly has reason
There to go pretending to see
His head's are empty
His Chest is broken
Let me go, let me stay home, and I don't need him, but I don't know.
Hey, yeah, I don't know.
They just didn't marry me, but love this game, and though he's time to stop and go, go,
it can't be burning, no, I'm holding you on, but please return to the road, it's not wrong, we have made it.
Let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go, let me go
Let him go, let me go, let me go, let me okay close my eyes, I'll kill you, I'll see that broken house with this
That's obviously what it's there for, just how and back at it.
But there's another big question we have to ask, and then I get answered after there's still a source car, I tell you.
Sometimes it just takes a little bit of emotional energy to get me all around, not to bring another dead source car, and this is one of those days.
They've been to 20,000,000 to 12.
And we hear our Lord.
Where we are asking you several questions.
Here's the Lord.
Really made of cheese.
A lot of me are plug-in here, let me get everything set up.
Yeah, that's a devour act, I don't know how long I got you, thank you.
Oh yeah.
We got at least an hour and a half, maybe two hours.
Awesome.
This is for you here on the Charlie.
As we roll down.
Six, six.
This is the murder edition.
As you want, just lock it to keep the planetary space travel, if you will.
You've been black crawls.
But no creep in.
I'm the Charlie.
Six, six.
Six, seven.
Six, six, six.
Six, six.
Six, seven.
Six.
Six, six.
Six, seven.
Six.
Six, six.
Nine, eight.
Six, seven.
Minutes.
Six.
Six, seven.
To watch our carpetก
uptime凋
Come
Lift the Chicos
아hh
нас
penance
Please
come quick
And I'm giving you the volume
It really
Yeah you live
In no matter
Even hotter
I don't think of a man, I'm sleeping in us, don't you cry
And we don't return, we're sending out and ending
Don't be a story, yeah, you can see
I've been with her, I've been with her, I've been with you
See what you got back and back, yeah, you can see
I've been with you, I've been with her, I've been with her
See what you got back, yeah, you can see
I've been with her, I've been with her, I've been with her
We're sending out and ending
I'm going to show you a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of an
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of an
little bit of how it's gonna be a good day and we have the Official porn star of the Charlie Showing, the Shadowama条 paint stream.com, no chin-to-chat.net!
Welcome Bobbi Eden, keeping all the humorion-reetsers, and retain them all happy.
I'm gonna be breaking this down on a minute.
Let me know exactly what we are doing this show.
But it's all a good thing because, Hey!
No matter which way you look at it, we´ve got another Daily SourceGorde.
Yeah, and Gree!
fuck all of you, wear aío drug.
I see a fair move of right and I see trouble on the way
I see fair moves of right and hit
I see bad times a day
Don't worry about tonight, but if I don't take your dad
I see fair moves of right and hit
I know the end is coming soon
I see a real move of right and hit
I see a fair move of right and hit
Don't worry about tonight, but if I don't take your dad
I see fair moves of right and hit
I see a fair move of right and hit
I see a fair move of right
I see a fair move of left and hit
I see a fair move of right and hit
There you've been moving on the right.
Don't worry about tonight.
Almost finally take your day.
There you've been moving on the right.
It's Credence.
Bad moon rise in here on the Daily Source Code.
This is episode 866.
And my name is Adam Curry.
You're a podcaster on duty for this entire episode.
Good to have you all back for the ride.
Let me tell you how this show got started.
First of all, I've been thinking about doing another day.
The source code for a while now.
We got back from our our tour.
Actually, somewhere during the last.
I'd say the the last week of the.
I started to get kind of a little bit of an inching a little bit.
Like, oh, man, I got to get going.
I got to start doing this stuff.
This Mickey of course is always goating me into.
It's like, yeah, I'll get the whiskey.
And by the way, not a drop so far today.
Right now, it's 430 in the afternoon here in the.
The drone star state in Austin, Texas.
But I'm sure, Mickey, I'll walk in a little bit with a beer to get me really rolling.
And I have a couple of shows.
And I'm thinking about.
I'm thinking about doing a truck and drive and show.
I'm thinking about doing a firefighting show.
And I'm kind of more into this theme stuff that we haven't.
You know, they seem to be kind of getting into a little bit recently.
So here's how it started for those of you who do not know.
It was very interesting that I was on to it.
This week in tech would be able to port yesterday.
Was it yesterday?
Not two days ago on Sunday.
Today is Tuesday.
And I kind of got last so into something.
And even though on the show, it was actually, I thought, kind of okay.
It really spun out of control in the.
In the blogger sphere, the Twitter sphere.
And it's something that I just, I noticed so many interesting things.
Surrounding what I had said that it warranted a little bit of a discussion.
And, you know, when I get, you know, riled up and I've got no one else to talk to.
Because I can't call the war act.
We only talk twice a week on the show.
I might as well be talking to you guys.
So let me, you know, let me play.
And I'll stop this and give some commentary.
Let me play a little bit from what happened on this week in tech.
He's got it down.
He doesn't have to practice anymore.
But I've been told if, if I should pass away during the show, you can perform.
I got you.
You're got me.
I got you back.
So actually, the, the top star will lead off with a, with a, with a story that is not apples.
Sam, so I'm shocking to everybody.
Yesterday, Neil, I'm strong passed away.
The first person to walk on the moon at the age of 82.
Adam, do you, do you actually believe that he walked on the moon?
I just should check probably before we talk about this.
Now, this is where the immediately got interesting.
And of course, Leo Leport full well is fully well aware of my stance on the,
Oh, thank you, darling.
Right on cue.
Love you.
Bobby says hi.
She's in the chat room.
Oh, this is a fireman's number four.
Blondale.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Hmm.
So anyway, so Leo is fully well aware of my, my position,
which you could call crack pot, whatever.
And if he's about to do some kind of eulogy to,
to the arm strong, it makes, doesn't make a lot of sense to jump right in with me.
And by the way, this is such a big red herring.
And I didn't know how bad it was really until I saw the response.
Because of course, when I'm, no matter what show I'm doing,
I would tweet as well.
I'm looking at the chat room.
I'm trying to see what's going on.
And in my response, I could only answer honestly.
Well, I have to be honest that I do not believe that he walked on the moon.
Because I was right.
I was going that land.
Good call.
Okay.
So we're going to answer it on a good time.
It's funny.
You know, let's laugh at the crack pot.
That's cool.
All right.
Now, I'm okay with that.
You can say it.
And unfortunately, he took the secrets of that within two is great.
Well, this is, now, I'm, maybe I shouldn't have said that.
But it isn't lying with my conspiracy.
And now at this point, I'm not getting into flags, not waving into shadows,
into all kinds of stuff.
And just so you understand,
I really only questioned certain types of space travel and that landing on the moon.
For some scientific reasons, which is very hard for anyone to prove otherwise.
And I was just giving an honest answer, not trying to jump in being a super conspiracy nut.
So not trying to sound like one.
I already know that just bring it up is enough.
But this, by the way, is a thing that's happened to Richard Bells or the other day on Pierce Morgan.
With the first question out of the gate about his new book, which is about, I think is what is it, 15 stories.
About American government.
You don't know.
It doesn't include JFK assassination, et cetera.
And you, whenever someone starts off with, so do you think we landed on the moon?
Basically, the only answer you can give is, well, of course I do.
If you answer any differently, you are crazy.
But even worse than that.
But I'll get into that in a moment.
I've always used to like that.
NBC.com posted a story where they said, first guy to walk on the moon, nearly young past.
So here I am trying to kind of steer the conversation away.
And you know, a little more fun direction.
Just to, you know, to bring it more back to what I know about, which is how dumb the media is.
They were the first, they were the first with the story.
And I guess sometimes typos happen.
And these people make a lot of money to do this.
Wow.
I had a lot of, I was out at a bar yesterday.
And I heard a lot of people wondering if it was a landstorm strong, who'd passed away.
There was a lot of, so at this point, this is Nile, who I incorrectly called Nile,
or some crap like that.
You'll hear that.
You know, so now we could have moved on from here.
It would have been easy for the host to take this and move on.
It's really, really depressing stuff.
Yeah.
Well, the good news is I'm sure there'll be quite a few documentaries and, you know,
people will be talking quite a bit about it.
And I think as we begin our exploration of Mars, it's really good to remember back to Nile.
I'm strong in those first words.
Yeah.
Okay. So at this point, I just, I'm just pouring it on because, you know,
I'm not anyway, the chat room is exploded with hate.
It's another one I really don't believe in, Nile.
You know, if you, I'm trying to take it to Mars, right?
Let's take it to the Mars rover.
Let's steer away from Neil Armstrong.
You put a picture of what the curiosity Mars rover has taken,
which always seems to take pictures of itself.
You put a picture of that into Google.
The Google API will say, would you like to see other pictures from New Mexico?
Now, this is not a conspiracy theory.
This is a true.
If you try it at home, you'll see this as well.
Well, it looks a lot like New Mexico.
All right.
Admittedly.
Well, regardless of whether or not you think we landed on a moon
or the curiosity landed on Mars, you have to admit that the effect of inspiring
a whole generation of scientists and people interested in space.
That's a good thing, right?
And I have to say, I like what, this is a Catholic priest of the, the Jesuit
Society of Jesuits of what is a father of the Robert Padre S.J.
is what he's known as, and on Twitter.
And he's actually, he's okay.
He's kind of respectful.
And which is why I probably didn't hammer into him.
He was like, oh, do you believe that the moon was made by God?
Which I did get an answer from him later on Twitter, which I'll get into.
I mean, even with all the other, I wouldn't say Adam has to admit anything,
but let's ask him.
Well, no, it's nice to get people's imagination rolling.
And I like all the 3D renderings that we saw of the sky crane and the parachute and the landing.
Of course, we never really saw any of that.
We just saw the 3D renderings.
They were beautiful.
Well, done.
The seven minutes of terror.
I'm impressed.
You really don't believe what would be the incentive.
There was no reason.
No reason to go back to this.
We could have let it lie for the government to, or NASA, to fake this.
Oh, just more money.
There's, it's a tiny bit of money compared to, you know, air conditioning, the troops in Afghanistan.
Wow, that was, that was a can of worms right there.
Now, this could have been my opportunity.
And I did think about it.
It's like, wow, you know, I could get into all that stuff.
But, you know, this is a tech show.
We're supposed to be talking about technology and science.
And so I think you can have an alternate view, possibly.
Now, I'm going to try and wrap this up and pull back a little bit and just say,
Hey, man, you know, there's other thoughts out there.
You know, basically trying to say, you know, consider an alternative of a paper instance.
I mean, really, it's a few billion dollars that way.
I, you know, I've put a lot of work into the into the moon landing.
And, you know, there's, there's just a lot of different theories about how that would work.
If you can get through certain parts of space to actually get out that far.
Now, I'm opening it up here for anyone who has read at least any of the so-called denialism to talk about
the Van Allen belts, which could actually be a pretty interesting conversation with the knowledge
that NASA has had just delayed, I guess, because of the hurricane near the Gulf Coast.
They're sending off two Allen belt probes, Van Allen belt probes into space to find out, you know,
more about this stuff.
Because, you know, this fry satellites, it fries all kinds of integrated circuits.
And this is one of the main theories as to why we did not go to the moon 50 years ago, almost 50 years ago,
46 years ago, I guess.
Because, you know, going through that radiation belt would essentially fry the equipment and,
perhaps even the human beings onboard.
And this is something that, you know, we could have gotten into.
And if you look up the Van Allen belts, it's very hard for people to prove that it is possible to go through.
And, you know, that we had in a very topical, we could have had a very topical conversation about the probes that are being launched.
Of course, no one else knows about, because all they know about is the stupid rover on Mars.
I'm just not wholly convinced that, you know, people call me a crackpot.
So there you go, I'm saying, I'm not wholly convinced.
I'm not saying, oh, it's not too big conspiracy.
You know, Kubrick, I didn't do all that.
It just laid low.
So be it.
I'm, I have to really keep to my guns on this one.
I'm really just not completely convinced.
I am dragging pictures of, uh, uh, from curiosity.
And I don't, I'm not getting new Mexico yet.
But I'll, but I'll keep doing it.
No, I don't, let me get your input on this one.
I, I got a costed by a few YouTube users who are trying to convince me that,
the Mars we see in the sky is actually just a big inflatable place there by the government.
So you don't actually know where Mars is.
No, no, no, I'm not on that thing.
I mean, I, I actually, there are bases on the moon and on Mars not necessarily.
Again, I'm opening it up to talk about some alternative theories.
And by the way, I've never understood why people will believe that we've landed on the moon.
We'll believe that we have, uh, the Mars, uh, rover, the curiosity.
But then, of course, completely will ignore any anomalies that are seen in pictures or video.
There's no way there's UFOs.
There's no, all that is all explainable.
They're open to that, but they're not open to anything else.
That always surprises me.
And, uh, who knows what the, with the ultimate agenda is, you can Google Project Bluebeam.
Now, this is a, a no agenda crackpot theory.
I had to throw in, um, and you should Google Project Bluebeam.
Um, uh, and again, no one picked up on it.
That may be one.
There's a, a number of different theories out there.
So I'm, you know, it's hard for me if I haven't seen it with my own eyes.
That is the core of my argument.
If I haven't seen it with my own eyes, then I'm just not, that ready to jump and then believe it.
Why?
Because I've been in television all my life.
I mean, if you believe you saw these guys landing on the moon and I remember my parents woke me up and I sat in front of the television.
I can distinctly remember.
I'm like, oh, what?
But if you, uh, will believe what you saw there, then why not believe, you know, in what you see on Star Trek or what you see in, in other science fiction.
Why not believe the hunger games?
Why not believe any special effects?
Why not believe it?
This is what astounds me.
I have a hard time believing things.
I can respect that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Nice.
Father, uh, the Robert there saying that I can respect that.
Great.
And he should.
I respect his view.
Now, here's what was interesting.
Uh, so an entire shitstorm of tweets, you know, and here's what I was called.
Uh, uh, people saying he called Neil Armstrong a liar.
Well, no, I didn't call him a liar.
I, you know, I didn't.
Those words did not pass through my lips.
Um, so people saying it's the same thing.
All right.
That's one.
Uh, the other favorite I got is, um, you're a Holocaust denier.
You know, or on the same level as a Holocaust denier.
Wow.
You know, that was like, okay.
That's pretty big.
At one point, someone even called me a stupid Republican.
Now, that to me was fascinating that somehow a questioning the moon landing or not being a,
a, the being an anti moon truther, I guess.
Uh, make sure we're Republican.
And that's something I got to talk with the, uh, with John about on, uh,
I know agenda for sure because that's basically how program we've become.
But this was like, it was like some kind of jihad.
It was really, really quite amazing to see all the hate coming through.
And all of that, you know, I can handle that.
And went back and forth and I even brought up, uh, about father Robert.
I mean, you know, it was like, hey, you know, I should have asked them if he
believes it to some guy in the sky, uh, created the moon.
And he didn't get back to me on Twitter.
And he, very smart these Jesuits.
He says, no, I, uh, I believe, uh, in the, um, uh, what do you call it in the, uh,
evolutionary theory.
I'm like, wow.
So here's a Catholic priest.
Uh, and I was specifically, uh, a Jesuit who believes in, um, evolutionary theory.
And his reasoning behind that is that God gave him the power to reason.
And therefore it's okay, which I think is a brilliant, brilliant way of playing
it, essentially saying, um, hey, you know, if, if God created everything, then he also
created this, you know, this idea.
And the reasoning behind it, which is, I mean, incredibly smart.
By the way, I'm very interested now in Father Robert.
And, and, and, and what his deal is, because from what I understand, the Jesuits call themselves
the Marines of God.
And you know, they think of vowels at celibacy.
So, you know, we should send Bobby Eden to Father Robert.
I bet we could fix him real quick.
And I know she'd be up for it.
Um, you know, so that, but their mission is to literally propagate the word of God.
And I think there was, uh, there was a quote somewhere.
Let me see if I can find that on my, uh, maybe I put that in my only in my Twitter stream.
I'm not sure, uh, because it was just interesting that he does have, uh, in a agenda.
Let me see.
Did I put that on my link blog?
Or did I probably only on my Twitter?
Well, I was second.
Hmm.
I'd be worth it to find that one.
It was like,
I'm scrolling down here.
Like, oh, here it is.
Conquering the web for Christ.
So, this is, it's just an interesting, interesting guy.
And I'd like to know more about there's a lot of trash talk about the Jesuits on the web as well.
By the way, that the Jesuits or the true Illuminati and all this stuff.
By the way, Father and J. Padre as SJ, if you ever listened to the show, Bobby Eden says she's up for it.
Ha ha ha.
Hey, I'm jealous now.
So, but that, that was, you know, okay, so I don't mind a little back and forth.
You know, hey, you don't kill the cow before you milked it, right?
I mean, I'm thinking for the lone wolf belligerence out there that are going to hear this.
And there have been quite a few.
And I got a lot of supportive messages and emails.
You know, we'll get some more listeners for the show.
And maybe we can save a few souls.
You know, we're conquering the web for our own version of Christ, I guess.
But then Leo, and this is what blew me away.
He's out there tweeting.
And let me, I don't want to misquote him.
So I'm going to bring up his Twitter feed right now.
Nice internal server error, really Twitter.
Here it goes.
Let me just bring up his tweets.
Okay.
Uh, blah, blah, blah.
So, first I says, the real devour act refuses to be on the show.
The same show with Adam Curry.
Now I know why.
We were honoring a great man and Adam called him and all of NASA a liar.
Not my proudest moment.
Well, I didn't call all of NASA and him a liar.
Um, now he already says, uh, Adam is a really smart guy with some strange beliefs.
I never saw that coming.
Yeah, you did.
But what's more interesting.
He says, no one believes me, but I've never listened to no agenda.
Conspiracy nuts irritate me too.
And, uh, we, uh, here is I agree.
We booked Adam Curry much earlier than before, uh,
Neil Armstrong's death, which is not true because they literally booked me, uh, Sunday,
Saturday night.
I had no idea he disbelieved.
I was shocked and didn't rebut as I should have.
And then my favorite, I was blindsided by Adam.
I apologize.
And now it, you know, so I'm like, well, that's really lame.
That, that's, that's, that's it.
It, it was always not true.
Second of all, it wasn't all that bad.
But, you know, he's, what is he afraid of?
Yeah, I miss Mickey actually.
He said, Adam, he has advertisers.
Don't you understand that?
You know, intellectually, I get it.
But come on.
So, I think actually the moon hoaxer week he had, uh, had an entry on me,
which was erased, which I'm sad about because I thought it was pretty good.
But if you actually listen to the real context and the things I said, you know,
I'm not, you know, some kind of holocaust denier.
I'm not all these horrible things.
But to me, the veracity and the anger that this provokes in people,
I mean, if, if I had said, oh, you know, a 9-11 was an inside job,
blessed people would have cared them about this.
To me, that was truly, truly astounding.
And, you know, we're talking about it.
You know, last night and today's thing is it's still going on.
Of course, as a podcast, lots of people are getting it.
And, and then I said, you know, I should probably do a show about this.
I'll do the lunar edition and Mickey's of course.
Yeah, hey, hell now.
And, well, luckily, I've got tons of tracks.
Thank you very much again, Marcus Cows for, uh,
pretty much getting all the tracks.
I wanted to get and I got a couple, a couple other ones, which I think you'll enjoy.
So, uh, we'll just run through it here and, uh, we'll talk some more about, you know,
being a Republican.
Really?
I don't know.
How are they, like, left?
I think they can start.
I said, I'd like to travel at night.
I'm afraid to stay here, you're fine.
I was gonna pick up our travel for them.
Can you open the room?
And I'm ready.
Here we go.
There we go.
Thank you.
Thank you, remember me?
Is there anybody out there?
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, also useful construction paper, see you in the next videos, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, so see you in the next video, see you on
another video, see you in the next video, see you in the next videos, see you in the next video, and check out the next video, see you in a next video
I'm going to do it.
Remember that whole album man, how awesome the police were then?
So that will of course be the song for this episode in history.
As I know, go down as a crazy nut, a Republican holocaust denier.
Ah, that's a bad joke, where probably.
But it does say a lot about how we think about things in the world.
And he was funny.
I got an email for someone who said, you know, I don't trust what NASA tells me.
But I do trust the myth busters, like, oh man, so I have when I looked in the myth busters,
they have a video episode where they went up and apparently the astronauts left a reflector
behind and they show how the reflector's work and then they go to this Apache point or something
I believe.
And this up must be up somewhere, maybe it's Alaska, I don't know where Apache point is.
And there's a giant laser.
And then what you see is the lady says, okay, initiating laser and she clicks on the mouse.
And then you see the little bit of green flashing and of course you can't see the laser
like coming back.
That has to be registered on a computer screen.
They see it a little line go up and there it is, we're receiving photons back from
the moon.
It's proof.
The science is in.
I know you're somewhere out there somewhere far away, I want you back, I want you back,
I never think I'm crazy, I don't understand, you're all ahead, you're all ahead.
And I win the stars, I'm on my own, I sit by myself, talking to them all, trying to get
out of the sky, talking to me, talking to me, talking to them all, talking to them all,
oh I'm feeling like I'm sayin' me is the top of the town, I say I've come on, I have come
I didn't know what I know, because when the sun goes down so much talking back again
And I'd win the stars like on my own
I sit by myself, talking to the moon
Trying to get to you
And hold your hands on the other side
So I can't stop it, so I'm on my own
So sit by myself, talking to the moon
And hold your hands on the other side
So I can't stop it, so I'm on my own
So sit by myself, talking to the moon
And hold your hands on the other side
So I can't stop it, so I'm on my own
So sit by myself, talking to the moon
We play a lot of old tunes on the daily source code
But this I would say is one of the best artists of our time
No Mars
What the voice, love the production, love the look, love everything
Just fantastic, talking to the moon
And of course the moon really is something incredibly special
When you think about it, I was a surprise
Miss Mickey and I were in the car, we know
I need some moon songs
And he just think about that so many songs
About the moon and the romance it's involved in it
And it really warrants a full chuckle dedicated to it
That's what you're getting now
Fly me to the moon, let me play
Among the stars, let me see what spring is like on
A Jupiter and Mars, in other words
Hold my hand
In other words
Baby kiss me
Fill my heart with song
And let me sing forever more
You are all I long for, all I worship and the dawn
In other words, please be true
In other words, I love you
Fill my heart with song
Let me sing forever more
You are all I long for
Fill my heart with song
Let me sing forever more
You are all I long for, all I worship and the dawn
In other words, please be true
In other words, in other words
I love you
You are all I am
She was standing in the lane
Trying how to speak my name
They say first love and love on time
The way to more the memories in the tiny clouds
We stumbled over once we long to hear
We talked about the dreams we lost
We are giving up
When always took up the light
And she said it's from my light
As the last dream walked on the moon
Though summer nights
When we were young
We cried the dreams
We never done we were dreamers
Only dreamers
And in our hands
You brought us home
We left our innocent
On there's a group we were dreamers
Only dreamers
On there's a moon
There's a moon
There's a world we'll see
The memories for us
I still can hear goodbye
On the summer nights
It echoes in the mountains
of my heart.
The night is doing and waiting for the dead as a train.
I know what we meant to say.
All our chances swept away.
Still remain on the road to the door.
The summer nights, when we were young,
we bring the pain, we never thought we would dream of.
Only three months.
All this past and time comes on,
with dreams we made,
for just as long as there's people.
All the dream goes on,
and there's more.
And there's more.
All this.
There's no.
Wow, that takes me back.
I think we made this the a lot of Skype,
which back in the day when I was working Veronica Radio
and the Netherlands was like the hit pick of the week.
He of course is the voice of sticks,
you know, and from babe I believe in Dennis D. Young Desert Moon.
I don't mark his couch, hated it,
or was excited to hear it.
I'm not quite sure.
So of course we have a lot of new listeners popping in on the stream,
or jenestream.com, as the Dennis source code is always produced live.
And then later release for podcast completely against all regulations.
I could go to jail.
And so I'm just running down the Twitter stream.
Of course, I appreciate all of the the no agenda and fans
and the chuckleheads who are posting great stuff there.
Here's one from surter as you are.
Adam Curry, the music you play is terrible.
Yeah, okay.
Let me see what else we got here.
There's always something fun.
Oh, this is always another one.
The tech gurus says Adam Curry,
I don't know, landing on the moon is not complicated,
but who knows, maybe Hiroshima was faked too.
To this, I don't understand how you can equate
that type of conversation with each other.
It's always very interesting.
Steve K says Leo LaPortitz.
I think it's time to sever all ties with Curry,
and never do business with him again.
The man is a nut job.
Certified, crazy, I tell you.
Yeah, well, dude.
I was slow dancing with Bobby Eden in the chat room during that song,
so I don't know.
Maybe you're just envious?
What?
Time to get my 80's vibe on.
Can't do without your hand.
Shit.
You got me coming.
I said it.
Can't do without me.
Maybe I can't get you right.
I couldn't believe that much pain,
but I'll wait till you decide.
Stay with me when I'm excited.
As if I make you never hide.
The less I'm not in love,
I love by the chance we've given both of you.
No, no, no, no, no.
From the five days through the night.
I stay with you, babe.
Will I miss out on my mind?
I love by the chance we've given both of you.
No, no, no, no.
From the five days through the night.
I stay with you, babe.
Will I miss out on my mind?
I stayed the whole day when I lost my life
If you know my name, I knew my name through the night
If you know my name, I knew my name
Of very interesting conversation, the chatroom, if I would accept an apology
Or if I'd never go on to it again, are you nuts?
Of course I'll go on to it again, are you kidding me?
I think if anything, the whole conversation about display advertising
That probably pissed Leo off
But I thought that was actually the crux of the entire broadcast
And I urge you to go and watch or listen to that
It was really good
And you're saying so myself
Stay with the heat, he's vibe
How else can you not play REM on a show about the moon?
My love before it became my life
Made it again
And become the rest of the galaxy
Made it again, yeah, yeah, yeah
Not between anyone, check there's a chance
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Mr. Fred Lassie in a breakfast house
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's wait to ester, let's play REM
See you in heaven if you may
Now, Andy, did you hear about this one?
Tell me, are you locked in the past?
And yeah, you could've been on it all the same
Are we losing touch?
If we leave, they've heard a man on the moon
If we leave, they've not set up this thing
They've not let us go
Those who swim walk in the staff room
They can't even get there
You can't even get there
Each and every struggle by the horrible hours
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Mr. Fred Lassie in a breakfast house
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Andy, did you hear about this one?
Tell me, are you locked in the past?
And yeah, you could've been on it all the same
Are you having fun?
If we leave, they've heard a man on the moon
If we leave, they've not set up this thing
They've not set up this thing
You can't even get there
Andy, did you hear about this one?
Tell me, are you locked in the past?
And yeah, you could've been on it all the same
Are you having fun?
If we leave, they've heard a man on the moon
If we leave, they've not set up this thing
They've not set up this thing
If we leave, they've heard a man on the moon
If we leave, they've not set up this thing
They've not set up this thing
Adam Koo, the second best thing you can do by yourself
In the morning
Ground control to major time
Take your protein pills and put your helmet on
Six, come and sink on down and jump
Three, two, check in, wash them and make a slow view with you
This is ground control to major time
You've really made the grade
And the papers want to know who shuts you away
Now it's time to leave the capsule if you dare
This is major tone to ground control
I'm stepping through the jaw
And I'm floating in the most peculiar way
And the stars look very different today
Here, I'm my floating rabbit again
For above the world
Flimate of this blue and there's nothing I can do
The one past one hundred thousand miles
The moon healing very still
And I think my special knows which way to go
Tell my work my love learned very much
You'd know
Ground control to major time
You're stuck in debt
That's something wrong, can you hear me, major tone
Can you hear me, major tone
She back, my bags last night, where he fly
Zero hour night. Yeah
And I'm gonna be high
I'm as the girl so much, I'm as my wife, it's lonely out of space, on such a time
I am less white
And I think it's gonna be a long, long time, took time to turn around and get to find
I'm not the man, they think I am a mom, oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Rock it man, run it out of you that I'll get lost
And I think it's gonna be a long, long time, took time to bring my stronger right
And I think I am a mom, oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Where did you love it long?
More than kind of place to raise your kids
In fact, this cold is now
And there's no one there to raise them
If you do
And all the science, I don't understand
It's just my job, but it isn't weird
Or rock at the back
Rock at my hand
Now I think it's gonna be a lot more time
We've talking now, brings me around and can do fine
No more%, man not think I am at home
I'm no no no no I'm afraid
Rockin' man, burnin' like a seas of air
And I think it's gonna be long, long, long
Just long, rings me when I get too fine
I'm not long, man, I think I am at home
I'm no no no no no no
I'm not afraid
Rockin' man, burnin' like a seas of air
And I think it's gonna be long, long, long, tight
And I think it's gonna be a long, long, long, tight
And I think it's gonna be a long long time
Hell, John is the rocket man
Of course, written by Bernie Toppin, which
Like the make mention of the fact that Bernie was in Austin
But Bernie here me
Bernie was in Austin the other day
He's on tour for his art that he does
He does paintings
And we were invited to the opening show with the gallery
And it was kind of interesting
Of course, I'm a big, big fan of all of the
Elton John, Bernie Toppin collaborations
And strings and I mean, even Crocodile Rock is one of my favorites
I'll be a fan of him
But I think I first started listening to Elton John
With the blue moves album
And I'll just tell you how it was
Kind of interesting this Mickey and I went
And he has a typical art promoter
Nice lady from Los Angeles
I guess she would have a gallery now
She goes on tour with Bernie
Looking at his art, a lot of abstract stuff
Kind of like who's afraid of red yellow and blue stuff
And boxes and a little laundry and kind of vibe
He also, I think he wants to be a cowboy
I know he lives in a ranch somewhere in southern California
And he had a couple of nice kind of Texas star
Pieces of art, you know, with lots of oil paint on it
I kind of liked it actually until I saw there was $18,000
Didn't like it that much
But she was very nice, they're all coming to me
Bernie who was probably five, four
So there's Miss Mickey and I like, hey, how you doing?
He was like, oh, I had to be so tall
You know, he took pictures kind of bending down
And then we were introduced to his wife who was six feet tall
And so he was walking hot by the way, wife number four for Bernie
But that's okay
Very, very, very kind, very nice
And when I was at least able to tell him I kind of did a fan boy thing
On him and said, you know, I really like your art
Which was kind of like a fib
It's okay
Not supersonic, but if you're a collector, you know, of course
If you got the dough, you'd love to have something from Bernie top and why not
But man, in the car I was going to go over over his discography
Just in case, I think that was like a year and a half or two years
They didn't work together
But just in case, you know, we would get to talking about music
Which of course didn't happen, you can't really expect that to happen
At one of these occasions
I have to look at the song list like, oh my god
And I think the way it works is Bernie writes the lyrics
And then he literally emails them to Elton
He probably sent them by pigeon carrier back in the day
And then Elton writes the music to it
So the stuff that comes out of Bernie top is brain is quite amazing
I must say
And of course, we'd like to always play something a little different on the daily source code
We'd like to bring out the tracks that from songs you know
But usually stuff you never hear on the radio
Now, of course, you've heard rock and man many times
Another great moon song would be a marvelous night for a moon dance fan
I happen to have a nice live version for you
So the sound of the praises that flow
And I'm trying to twist to the calling of you
High strings that place of them low
Well, and I expect it seems to whisper
Well, that's so fun, that seems to shine
And you're blessed
And I just hope a moon dance with you
I don't know
Can I do the mix of a moon dance with you
Well, I want a big love to you tonight
I can't wait till I'm all in this car
And I know now the time it is just right
It's great and tomorrow you will run
Oh, when you come, my heart will be waiting
To make sure that you're never alone
Well, and then all my dreams will come true
They're round and I will make you my own
Have a try
And I touch you, you just
But it's under
Who wants someone to
Well, that I can't hide
And I just hope a moon dance with you
I don't know
Can I do the mix of a moon dance with you
You just hope a moon dance with you
And all my dreams will come true
It's great and tomorrow you will run
All of us, all of us, all of us
All of us, and all of us, all of us
And I'll bet it's fantastic, he comes through awesome, I will definitely go take a look.
What a marvelous night for a mood dance, and this I believe is one of those tracks that
was used for the movie paper, Moonwood starred Jodie Foster when she was young.
But it wouldn't be made to leave if you'd be leaving me without your love.
It's a hunky, it's on parade without your love.
It's a melody played in a penny arcade.
It's a barn and then barely word, just as pony as it can be.
But it wouldn't be made to leave if you'd be leaving me.
Say it's on the paper, Moonwood.
But we'll be sailing over a cardboard sea.
But it wouldn't be made to leave.
If you'd be leaving me.
But it wouldn't be made to leave if you'd be leaving me.
Yes, it's only a canvas cut.
But it wouldn't be made to leave.
But it wouldn't be made to leave if you'd be leaving me.
Without your love.
It's a hunky, it's on parade without your love.
It's a melody played in a penny arcade.
It's a barn and then barely word, just as pony as it can be.
But it wouldn't be made to leave if you'd be leaving me.
It's funny, it's plain to see.
I have me, I would be if you'd be leaving me.
Of course, it's Ella with the Mills Brothers.
It's only a paper, Moon.
And I will thank you very much, Marcus Cos, once again,
couch, once again, for sending that to me.
I'm going to take that to our miss-making eye.
I don't know if you know that we have been taking dance lessons
for about four and a half, maybe five months now.
We initially started because we wanted to do a dance,
an entire choreographed number at our wedding,
which was actually intended for Christina,
of course, didn't make it because of her passport,
woes, or issues.
And it was to Charlie and the Chocolate Factory,
the pure imagination, name of the song.
I actually did a little edit of the song,
and we had dips and swirls and swings,
and we literally studied for three months.
And it turned out pretty good.
There is video of it.
And we were actually quite, people could not believe
that we were dancing like that.
We've always called each other kind of,
like, hey, we would be great ginger-rodgers for a to-stair.
And I would love to learn how to dance with this song,
with her, so I'm going to ask a Christina,
our dance instructor at Uptown Dance in Austin,
to help us, but first, right at where now
we're studying the Texas Two Step,
which by itself has a whole bunch of challenges.
I'm telling you, that's us complicated, quick, quick slow.
So this is fun, so this is holiday,
but this is where we saved our month for all year.
This is the sun, this is a good, good life.
This is where everybody wants to be,
you it out their ways.
This is where I won't be flying.
I'll be singing a moon on a moon.
Hallelujah.
I really got it made.
I got two cars on the driveway,
ready to take me anywhere.
Glory, glory.
Ooh, what a beautiful place.
All the water and the mountains.
All the people look the same.
This is where I won't be flying.
I'll be singing a moon on a moon.
He's only being submitted.
My heart hits like a drum.
I'm ready to leave this credit.
If I can find you here,
I look down every corner,
every leaf out, around.
Stop my engines, I got only this time.
I've been west, I've been losing.
I travel everywhere to find my news,
but only this I found it wasn't my news.
I woke up at the soon.
I lost everything before I reached the moon.
Now I'll still try and get them over you.
And I know where I'll be flying.
I go everywhere,
Ooh, what a beautiful place.
All the water and the mountains.
My heart beats on the moon, I've played that many times on daily source code, but well, there you go, it's very appropriate for me, so I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my
best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm able to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm gonna do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to be able to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to decir my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm just going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm just going to do my best, I'm just going to do my best, I'm going to do my best, I'm just going to do
And the song that I sing is a moonlight
I stand and I wait
For the touch of your hand
In the June night
The roses are sung
A moonlight serenade
The stars are glow
And tonight how their light sets me dreaming
My love
Do you know
That your eyes are like stars brightly beaming
I bring you
And I sing you
A moonlight serenade
Let us trade till break of day
In love's valley of dreams
Just you and I
A summer sky
I have any breeze
Kissing the trees
It's so dumb
To let me wait
Come to me tenderly
In the June night
I stand
Not your game
And I sing you a song
In the moonlight
A moonlight serenade
My darling
I am moonlight
Serenade
Or as Bobby hadn't we say a fleshlight serenade
No blue eyes
On the charlie
Absolutely lovely
By the way these songs have been put together by the one-only Margarce couch
You know the guy that kind of likes to rock out a lot
That's what you want to visit as well
Can you believe me?
Love it
Till the sun goes down
I don't need the starlight starlight
There's a magical feeling
So I
Him and steal your heart to die
You can rock
Just a heart
But you know what you know that you
Can't find the moon
I see
And I'm done
You're so random
But you know what you know that you
Can't find the moon
I know
You can't find it
It's gonna get to your heart
There's no escape from love
Was it true?
We've just been upon a heart
No matter what you think
It won't be too long
So you're in my arms
I don't need the starlight starlight
We'll be losing the rhythm
So I
Feel it steal your heart to die
You can try
Just a heart from right here
But you know what you know that you
Can't find the moon
I see
And I'm done
You're so random
But you know what you know that you can't find the moon
You can't find it
No
But you know what you do
Can't find it's gonna get to your heart
There's no escape from love
Was it true?
We've just been upon a heart
But you know what you know that you know that you can't find the moon
I see
And I'm done
You're so random
But you know what you do
Can't find it's gonna get to your heart
Just a heart from right here
But you know what you know that you can't find the moon
I see
And I'm done
You're so random
But you know what you know that you can't find the moon
You can't find it's gonna get to your heart
You're so random
But you know what you know that you can't find the moon
I see
And I'm done
You're so random
But you know what you know that you can't find the moon
You can't find it's gonna get to your heart
The theory.
Fuck all of you.
We're here to rock.
Now, we're scored.
Hey, him, though.
Come on, you're a friend.
Gary, I'm living in source pool.
Right now, stream seated, mad music.
All right, live, man.
Stream up here.
A crazy people.
Hey, you say.
10, 10, 10, rock it man.
Stop the baby.
And the man.
Take it.
Ready.
And the tips.
I'll take you rock it.
And take it down.
10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10.
You've got to be my head.
You've got to be crashing to my head.
Woah, woah, woah, woah.
I'll be, oh, rock it.
Yeah.
Snecessary.
Rock it.
Yeah, I'll be, oh, yeah, yeah.
Snecessary.
Rock, baby, come on, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy,
I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy, I run
Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock
It, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock it, Rock rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock Guitar, Rock it, Rock it rock, Rock it, Rock, Rock it, Rock it, Rock, Rock, Rock, Rock rock,
Down, down, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up
up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, down, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, setup, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. be now going, now, below, up, up, up, up, down, up. keep up to the smoke, down, down, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, back, down, up, up, up, up, up, up,
We're just got to be
We're just getting to be
Right
貸ing
With luck
go pee because misnicky is definitely laying on the the rooskees here and thank
you Mike Marlott Malaro from Austin Texas I don't know if he's listening but
he left the fireman number fireman's number four beers which is who makes
this actually let me see if I can find out who makes it is a local beer brewing
company yeah Blanco Texas is good man it's nice and smooth but of course you
only the middle man when it comes to beer right so I have to tell you another
story though so of course this entire episode is instigated by the the
moon truth in episode of this week in technology but I had to do and I told
you earlier in the show I really Mickey it suggested to me that I do a
daily source cook because I had a mental issue the last week of our hot
pockets tour and it started I'd remember very clearly where it started in
Moab on our way to back I think to we come from Salt Lake City going to
Moab then we go on to New Mexico and you know when we would pull up into
campground mismicky would do everything on the inside and I you know park the
car sometimes it have to unhitch it set the stabilizers you know hook up the
poop tube hook up all the electricity the water etc and at this point I think I
was emotionally not really emotionally but mentally drained not it's not the
driving or anything like that but that's a it's a part of it's a part of a
combination but also just meeting people and being with people continuously you
know I think it's pretty well known I'm kind of a loner I like hanging out
with Miss Mickey and sitting on the porch and do my work as a government
legislation analyst for no agenda but I I got into this weird thing I
actually I think I did mention it on maybe I mentioned it on no agenda my brain went
into a loop and I would catch myself literally singing snippets from songs or
worst jingles like devorex slash or devorex dot or slash in a or dosy
notes and mayorsy notes and little lambsy divesy I mean that's a horrible one
to have stuck in your head you know that loop but I couldn't it was I wouldn't
recognize until be going on for like half an hour and it's mainly because I'm
hooking stuff up and and normally at night when I'm in bed or in the morning
when I wake up I usually just let my brain kind of flow and I'm thinking about
things I just kind of wait to see what comes through and I would keep getting
these freaking loops in my head and I know if it's a part of just the pure
exhaustion that we had on the tour at that in combination with my OCD slash
Tourette or whatever it was but it was quite annoying and I really had a
hard time stopping it I have to really the only way to stop it would be to
think of a different song and Miss Mickey said I think quite correctly
you just gonna play some tunes on the daily source code that'll help you out
and I have to say it's absolutely healthy I never heard this song but it's
about roses and moonlight so it fits in the show it's Cheryl Crowe I like the
tune by and way I hope you enjoyed as well on the source code 866 of the
rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose rose
I have to don't create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things
I have to don't create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things
I have to don't create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things
I have to don't create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight
I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just
going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going
to create things, and tonight I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'm going to create things, but tonight I'm going to create things, I'm just going to create things, but tonight, I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'm going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'm just going to create things, but tonight I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'm just going to create things, so tonight I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'm going to create things, and tonight I'm so going to create things, and tonight I'm just going to create things, and tonight I'll create things.
I don't know, Cheryl Crow's weird, man.
I met her, I'm going to say 1987, maybe 1988, I interviewed her.
She was a backup singer for Michael Jackson on tour, crazy hair and it was really, really
sweet.
I wish I could find that interview because I remember quite simply, you're like, we're
there to interview Michael Jackson, you're right, like that's going to happen.
Yeah, so of course, they, well, you know, Mike has come on, oh, shoot me, I already left.
And we got one of the background singers for you, and she was very, very, very
sweet.
And she was like, you know, like, so, um, would you like to let get out in front of
yourself one day?
Oh, yeah.
I'd love that.
Well, there you go.
She did it.
So good on her.
Nice conversation in the chat room, no agenda stream.com, no agenda chat.net.
Well, the artwork created by yellow, yellow jacket, I guess, and he's done a fantastic
job.
You'll see you, of course, in the, in your player or on the, what do we do in, uh, it'll
be, uh, DSC86.curry.com, um, about the, I think it's a JVC boom box.
Wow, that brought back memories, huh, and what kind of cassette tape you had to have, you
know, was it the, uh, you had the metal tapes, I never liked the metal tapes.
Well, then you could, if you had the metal tape and you had Dolby on, then it sounded
okay.
But otherwise, it had a little bit too, I don't know, just had too much going on there.
I kind of like the older crappy tapes.
And by the way, yellow, there is, you do have time.
If you still want to put, uh, because I see Bobby's sitting there in the, uh, was that
like, uh, the, the, the moon rover or something or the, the, the, the moon buggy.
If you want to put her in a spacesuit, you know, there's still time, um, I still have some
songs left.
Some shit that'll take you back though, if you're old enough, like this one, Jim Morrison
in the doors.
Let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's climb to the time.
Let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the
moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait
out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait
out to the time, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's climb to the time.
Let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the
moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the
moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's climb to the time,
uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let
the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out, let's wait, let's wait out, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, let's wait, let's wait out, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait out to the moon, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait out to the moon, uh-huh, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait out to the moon, let's wait out to the moon, let us wait, let's wait, let's wait out to the moon, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait for a little 날 show, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, let's wait, oh she's like busted, yeah, oh she's like gotta get
from Camp Mofo here in the capital of the drone star state.
Notice Austin Texas since she's been so kind to hang out
and entertain us on the child room.
I think I should play a song from Ms. Bobby Eden.
I know this is one of her favorite bands.
And it actually turns out it was the first band on the moon.
Yes.
If you don't know who it is, all you have to do is just close your eyes
and listen to that bass line.
You know it's gotta be the one and only Nikki six playing it for you.
Yes, I'm the source code.
This is Bully.
Cool.
Oh.
There's a problem with the girls here on the stage.
Now, they're getting over the knees.
They're getting over the knees.
So, they seem to look everything well.
So, they seem to be a star.
God, give a frame off the narrow.
How it's played.
Oh.
I'm just a girl band and my own brains are the tears
Just a mention, how I go
Loving space
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
He can't come to suit me
Someone always has to break the rules
Like a rock, it won't come to the first man down the road
So never wanna think too loud
So we can't just think about souls
Even if we're out of tune, we're doomed all alone
Everybody wants to know that give me a sense
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
He can't come to suit me
Someone always has to break the rules
Like a rock, it won't come to the first man down the road
So we can't just think about souls
Even if we're out of tune, we're doomed all alone
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, how, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
We didn't need for that.
I still want to first pass down the road.
We didn't need for that to first pass down the road.
And I'm curious.
You see, I know you're not real man.
Because I'm loaded, okay.
I've had some experience in that area.
Besides, that whole route for yours is full anyway.
Good.
You've let's all the same crap.
Rock and roll is the only thing that counts.
Dig, hard, ass, blistering, awesome, heavy metal.
Rock and roll.
You'll see.
It's just for yourself, for me,
and this whole crambody.
And I'm got to chill, too.
You'll see.
You'll hear the harmony,
and harmony.
And we'll be on,
and we'll be here one hour,
one hour,
one day a day a day a day.
So I felt it
If you don't talk to the crowd, you're distracted by the sound
I'm standing out, I'm just splashing above you
But don't be afraid of me
Cause I wanna hurt you at all
And I was waiting to catch you to catch you
And they'll be on me
So I'm standing out, I'm just splashing above you
We're still on the ground.
Damn, I'll tell you, man.
It's only I had walking talking's back in the day.
My show would have been so much better.
Cage 9.
Beyond the Daily Source Code episode 866.
This is the Lunar Edition.
No gravity.
No.
Although maybe there's just a little bit.
Yeah, that's why those guys bounce around so much in the studio or whatever.
All right, we're winding it down.
Although I still see about 10 songs left in the box.
Good to go.
Wait for the artwork when it's done.
We'll wind it up.
That's how it works.
So easy D.C.
I'm the charcoal Charlie Hill.
Right.
Time out.
They went to the railroad.
Down the line.
Give it back.
Roll with just a one-note chance.
Give it to the one-note time.
That you do wish it was home in bed.
I'll do my best.
But I won't have a mind ahead.
Think of our problem.
I wasn't sure love that I won't.
It's your love that I need.
It's your love that I've got to help.
It's your love.
Everybody back, cross the sky.
It's what the hell was that I told.
But now, running down and chill your chill.
Go to the snow and down.
Drop the snow and look at the old free ride.
Think of our love as long as it's a bird.
It's a bird.
It's a bird which I should take care of.
To get a map of this ship.
It's a bird.
I didn't mean to hurt that woman in my life
It was a heart attack, it's a love that I want
It's a love that I need
It's a love that I have
It's a love that I don't want
It's a love that I need
It's a love that I have
It's a love
What's next to the moon?
The moon is star
Hello there, my friends in the long cabin
In tens of minutes you rocking out yet
Amazing, now you can go on in this country
It was just one topic and boy does the moon have a lot going forth in C.G.C.
What's mentioned the moon in the daily store's code 866 and I do have a couple of my own
selection that I thought about in the car like being on the phone.
Yeah, remember that?
Whatever happened to them, I love these guys as we're such a great song.
The whole of the moon, the water voice and source code 866.
I've pictured a rainbow, you held it in your hands, I had flashes, you saw the plan,
I wandered out in the world for years, but you just stayed in your room, I saw the
present, you saw the whole of the moon, the whole of the moon, you held it in the
turnstels for the wind and your heels, you spetched all the stars and you know how it
feels to reach too high, too far, too soon, you saw the whole of the moon, I was granted
where you filled the skies, I was dumbfounded by truth, you cut too late, I saw the ring dirty
valley, you saw the ringer do, I saw the present, you saw the whole of the moon,
I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do,
I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do,
I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do,
I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ring
do, I saw the ringer does, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringel do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do, I saw the ringer do
The trees and the speckling
Carrying a red fire moon light
Shadows sing a song from the wind
Shadows sing a red fire moon light
Carry the way, find me my shadow
Start what's going in so very light
Fall away on the other side
Will you come to turn to me this nest
That you couldn't find what I was through
I say, I bless you in heaven
I bless you in heaven
The one day
Will you come to turn to me this nest
That you couldn't find what I was through
I say, I bless you in heaven
I bless you in heaven
The one day
Will you come to turn to me this nest
That you couldn't find what I was through
I say, I bless you in heaven
The one day
Will you come to turn to me this nest
That you couldn't find what I was through
I say, I bless you in heaven
The one day
Will you come to turn to me this nest
That you couldn't find what I was through
field, vocally assisted by Maggie Riley, I think, was her name. Irish girl, girl,
you know. And you know, by the way, I got a voicemail from Bobby early this week. And
you know, she wants to, I think, she wants to live in the United States full-time. And
she's working on her paperwork. I think she's actually getting, getting an O1, which is
for exceptional talent in the arts, which no one can disagree with, obviously. But she
may need a few resumes, you know, to convince Lucy Napolitano that she's legit. So if that
were to be the case, I'm sure that we can arrange a couple hundred from the Debbie Source Code
list. I'm sure you guys would be more than happy to help out, right? Hey, if we're doing a full-on
lunar edition, we just can't miss one of my favorite categories of music. And that, of course,
would be country. And if you're going to talk about country, you might as well get this crap.
Oh crap, if you, he will edit that. If you're going to talk about country, you might as well get
the two top guys in the business. Here we go. Go. Yeah, can't win them all, I guess.
I'll talk to my books and done, of course. Me on moon. When the sun goes down on my side of
town, then no sun feeling comes to my door over a time. Blue. There's a run-bound bar across the
railroad park. I got a table or two, way back where I said no, thank goodness you.
I spent most of it night beneath the light of a neon moon.
Now if you lose your heart, it's lonely, it's always to be far, lonely.
Don't watch your broken dreams dancing out of the beans, ever neon moon.
I think the two young lovers are running wild and free. I've lost my nose and sometimes see you settle.
But it's not for you, Rose. Don't tell me how many tears I've said here, Rose.
I'll have many lives that I've lied to in my heart.
See you come back someday. Oh, but I'll be all right. As long as there's light for my neon moon.
Oh, if you lose your heart, it's lonely, it's always to be far, lonely.
Don't watch your broken dreams dancing out of the beans, ever neon moon.
If you'd buy to play it's home, bring back, and the words that I've never said, songs in the
same way. And it's heard inside. They never got me. Oh, but I'll be all right. As long as there's light for my neon moon.
Oh, if you lose your heart, it's lonely, it's always to be far, lonely.
Don't watch your broken dreams dancing out of the beans, ever neon moon.
Watch your broken dreams dancing out of the beans, ever neon moon.
Yeah, they are kind of the go-to guys. If you look for something like the country genre,
Brooks, and Dunn, although I don't see him win too many words anymore on the country music awards.
All right, add two more songs. Let's just stay kind of in this vibe for a second. One more,
it's all lunar edition. Send me the moon. Sarah Burrell is on the Charlie.
To live on all with a pieces and parts of me left.
Every last day seemed to carry the weight of a lifetime.
Watch from the ground as the gold fluttered down from the sky.
Sweet sun, send me the moon.
Empty the skies out, bringing me one step closer to you, send it to you.
I will wait and breathe out till you come in and out, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I'm still here, I'm sinking like standing your sea
So it's time to send me home
Empty the skies out, bringing me one step closer to you
Send it soon, I won't breathe in, breathe out
Till you're coming in now, call me you
You already do
Never you mind whether you look should find us together
Distance can take what is hidden here safe in my chest
Wait for the day when we finally say no, never
Till then I'll be here wanting more as I settle for
At once we've switched on, send me home
Empty the skies out, bringing me one step closer to you
Send it soon, I won't breathe in
I won't breathe in, breathe out
Till you're coming in now, call me you
You already do
Never you mind whether you look should find us together
Oh man, that's such a pretty song
You know that's about all you can hear on the road by the way
When you're driving around these great states of
Communication, it's country music and sometimes you hit upon a station
It really is playing some of these tunes, very very nice
And just as I was about to start whining it down, I got an email from Mike D.
He said, dude, how can you not play King's Harvest?
So right, we got a dance in the moonlight baby, you and me
And Bobby makes three, I made a rhyme
But yeah, we get it almost every night
And when that moon gets a pain and bright
It's super natural that light
Everybody was dancing in the moonlight
Everybody here is outside
But they don't bark and they don't bite
They keep things loose, they keep things alive
Everybody with dancing in the moonlight
Dancing in the moonlight
Everybody with all that freedom
All that bright in the sunshine
Everybody with dancing in the moonlight
Like a phone and we never fight
But you can't dance and stay up tight
It's super natural that light
Everybody with dancing in the moonlight
Dancing in the moonlight
Everybody with all that freedom
All that bright in the sunshine
Everybody with dancing in the moonlight
Everybody here is outside
But they don't bark and they don't bite
They keep things loose, they keep things alive
Everybody with dancing in the moonlight
Dancing in the moonlight
Everybody with feeling warm and bright
It's a super trough fine and natural sight
Everybody with dancing in the moonlight
Everybody with feeling warm and bright
Everybody's excited, oh you're like a footballer dancing in the moonlight
Everybody's feeling, oh, I'm blind, so don't find them after sight
Everybody's dancing in the moonlight, everybody's feeling, oh I'm blind
Everybody's feeling, oh I'm blind
What an obvious choice, I'm so glad we got that one at the very last minute
There we go, two hours and 33 minutes, it's a magic time to leave
And I want to thank everyone for participating once again
On the live stream, no agenda stream.com
I think you'd get mostly for flipping the switch
Mr. Oil, of course
Thank you Bobby Eden for dropping by, beautiful to have you along
And a yellow jacket for the artwork
Marcus Cowche, executive producer of all the music on your program
So next time we get together, I think we're doing the fire episode
We'll have to do that one pretty soon because that is specifically going to be produced for fire fighters
Fighting wildfires all across a good donation
And how could I not end the show without thanking my lovely wife, Miss Mickey
For prompting me, supporting me, and getting me getting my ass and gear to do the show
And clearing the decks in order for me to do it and supplying me with nice databases to get it done
So I want to leave you with a song that even your mom will love
Talk to you next time, charcoal heads, bye-bye
You're way too busy
I'll see the world, there's such a lot of work to see
We're after the same
We're from the day
From my heart from the friend
We'll see you with stars from me
We'll be with you
Wherever you're going, I'm going your way
To the rivers of the city world
There's such a lot of work to see
We're after the same old man
My heart from the friend
We'll be with you