Delta Sheriff Charlie's 7-9-8, we're so screwed.
Hey, everybody, it's the Poo-Bar Friday.
The extended Saturday edition, enjoy.
It was $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You're so handsome. You're well. You're time.
You're ideas. No barcode. No party. No ideas.
You're fancored. You're licensed. You're thoughts.
You're fears. No sim card. No disco. No photo.
Not here. You're blood. You're sweat. You're passions. You're regrets.
You're profits. You're time off your passions. You're sick.
You're pills. You're grats. You're tips. You're laughs. You're false. We won't.
We won't. You're false.
You're habit. You're fat. You're cured.
Give us your address, your shoe size two years.
Your digits, your plans, your number, your eyes, your schedule.
Your discount, your gift, your life.
You're jealous, you're jealous, you're jealous, you're jealous.
You're home.
Here.
Take credit, take insurance, take a loan.
Get a job, get a pension.
Get a haircut, get a suit.
Plating the laundry, play food while playing the field.
Smart time, too.
We'll show you three.
Get show you three.
We'll buy you three.
You're emotions.
You're love.
You're dreams.
You're typical.
Your relationship, your sweat, your screams.
You're securing your subratives.
your innocence, your society, your slows, your place, your distance, your space.
Go back to bed, America. Your government is in control again.
Here's what's this, shut up.
You are free to do as we tell you, you are free to do as we tell you.
Here's what's this, you are free to do as we tell you.
Go back to bed, America, your government is in control again.
Here's American Gladiators, watch this, shut up.
Go back to bed, America.
Here's American Gladiators.
Here is 56 channels of it.
Watch these picturing guitars, they're from their skulls together,
and congratulate you.
Let me know that they're free to do as we tell you.
We're free to do as we tell you.
Here's what's this, you are free to do as we tell you.
That's right, America, everything's okay.
Go back to your living rooms and watch American Gladiators.
Your government is in control.
No, it's not the same.
The metropolitan police of London had millions of stacked up there as a safe haven.
And now the money's been locked up.
What does the Prime Minister of the United Kingdom do?
Gordon Brown.
He invokes the terrorism law.
He says, hey, wait a minute, you know, we've got to freeze everything up here because
these guys nice and they're, it's just terrorists practices to lock up our money.
How are you nuts?
This is crazy.
This Europe is falling apart at right there, right in front of your very eyes.
No coordination whatsoever.
And I am now more convinced than ever that the entire push behind the Lisbon treaty.
Go ahead and Google it.
Go on Google news and you'll see that they're still really pushing to get this thing wrapped
up as soon as possible with a second referendum.
God bless the Irish.
They were so smart.
They wanted this Lisbon treaty done because it would have gone into effect around
now.
Round October would have been ratified by all the countries just in time for the world financial
system.
This is what they have been planning for maybe decades as far as I'm concerned.
Bankrupt all of the banking system get everything to flush it all out.
All the G7 finance ministers were in Washington yesterday in this morning and they've been
meeting, but they've been meeting about, they've been meeting about one financial system,
maybe even one bank.
And they're going to, and you can mark my words on it right now, right this down.
They're going to come back with some kind of new financial system, what they need now
is time to rewrite all the rules and it's going to be something based on carbon credits.
Mark my words, my friends.
We'll get into that a little bit later on because I do want to get to the music because
we've got plenty to do today.
Just one more thing about the absurdity of what's going on with Iceland.
This comes from the BBC, Norwegian politician, I'm sorry, I said Iceland, but now I
want to talk about how crazy our elected officials are in Norway, there you go.
Norwegian politicians said she will not seek reelection after running up a large phone
bill, ringing fortune tellers at Parliament's expense.
Sarah Khan, Minister of Parliament for the ruling labor party, amidst calling paper, minute
fortune tellers, 793 times in one nine month period for a total of 133 hours.
This is what they've resorted to.
Their freaks, the people running our governments think about it, who are these people?
Their crazies, their lunatics, of course not all of them, but you can bet a good 75 to 80%
are just fucking wackos.
That's why they took those gigs in the first place and crazies attract crazies.
That's exactly what's going on.
Ah, fortune tellers, can you believe that ship?
Anyway, what has happened now?
You heard it there in the beginning from Adam Freeland, we want your soul.
Everything's being taken away from us systematically and everything you thought that was
all a part of your reality, there was a part of what you quote owned.
You may wake up one day and you say, how did I get here?
This is not my beautiful house, this is not my beautiful car.
No, it belongs to the government, you are screwed.
You may find yourself living in a shut-con chat, you may find yourself in another part of the world.
And you may find yourself behind the wheel of a large automobile.
You may find yourself in a beautiful house with a beautiful wife, you may ask yourself, no, how did I get here?
You may find yourself behind the wheel of a large automobile.
And you may ask yourself, how did I get here?
And you may ask yourself, where is that love, daughter of a beer?
And you may tell yourself, this is not my beautiful house.
And you may tell yourself, this is not my beautiful wife.
Same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was.
Same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was.
What are the jobings and what are the moves?
There is water at the bottom of the ocean, under the water, kind of the water.
And you may find yourself behind the wheel of a large automobile.
Same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was.
Same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, same as it ever was, so as it ever was, same as it ever was.
You might ask yourselves, what is that beautiful house?
You might ask yourself, who does that, how they go to?
You might ask yourself, I'm alright, I'm alone, and you may say to yourself,
I'm not God, what have I done?
And you may say to myself, whatever, come in, I understand where's my life?
What a growing heart, that doesn't bid it blindly
into the silent world of the fog replaced?
Where's yours with what?
And you may ask myself, I'm alright, I'm alone, and you may say to yourself,
whomever you convince them to be born with nothing my money can do.
The party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's
coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party the party's coming, the party's coming, this party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming, the party's coming,
very, very lucky that I consciously lived, as far as I was concerned, freely through the 80s
and most of the 90s, and here we are in the zeros, in the knots, as we see and say in the UK,
a whole new ballgame. What exactly is it all going to mean? Well, it means that we are
making a massive reset. When the Dow Jones falls and it will fall down further, I
believe we will probably see 7,500 this coming week on the Dow. It could even go 6,000 or
even 5,000. We are really resetting. Are we going back to the life of the 1950s? Very, very
possible. And by the way, we are all screwed. It doesn't matter how much money you have.
It's all going to be reset. It's going to be bait. There will be new standards. I mean,
just look at the coordination of the lowering of the central banks for their interest rates.
They did it all simultaneously. So it's not to screw one currency over the other. Of course,
all currencies are severely suppressed right now, except for the dollar. It's being held up completely
on, well, I guess it's the faith and credit of the United States, whatever you want to call
up, but it's all manipulated. All of these markets are. And it's been going on for decades.
And now it's finally come home to Roost. And this is not just the mistake. It's not like
no one could see this. Even I can understand how this worked. This was planned. Totally totally
planned. And how do you know? I know it's planned. Well, because the signs have been there.
The warnings have been there. Smart people have been telling us this for years. And this
kind of what bumps me out, honestly, is that I certainly wasn't listening. And by the way,
we're not going to change anything overnight. It'll take a long time for us to change,
but just by realizing what's going on, just by understanding the situation will help us,
because wow, I sure wish I could take some of that anger that people are feeling about the
possibility of Obama not becoming president. And how angry everyone is, I wish I could take
some of that anger and focus it on the fact that both parties are the same. That they're all
out to screw us. They're owned by the corporations and by Wall Street. And who's been preaching
this? Who has been preaching this for decades? Let's step in the way back machine, my friends.
My chuckleheads. The community that is awake and listened to Dr. Ron Paul from 1983,
25 years ago. He knew it was going on, but we didn't listen. There is no other power greater than the
power over money. The power to create and contract the money supply. The power to control the
purchasing power of your money for out history. This has proven to be the most sought after monopolistic
power of man. It has been come more sophisticated over the decades and over the centuries,
more sophisticated now and more international and scope than ever before. So I see the issue of
power and the control over money as being something that we cannot ignore, we must address.
I believe closely associated with this is the issue of morality as well. By what moral right
we have to create purchasing power out of thin air. Whether it's done by the creation of credit
or federal reserve notes or whether it's the creation of SDRs in an international scope,
by what right do they do this? Is it any more moral to dilute the value of your purchasing
power or the money you hold in your wallet than it is for the farmer to dilute the milk supply
with water? I would say there's an issue of morality here just as strong as the issue of power.
I also happen to believe also because it's a moral issue more than an economic issue. It is for this
reason that people have lost trust in their government, trust in the banks, trust in business,
trust in themselves and that we are a nation of distrust. It is for this reason I believe that
until we restore trust in government, trust in the system and trust in the money,
there will be no resolution of this problem. It is the issue of trust in people and trust in money
that must come before you can start talking about nickeling and diamond that trying to get back
to a balance budget because that certainly hasn't worked. So I think it's important to address the
issue of central planning. The issue of power and third, I think that we must address in general
terms the issue of the origin of money. I know that's been talked about and we recognize those
of us who believe in commodity money. Clearly understand that money, paper money and credit creation
didn't come out of the marketplace. That came out of the heads and the fantasies of the
intellectuals and the government officials of those who want paper to be money but never
out of the marketplace. So I would say the paper standard is bucking history and it's bucking
economic law and economic truth and they only can do it with force and more power to make people
accepted because economically and historically paper is not money. It can't be money. It's only
money because we're forced to use it and because there's a residual trust in the pieces of paper
that we cared around because at one time it did help real value. You have to have something
that people seek after and they hold as something important is something that they will hold
as money. History shows that people have chosen gold first and probably silver second and rather
have cigarettes than pieces of paper.
I felt this way, a lot of times we live in our way, who we will not only just say, and nothing else
lost love. Trust us in their mind in you, every day more or something new. Open mind more and different
you and nothing else matters.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they know.
Never came for what I know.
So close to no matter how far, can we reach more and more,
to remember our trust in you and everything else matters.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they know.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do.
Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what
they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never
came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. It turned out to be a good thing. Never get in touch them. Never came for what they do. Never came for forgotten what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they did. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never come for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. não came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for what they do. Never came for
all. And I wanted to see is it from CNBC?
Just check. Let me see this. Oh no. Yeah, it is actually. This is from the UK version.
I think of Squawk Box. And on the program, they have legendary investor, Jim Rogers.
And so, you know, we heard Ron Paul talk 25 years ago. Now, listen to what Jim Rogers,
who is a very wealthy man, he definitely knows how to play the markets, listen to what
he's saying about what's going on right now. Jim, of course, a legendary investor.
Jim, can I start off by asking you why you think the equity markets are not responding
to the stabilization plans that are being introduced around the world at the moment?
Because they're absurd. Jeff, we have people. If I had come on your show every week for
100 weeks in a row, and everything I said to you was wrong, would you keep me on your
show? Would you have any confidence in me? Would you listen to me? Mr. Paul, Mr. Bernanke and
the guy at the New York Fed, Tim, somebody every week. They have been dead wrong.
Absolutely. This is what I love about the internet. You can track all this stuff. They
have been wrong. Because they've been lying to us.
Would you listen to them? I wouldn't listen to them. Jim, but we all were we all. And this
is so funny. The guy from CNBC. Okay. This is not the answer he wants to hear. He doesn't
want to hear the death doom and destruction message. No, no, because we want a controlled
situation. We don't want any losers. It has to be controlled so we can all kind of smoothly
regain. It's not the way it works. I think our audience would love to know from you what
you're actually doing with your money right now. Because you obviously will be seeing
some opportunities here. I'm sure you've kept some of your own power to drive. Maybe you
could give our audience some advice as to how Jim Rogers is allocating his capital.
Well, I have an enormous amount of cash and I've been using it to buy more Japanese yen,
more Swiss francs, more agricultural products. There's a liquidation phase going on here for
everything is being liquidated. I bought agricultural last week and it's down this week.
So pay close attention to what he's saying. First of all, he's moving into the Japanese
yen and the Swiss franc. Those are the safe havens. So if you want to do anything with your money,
buy that. I recommend this. It looks months ago. I told you I'm totally out of the markets.
I've got nothing but cash and gold. I've been very open about that. I've shared that with the
chuckleheads and the no agenda audience. I did interviews in the Netherlands for investor magazine.
And I said this very same thing. I've got cash in four different currencies and four different
banks around the world. I've got gold physically in my hands or close enough to it.
And of course everyone. I'm crazy. Crazy curry. Now I'm getting emails from people saying,
hey, wow. I'm even being compared. They're putting me in statements with bank directors of like
ING. No, then your curry strategy doesn't sound too stupid now. Yeah. Exactly. But there is a
liquidation process going on. They're liquidating everything. They being the guys you're seeing on TV.
Paulson, Bernanke. Now we've got Paulson's old buddy. He's assistant. Basically his PA is
personal assistant is now spending our money. And essentially blending it back to us.
Charging more interest. It's nuts. Let's listen to more of Jim Rogers. You know, they're selling
everything inside. But that's what I've covered some shorts. I covered a few shorts here today.
That's what I'm doing with my money now. Let's do that at some point. This got to end. Right.
And at which levels in the markets would you start thinking, you know what companies look
cheap enough for me right now to get back into equities? I'm not sure. I want to buy equities when
the market caves in. I don't think equities are going to come out of this on top. Normally when you
have a panic, the way you make money is you buy the things where the fundamentals have been
unimpaired and they will lead the market coming out. Most equity, I mean Morgan Stanley's not coming
out of this unimpaired. So I'm buying our commodities. I'd come out. So funny. Again, he's saying,
I'm not going to get back into the market. Are you nuts? I'll buy stuff that's, you know, bricks. I'll
buy oil, probably, although I wouldn't be in oil right now. Because that's going down to 50 or 60
bucks. But he's saying, buy fundamentals, buy real things. Forget the stock market. It's fake.
That's essentially what he's saying. And they don't want to hear this answer. Listen, the only thing
I know that are coming out of this unimpaired was supply and demand is still terribly out of bounds.
And the Japanese Jan and this was right. There's a real feeling at least here in Asia of helplessness.
Watching what's being done in the financial markets here, the disease. The wealth destruction
that's happening through no fault of their own. The Asian seem to feel because this was a problem
that was primarily a western financial system problem. But Asia is not immune to this.
I happened to agree. I thought it out of rages. Did anybody has the step in and bail out of
a bunch of 29 euros driving miles around? Oh, I love that. Outrageous that anyone has to step in
and bail out a bunch of 29-year-olds driving mouserodies. Absolutely. We nuts. Obama and McCain voted
for that. Why? Because they are under control. Money owns all. The money talks.
What about all the people and countries that monitor their manners? Save their money. Didn't
get overextended. And now all of a sudden they're being asked to bail out a bunch of guys on Wall Street
who were incompetent at death and some of them crooks. I found it outrageous. But by the way,
even if it's not outrageous. The way to solve this problem is to let people go bankrupt. All of this
pumping money into the system is not going to save it. You see what the market is saying. The market
says we don't buy that. Let people go bankrupt. Then you will hit bottom and then you will start over.
The people who are sound will take over the assets from the people who are unsound and we will start
over. This is the way the world has worked for a few thousand years. Exactly. This is exactly it.
And Dr. Ron Paul will back him up on that because I've heard him say it. You got to let everything go
bankrupt. You just got to do it. Now, of course, as they were on the way to this controlled financial
economic collapse, they changed the rules in the United States. It made it much harder to actually
go bankrupt because, wow, we don't want to get late. You get away with anything. No, no, no,
that's we're going to take all your real stuff. All the stuff that you actually own that is tangible
and you can touch. We're going to take that bandits. Yeah, but Jim, we do want to know the
Lee restructuring of the financial accordingly. We're currently one to throw lots of people out of
jobs because we have a little bit because we are a society that no longer understands losers.
Someone has to lose in this game. It's always worked that way. Now, just lots of people got to
lose at the same time. It's unfortunate. But any other way will be prolonged and much more painful.
And by the way, we have a responsibility not to let our friends and neighbors just die on the street
because everything's being taken away from them. We have to help them. No one's talking about that.
This is the problem in the global economy at this stage. And that's the issue here, isn't it?
We don't want to go back to depression, era, economics just because we cannot manage and
orderly deleveraging of the financial economy. Jeff, we had the worst successes we've had in
the more credit markets in world history. You think we just wake up one morning and say, oh,
well, we had a horrible, horrible period of excess. And now everything's okay. We're just going to
ignore that. We're going to have to take some pain, Jeff. Never before in world history,
well, people able to buy houses with no money down. Many people bought four or five houses with no
money down and no job. And then they did it with cars and student loans and credit card loans.
You think we just say, well, that's too bad. We're going to start over. Nobody loses his job.
Jeff, leave realistic. You got to see the rest of this interview is just too funny.
The people from CNBC just don't want to take that for an answer. Like, yeah, but we want an orderly.
We want don't want anyone to get hurt. That's not the plan, my friends. They mean for you to get hurt.
Utilize your freedom, my friends. Utilize it. We really need to watch out for one another right now.
And the chuckle heads are waking up even the most skeptic. Hey, out of my no two calls and
one days a lot, but I was just listening to the latest daily source code. And it occurred to me
you have overlooked one of the ultimate conspiracy theories. I don't know about that. And this one,
I might actually buy engine. This is Chris from Seattle. The one who always does your full crap
about this conspiracy stuff. But this one I actually, I guess. I think it's what is it crazier than a
shithouse rat. That's what you call me, right? See this happening. Something that's reconfigured too.
So I find it an interesting quote unquote coincidence. The entire world banking system is
melting down at the same time. You know the easiest way to have a United Federation of
countries, you know, startfully academy or whatever. You know, the quickest way to get to a global
one world governance would be to hold it by the ball through it's first string. So the minute all
the banking system is not down, everyone's going to have to reboot their economy. And why not?
Just since we're now in a global market, why don't we just reboot the entire world of
the economy? Everyone's switching over to the exact same currency. It'd be much easier.
When you want to have the economy and when the dollar is not worth anything, and the pound is now
not worth anything. And then the euro is not worth anything. So stability needs to be brought into play.
And no one wants to go to the Rouple. So why not start a new currency altogether and put everyone
under the exact same monetary system all over the world? Or at least we'll put the majority of
us under and then bring in the little countries like Zimbabwe later. I can see that happen.
That's the first period by and to, anyway, I don't know, it's one of the best I've ever did.
Chris, you could not be more clairvoyant. And by the way, you know, I tell you to ignore mainstream
news. There are two recommendations I would make. The financial times, which you can find at
ft.com as well as Bloomberg, which you can find at, of course, Bloomberg.com. So yesterday, Chris
won those lines. Italian Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi said political leaders are discussing
the idea of closing the world's financial markets while they quote rewrite the rules of international
finance. This was of course on a day when the Dow was went down. But this was the time this was
said the Dow was going down to 8,500. So listen to what he's saying. He's saying, you know,
I'm pretty sure that we're just going to close on the markets rewrite the rules. Yeah, of course,
they're going to rewrite the rules. They're going to change it. They're going to add in all these
carbon credits because they need something that is finite. They need a resource of there's only
so much. Now, of course, this is all bullshit and all made up. And you know, my stance on that,
the basic elements of life, the sun, the seas, and water, oxygen, and CO2. It's what the
plants and the trees live on. It's a it's a given take. Of course, we need to clean up the earth
and we need to stop raper and we need to utilize the alternative energy that we already have
access to and we need to let our true creative spirits find more because they are out there.
I'm convinced they've been held back from us. Just look at the work that Tesla was doing over 100
years ago. And so of course, the carbon credits, that's going to be the new type of money.
And yes, they're going for a one world banking system, a one world financial system. I'm
pretty confident. It's all been set up and orchestrated. The European Union was supposed to be
an integrated part of this. Didn't quite happen because the Lisbon Treaty did not pass.
And then hours later, Italian Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi reversed his comments that leaders
are discussing closing the world's financial markets while they quite quote rewrite the rules
of international finance. Berlusconi says, I heard it on the radio. The hypotheses
wasn't put forward by any leader, including myself. Man, he got a call didn't he?
And red phone was going, Silvio, what the fuck are you doing? Don't tell him what we're doing,
dude. Don't let him know. Remember when Congress had a secret meeting, closed meeting this
couple months ago. And many congressmen said, no, I don't want to have any part of that,
but a whole bunch of them did go in and they said, well, you know, now we kind of know it's leaked out
through, uh, I think a mainly Australian newspapers, but a number of other mainstream publications
of now basically said, look, they was all about the collapse of the financial system. When it was
going to happen, how was going to happen? And of course, the actual possibility of martial laws,
people see their money dry up. And right now, certainly in the United States, we're all hanging
on to this dream that Obama's going to come in and he's going to save the day and everyone will
have a beautiful world. And it's just not true. It doesn't matter if it's McCain or if it's Obama,
and we'll be talking more about how the elections are rigged, how it works the United States,
because there's not just two representatives of the same party, the Democratic and the Republicans.
There are independence with many different and varied views, and they actually kind of all agree
with each other and what should be done. But they're not participating in the debates. I don't have
the money. Good shipment. Obama's going to do a half hour commercial on ABC or probably NBC.
Can we have that cost by a half hour of prime time television? If any idea, there's no way.
And what is America doing? What is the rest of the world doing? We're just stuck to our television
sets. We're completely hypnotized. It's okay, America. Your government is in control. Go back
to your living rooms. And please watch American Gladiators. You are free. Even Glenn Beck understands
what's happening. Here's one of his most recent shows. Listen to this. Don't trip you out.
Here we go. It's a recording from YouTube. You and I grew up in
is gone. And maybe it's gone forever. If we don't wake up now, McCain said last time,
was anybody stunned by, I want to buy up all the bad mortgages, so there would be no foreclosures
as this outrageous as that was that news for you gang. It's already in the bailout bill. Believe
it or not, Paulson can do that. He doesn't have to even ask you anymore. There is a global meltdown
coming. It is a global depression and one world currency and one world financial system is the end
game. China said last week they want one global currency. France said yesterday or the day before
that they want one world order, a new world order at the end of this event. Two nights ago,
the government used $900 billion of your money to give loans to businesses and guarantee those loans.
Did they even ask you? That's your money last night for the first time. The interest rate was
cut globally. Yep. Hey man, don't believe me. Believe me on this if you do. We're not going
to fix this overnight, but we've got to be awake alert and help each other out and pass the
word. Wake people up to what's going on. I wish I had listened 25 years ago, man. They were telling
me that message was in the music I wasn't listening.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Nightingale, Nightingale, Yeah, Nightingale Yooh刚才, Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Really, really bums me out that I wasn't paying attention.
It's so on came out and like 81 or 82, maybe even earlier than that, David Bowie 1984, that's right, they got cameras,
they're watching us, they've got to face recognition, license plate number, recognition, GPS, RFID,
and now they've taken our money. Next step, electronic money based on carbon credits.
And if you don't behave, they'll just turn off your money. Still time to go out and buy gold,
chuckle heads. Look, we're buying a house, needs some real assets, something that they can't take away from us,
because my money is no good, it's just as worthless as your money, it's just papers, just entries in a couple of banks,
it doesn't really mean anything. And with hyperinflation, which means you put all this money into the market,
you print it up, that means the money becomes worth less. That's where the word comes from, of course, worth
less. And this is proof is right there, where the dollar went up, gold went up as well. It had to,
it had to, because there's no value left to this paper money. As Ron Paul said, cigarettes are worth more,
in my case, hell yeah. There are heroes in this, and they're starting to pop up, and I want to
bring attention to them. The first hero is a sheriff in Chicago, sheriff, by the way, is very interesting
position in the United States. It's pretty high on the on the state level of sheriff, just like the
world, the wild west, you know, can do a lot, can say a lot. They don't wear hats anymore and spurs.
In fact, if you take a look at the CNN report on this story, show notes of links in the show notes,
of course, a daily source code.com. This is Sheriff Thomas J. Dart, and he has been tasked as
all law enforcement in the United States, and you'll see this happen in other countries if it is
an already, you just don't have as many reports yet, where, you know, people can't pay their
mortgage, they get kicked out of their house. It's called foreclosure. And the guys walk up, they say,
hey, you got to get out and they pack up your shit, they throw it into a van, and you're out,
you're out, and they board it up, done. The bank is repossessed. Of course, the government is now
repossessed, now that the government owns most of the banks and owns the mortgages directly.
So here's what's happening to many people who are renters, think that you're going to be
Scott-free, I don't think so. So you're renting a house from someone who has some form of lean or
some kind of mortgage or loan against the house that they're renting to you. They default on the
mortgage. The bank says, okay, that's ours. Kick the renters out. Kick the renters out. Even though
if you've paid your rent on time forever, you're getting kicked out. Your shit is being thrown out
on the street, literally. And this true patriot, this true American hero, Sheriff Dart,
said, I'm not doing it anymore. I'm just not going to do this. You can, you can sue me. You can do
whatever you want, but my people are not going to his people, his staff. We are not going to throw
people out on the street who are innocent victims of all of this, innocent victims. It's a great story,
great patriot, and I'm so happy that he's doing that. And that's just one of the many, many voices.
I want to talk a little bit about some armed forces stuff just to stay with the 1984
vibe and the theme of the United Kingdom, which of course collects more data on its citizens and
inhabitants of the country than any other country I know, truly get my own nation.
Have lost yet again, more data that they've collected, 100,000 members of the armed forces,
personnel data gone. It was held by EDS, as supposed to be a real company. That's their main
IT contractor. 100,000 records, including names, addresses, passport numbers, dates of birth,
driving license, details of those serving in the Army Navy and RAF. The Air Force includes
next-of-kind details, as well as information on 600,000 potential services, applicants, and the
names of referees. Officials said it also may include some bank account details. What the hell are
they doing with the bank account details? Maybe they didn't even lose it. We just got stolen
by another division. They incompetent. We've got to rise up against this. I don't expect
that to happen tomorrow. We've got to get a lot more pissed off before all that happens.
The Army now being used to find the new black gold. It's going to be water. I think I've said
many, many years that water is the next oil. Water that can be as drinkable, that is healthy.
Great story on Reuters about that, about American troops in Iraq, securing water, water resources.
It's all happening. It's all taking place right before our very eyes. All right, we'll get back
that. Let's do a little bit of fun stuff. Just to lift the mood for a second. Because we're not dead yet,
we can still have fun in games. Can we?
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show. I review we paint them up to blob,
sketch a grips with sonic chronicles on the DS. You can win copies of FIFA O9 for the PlayStation 3
and we meet the monsters of Games of War 2. That's all the gamesweasel.com.
Hey Adam, how are you doing? Hey Young pretty good. It is hit test number 142.
This is considered right away with intro number one.
I want one. I'm sure though.
I want your love, um, cheek. I think it is. I want your love.
Yeah. Number two.
Diamond flame.
Move again, Chris Ria. We'll look you think it's over.
I think. Short intro there though.
And number three.
That's a tragedy, VG.
And good songs, young. It was a financial crisis theme show.
And it's time for the answers in this week. They're all from
and this is answer number. Oh, it's good times. She's good times.
I got cheap right at least.
Good times.
These are not good times.
You are short again.
All right, one star for getting a cheek right. She gets answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
This is rock. She music. She is.
Oh, I was wrong and I want.
We're still so cool.
It sounded just like Chris Ria.
Oh, kiss tonight.
Just kill and guess who's not in the way the heart is.
That's way.
That's way, that's way.
Dance away, rock. She music has answered number two.
And this is answer number three.
The VG. Strategy.
The VG has answered number three.
And this concludes hit this number 142.
So Adam, how did you do this week?
I thought I did better. You only got three out of six.
I really thought I was press three. I fully think it's over. It was boxing music.
Let me find that song.
All right, the usual place to find the answers to this and any other hits.
And also the links to iTunes. You can buy the tracks featured in it.
This online is hit this.mifio.com.
Thank you for playing Adam.
Oh, thank you.
Don't want else. Thank you for listening. Next week, I hope to be back for another hit this.
So until then, take care. Have fun.
And remember try to think with your heart. Bye-bye.
Well, even though I missed out on a young, you give me a great idea.
I just went into my library and pulled this one out.
Miss Chris Ria, full of you think it's over.
We'll save your tears.
God isn't here.
I've been to save my tears.
I'll be where I'll live.
Save your cryin' for the day.
Oh, if you think it's over, I can take care of my heart.
Oh, if you think it's over, tell you why.
She won't know.
No one has alwaysносed me.
Look at the morning sun.
Who would give me a kiss?
Well, I just mean God.
This day they dream.
Such a tragic saying
Not your crown, no matter who he is
I was one of the pride
And I am pride
Seed your team
That isn't you
Who would if you think it's your home
All of you say goodbye
Did you want?
If you think it's your home
I'm pride, I'm pride, I'm pride
Seed your team
That isn't you
Who would if you think it's your home
Did you want?
If you think it's your home
I'm pride, I'm pride, I'm pride
I'm pride, I'm pride
How all has always piled up and
I was going to get the morning sun
Oh, I can't think it's over
Just begun
I'll buy you first but one
Oh, you have a real good time
You say your time
Two ways to interpret this song of course
You could say, fool if you think it's over
That the crisis is over
Or
You traitors
Governmental traitors
Fool if you think it's over
You think we're done?
You think we're over?
No, we're just getting started
It may take another five years, ten years
Twenty years
We're not going to let you win
I like you steal from us
We're connected
We're protecting the internet with our lives
We have to protect these free channels
Keep everything wide open
Because that's the one thing that they messed up on
And the internet is so completely intertwined
And ingrained into society that they can't shut it down
But they are definitely going to try and hit you with the last mile
And any other place they can
You're mobile phone
There's no way they're going to let anything
Really through there
They don't want to
They're setting it all up
They're infrastructures coming
So we have to fight against that
We really do have to get pissed off
But we got to watch it
People have laughed at me about
What I'm about to tell you
This is a story from Wired
Who has he wired from October 10
So just yesterday
After years of testing
The active denial system
The pain ray
Which drives off riders
With a microwave like beam
Could finally have it today
The army is buying five of the truck-mounted systems for 25 million
Dollars
The great picture of this thing
However, the energy weapon
May face new hurdles before it shipped off to the battlefield
Which don't think that's just going to be the desert
You know that that could be rolling through your street
A new report details how the supposedly non-lethal blaster
Could be turned into a flesh-frying killer
So here's the deal
And this is made by Raytheon, of course
It's a microwave
For crowd control
They can just sweep this thing across the crowd
And what happens is you start to burn up
You get really, really hot
And of course that will make
It's like a super tazer
The tazer is just one way of training us to understand
What will come next when you see the super tazer on the truck
You will walk away
You will be much more afraid of this than bullets
I'm telling you bullets can miss
This thing you just boop
Just shoots out a beam
These are they call them
Directed energy weapons
You've heard that here on the daily source code
This is no joke, this is for real
And they're putting these things into service
And they will use them against our own citizens
Worldwide
When you start to rise up
So we've got to find some effective way
To deflect these microwave beams
How fucking science fiction is this?
Crowd control with microwave beams
And people laugh at me when I say this stuff
That career fucking nuts man
You're living a science fiction movie
It's in the mainstream media
I'm not making it up
Drop.au slash daily source code
By the way, the place you should go pretty much every single morning
If you want to see a great collection of mainstream news
Pulled into a nice little connect
The dots formats you can really understand
What's going on and what's being said
Because it is being said
But it's not the headlines
It's not what's being pumped into our brains
Through television, mainly through television
And a lot of it through newspapers
And it's in the newspapers, but it's not on the headline
And this is just a despicable story
That got plenty of ink
I'm reading the version from the Los Angeles Times
U.S. intelligence analyst
Eves dropped on personal calls
Between American, over Americans, overseas
And their families back home
And monitored the communications of workers with a red cross
And other humanitarian organizations
Two military linguists
Have turned whistleblower
And they've come out and said, hey, you know
We were basically listening to this
We were basically listening to people's pillow talk
And we did pass around
You know, almost like the Casey case
I would take tape and we'd pass around this stuff
Of high ranking officials
Really a lot of fun
Listening to non-people
You evil bastards
Evil
What's going on
And a story that I can't
Relay in its entirety
It's like five web pages
That's from sqi or magazine
You can find it sqi or dot com
Of course, links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
This is about a
U.S. servicemen
Who
He'd signed the deal
With the U.S. Army
He spent his tour
He did what over
I think two years
Suffered from post-traumatic stress disorder
His wife left him
Upon coming back
He had a lot of problems
Understandably so
And he gets a letter
After three years
And they say, hey, we need
We need your help again
Come on in
He gets certified letters from
Written statements from sqi
Atrists to say he's unfit
And they just say, well, you know, hey, next time you come out
We'll make sure you don't have to go back in
So it's really the story of him being re-enlisted
And one thing that really freaked me out
He said, you know, so it was a ratio of three to one
At the office, you know, where you go sign up
Or at the office at Fort wherever he was
So 25% were poor guys like him
Who really had no business being over in
War torn
Deserts in the first place
Throwing depleted uranium
And other people in catching
Fireback
75% are contractors
Blackwater
And he describes it so well
He says these guys are working
Walking around with basically military porn
They've got all kinds of holsters and harnesses
And gadgets and stuff
And they're just getting off on it
They're overweight
And they're horny on death
And military
And they're, you know, they've probably been playing
All these fucking video games all their life
And now they're like, ah, we're going in for real
Let's go fucking
Let's go Nuka
Nuts
Only one thing you can really say about that
Singin' y'all
Who the god
Why didn't it hurt?
I have to live
That doesn't to make
Oh, oh, oh
I can smell
Cause it leaves the storm
Till I'll be safe
What leaves tears
And the office of Fort where they're
When they're so good to fight
And lose their life
I still walk
Look at God y'all
Why didn't it hurt?
I have to live
Yeah, get out of here
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Why didn't it hurt?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I have to live
Listen to me
Whoa
It ain't nothing
What a heartbreak
Whoa
It ain't nothing
What a heartbreak
Whoa
Oh, oh, oh
It ain't nothing
What a heartbreak
The bottom of our home
Blows memories
What is constant means
With an incompetent generation
Intention, indestention
Who was me now?
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Good God y'all
Why didn't it hurt?
I have to live
Yeah, get out of here
Oh, oh, oh, oh yeah
Why didn't it hurt?
I have to live
Listen to me
Whoa
It ain't nothing
What a heartbreak
Whoa
It ain't nothing
What a heartbreak
Oh, oh, oh, oh
It ain't nothing
What a heartbreak
The heartbreak
It ain't nothing
I'm afraid it can't break
Walking in light, you can always take it away
Oh, wow!
But God, y'all!
What do you call?
Absolutely!
Shit again!
Whoa!
What do you call?
Oh, absolutely!
Listen to me!
Whoa!
Nothing but heartbreak!
Friend only!
The heart to take her!
Whoa!
Please help me!
I can't believe it!
It is not complete!
Believe it!
They say we must find!
To keep our freedom!
But God knows this can't be open away!
Whoa!
Who are you?
But you can't!
You tell!
Once again, the message has been in the music
for decades!
I am so angry of myself!
Disappointed!
I didn't pay attention!
That was a good hit record, you know?
Hey, of course!
War!
What is a good for?
Whatever!
I'm not paying it!
I'll just go back to my living room and turn on American Gladiators.
At one star on the Charlie episode number 7-9 or 8 coming to you from San Francisco
as if you had forgotten.
Hopefully you're doing what you did last week with this extended form
out of show and just putting on the speakers chillin out.
Relaxing.
And just taking it all in.
Still the biggest war, as far as I'm concerned, that is going on for our young, our daughters
are 9 to 12 year olds.
I'm going to bring up Gardasil again.
This is the vaccine invented by Mark.
Rushed through the federal drug administration program
and other certification agencies worldwide,
a fantastic to watch how this marketing machine is running.
It must cost them hundreds of millions to do what they're doing now.
But you cannot trust this.
And we heard from Franco, a medical doctor, earlier in the week,
who explained very eloquently the problems with this vaccination.
Because people think of vaccines.
I think of polio and measles and some of that stuff.
Of course, but they've taken hold of this.
This is the next wave for the pharmaceuticals to make so much money.
Now that a lot of these other drugs, many of which I'm convinced are just poisonous,
have run out the patents of run out.
So they can't screw you for it.
Okay, this is a report from Toronto.
I'm just going to read through this with you because it's really important that you take this information.
And particularly if you're considering vaccinating your child.
And by the way, it's only been approved for 9 to 12 year olds.
They're going to do boys next.
Medical health authorities have repeatedly assured us that
Gardasil, the vaccine injection given the young girls to allegedly prevent
cervical cancer is perfectly safe.
For example, the National Advisory Committee on Immunization,
group of medical specialists endorsed the vaccine last February.
The Society of Gynecological Oncologist of Canada claims the vaccine is safe as does
Dr. Dave Butler Jones, Canada's Chief Public Health Officer, the Canadian Pediatric Society
and the Society of Obstetricians and Gynecologists of Canada have also endorsed the vaccine.
Of course, because they're all making money.
About 500 bucks is what it costs for the treatment.
And it's just a treatment and you might need more later on because they don't even know if it works.
Three medical authorities have ever puzzled and also indignant that the use of this vaccine
still remains controversial ever since it was rolled out at lightning speed.
After Ottawa announced they 300 million funding packages for participant provinces.
So this is not works.
The pharmaceutical company comes up with some bullshit story about something that's not necessary.
And then they get government buy-in.
There's all the money.
That that is so huge.
All this medical stuff.
The money that flows through that.
Many young people get paid off, bought off or just convinced otherwise.
The hookers.
I'm sure.
Any legal drugs.
To rush this shit through.
If you only took six, six months, that didn't even do all the tests.
But it's okay.
It'll be all right.
Just inject this into your daughters.
We'll do it through the school system.
Yeah.
We'll do it through cool commercials on television.
Peer pressure.
This is the same company that brought you Viox.
Do you remember Viox?
Merck, the manufacturer of Gardasil also developed a mucher claim.
Pain killer called Viox that was subsequently used by thousands of individuals suffering from arthritis.
Unfortunately, this is just from a couple of years ago.
The drug had the side effect of causing heart attacks and strokes.
As a result, the medication was taken off the market in 2004.
And Merck is still facing thousands of class actions,
and there's also a amount of billions of dollars in claims.
Once and more examples of medicine that was always safe.
It's approved.
You can use it.
Go ahead and take it.
The shit we're now going to put into our daughter's bodies.
Nine year olds.
His one.
1960s.
The little mind was pronounced a safe drug for pregnant women experiencing morning sickness.
It was not safe as thousands of adults with flipper arms and legs can attest.
It goes to 1960s.
Well, of course, there were some other things going on.
The birth control pill was developed in the 60s.
Women were assured that it's used had no harmful side effects.
Go ahead, take it.
Don't worry, be happy.
Studies now report the pill can be the cause of greatly increased risk of stroke, heart attack, blood,
clots of taken for eight years or more.
That is from the birth of Journal of Medicine from September 2007.
It's only taken us 40 years to figure it out.
Between 1938 and 1971 as 4 million US women and many Canadian women took the drug.
DES.
Remember this?
DES?
Dethilistobestrol?
DES was to prevent miscarriage.
Darders of these women were exposed to DES in utero in the womb.
They've experienced a range of structural reproductive tract abnormalities.
So it was meant to actually prevent miscarriage.
And now it's poor women.
Have all kinds of abnormalities in their uterus, their cervix of vagina.
Incidents of abnormality occurs in 18% of the cases.
Hey, nice testing, guys.
Jesus.
2001's 15 million women in the US alone as well as millions of women in Canada and abroad.
We're taking hormone replacement therapy, HRT.
I remember Patricia was taking HRT and I started reading about this around 2002.
And I said, honey, you got to stop this shit.
This is killing people.
It really is.
It's fucked up.
And she called her doctor said, and I haven't heard about this.
I don't know anything about it.
And then I sent him the articles.
He started looking into it.
A month later he said, holy shit.
I've been doing some research.
Stop.
We got to stop.
July 2002, estrogen therapy was exposed as a hazard to health rather than a benefit.
It was found to constitute a potential health risk for postmen to pause a women by increasing
risk of heart disease, stroke, blood clots, and breast cancer.
My wife has heart disease now.
Makes me so angry.
God, just read the rest of this article.
And I also put a link into the FDA, actual link from the FDA.gov website where they approve
a guardazil.
And it tells you that they haven't actually produced cancer by injecting the actual virus.
We're not quite sure which strain it'll lead to.
It's like a fucking legal document.
It might work.
Kind of work could work.
And they're going to do this for boys.
And they're going to continue.
Stop this shit.
We can't allow this to happen.
I don't care how many people think vaccinations are good.
That maybe something has changed.
Do you think since we had polio vaccinations?
Maybe they've taken the concept of being able to shoot something into our children as an opportunity
to make money.
And God knows what else they might be thinking about it.
And you watch the avian board, bird flu, the H5N1 strain that, of course,
has maybe only allegedly killed 115 people in 15 years.
Oh, this is the new $1.7 billion pipeline for the medical companies.
And they're going to start giving you primers.
It's already taken place.
So we have, it's not quite ready for the bird flu, but here take this primer shot.
It's like stockpiling.
Only we stockpiling in your body for in case it comes.
You watch these messages will be coming.
They will be coming.
I'm just saying this to help you.
That's all.
It's why I'm passionate about this shit.
Hello, this is Charles your drunk Londoner.
I'm just saying to say, I'm not finally leaving an audio message to say,
Roger Smalls.
I'm so glad you called this lovely to hear from you.
Hope you're well.
Hope you weren't actually in the clink.
And that everything's all good.
It was nice to hear from Roger earlier on in the week.
All right.
I got to play one from my, my lovely lady P.
And Christina, because I miss and both so incredibly much.
But looks like I'm going home mid week for a couple days before I come back.
Can't wait because I can dream about you girls.
And I do.
It's the Charlie.
No, no.
No time.
Each different falls for fire.
I know.
I need the remedy to cure this over.
I can't dream about you.
If I can't help you tonight.
I can dream about you.
You know how to hold it just fine.
I'm gonna dream about you.
If I can't help you tonight.
I can dream about you.
You know how to hold it just fine.
Who will be inside the world?
I don't see under fire.
I'm gonna be all alone.
Now here, there's no one who's crazy.
We're lonely for you.
You know how to hold it just fine.
I can dream about you.
I'm gonna dream about you.
I know how to hold it just fine.
You know how to hold it just fine.
Who will be inside the world?
I don't see under fire.
I'm gonna be all alone.
I can dream about you.
You know how to hold it just fine.
I don't understand it.
Can't dream about mine.
You know how to hold it just fine.
very around 1991 and missing every single time I hear one of his songs and he wrote a lot
from our living in America James Brown he wrote that note a hand race
free ride and a gewinter group
right musician is that guy
hey I found a fantastic clip on the source code drop at drop.io slash daily source code
the place we also leave comments links other files songs anything you can think of
and it was of
johnlin and yoko on on a usually
footage of them is pretty shitty quality wise and this is this is a really good footage
and it's from
let me see
so I must have been from late seventies let me see
yeah oh no I'm sorry a nineteen
eighty i think
yeah seventy nine or eighty
they may even be earlier than that i think it's uh... it's film footage as well
and uh... here's a guy who uh... hand
he really he really uh... was switched on pretty early i think that that's what
happens you know
you get a certain amount of uh... finances and fame and recognition or
critical acclaim whatever it is and you start looking for more and that's when you're
i start to open up at least that's what happened with me
and then you see the true travesty that you've probably contributed to in the world
and i just was a little piece of uh... have johnlin and uh... talking about uh...
our overlords the governments that they're evil
and uh... and not cases
but uh... sit on a view
our old officers run by
insane people
for insane objects and objectives
yeah and i think that's what i suggest when i was sixteen and twelve
way down the line i mean i wish i had had the same johnlin
wish i'd known this when i was sixteen or twelve
had to have to turn forty before i freaking figured it out but i expected
differently all through my life
it's the same thing of expressing all the time
but now i can put it into that sentence i think we've been
run by maniacs from maniacal means uh... run by maniacs
for
maniacal means
if anybody can put on paper what
our government and the american government et cetera
and the russian china dot what they are actually trying to do
you know on how would what they think they're doing
i'd be very pleased to know what they think they're doing i think they're all insane
now but i'm liable to be put away as insane put expressing
passageway as being insane or a sassanated
saying about it
every country's had it of an evolution for one reason or the others
not one of them has the freedom we're all talking about
so we're saying give peace a chance
you know like nobody's ever done it before
and it's not a matter of
we're not thinking in terms of ten years
we're thinking in terms of peace forever you know
All right, take a look at that because there's a lot of good information that John and actually I've never been to be a Yoko fan
But I have to say that I can see where he actually explains their relationship in this clip
It's about 10 minutes link in the show notes a daily source code calm definitely worth checking out
Because we do have to work towards that and you know, do you remember when
War is over those posters everywhere that John and Yoko put up
So it was a very valiant effort, but it clearly didn't work now. I think we have to we have to have a violent revolution
And it doesn't have to come to blows, but we have to show our strength because we have the power in numbers
We actually have the power we elect our government officials
We have to remind them of that we are the ones that have that power don't get sucked into their stupid ass games
This Obama McCain race is a sham. It's a television show
It's like American Gladiators. It's all set up by the commission for presidential debates
They don't allow any of the other presidential candidates of true political parties to appear on television
Which is the whole reason why Dr. Ron Paul ran as Republican?
He of course didn't make it still didn't have the money didn't have enough movement
But his message is really coming through and it's these scams and this injustice that we have to expose
That's how we get our people who really represent the people into the places that we need to have them
Hello, I don't they out the carry. Oh, shit. I how can I even have comic strip blogger?
Comics strip
All right, see as be what's up my friend my European correspondent
Yes, let's disband the commission on presidential debates in USA
So that your left libertarians could get president too and we're guiding you despite crisis meetings
European Union failed to agree a common action
Against a common action against financial crisis. This country is only focused on some interest and
some bailing out local banks and cutting interest rates
No come on you bail out. So this is means that the end of European Union no
Do have to avoid your opinion was
You're up needs you so you will live long and prosper
Yes, they European Union commission work for us now. They don't now they don't see SP
They don't it's all gonna merge into one one-world government. They they don't work for you
Then it worked for me look at this
It's exactly how it started started with a monetary system the European economic community and
Before you knew it we had the same money and then all of a sudden they're making the laws in Brussels and in
Strasbourg with that horrible thing looks like the tower of Babel
That's what's going on. It's almost been prophesized you can read revelation lots of people are equating into that
Okay, so just briefly on the upcoming elections. This is really important. You know, and I've been talking to a lot of people
And yes, I understand that a lot of
Americans will want to vote for Senator Obama because he appears to be the lesser of two evils
He's young. He's hip. He's good looking. He looks like he walked out of the pages of GQ
But just like McCain he's all for the same things. Ah, they difference some numbers
$5,000 versus two and a half thousand dollars versus a tax credit versus only to a certain amount
I mean, it's all the same thing and they'll never do it. Oh, yeah, we're gonna stop the war in Iraq
We can get people out and we'll move more to Afghanistan
They both voted for the bailout. It they are representing the same people
And there's a fantastic article on rents.com
title of it is Soros Brzinski
Brutchaton
Rodman
Running Obama you need to look at who is behind this man and what their plans are and their published authors
They have written many many white papers their plans are clear and known all you have to do is go and read the information
Now we know who's behind McCain
We know that call roe is running the show the best television executive in the business
We know that the the grand show is being made by him, but we also know the motors behind it
It's exactly what Bush has been doing. It's those guys. Okay, who report back to Wall Street and corporations?
Now go over and look at what these guys are doing Soros Brzinski. They're Wall Street
They've got Obama in their pocket
Okay, he'll make you feel good about them fucking you
All right, we'll feel very patriotic. We'll feel very American. We'll think that it's all gonna be right
But it's just gonna be more of the same with a nice little bit of icing on top
Please read what these people are doing the next bubble is infrastructure
That's what this article prophesies as I have to agree with it
So this is happening all over the world. I've seen this happen in Europe and I've seen the horrible things that it brings about
privatizing our our roads our bridges
Our water our electricity everything will be privatized everything will be run by big companies
It will will be in effect no open market will be paying exorbitant prices
That's the next bubble that's going to take place and it'll all be based on carbon credits and all kinds of other
crap
But the thing that I want to warn you for and God, you know, I really at this point
I hope Obama wins because the zombies who actually believe that they have a choice will be so angry for all the wrong reasons
If he doesn't win so I'm willing to sit it out we can go for more years we can go five years
I'm I'm happy to do it just give me a microphone and able to live in a MacBook Pro and I'm good to go
I'll continue pointing it out so let's have Obama be the president and along the way
I'll point out every single thing that is really evil about the entire system behind him
He is programmed he truly believes he's doing right nothing wrong with that
I'm not attacking this man, but just like John McCain run by Wall Street run by huge corporations run by
Oh, yes the new world order here me now believe me later
And that my friends is just a fact of life
Nothing you can do about it, but be aware because our day will come when true changes in our life
That's what all the people say
You're riding high and April
Shot down in me
But I know I'm gonna change that too
When I'm back on top that going top and you
I said that's life
And this one here's it received
Some people get their kicks
Stopping on a dream
But I don't let it get me down
Oh
This final world it keeps spinning around
I've been a must have a girlfriend, a boyfriend, a poet, a born and a king
I've been up and down and over and out and I know one thing
Each time I find myself
Flat on my face
I pick myself right off and get back in the rain
That's liar
I can't deny it
I thought of quitting baby
But my heart just ain't gonna buy it
And if I didn't think it was worth one single try
I jump right on a big bird and then I fly
I've been up and over and over and over and over and
I fall in a king
I've been up and down and over and out
And I know one thing
Each time I find myself
Flat on my face
I just pick myself right off and get back in the rain
That's liar
I fly
And I can't deny it
Many times I've fallen and come now
But my heart won't buy it
But if there's nothing shaking
Come this year to lie
I'm gonna roll myself up
If you'll be a big ball
And I
Frank Sinatra that's life
Hell no
That's the stuff
The moon is freedom is made of chocolate
Turn off the TV, stop reading the stupid newspaper
Go outside, walk around, enjoy it, rain, snow
Sunshine, breathe
That is what your life is about and we just keep on going
Adam says uh, bull co you asked for comments from people who are doing something about the current situation
What are you doing? Well here's what I'm doing one
I've been reading rise and fall of the third right to broaden my understanding of how evil
People can come to power very interesting for example
Hitler did most of his invasions on sunday because it would catch people off guard and there would be less news coverage
And more even more scary in the early days Hitler achieved his power largely through legal means and only started his illegal actions once he had control of the media with in Germany
But by then a surprising number of people around the world had accepted him as the legal ruler of Germany
exactly what
With question was on the first presidential debate when you rule the country what are you going to do when you rule the country as Jim the moderator when you rule the country
Number two ballcoads
I'm becoming more and more annoyed over the headlock that the Dems and Republicans have over our media
I've been vocally complaining to them about this fact. I had an exchange with AARP magazine yesterday for instance
In which I told them that their criteria of only accepting candidates with 5% of the popular polls was horse shit and told them why
It's ridiculous to assume that the most qualified candidates are the ones that have managed to buy their way into the two major parties boy
This is such a battle
Thanks for a great show even I internet ballco says absolutely it is ridiculous
The person who is quote going to rule the country
It's not allowed on television. We have four very qualified independent candidates they're not allowed any airtime
But there's plenty of airtime for Britney Spears for Lindsey lowhand Amy Whitehouse and all this other
Crap that we seem to care about why can't we give up some of that airtime? No because we buy our presidents the way they are sold
Just like washing powder. That's what this country is doing to you America
That's what your leaders are doing
selling you soap on a rope
But together we can get by we can change it. Oh, I may not witness that change. I may be long getting gone
But all of Virginia's one little stepping stone towards true freedom
The power that we harness ourselves
That we need to share in these times of trouble and despair
With a little help for my friends. I can do whatever I set up to do
And so can you
What would it do if I say out of two
Would you stand up? Oh, I don't
Let me all ears and I'll sing you song
I will try not to sing out again
Oh
That's
I need someone
Oh
oh
I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you
Baby, I'm so proud of you
But a show feels like metal
Don't you know I'm all alone making a noise
I'm all alone making a noise
I'm all alone trying with a tool
Oooooooh
That isn't where I fear you belong
Oh, let's come in someone
Don't you think?
Oh, yeah yeah
I'm going to die, I'm going to die
I'm going to die
I'm going i'm going to die
All card is October 14th, and this has been prophesized around the globe, of course,
this information not being relayed in mainstream media and who knows what the truth is,
but the 14th of October, the word is that will be saved.
And this would be by surfacing of an alien spaceship.
The word Alabama has been mentioned, we don't know if it's going to be above Alabama or
somewhere else, and I'm not giving you this as empirical proof of anything.
I'm saying that it's being talked about, and it's the ex-factor, now the wild card in
all this may las, where melee, as you might say, wouldn't be amazing if hope came from
above.
It actually can happen, and it's often darkest before dawn.
You can't manufacture a miracle, the silence was beautiful, that day, though,
although it's getting too cynical, cash on just physical, these days.
You realize everyone in me, but can't know how far I'm living, yeah.
Every night you would meet the feet, it cry as a blind heart, if you can't wake up
in the morning, because you're made last week in the night, if you're lost, you're
trying to lonely, and controlling, try as you might, be your father, love your own
baby, may I find it that the end of the day, you won't be lost, I'm trying to lonely
or something, you won't come your way, if you can't set on the radio, lap should be
here you, each day, you'll be fresh to cast the unsuitable stare of some kind of beautiful
you just could away, oh your friends think you're satisfied, but they can't see us so, no, no, no,
forgot the time feeling better to find, when they live alone, if you can't wake up in the morning,
because you're made last week in the night, if you're lost, you're trying to lonely,
and controlling, try as you might, be your father, love your own baby, may I find it that the end of the day, you won't be lost,
try as you might, be your father, love your own baby, may I find it that the end of the day, you'll be fresh to cast the unsuitable stare of some kind of
beautiful, you won't come your way, oh your friends think you're satisfied, but they can't see us so, no, no, no, no,
forgot the time feeling better to find, when they live alone, if you can't wake up in the morning,
because you're made last week in the night, if you're lost, you're trying to lonely,
controlling, try as you might, be your father, love your own baby, may I find it that the end of the day,
you won't be lost, try as you might, be your father, love your own baby,
certainly the most personal song I've played on source code 798 for you, it was a time in 2002 when I had a business venture go wrong and it wasn't about that,
but I had known my partner for many, many years and he turned out to be complete fraud, so I know what it's like to be,
you know, you know, you're doing it, literally with a rule pulled over my eyes, guys name wasn't even legally the name that he used,
and it hurt a lot of people who were working on stuff, it wasn't about the money, but it was about what we really thought was right and we're doing together,
and it was this song that pulled me out of a week of real, I mean I went off to another house that we had and I, you know,
stayed in bed for days and then this song is corny as it may sounds really, really helped me through that,
so I suggest you go buy that at iTunes or wherever you might purchase your music and play that when you're feeling lost hurt,
and if you're lonely.
Okay, wow, final song for the Charlie for today, and this is something that is actually it's another Sinatra song,
I was going through my Sinatra library and man, this guy had some songs.
Back in the day when you could actually understand the lyrics and they were kind of spelled out really plainly,
I want you to, if you can, if you're driving, please don't, but you might be listening to this on an airplane,
for the holiday weekend, or you might be chilling around the house.
I just listen to this on the speakers, I'd like you to close your eyes for a second,
and if you're not an American, I hope you will be able to visualize because these are the ideals and the thoughts that I grew up with.
Of course, this song being recorded probably just a little bit before I was born, I heard a lot around the house,
and this really was the reality that I believed in for so long until that bubble was absolutely popped,
but in essence, it really is the truth, so close your eyes for a second.
You are American, I want you to take a trip down with me to the place that is America,
to the people we are, and the values and ideals that we stand for, as sung by Newark's favorite song, Sinatra.
What is America, to me, a man, or a flag I see, a certain word, democracy, what is America, to me.
The house I live in, a plough of earth, a street, a grocer, and the butcher, and the people that I meet,
the children in the playground, the faces that I see, all races and religions,
that's America to me, the place I work in, the work of my son, the little town or city,
where my people live and die, the howdy and the handshake, the air of feeling free,
and the ride to speak my mind out, that's America to me, the things I see about me, the big things in the small,
the little corner new stand, and the house of my old home, the wedding and the church, the laughter and the tears,
the dream that's been a crime, more hundred and fifty years, the town I live in,
the street, the house, the pavement of the city, for a garden all in bloom, the church, the school,
the house, the million lights I see, what is the story of people, that's America to me.
That's what it was before printing and playing in the bombs, it's all above the people, and the people worldwide.
All right, chuckle heads, with that I wrap it up, I'm sure I'll be talking to you tomorrow.
I know a gender with John C. Devore Act, but I am happy that we had this time together.
It's almost just after three o'clock, so I believe actually I get to see the demonstration of the blue angels flying by the condo,
maybe it's tomorrow, I don't know. So, summing it all up, I would say, please utilize what freedom you have left,
mobilize and above all, live your life with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation, stick it in your ear.