Delta Sheriff Charlie, 782.
A very unusual noise, buzzing sort of noise, but many of many of buzzing buzzing say it the same time.
All at the same time.
And suddenly it just stopped.
It stopped as quickly as it had begun.
You're waking me up.
I'm going to reach the first one to the most immediate hitman.
Four years of conversation that we've been to having has brought me to this point.
Many of you may feel the same.
Some may be afraid to speak out and fear of ridicule.
Fear not chuckle heads.
Together we're going to face the future.
The light that is our destiny.
Welcome to the next level.
Welcome to the Awakening.
Awakening.
Now I say it's been a six month excursion,
but the process has actually something's been taking place my entire life.
Imagine a world where you wake up one morning,
only to realize that everything you believe in,
function entirely differently from the way you're perceiving it all of your life.
A world in fact with the truth is off of the direct opposite of your reality.
The fun story is about power, three kinds of power.
The power of minds, the power of rule.
And the power as in what makes our lights glow and keeps our vehicles moving.
Individually, collectively, these three forms of power all insist.
The energy in your life.
The light of illusion is that energy innovation was stifled.
The blue of this blue flag called the power of the generator
to create a world of energy and motion.
They spot oil.
See the illusion and of course were amplified,
but we know this is a trick because of the context of being aware
that we're watching.
Imagine show that of course you'll instantly be in love
like a god or fear like what you wake in it.
We're gonna wrap this program to bring you this new splatter.
I'm very mean.
In particular, television is a trick.
I was a multimedia hitman.
I was merely meant to keep me a slave entertained into the next perished break.
Reading a reality in our minds.
There's a servant, I think.
I was meant to keep me a slave entertained into the next perished break.
Reading a reality in our minds.
There's a servant, I think.
Energy, I think.
I think it's working.
A media program.
I can create content that will make your brain react
in a free-determined manner.
If you really can't figure out how it works,
then you understand that it becomes ineffective.
Once you're aware of the code,
it can easily be borrowed from executing it to your personal.
Super obscure brain.
That's how the youth and ex of E.J.
with a podcast can do that.
Imagine where people would money a plan
or the decades it built up
an impressive infrastructure
of government, social and monetary systems
that they control entirely
all of the continued exploitation of us.
This professional system, however, has one fatal flaw.
It must continue to grow in order for it to survive.
It needs us.
The slaves
to be embedded to it in order to prosper
once upon a time.
Those as cars and other true physical
stuff has been repossessed
they'll be no more meaning to the content of money.
Remember that none of this machinery
would ever have been created
at free energy been available to everyone.
I think we are about to discover
ourselves.
Thanks to the evolution of our species.
I'm certain.
Our DNA has been defined
the pre-programmed to evolve
and due to centuries of suppression.
The internet was, of course,
the elite's big Coca-Cola
and I simply cannot solve it
or what designed our beautiful body machinery
wouldn't have added the required bits
to our brains to make us capable
of even its system of bread.
It can't happen
to turn it up.
Either way, most of you are still very much asleep
in the reality created by the masters
that own us.
Many of you are awakening
seeing the truth that lies with it
it's only live to our limit.
The elite's machine is creaking
under the strain of itself
and fear.
It's all about the timing.
The machine comes crawling down.
And now for us need to be awake
and prepared to take action.
That's actually my role to assist in your weight
and it to communicate.
It's much more than I can.
Now, I don't see it all again.
I'll write all the praise, please.
Hold ones.
The zombies are earthquakes and land mass relocation.
Nor do I fear black helicopters
in a misnive way, the snow for the night.
But I certainly cannot get a rule any of it out.
Four years of conversation.
We're going to have a nice party to disqual.
We're going to the next level.
We're going to be in the air.
You're awakening.
Yo Ray, my brother.
Thank you so much for that abbreviated 781 away.
Getting chucklehead to low from the curry condo
on San Francisco. This is the daily source code.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm casting this out of the curry.
I'm going to rest my eyes.
Because I'm growing weary of
It's probably even trying to make
So rather than imply
I don't know what you just realized
All the things that you're trying to say.
I've turned up a well
But I think it ain't to see that
Instead it's crumble
Into a pattern we fell
I'm floating raw in never itself.
Why don't you
What I'm saying?
Even if the words are probably going to hurt
I'd rather have to choose to stop
If it isn't here
Don't you know
What I'm saying
What it is
You're thinking
Go I'm thinking
It's not what I want to hear
And check my pride
Because I'm a starting thing
I will find something
Good for things
What it's like
I'm sinking in retrospect
I'm getting mad
I miss understood
I make up your mind
You're ready to decision
I'm so excited
I can't be touched
I'll show you a way
And so kind
But keeping your mouth
Feel short
Rather than just walking
Of the words
Don't you know
What I'm saying?
Even if the words are probably going to hurt
Rather than choose to stop
If it isn't here
I'm not going to hear
What I'm saying
What it is you're thinking
Go I'm thinking
It's not what I want to hear
And I'm trying to get
I'm trying to get
Because I'm your mind
I just might find
All those things you left don't say
And I'm trying to get out of my way
Later on, after I'm gone, but you wish that you ever listen to me
Ever listen to me
Once on you, come right out and say it
Even if the words are going to hurt, we're better off this one
While it's on you, come right out and say, come right out and say
But I know you're thinking anyway
Once on you, come right out and say
Even if the words are going to hurt
I'd rather be truth to you
Think it's not the essence of the world
You're the one who runs away
What is your thinking?
I'm thinking it's not what I wanna hear
Ryan K. Come on right out and say it of course source from the drop the daily source code drop drop.au slash daily source code. Hey everybody how you doing it's
Episode seven. What's it? 72 coming to you from the curry condo and so a San Francisco Northern California
Been here for a couple of days apologize. We haven't had a chance to hook up, but it was another interesting journey that I went through leaving Sunday morning from
the
From the manner off on
Virgin it actually for the first time and we really had a bad experience with the
With Virgin not that the trip was bad. Okay, there was a two hour delay, but you know, it should happen
So I'm used to that and actually gave me a chance to chill out a little bit longer in the clubhouse and have a nice leisurely black black fist breakfast
But upon arrival in
in San Francisco my bag apparently did not make the flight
Now there's some couple of things that happened before I find out about that of course
I had my regular customs border patrol entry into the United States my mother land home
Where I was born. I have a passport. I've always had an American passport. I've never had anything else and for the past 11 times now in counting
I get secondary questioning this time. However. I got some actually secondary and tertiary
questioning
I
I learned a lot this time. So here's the sequence
And of course, I'm going to have to repeat this on no agenda for those of you that listen to to both the the daily source code
Or someone pointed out the diligent source code. I like that one
No agenda. I'll have to retell this
this
The John C. Duborac as well. My my jab and buddy
So they read the RFID chip on my
No my passport and I can see in the
Port of Port of Patrol customs border patrol agents eyes. You know, I get to go. She got one of those
Starts tapping away at the keyboard and I make my usual mark like she let just walk straight on down the secondary
I know where it is. It's happened to me ten times before and you know, she gave me one of these looks and but she was nice
I could tell she had a good pretty good vibe
said, well, let me just make a call
So a colleague of her came calling of hers came over
They looked at the screen a little bit now by by now. There's a lot of information on my account
Okay, because I've had to give all this information to them
So they know my address in the UK. They know my the condo address here in San Francisco
You know the address of the office. They've got my phone numbers
They know that I have a wife and daughter
They know a lot because I've had to answer all these questions and of course I have to answer all those questions because there's no
You know, no basically no rights before you are admitted into the country
Which is why they could also if they wanted to look at my laptop scan and take it away and whether you like it or not
It is kind of a gray area, but you do not you are not protected by the
Constitution before you enter the United States
And they were actually quite nice now, you know what they said and they put an M on my landing card
Now you can just go through and after you get your bag you can you'll talk to the agents over there
Which is what I would call the territory or the third question, but I could skip the secondary this time
That was nice because that's that back room
Which makes you feel like a real criminal in your own country
So and and of course I still had no idea what the M was for
Then I'm waiting for my bag and my name is announced
I'm going to pay his cup to the desk
I'm like oh man back to secondary
And that's when they told me about my bag of course I was somewhat annoyed by this
But I went to the to the accident of course
They saw the M on my landing card put it into the little blue envelope when over to the
Customs border patrol agent who was also I have to say nice, but you know they know me by now
You know they call me but my first name
I hadn't met this agent before, but you know he goes in and checks it and he verifies a couple things which of course
I just said you know and I said yep, that's right. That's the address
And I get the chat and with my said what's the M for?
That's for like money, mayhem, mojo
He said no, it's a match. Oh, that makes sense
I said this is the Adam Curry in Nebraska, and he gives me a look like I know all about it
You know I know but you know come on and he has a different date of birth
He lives in Nebraska. Yeah, you know I'm not him. It's him by the way
Why don't you just arrest the guy please?
Let's get rid of this. He says well look
I can't tell now the agency that is observing him does not want to arrest him and they can't
They're observing him
Okay
You are warned Adam Curry in Nebraska and
I said well can't you just take my name off the list?
That's kind of the problem because if I take your name off the list then we won't be watching for him either
So there's the conundrum
As it turns out and many did the John Smiths out there and know this but there's a couple of Adam Curry
You know there's an Adam Curry place basketball
There's a young Adam Curry who passed away recently
Because you know this shows up in my ego filters right?
No, so I think it was a 17 year old kid and he died recently
I think leukemia
That's a real bummer to see your name on no bituary
So that's another part of the system that of course is an inherent flaw which you
Yeah, you really yeah of course you could match birth date records
But you know you're still they're still going to want to question you
So that kind of makes sense and I sent me on my way so
Learn something and now I'm just going to lay it right out. Hi. I'm not the Adam Curry from Nebraska
Just please send me on through. I'll tell the other agent that in a good day
So
Okay
But of course, I didn't have my suitcase. This was not good
And it took me a full let's see
So the next flight was going to arrive Monday afternoon
And my bag actually didn't come into my possession until around 830 Monday evening
And of course contained in my bag was all my shit
You know my microphone, my equipment
So that's part of the reason that we haven't spoken
But also I've just been kind of beat on the on the time zone
And great to be back in the office though it's mevio man
It's what a great vibe. We're going to make it
If the world doesn't melt down around us if if we don't go into a complete economic
And mayhem
This is a good team, you know, we're working in some ass
I'm really proud of what everyone's been doing
Very, very proud
And yeah, it's just been good and so obviously working hard
We've got another level of things that we're coming out with
So plenty of work to do and that's what I'm here for primarily
Of course this is a
This is not really my mevio responsibility this show is between you and I
Before I go any further I want to wish Dr. Ron Paul's wife
All the best and health and good vibes to her
She's in hospital you may have heard about this
Ron Paul of course is holding the rally for the Republic on September 1st
And second in Minneapolis I'll be emceeing the event on September 1st
I can't wait for this. I'm so energized now that I witnessed my own awakening
From the terror of the energy elite under whose power we've been living
I've certainly been living for almost 44 years
Excited about meeting a lot of other people who are awake on one spot
That's going to be fantastic
But this is of course is a massive bummer
For Dr. Ron Paul is wife of course and their family
So no sooner had I released episode number 781
Which thank you so much for all the feedback
It started off kind of slow but then it just came barreling in you know people
Actually I'll play some of these some of these comments and I haven't gone through the voice
Mill yet. I just haven't had the the time
Because you know I have to listen to all of it each one has a maximum of three minutes
But you know that I mean that could that's sometimes as hours of work
And I just don't want to miss anything. I want to get all the good ones
But you know just fantastic comments and emails and links and
And I just opened up a whole new world to me
But of course no sooner had we talked about a lot of these things
Then the energy elite strike once again and the media particularly in the United States
But also the BBC what I've been looking at have really I mean
Oh what when you when you know what's going on and you see how it's being being reported
Because many of you will think that Russia these evil dudes have tried to commit genocide
On an ethnic group of people who had separated themselves from their country
Nothing could be further from the truth
Now of course I'm talking about Georgia and the fighting in South of Syria
And the Russian retaliation because that's exactly what happened
You have to understand some of the facts to start off with this is all about oil
It is indeed the black gold and I could have seen this coming this is really pissing me off
If you look at the map and please from time to time go ahead and roll out Google Earth and go look at Georgia
See where it is see how it lies in relation to Turkey to the black sea
How you know where the cast be in seas in regards to what the caucuses
Look at South of Syria and read some of the history you know
Even Wikipedia will be good enough just to read up on some of this stuff
Come on please that's really important that you do this
But just looking at the map it can really really open up your eyes
So without going into all of the history of Georgia and how it came to be and why it separated from Russia
It's quite important to understand that the president of Georgia
Soxvali
Mikhail Soxvali
Was educated and of course cultivated and probably chipped in the United States
And for the past couple of years this country whose minister of foreign defense is an Israeli
I believe at all they don't have absolute proof but from what I've read he's ex Mossad
In fact there's several Israelis in the in the Georgian government
They've been building up weapons they've been doing war games back basically practicing for war
There's been American mercenaries who've been sent over there
Those are actually called security consultants that's black water
Okay, that's that's what that is mercenaries
And you know they were essentially going to fight a war on behalf of the United States
The European Union will just put them in there certainly NATO
Against Russia
And it's all about oil and here's where I could have seen it coming because British petroleum who has a pipeline oil gas pipeline
Along the Caucasus, which is right there in South of Syria
Where the with all this has taken place
Remember the Russians kicked the CEO out of the country
About three or four weeks ago and there's you know something these are problem whatever
That should have been the clue that something was a foot of course not to mention the fact that Russia has
There was a Putin or was it Medvedev who said you know I'm kind of considering doing some business with Cuba once again
Now that the United States wants to put rockets in places near to our border like Poland
And that's what that would have been that would have been the tip off
So here's what actually happened of course you can find accurate reports around the web
But in general what you've heard probably is Russia has started to commit genocide for apparently no reason
And by the way, I'm not going to try and tell you that the Russians are good guys, you know
It basically absolute power you've heard this before corrupts absolutely
So no one is completely clean
But the essence of it is that the United States doesn't want Russia to become powerful with oil
And you know and it blows me away, but we literally are so courageous in our audacity to go and and capture their oil
Trying to steal their pipeline and here's how we did it
We sent troops in the form of mercenaries and weaponry and God knows what else to Georgia
You know we've been working with the president there Georgia for a long time these railies did the same
And in the stealth of the night
On the eve of the Olympics I mean how cowardly can you be
These guys went in and attacked civilians
5,000 people by the accounts I read are dead just blown to bits has nothing left
But pieces of hands and fingers and feet
And then of course the Russians retaliated
First strike was the Georgians make no mistake chuckleheads
First strike was the Georgians has even some great articles on the source code drop at drop.io slash daily source code
We can read all about it. Please read up on the history
So the Russians of course saw all this coming that's why they had built up some armament on the other side of the border
That's why they kicked out the CEO of British petroleum because they saw all this coming down
They saw what was happening and this has been completely orchestrated by George Bush Dick Cheney
Please let me put in there the fine Dutch politician, Yaptaho Scheffer of NATO
Who's the Secretary General
And they basically started a war by proxy
And I think there's a couple other things to this
I think that this is really a tipping point a massive tipping point
First of all we could we could be on the brink of a serious
Conflict with Russia I mean this could be real war
I mean and this could include like you know nukes why not
Because the Russians have the oil now
They are the ones that are really
Running a lot of the oil game particularly for the European Union
So you see how it all fits together and I believe
I believe that this the whole trying to ratify the Lisbon treaty to get the European army together is a part of this
It's starting to feel like it because you know who's who's going to fight the war with Russia
If America is over in America
Well it's of course it's the EU
And this is going to be maybe another wall or you know block head
It's just oh it's starting to unfold right before I very eyes and yet it may be a long way away
But it's coming closer to you every single day
And it's not even that far you know if you're in the UK you know how far is it really
And it's coming closer
Along with this
I say remember Lindsay Williams was talking about that oil
That was going to be discovered up in the north pole
Well, so I think this is going to be a part of it
So I guess there's this is a huge oil reserve up in the north pole which is going to turn out to be
Unclear whether it's Russian territory or not
And there's going to be some fighting for that for sure
He also said that there was going to be a huge oil reserve
This is Lindsay Williams
The pastor who has all this information
If you have a Google Lindsay Williams to get the backstory on that
Most of you are probably heard about it through a source code
He also said that there would be a huge oil strike in Indonesia
And I'm only starting to realize now you've heard of the of T-Boer
East T-Boer and the conflict
Go look at the map and all of a sudden you're going to understand that all of this shit is about oil
We're killing people
Blowing them up with hand grenades
For oil it truly is the only currency that matters
So the Russians actually did I think something that you know
Let's just say that this whole piece of cord hangs together and the and the truce
At least for now with Georgia
The fighting stops or you know continues to start
I think it's still going on and no one's really quite sure
The news is you can't trust it
You expect particularly when you've got reports saying Russia is the aggressor
So and I'm just trying to find time to do all this
Russia I think did the right thing
And actually a very powerful statement by saying hey you know what okay
We're just going to withdraw stop no more
And we'll shut off that oil too
You watch
Now the next part of the plan that I think is going to it's going to take place
I think that oil and I'm totally changing my stance here
Oil is going to drop down to 60 or 50 bucks
And and what probably will happen
Is that
The United States is just going to become insignificant on the world scale
It's going to be Russia. It's going to be China. The Middle East will probably be
Bankrupt by an extremely low oil price
Remember this has nothing to do with supply and demand
I don't know how they do it
But you cannot argue that someone's fucking with the price of oil
I mean you just don't go to 145 and 14647 dollars a barrel
And then a couple weeks later down to 1312
You don't do that unless someone really controls it
Someone is controlling this and just doing whatever they want to manipulate our heads
So I think the Arabs are going to go out of business
The Middle East is going to be just going to be shut down
It's going to be Russia. It's going to be China
And unless we do something about it unless we change what we're doing
Internally in our own company in our own country
Yeah company it is kind of a company when you have a commander and chief
In the United States and by the way
Let's not rule out the United Kingdom
Also a part of this
And of course I'm not talking about the people
I'm only talking about the leaders
And who's doing all of this? It is the same people as always
It's the Roth child, it's the Rockefellers, it's Warburg
These are the names that you got to look out for
And it hit me again and this totally makes sense for this
Dollar 50 dollar barrel of oil
Maybe 60, I'm just guessing
But it's going to be that low
I saw a report and I'm going to have to look it up
Because I didn't have time to do the prep on this
There was an investor
I think any was an Australian investor
Some guy who put like 30 or 40 million dollars into an airline
And he thought it was a time now to invest in airlines
Sounds like why is this guy putting money into airline
Oil is out, the cost of flying is so outrageously expensive
And then I remember recalling that the advisor on the deal
Was the Roth child bank
So of course, so they know they know that the oil is going to drop
Because they're controlling it
Am I not? Maybe
In fact, maybe I'm just freaking psyched
Who else is the skin to fling excited go?
And then I remember recalling
Can we make everything that's gone
But she's time for no big time
And then it makes me want to win one
The back and the change when we were young
When everything was like you're lonely and gone
Ready to go up in the middle of the night
And yet you know we're gonna win again
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Baby I'm the one, baby I'm the one
Baby I'm the one, no we are
It's the first time you're here
Baby I'm the one, baby I'm the one
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm the one, no, no, no
I never met any of the little girl
She has something to feel at both
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah
You'll imagine the girl
And the back and the change when we were young
When everything was like you're lonely and gone
Ready to go, a man in the middle
Yeah, yeah, no, I can't
Well, no, I can't
Baby, I'm the one
Who is it?
It's the first time you're here
Baby, I'm the one
Yeah, I'm the man in the middle
I can't play, I'm the one
I'm the one
Yeah, I can't play
Yeah, I'm the one
I'm the winner
I'm the one
You've been to this world
But everything's like a normal
It comes out
What an wild, big camera
It isn't enough
We're not here, baby, I'm the one
Baby, I'm the one
We're not here, we're not here, we're not the one
I appreciate all the work you guys been doing, uploading tracks to the source code drop the drop.ado slash daddy sort of
ceote pudding um I need three tags in there in the comments. unfortunately not for this one
code putting ID3 tags in there in the comments. Unfortunately, not for this one, but I'd like
the song a lot, say I knew I'd go off on the deep end there with the youngest Georgia thing.
So I had to play that psycho is the title. I have no idea who did it. Please go back and
put a comment. It's a great idea. That dropped stuff. I'm loving that more and more. If you got
a voicemail comment as well, go over to drop.io slash daily source code. There's a number there
and you have to use a pain code. I know it's a pain in the ass, but then everything's in one place.
It's really fantastic. It makes production so much easier because remember, it is kind of like a
one man ban, you know. Let's see. This one's been in the email for a week now and I want to
make sure I get to it because it is my buddy who I love talking to whenever he can stop by CSB.
Come on in, CSB. Hello, Adam. Hey baby. Hi, Kerry. Here is CSB or EU correspondence. Yes, what's
happening? I wanted to mention that European Union cares about its citizens and it is why
self-extinguishing cigarettes will be compulsory in three years. You know, I heard about this.
And the reason why the self-extinguishing cigarettes will be compulsory is so that you don't
burn down your house while you're smoking in bed. This is a long alliance. All of this stuff
is happening. It's not just in the EU. You know, I think I've mentioned the codex elementarious.
You should Google that. It's basically, I think it literally means codex, CODEX,
elementarious is food law. And this is, people have been talking about this because pretty
soon, not only will governments around the world starting with Europe and this is already law
and many of the member states, but it's soon to be harmonized, harmonized. Another word for law
everywhere. And it's determining what kind of nutrients you can have. How much vitamin C you can
take and how much vitamin C and other types of organic products and minerals you can actually
have determining what you can put in your face, which is just fundamentally wrong.
No one should be able to determine what I want to eat. That's up to me.
But it's actually happening. And so along the lines, there's CSB just like it was on the news recently
in the States and no longer allowing fast food joints to be in poor areas because it makes poor
people sick. It makes rich people sick too, by the way. I just like the point that out. But
regardless, how about education, how about giving us some good food? To food that is affordable
instead of telling us what to do. Yeah, okay. Yeah. So it's automatically extinguishing cigarettes.
Very important. You who for the EU and EU cares not only about the people, but also about the
cause. So the new panorurapian frequency range will be assigned for smart vehicle communications
system. I've heard about this. This is so the cars talk to each other. So cars will be talking
with each other to reduce traffic and excellence. So really use a force of good and peace in the
way. You don't think that that's so we can track your car. Do you? It's only so the cars can talk
to each other. What is that all about? Interesting. Interesting way to solve the traffic issues.
But what about you say Adam? Why don't you tell us who do you support for next
EUSA president? Is it Obama or McCain? Only these two choices, which one? Well, you said us.
Well, CSB, you know, first of all, there are more choices. You don't have to vote for either one
of those. And neither of them are the official candidate for their party. So I can't give you an answer.
I don't kind of still kind of write Ron Paulin. I mean, I'm sure there's all kinds of stuff.
I can do. I don't have to vote for Obama or from McCain. So I hearing now that someone said that
it looks like Hillary, Hillary might indeed. Hillary Clinton might indeed become the vice president
and presidential nominee. It's crazy. It doesn't matter. They're both two sides of the same coin.
In fact, I read somewhere I really like this quote that the new world order, which by the way,
you might have heard the president of Georgia on maybe on CNN. I don't have a sound clip of it.
You might have heard, uh, Soxvili call for a, we need world order. He said, we need world,
it didn't say new, but they, but just add that. We need new, we need world order.
And I think Bush said it too. We need some world order. Well, they've often talking about
new world order.
Um, shit. Now I don't remember when I was talking about crap. I lost it. Never mind. This is so much
more to do. Um, here we go. A couple of, uh, a couple of news articles. This is nuts. I don't
understand, this is really funny. Out of the UK, BBC reports that Prince Charles is now coming out
against genetically, uh, that's where that's where I was on that rant. They're good. I knew I
knew it all fit together. But genetically modified food. And, uh, he's calling, uh, he's warning
for a disaster. Companies developing genetically modified crops, risk creating the biggest environmental
disaster of all time, Prince Charles is warned, which is fantastic. But I'm, I'm looking for the
employee here. I'm looking for, where's the hook? Because as far as I understand, Prince Philip,
the current, uh, Queen's husband, you know, he's been, he's been, uh, called out and identified
as, uh, one of the architects behind the plan for depopulation for killing us all. He said it.
There, you know, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's quoted in, uh, I think, um, certainly on the BBC,
but also I believe on the Guardian. He said, you know, uh, overpopulation, we got to do
some about that. And I think that he's probably behind or involved a lot of these genetically
modified foods, which are killing us, which is not food anymore, that all the food is sucked out.
I, I don't know what they're doing, but it's no good. So, uh, keeping my eye on that story for you.
But good on your Charles, if you're, if you're real about it, more European news, this is, uh,
this is pretty funny. It's like a bad omen. The, um, the ceiling of the European Parliament in, uh,
Straussburg, you know, they have, they, because they couldn't work it out amongst themselves. They
have to meet in Brussels and then 12 times a year in Straussburg. I think it's 12 times, um,
the ceiling cave did. Now, luckily, no one was heard because they're all in vacation
all the world is collapsing around us, but there's a little picture. I'll put all these links
in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com. And I can't even see this video. I haven't seen the video,
but there's video of it, too. Um, and it collapsed down onto the seats where normally, uh,
administered of Parliament, uh, would have been sitting. So maybe the timing was just wrong
of the ceiling falling down or, uh, or it's just an omen. Um, I was talking about the Lisbon Treaty
earlier. There's a, I got to turn it on this new website that I found called euroactive.com.
Only don't complete the active with an e-sodes echo uniform Romeo, Alpha Charlie Tango, India Victor,
euroactive.com. And there's a piece here by, let me see if there's a byline. It doesn't say who wrote it.
Oh, it's an interview. No illusions on eU Treaty ratification.
Uh, see if, uh, this is the chief editor of, um, the French Quarterly Politek ettology. I think
as I pronounce it eU later's plan to return to Brussels in October. October. That's got to get
some good vacation. To debate the union's future after islands no vote, but Dominique Moisey of the
French Institute of International Relations warns the eU's French presidency is, of course,
that sarcozy. With its attempts to pressure Dublin into a revote and to blackmail the check
and Polish presidents into ratification by threatening the blocks further enlargement.
I'll just, I just got to continue reading this because the best way to explain what he's trying to
say here. The iris know to the Lisbon Treaty and the referendum last June represents a warning
signal for Europe said, uh, Moisey, who found it the IFRI. That's the Politek ettology air.
He insists that islands rejection of the text is not an isolated case. See, this is another thing
that that we've been misreading and misinformed about in the media. He calls it actually the third
negative referendum after the no, uh, from France and the Netherlands on the Constitution in 2005.
We've had a profound divorce between Europe citizens and the European Union. So as the
practical hurdles of ratification here comes the analysts underlines in particular that the
Euro skeptic check president, uh, Vachlav Klaus won't change his mind. That means he's not
going to ratify it. Being determined in his euro skepticism, Poland also will prove difficult.
So, um, you can read this whole interview, uh, the links at, uh, daily source code.com. Just so
you know, it's, it's not, uh, it's not going to be that easy. And they are definitely trying to force
this night. And at this point now, I've got to believe it's all about putting together a European
army to, I guess, fight the Russians. Are we fucking nuts? I've been to Russia.
You know, uh, uh, uh, I've traded stuff with people on red square. You know,
and I'm sure that Iran is now in peril as well. You know, of course, Russia's relations with
Iran. That will be seen as, as wrong by the US and, and the Israelis and, uh, or Israel, I should
say, and, uh, the NATO. It's just people, man. I don't hate anybody. And anyone out there hates
us hate anyone. It's enough to go kill him. I mean, our army of waking up now to see that it's not
the population that every word just as much slaves of our government as they are of theirs and
an up on top, sit, uh, the energy elite, because it's all about oil. It's all about oil. It's not
about oil. Then it's about drugs. Approved with that BBC news. This came out to, uh, that may
make it got this off of the drop. Now, this is from us from today. Britain's policy of being tough
on drugs is pointless as a former civil servant who once ran the cabinet's anti-drugs unit.
Yeah, no kidding. So, of course, it doesn't, doesn't do anything. But I was thinking about this,
where are all these drugs coming from? You know, if it's so hard for me to get into the country,
you know, whenever even I fly the delta share of my own plane, you know, I've got customs agents
and immigration's waiting for me. Not just for me, for anyone who's who's flying around privately,
you know, you can't just sail about, uh, right onto into the UK, loaded with drugs.
And God knows it seems like there's enough available. So these are not small shipments, either.
Who is the only outfit organization that could actually get drugs into any country?
And I'm not talking about marijuana because, you know, that's a plant and it grows and it's called
weed for a reason. You can do a lot more with hemp than smoke it. I think that's part of the
reason why it's illegal for other things other than smoking. But anyway, heroin, cocaine, opium,
that's what I'm talking about. What outfit can actually get stuff moved stuff around the world
from places like Afghanistan all the way to the United States or Britain? Do you think maybe it's
the government? Do you think maybe that there's, uh, as money being made there? Think about that one.
So as I was saying, of course, it's the energy elite who sit up at top and make money off of
both sides when there's war. Oh, I'll shit. Now I remember what I was talking about, uh,
I'm sorry to be jumping around today. It's that the time quantum difference of me shifting through
from nine hours of eight hours of time difference. I was going to say about the Republican and
the Democratic Party. That was my reply to the comic strip blogger. The quote that I had heard
is, if you look at the new world order, so the energy elite up at the top, then the Democratic
party in the States and the Republican party are like one leg each of the huge new world order
because they're both on opposite sides, moving one, the right leg forward,
then you vote in the right, the, you know, the, the, the Democrats and then the left leg moves forward,
but it's still advancing the huge giant known as, to me, as the energy elite. That's just what
I want to call it. So if it's not about oil, it's about drugs. There you go.
See, there's anything else. I'll say this was on BBC Radio's Radio 4.
Um, and it's just basically saying, I see if there's a good quote here.
Basically saying the way we're doing it is not working.
Mr. Critsley went on to argue that wishing drug use away is folly and that there was no doubt
there would be a fallen crime as a result of legislation that he's saying he wants to just
make illegal tax it. The argument always put forward against this, uh, is that there would be
a commensurate increase in drug use as a result of legislation he says. This, it seems to me,
it's a bogus point. Tobacco is illegal drug whose use is declining and precisely because it is legal.
It uses a form far more amenable to government control education programs and taxation than
they would, if it would, if it was illegal. There you go. That's coming out of the UK, but, uh,
I don't think, well, maybe the government could and they could go legit, but, you know,
the Brits are up there in Afghanistan. I think they're running the whole drug show.
What else are they doing? Rebuilding? What's it about? Are we looking for anybody?
No, we're defending our position or we're just fighting drug lords?
There's certainly not enough information about it coming through.
Okay, let me, uh, chill out for a second. Actually, would you like to play a game?
It's just young bullets. Hey Adam, there's this number 133.
And it's the first one recorded with a Mac pro. Oh, here we go. It sounds good. Number one.
I think I'm, I may be supposed to be for this, uh, young, um, oh, no, number two.
Uh, uh, yeah. Is it EMF? KLS? Unbelievable? I think it's KLS. EMF? KLS? Unbelievable.
And number three. Damn. You know what? I don't know, yeah, and I'm going to have to give up on you.
And that's it, and all of these strikes are from.
And this is answer number one. DJ, yes, DJ. Oh, summer time. Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's summer time. What's and number one?
That's number two. EMF ELa.
That's right.
You're unbelievable.
You're so believable.
Answer number two.
You're unbelievable.
EMF.
And this is answer number three.
What is this?
No, you show.
This is simply red.
Something got me started.
I would never guess.
You know that I would love you.
Yes, I would.
Start it.
Answer number three.
And hit us number 133.
Simply red.
And something got me started.
So, Adam, how did you do this week?
Well, really only two out of the possible six there, young.
Maybe a little tired, but I wouldn't have known simply right anyway.
Alrighty, the answers to this hit us.
And also the links to iTunes.
You can buy the tricks featured on a test online.
Or to be found at hittest.mefio.com.
Well, that's it for hit us number 133.
The first one recorded with a Mac Pro.
Sounds great.
With the Ableton Live and Pro tools.
Alright.
So, it takes a bit of getting used to it.
Yes, it does.
Well, I think.
So Adam, thank you for playing.
Thank you, man.
One else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I'll be back for the next hit this.
So until then, take care.
Bye-bye.
And try to remember.
Think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
Be back to test at gmail.com.
In home.
Yon Pullen.com.
J-N-B-O-L-E-T-G-O.
Yon, thank you so much, man.
Always a pleasure.
I know him a little bit behind.
He's already sent me a 134.
So maybe I'll be able to squeeze that in on Friday for the footballer festivities.
If I don't fall down.
Let's just get back to oil for one second.
Oh, I was going to say, Yon, by the way, before I forget.
First of all, sounds great.
It sounds really crisp and clear and clean.
I'm not quite sure what it is.
Different processing.
I'm sure.
But now I definitely, I have to get around to show you how I've set up Ableton Live
with the aggregate devices and the core audio drivers on the MacBook Pro.
How I'm using the Fader Fox MIDI device.
How I'm using soundbite for jingles.
How I'm using what's the other program here that I have hold on.
This is a great program.
MIDI pipe.
So you can actually write.
Well, here's the way I did it.
I have a little Apple script.
I wrote some Apple scripts.
And when you do something through MIDI with the Faders,
then you can trigger stuff.
So when I open up the mic, my background,
my desktop goes red.
So I know that the mic is open.
Right, kind of like a virtual on-air light.
The cross-fader on the Fader Fox actually use.
If it's all the way to the right, then Ableton Live pops the foreground.
If I turn it all the way to the left, then it overlays soundbite,
which is kind of like a virtual cart machine.
And my Omnila Outliner Pro, which has the run-down for the show.
And it activates the soundbite, the cart rack.
So that, you know, I can just basically with my left hand,
I can control everything.
So instead of switching applications with Apple Key tab,
I can just move this Fader back and forth.
And it brings up all the apps I want in whatever states.
You can do a lot of cool stuff with Ableton.
And I'm also using Jack Pilate, of course.
That's how much shit I had to do to get this thing work
I wanted it to. Jack Pilate is like an audio virtual patch panel,
which is open source.
And I think comes from the Unix world, the Linux world.
Back to the price of oil for just a second.
Once again, you know, although we'll never see the exact discount
in our gasoline at the pumps, I think, just based on US prices.
We may go to 350 and we'll be really happy.
But this price is going down, and it's not speculation.
Well, actually, sure.
I'm sure that the guys like,
was it JP Morgan?
Who was it that was saying,
Oh, dollar is going to be maybe $300.
They're probably long on this,
and they're probably waiting ready for it to drop
down to 50 to make some money.
Because someone knows the energy elite,
they really take care of all of it.
Anxon mobile reported their best quarterly profit ever for a corporation.
With a total of $11.60 billion in the second quarter.
That's three months.
That's like $90,000 a second.
No, I'm in it, I'm sorry.
$90,000 a minute during the quarter.
And then, of course, the Anglo-Dutch company shell oil,
ah, they didn't do too bad either.
We're going to profit $11.56 million.
This is a lot of money.
I will, you know you're being fucked somewhere.
The price is set.
So I'm going to hoax bear.
Thank you very much, man.
I think it's there was a podcast,
Studio.nl, fantastic.
Love that.
Here's some kind of cheery that I tried out today
in a couple of people I know.
And wow, does this really work?
This is a cool website.
The art of manliness.
And of course, all the links in the show notes
at dailysourcecode.com.
Be it modern night as in a night in shining armor.
Protecting your lady in the 21st century.
And it's really a fantastic article
on really about how the media is twisting women's minds
into really feeling unhappy about their bodies.
And let me just see those a great quote in this article
and it's based upon a study,
which shows that while women believe a thin figure
is the female ideal men actually prefer a more curvy lady.
Even more interesting.
The story made the front page of dig.
And of course, dig users are known for the terribly disparaging
cost of comments.
This is according to the article.
This is not Adam.
The vast majority agree with the results.
So what does the story show?
First men like women with curves.
Second women don't believe this.
Third contrary to popular belief men
are not to blame for this disconnect.
The blame lies instead with the media
and the caddy expectations of a women's female peers.
Yes, that it's an epidemic.
And I've seen this.
No one guys are sitting down.
First of all, the guy walks by.
And you know, we're not going to say,
wow, you know, he looks like a douche.
Boy, he's got dumb shoes.
We don't say that.
We don't say anything.
When a, when a, when a woman walks by,
if she's really cute,
we'll probably say, hey, now.
You know, and of course, if you're rude,
you'll make some kind of cat call.
I don't do that.
But when women are sitting down together,
man, they've got nothing but,
and this is, I'm generalizing, obviously.
But they've got nothing but criticism.
Look at her.
She's fat.
No, she's too thin.
No, she's wearing this.
That's last year.
You're sick.
And I'm not saying like,
I mean, it's sad because this is an epidemic.
This is media destroying your brains ladies.
You're beautiful.
I've said this many times before.
All women are beautiful,
just by definition of being women.
And it's true.
And luckily, even though Patricia and Christina both
participate in the catiness,
and of course, it comes by what's being portrayed in the media.
The, you know, Patricia isn't unhappy.
And she was telling Christina the other day.
Because Christina, you know, you can see,
you can see the sickness start to creep up.
And my daughter is stunningly beautiful.
My hips are too big.
What?
Yeah, they look big.
She's actually so beautiful.
My daughter.
She's a child of the sun.
And Patricia said,
hey, you know, just so you know,
guys actually like women with, you know,
that are voluptuous and curvy.
Don't buy this, you know,
size zero crap or even size four.
You know, and it's true.
Chocolate heads, guys,
let your ladies know they look good.
You love them.
They look sexy.
And keep them away from Cosmo and Vogue bullshit.
Good article read that in the show notes,
a daily source code dot com.
Got some good stuff on the way for you.
Check this out.
Jesus.
With Mac.
Hi, Adam and Matt from Games Weasel.
On this week's show,
we've got a review of Soul Calibre 4 on the PlayStation 3.
Also guitar hero, on tour,
we find out what Microsoft's new Xbox 360
avatar is going to be like.
And you can win copies of Space Chimps for the Wii.
That's all it gamesweasel.com.
Let's show.
The livin's unspaced.
What's it doing now?
Let's put it through your belly.
Who fell away?
Is it called that in Space Bay?
You can borrow my junk for a few luck.
But with the code of Deep Space,
make your nipples get pumped.
Do you use your protein nipples as a telescope
and contact the transmit?
Or the button?
A bit too too.
Do you freak it out?
Do you have one really funky sequence
with space to play?
Or do you have several to change?
Yes.
The investment grass out in Space Valley?
Or do this move as jetter?
Ooh.
We're seevin' John's mission.
Come play with us, Nippeant and I.
The rhythm of ten and four.
I said, be the only man.
It felt very weird.
This is the moment to play with.
They hear me out there, man.
They just feel it like to play with.
I'll reach it all clear, man.
Who you are, man?
You're signal-free.
Come play with us, green.
All the things we've done
Jump in my skin
I'm a tensioner girl
I'm jamming, I'm a woman
I'm jogging on
So, the night thing is ready to come
No, no, no
Okay, perfect
What's that sound?
I don't know if I'll have to turn back
Who's the craziest thing?
Yeah, I'm thinking it's out
For my honesty
Can you say the stratosphere
But we're getting
We're too low, quiet, all
I'm from no second
Now we're in space
Oh, yeah
played those guys before on the source code
Flight of the Concord's Bowie, yeah
I love that. Thanks for whoever uploaded that to the drop. I really appreciate that drop.io slash daily source code
You can find that link in the show notes and and I want to thank you all every single one of you once again for contributing to the show
We've you know, I figured out this is the format and this drop.io thing is a big part of it
And I love those guys for hooking us up with lots of storage and bandwidth and just keeping it going
It's great because you're really putting the show together
You're doing all the show prep. You all are the producers of this program and it's working. I love it
You know, you're sourcing all this material and you're getting the links and pointers and things to look at and watch and listen to and read
And and and and and this and you know stuff like what rated at the top of the hour with the you know
The welcome to the the awakening edition. We're gonna hear from Ray in a second though
But first let's go up to the Northwest
My brother Joe and I just I just
Initial listen into seven 81 and got a mid-man it gave me the chills
Fantastic performance art and I kept waiting for the words
Inclusion to come on come into the conversation because it was a let me just respond for one second
You know performance art. I appreciate you saying that because I do I do perceived what I do as to be a form of art
It's my version of art some people sing some people play an instrument some people write some people. You know everyone does some paint
This is definitely my art and I appreciate you seeing it that way and and I did I had a long think before I did that show
That I appreciate a man a lot summation of
A couple years of research that you've been doing and I've been following along with I still this
And this dropped I oh thing is great because it's just kind of
Give me a place to participate more and to pull more from the community of
Chocolate yeah, but wow the reason is the word
Inclusion wasn't there is it what you did
On 70 71 was not a conclusion it was a start of the beginning yes, and
And
And that's why I sat in silence for a couple minutes after listening to that
Because I am
White awake in cream land
All we want is
My life let's take a look at the landscape on a road trip through your life
This episode of Adam Curry's the soundtrack to my life brings us back to
1990 and
Almost 26 years older recently moved with a lady Patricia and dog and a cat from Amsterdam to New York City
He got married moved to Livingston New Jersey and became a father on August the 27th of his beautiful daughter Christina Valerie Curry
Look how sweet she is
A good she could she could she
Like a smile in
Okay, back to 1990
And became a VGA for MTV besides making spot appearances between music videos
Who was also host of the programs had bangers ball and the top 20 countdown in which he got into few stars like Michael Jackson and Paul McCartney
While working for MTV he also did radio work for New York's number one radio station
W8's TZ
Ben and Oless
C1
Adam hosted several programs on C100
Got a letting roll in the Donas movie truth of there hosted a national program
He'd like you as a and produced a buzz which after times a day on 150 radio station true out to
West for our Dutch guys and it was really the shit who was the media star made
We only got mad copies of radio formats with absolutely worried and I see my Robert and all the other radio stations in the states
Okay, coming up a little experiment on the challenge
Oh
First it's time for a new embarrassing moment for you, Adam
Oh, man
Feel free to visit the web of boys room
No
Nobody plus more music than Z100 and here is true fun MTV's Adam Kirkking off at least another 10 songs in a row on number one
Continuous music V100 MTV's Adam Curry broadcasts and live from the top of the Empire
Stay built and can't kind of chill here, but this is Z100 where soon you can vote yes at 100 223
VOT that's 1800
8 6 8 3 and one of free concerts so I'm one of the most electrifying groups in America details on the suit
Adam Curry
MTV guys
broadcast live from the top of the Empire stayed building with the free money money later on with a hundred bucks on
Z100 and before so but at least 10 songs in a row. Thank you. Yeah. Thank you for reminding me
From my friend and former idol well, I saw he's still my all the channel to where this is I'm gonna jump
Blar as you told me to look for partly cloud it's night low 43 degrees mostly sunny in warmer tomorrow
High-round 60s right now it's cloudy in 57 and the south runs it's 59 the Empire stay building and on your FM it's 100 point three
Adam Curry
Everybody you want to say something
Shit, this is where I come from okay this is my roots. What's this?
It's 100 come a long way son from Z100 and the free money buddy
I was a fucking robot. Listen to me part of the machine. What you name I need to eat a reason
Do you change your birthday?
Congratulations would you like a bunny as a present?
Yeah, well congratulations. I'll give you that one too. Okay. Thank you. Hey, who plays at least 10 songs in row every hour Tina
soundtrack my life
Yeah
It's a TV's out of curry makes sure you call the free money hotline and one hundred two four two zero
100 they call 100 right now
Be I'm look out for the touchtones right now with the bond one it's the material girl
That's banana was mobile on the 100
Yeah
Oh
No, no, no, no, no
Let your body hold to the music
And let your body hold to the music
No, no, no, no, no, no
All you need is your own imagination
So use it, that's what it's for
That's what it's for
All the time
All you're on is integration
Your dreams will open in the door
And as for you
I know what it means
You'll pass away
You'll give your role for your research
You'll be the music
Open and book you'll realize
You'll understand
Yes, that's what you are
You'll always come on
Let your body hold to the music
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
You've got a kit to hold me, yeah, I'm in control, hey
All that you might know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't see, I don't know, I don't know, I don't, well, so I can see, I don't, well, so I can see, yeah, I don't know, I don't, I don't, I don't know, I don't know I don't know, I don't know, I don't know. I don't, I don't, I don't know, I don't, I don't know, this is fun, okay?
This song is fired by a dance performed in Rio Flops on the Underground KC in which
dancers used the series of complex hand moves to entertain their favourite world stars
as well as the couple models on the magazine vote.
Madonna, the number one song from 1990s in the globe.
So, Adam, all the chocolate, why to know what it is feel like to broadcast on New York's
No one really understands you 100s and more important questions for you to become a dance.
The hour has gone through the soundtrack to your life.
Hello, Adam's road trip through his life.
Oh, drop the I-O, slash, ray of jarlic for now.
Oh, come on, Mickey Ball.
And if you like it, I'll be back next week with a soundtrack to your life from 2002.
Oh, come on, come on.
Hell yeah.
Oh my god, Ray, man, don't ever do that again.
Don't make me do that.
Of course, at the time it was fantastic.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, I can just listen to that I can hear how much fun I was having.
But, you know, total tool of the system.
And for a minute, that was like, oh, man, we'll have to listen to Madonna's vote.
But I could listen to it with new ears and it was actually here on the headphones.
I really liked that production.
It was a great pop record.
So, even though it wouldn't be a choice, I wouldn't put it on the collection.
Um, you know, I dug it.
Thank you very much.
Uh, 2002.
Actually, when you start off talking about Christina, you know, when she was born,
um, we had light FM WLTW on in the delivery room.
And she was born during the Beatles in my life.
I thought you were going to play that.
But this was, it was a twist.
It's a, this whole show has been kind of a roller coaster there, right?
Oh, let's hit the phones again.
Oh, actually, this is the, um, this is from the drop.
Oh, I had them, paranormal in here.
Given what we know about the new world order, we have three options.
Fight, flight, or be assimilated.
So let's see, I don't fancy being assimilated and collaborating
in the building of my own prison.
I've been fighting, but I found that most people don't want to know, or label you as a nutcase.
So why would I want to risk my well-being for these slaves?
So not to sound defeatist, but the flight option sounds viable.
My dilemma is, where should I go?
You can rule out the US, Canada, EU, Australia, New Zealand,
as they're all in lockstep to fascism.
So where can I go?
To be off the surveillance grid, still have a decent job and a good living standard
and be confident that it won't be assimilated by the bored new world order.
That's a tough call. Any ideas, Adam?
Yeah. Oh, and remember,
they work almost at a good point.
We kind of answered your own question there, my friend, because there is no place to go,
because they're all working on us worldwide, so you can just forget it.
So the only true option is fight, and it doesn't have to be a bloody fight.
All it has to be is an awakening, wake up other people, and don't do it for yourself.
I'm not doing this for me. I'm doing it for a Christina.
I'm doing it for your kids. We're going to deal with all this crap.
We have to deal with that. We can make this world a better place, but I do mean it.
We can, and I'm doing it for Christina. That's what I'm doing it for.
I can see all the shit she's having to deal with.
God knows if she's dealing with chemicals from chemicals and shit and stuff in the water.
I don't know. You read about it, but it's certainly tough. It's really tough for our youth.
And that's why I'm fighting for her, and I recommend you do the same.
I just wanted to mark something down in the calendar. September 10, 2008, which is the 10th day
of the 9th month of the 8th year, is when they're going to fire up the large
Hadron Collider in Geneva. This is the Super Collider, which cost over $8 billion to create is taken
14 years over 30 countries have contributed and not a single article to be found by a politician who
can actually explain what the good of this experimentation is going to be.
It seems like there's a lot of young kids actually who are participating in this project.
It seems like they're all 20 year olds who are all these super physicists scientists.
And they're going to fire this thing up, and there's a lot of debate about what it's going to
be, and what it's going to do, and could it create a black hole, and are they trying to find
the mystery behind the Big Bang Theory? Do we really want to know?
So I just wanted to mention, they did test fire that over the weekend, and we've had
really shitty weather and Britain, and we've had flood warnings, and it's just been bad bad weather.
I'm just saying, you know, it's probably a complete coincidence. Is that typical August weather?
Will we've been having in the UK? I don't know. But they're going to fire it up on September 10th.
I hope they don't slip at a date and say, oh, there's a delay. Let's do it on September 11th.
That'll freak me out even more. But if I don't go really, really in a minute and a half, maybe
just explain really what this thing is for. And I've heard it all, stargate, black hole creation
machine, but I haven't really, you know, alternative energy. I've heard that when I like that.
I think it's basically huge magnets, right? So that could be it.
I will find out. But there's certainly some kind of agenda that I don't think most politicians
or if any can explain or understand yet they did approve financing for it, so we'll keep our eye on it.
Read that. Okay, ready? Hi, this is Julia Kribbide. This is Blake Morgan.
Hi, this is Guy David. Hey, this is Julia Kribbide. This is Blake Morgan.
This is Lee Colter from San Diego via the land on Dane. This is Angie.
And this is Ryan. Oh, love spirals. Oh, no. This is Christopher Bell.
And this is Warren. And where from the band, how many?
Hi, this is Randy Jackson from Zebra. Hey, Brent. This is Don La Fontaine. Hey, everybody,
this is Ricky Hills from Keep Pretty. Here, let's a breath rat. Hey, everybody,
Slaw here. Hey, what's up, everybody? Compton, plain white tea. Hi, this is Jeff Smith.
This is Jaden Olson, that was planned by Miles. But when I was a Kevin Brook,
if I were riding you looked at a pod for radio to enjoy these and other great artists join me,
Brent Bradley over podshowradio.com.
So much pain. We don't know how to be, but angry.
Feeling facted like we are gangrene. Please don't let anybody try to change me.
Me, just me in the middle of a sea full of faces. Full of faces. Some laughs, some salivate.
What's in your valley where recycling bins are bullet cases?
It's not equal. It's not fair. We're different people. But we're not scared.
We ain't never scared. It's a paving new path. Make a new street build a new way.
They can't use thee by the dawns or the night.
Three slaves on a song's words weren't right. Now when new days,
common of you stays done. Now while the many are handsome,
your soul is alive, but they want it for ransom. The face promise to anthem,
we step to the heart be some our grand feather, bring swords and rocks together.
We rise together, we rise together, we rise together, we rise together, we rise together,
we rise together, we rise together we rise together, we rise together.
We rise together, we rise together, we rise together. We rise together.
We ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the
Lost, open, found me, ground, did buy y'all so round day
Did the wall scrape, you know, verse cities
Or you were not verse the T's
React on a mannequin, we both were squeaks
And make 9-11 each emergency, earth to sea
And put your red, like the turn to lead
Oh, please let the hurt see
Don't let it happen, people, it's the populace
We will not to cross
Don't spare your tights there for my philosophy
And does not be as sweet, twist the cops and they say
T's no it's a work, it's a man-comment life
And we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride
And get the pre-line
We ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we
riding the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the end of the wheel ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride the pedal, we ride,
I've been seen these guys around, they've got a Newton song out of it, I've seen a song in a video called Handle
bars.
Their name is Flow Bots, without the W. Mynexpects, Foxtrot Lima, Oscar Bravo, Oscar Tango, Sierra,
and that was rise. I thought completely appropriate to wind up this daily source code
with and of course it was left on the drop at drop.au slash daily source code. With that
my friends, I say goodbye to you. Hopefully Friday we'll see what we can do. This is obviously
a show in a half. So the next time I have some time to sit down, I really want to get to your
phone call. So either leave them on the drop, there's a phone number there with a pin code.
You can use, of course you can always call into the regular voice mail lines, but I'll just
take a little bit of time for me to get to it, because I do want to listen to all of your
comments. So until we speak, please live your life with passion. It's worth it. Live it
for your kids. And while it lasts, enjoy your freedom. Another fine, medium presentation. Stick
it in your ear.