It's time for the DSC 747, one model that has not been grounded in the last two weeks.
On Father, you are clear for takeoff.
This is the daily source code, the daily source code.
16 million dollars worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing his battery.
It's time for the DSC 747, one model that has not been grounded in the last two weeks.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
Then the next generation radio advertising events in my ears.
Next generation radio content in my ears.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
Then the next generation radio content in my ear.
And it was just great and it's a fantastic opportunity to catch up on a couple of shows.
You know, I can really only choose one because of the amount of time and most of the shows that I listened to are indeed at least half an hour.
But it was great and I'm feeling really good. You should try that. You should walk around the block.
You know, just to secure iPods and have nowhere to go except in circles.
And then the next day, make sure you go around the other way.
Turn left instead of right or right instead of left because that really makes your brain work that much.
That's not much better.
A lot of interesting stuff in the newspaper today.
I should tell you that I also went to hand off the insurance cover note at the dealer for Christina's car, which will be picking up tomorrow.
And next, I think it's Tuesday. Next Tuesday is when she has her test.
I really hope she gets her driver's license.
I think she's a pretty good driver.
And of course tomorrow evening, I'm sure we'll be doing some parallel parking.
I'll be the designated over 21 year old driver with her as we cruise around the streets of Kilford.
So then I picked up the papers and picked up the financial times, of course.
Right on the cover there, JK Rowling.
The author, of course, of all of the Harry Potter novels.
And I don't know if you've been following this. It's really interesting.
And it caught my eye, of course, because I believe that this is being misconstrued in most of the press.
What it looks like, it looks like a very wealthy woman who actually came from nothing herself.
Is now trying to be the man and put people down who are just fans of her books and have written stuff up and put it on a website.
And now they want to publish that.
And this is a pretty high profile case.
And of course, you almost automatically.
And I believe that's a lot of what the newsworthiness is for tabloid newspapers.
Oh, you know, she's a money grubbing bad person.
I have to say some of the quotes coming out of her mouth are always about money in this particular context, which is unfortunate,
because she's actually doing something or she and Warner Brothers are doing something interesting.
It's a very interesting copyright case where it has always been allowed.
I believe for hundreds of years to write cross references or indexes of other literary works.
And there's tons of them. As an example, take the Star Trek movies and TV series.
And of course, there's Star Trek books as well.
And there are tons of Star Trek books that are reference works, which tell you exactly, you know, the history of James to Captain James T. Kirk,
all the way up through, I guess, Deep Space Nine, whatever.
And that is a fair use under copyright law.
And so what Warner Brothers and Rowling are saying is, it's not fair use.
90% of all of that is copied directly from my work.
Well, that's kind of the idea.
You know, it's like if I were to write a Star Trek reference manual, you know, it would come, you know,
I'd try to be as true as possible.
And of course, I'd say, well, you know, Captain James T. Kirk was born on this day and this date.
And I used existing material to do the research and put all the work together.
And what I don't like is, is, and I presume that the financial times has accurate quotes from Miss Rowling.
I don't really like, oh, what is she saying? Hold on, let me just grab a person.
She said something, it's on the front page, big picture.
Hold on, let me just find it.
Where's the quote from? I didn't like that. Here it is.
Should it be bubbly?
No, that's not it.
Should it be published the book? And this is JK Rowling speaking.
I will feel that carte blanche will be given to anybody who wants to make a quick bit of money.
Mrs Rowling said, the idea of my readership,
parting with their parents hard earned cash for this, is a travesty.
I don't think that helps her case very much.
Because it's more about ownership.
I guess ownership comes down to money.
There's tons of other Harry Potter books that have been published.
And I believe they didn't have to have any kind of permission.
The interesting case, I think we can really keep to the facts of what's going on.
That should be very interesting to see what comes out of that.
I don't necessarily agree with Miss Rowling.
I think literary work should be possible.
Be always got to kind of projects that I yourself.
If someone wrote a book about me, wouldn't that just be an unauthorized biography,
and wouldn't they have copied stuff from my weblog and my experiences?
Can you fight it?
I don't know. I just don't know if it's worth it.
What I do know is that it's always worth it.
To welcome a very special savant back into the family.
Let's have a word with the Nylon.
Spreading the news with the smile on where the wrong old right.
We go polite. Let's listen for a while through the Nylon.
He is back.
Hey Adam, it's the Nylon.
Hey Bay and your native's country.
Oh, man, sit down.
Walking back to the Pulitzer.
That's interesting.
No, no.
Yeah, I know exactly where it is.
I used to live right around the corner.
I guess they weren't checking passports today.
Were they that you got in the country?
These new savant's new shelves.
They're like foxes.
They take the territory.
A new one comes in.
Yeah.
Shine eye.
They're making a new york.
And now the monetary scientists.
Yeah, these are excellent savant's my friend.
You're a wall.
And of course they're moving in.
And I love them.
Who would he come from?
So quick thoughts.
Yeah.
It's federal reserve.
Get off of it.
U.S. has had 15 years of unprecedented growth.
Everyone is better off than they were five years ago.
Oh, nylon.
This is where you go off on the wrong path, my friend.
Yes, of course, unprecedented growth.
But we were headed towards oblivion.
And it turns out that lots of people knew that,
including Alan Greenspan, former chairman of the federal reserve.
And by the way, who has had this great 15 years?
You?
Everybody?
In general, probably.
But come on.
If lots of people knew that we were basically running out of runway.
And would never really have any lift off.
And it would just, you know, crash and burn.
I don't think you can call that a good thing.
But I'm willing to listen.
Just about says always correction.
I.E. recession.
We'll get past this.
We'll be growing again.
And the 15 years will be another recession.
You know, spoken like a true bank.
I think about the Fed now.
But, you know, Greenspan basically did a very, very good job,
15 years as well as Clinton.
No.
My next subject is just no agenda.
You know, when nine months into the sand fair of devour act.
And the most groundbreaking thing he's come up with is sit down with you
and talk about nothing.
He does it on Twitter.
He does it on his blog.
He does it on the floor.
Actually, you do it on the SC.
I don't get it.
I really don't get it.
Yeah.
This is what the big announcement was.
You know, you know what's interesting there, Nylon.
Is the audience for these shows is astronomical.
I'm not saying that I can explain it.
First of all, we're not talking about nothing.
You know, that's a false statement.
So that's just not true.
But my audience is growing again month over month.
I know that spillover from no agenda.
It's almost rivaling daily source code numbers.
And that happened in only 26 episodes.
And you know what I asked people all the time?
Why do you listen?
Why do you want to hear that stuff?
Why do you want to hear two old guys?
And people say they're just hooked on it.
They're with their main line in buddy.
And I'm the candy man.
Anyway, um, not a lot to say.
Because there's just a lot of crap going on here.
So about nothing.
The goals stand in which we don't even have anymore.
So anyway, I'm listening.
By the way, I am employed.
I never said what I'd do.
I'm not going to tip my hand on that.
But I'm around.
And listening.
And monitoring.
Good night, Juan.
Okay.
All right, nylon.
So what you just gave me there was one minute and 40 seconds of nothing, my friend.
Your band from the show, if you don't start sending in something that is useful.
And was completely crap.
Nothing came out of that.
The nylon ladies and gentlemen,
New Yorker living in London, delivering nothing.
Hopefully, you'll call back in with something useful.
Good morning.
Hello.
John.
The A3.
Just a little bit here.
Like this.
The A3.
The car insurance.
Yeah.
You need to avoid these 90.
It's a big, big ass car.
Yeah.
No kidding, man.
I've been talking to a number of people about this.
And people have been laughing and saying, oh, mate, you just never had to deal with this.
And I was like, I did.
I have two cars.
And I got to Jaguar insurance, whatever.
I don't care as long as it's comprehensive.
And honestly, I just, I can't be bothered.
Shopping around for the cheapest rate because of it.
I just don't want any restrictions.
I'm just like, I'm just willing to pay more for that.
But yeah, boy.
Is it a scam?
Once you really get into it.
Cool.
You're going to like, they're all underwritten by one of the other companies.
And they come this year, you know,
right?
I've got a hundred.
So I'll get by a hundred insurance.
We're going to get the hundred deal for any work that needs to be done.
And man.
Yeah.
No.
So I do like church.
Okay.
But I've been stuck.
Did anyone respond?
Well, I've put my car.
I've got a five year old runner clear.
It's similar.
I've got a death report for driving.
That's like 12 pounds in church.
Yeah.
Fortunately now.
I think I'm paying for like 25 pounds a month.
But that's still going to do that.
But hey.
Anyway.
Wonderful.
Richard.
That's right.
Yep.
Indeed.
God.
And we're so lucky, man.
Because I had health insurance before Patricia got sick before her.
Her cardiovascular disease kicked in.
Oh, man.
I'm so, so, so lucky.
Can you just imagine in today's day and age going out and trying to get some insurance
at a decent rate for a pre-existing condition like that?
Oh.
I had this in the war.
I can now.
We're talking about about insurance.
And I should let me just write down a note.
I need to talk to him about that on the next show, which will be over the weekend.
By the way, I think the delta share is coming back on Saturday.
So my plan was to fly.
Well, first I got to fly the wing commander back to Antwerp.
Of course, drop him off.
Then I was thinking, I'd go have dinner with my banker.
Share-D.
My lovely.
What is it?
Five foot.
11 tall, blonde banker.
I can't wait.
And, you know, another thing that I over-insure.
Just want to make sure I've got all the bases covered.
That's the best promise.
Yes, I was wondering if you could help me.
Yes, I may have you.
I need a curry.
Do you have a curry?
Yes, you have a curry?
No, I don't have a curry.
What do you want?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I just need a curry soon as possible.
I'm going to the restaurant.
I have to come there.
Yes, sir.
You don't come to my place.
Where do you live?
Pardon me.
Do you live off?
Yes.
Well, then maybe we do a delivery bar card.
Do you want to come down to the restaurant?
Yes.
How fast is your service?
Pardon me.
Well, how fast can you get it through?
Do you mean a curry?
Yes.
And if you're not good to a court, I'd throw you.
So, what do you come down or not?
No.
Well, so, I have to bring the package to you.
What package?
The package for the curry.
For the curry.
We put it on the plate.
You put one on the plate.
The body.
You put a man on the plate.
No, we don't do it.
What do you mean for the man on the plate?
Are talking what food?
Do you have a curry for the package?
On the dirty, what curry?
Are not curry?
No, but I'm going to curry.
Well, you're not going to come here.
I need someone to deliver a package.
Well, we don't do that.
We said for you.
No, but you have a curry.
Do we have men?
That's a curry.
But you want a curry?
I don't understand what you're saying.
You have a curry.
I don't have a curry.
But you don't have a curry?
No, I didn't even know that that's that.
Do you have curry?
Get me a curry.
Well, I need him to deliver my package.
So, we don't deliver packages.
We still put it here.
Good to send me.
No.
You want someone to deliver package.
You just said, I have curry here.
Get me a curry here.
Exactly.
And I need one to deliver a big package.
No, not you wanted a curry here.
It's always said.
It's company that deliver packages.
We make food.
We serve food.
You come here.
You eat food.
We don't deliver packages.
Do you deliver food?
You're beautiful.
Yes.
Can I put the package with the food?
So, I got it before we don't deliver packages.
But you deliver food.
Yes, that we do.
What have you got against packages?
Godly, it's my time.
Any more you buttoned.
Oh, man.
Someone dropped that in at the daily source code.
Drop.io.
I have no idea who dropped it in.
But wow, it was that thing.
Function is putting cool stuff out there.
And someone also suggested this song for the food bar Friday.
But I just couldn't wait.
It's too much of an opportunity to play it today on this beautiful Tuesdays.
The natives of the new dawn.
I'm here.
I want to talk to them.
They're here all my friends.
All the fact that we are here.
That makes it a good day.
A good day.
We're going to summarize and shine.
Just another day in this life for mine.
I took off.
Deep breath my lungs still took a pass.
It's got to be a good day.
Because it has to be touch out my arms.
I take a lot of my worries.
But you've been aided.
No end of the possibility.
Deep breath my lungs still took a pass.
Deep breath my lungs still took a pass pocket pé
I'm a baby, I'm a friend
Oh, I gotta be here
Can make your day feel your day
I'm a baby
The sun finds a horizon, long shadows fetch out
But this game flies in
We're in the room in the corner conversation
I come set in the moment of meditation
The whole day is playing back in my mind
The world of people in the phases in this moment of time
It's the part where the smiles of this following in misery
It's the point to mama while others become
Haterie, where the wife is in the mind
All through all the hardest stuff
When all the scars of the sun are lighted up
It's the darkness
And they can keep the smartest
I learn about the spades between the close and the pharmacy
I've been the part we're in this season
Of the hardest things you've learned
Still the speeds that I leave for the hardest
Everything can be taken down
Be around to the world
Nothing but the past it is no longer good day
I know what it's all about to fail
I'm a friend
All the fact that we are here
But a knife should end for your day
I have a car And I am a girl alone
All all the time To pass to me
Ha, yeah, all my friends
All the fact that we are here
Oh, the face today
I don't let you out
Are good Hey, Sanut's in
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, oh, hey amount of excitement.
music now where it's been around for a couple of years native of the new dawn good day no idea
what's up with those guys if they're still making tunes or not now this one awesome if you want to
hear if actually when you want to purchase some great songs just like this one it's a great
independent outlet it's emusic.com we've got an offer explicitly through pod show and of course
uh for all chuck ahead we've got a great uh a great offer if you go to emusic.com slash daily source
code you'll get 35 free songs these are MP3's uh free of all DRM you can put it on any MP3 player
move it around your devices even put on your iPod if you want 35 free songs to the absolutely no
obligation it's emusic.com slash daily source code i wish you could link in directly uh to some of the
songs that i'm playing but unfortunately it's not set up the ways if you want that 35 free option first
you got to go through emusic.com slash daily source code and then uh look for uh the well just do
a search man you'll see what they've got they got tons of stuff and of course their proud sponsor
of the daily source code hey let me see uh been talking uh it's kind of an interesting
it's turning into an interesting conversation about uh oops about protests about uh protesting
the Olympics and um they were you know people who are protesting the Olympics and trying to
douse the torch are uh essentially protesting against china's uh human rights violations and you
got to wonder you know at least i do you know i thought i wrote a statistic somewhere that uh
china killed 1400 people executed 1400 people last year uh and that's being cited as one of the human
rights violations it doesn't the united states uh execute people as well i think i don't know if we hit
1400 a year but uh 10% of our population is in jail and i'd say 70% of that is uh probably for
marijuana offenses i don't know that for sure i'm just thinking it's gonna be pretty high
and uh you know if we're really willing to stand up and say look you know this country is much
worse than ours instead of of course looking at fixing our own problems and changing our own attitude
which is really the way to go then you probably should just stop buying products from china
that will make the message very clear you don't need to write letters you don't need to do anything
but just stop buying products and uh it's very near and dear to the geeks hearts because a lot of
this stuff my friends comes from china start looking at the labels if that's what you really into
or we could start looking at ourselves and changing our own ways and maybe not pointing over to uh
to people on the other side of uh the walls of our glass house it's just a thought
hi Adam this is bird calling from Belgium i was listening to uh latest the dfc version
in the traffic jam because i've been spending like uh actually three and a half hours now in
my car just missed the things uh nice oh anyway uh i was listening to your comments about
are you're renting about a spanning or everybody having to it should be banning chinese products
and uh i was thinking well let me should probably ban US products because uh you're in
or the US is invading other countries yes we as you said yourself uh we should probably
ban Belgian products because we sell weapons if we're at this i'm from Belgium and we sell
you sell weapons that's right and you sell good chocolate which it also be outlawed but yeah absolutely
everywhere in the world like real people so it's not that simple to just simply ban uh products
that come from one or the other country the solution is not in there uh it's probably the other
way around with this word what we're talking about here is human rights and if we want to
want to be we want you human rights to be respected so maybe this is where it's coming from
and this is even more twisted when you think about it so the human rights i guess part of that
is is coming from uh the knowledge that a lot of this uh industrial work a lot of these factories
a lot of that work is performed by uh underage children uh under horrible circumstances people
are enslaved to the factories but guess what it's to make the crap it's to make all the crap
that we're buying so if it really bothers you stop buying crap it's the only solution
and boy you know did that open up and just in in in the span of a couple years huh
not good nothing against china uh really i don't uh because i don't think that there any
worse than we are i think inherently all humans do uh really nasty shit to each other um now they're
not exactly playing by our rules they're sending uh over to a toys that are poisoned with
lead and you know stuff that is just wrong but isn't that driven by our insatiable lust for more
product for more gadgets more gear more stuff is not exactly are we creating the problem ourselves
just a thought then we the best ways for me to help this country to make money like we see
china make money grow up and become a civilized girl or well another civilized but a rich or a
rich europe country um and then i would hope that civil rights would at least be respected a bit
better um obviously there's always complaints here or privacy rights with cameras and stuff
that's the problem we have in rich countries but at least we're not being uh detained uh a
lawfully uh well and it's not what do you mean lots of people are detained unlawfully how about uh
get oh oh please that's not true i don't know what hope so uh make these third world countries
richer don't ban their products don't buy a system um okay thanks uh for all these lovely
DSC's have been listening for years now uh thirty nine years old uh male uh gray hair hope you
win uh gray hair or gray hair love the stuff love you bye. Hi my thanks appreciate it sorry about the
the traffic jam you're sitting in there and i do love the fact that uh the audience pretty much seems to
be 24 and up and uh lots of people have one or two kids you know we got a job we're just trying to
get by we guess what we actually we grew up we care about the world it's not amazing uh unlike
the president of the United States i caught this little bit off a sea span uh unfortunately i don't
have the whole um the whole speech but listen to what uh president George Bush is saying about
people like well it's like you and i my friends chuckle head to love a good conspiracy theory when
you see one let us never tolerate outrageous conspiracy theories concerning the attacks of September
the 11th malicious lies that attempt to shift the blame away from the terrorist themselves
away from the guilty wow so uh i i'm not quite sure how to respond to that and it and again i'm
looking for the whole speech i had this is just too little of it to put into context but let us never
tolerate never tolerate conspiracy theories shifting the blame that's not i mean whoa that's
shit let me listen to that again let us never tolerate outrageous conspiracy theories
concerning the attacks of September the 11th malicious lies that attempt to shift the blame away
from the terrorist themselves away from the guilty now i'd really like to hear the rest of what
president Bush said there because i read and i don't know this is true that the conclusion and
i'd like to know if he actually said the conclusion is that conspiracy theory and participation there
in is terror recruitment so if someone can find that for me the video we're audio and i want to know
if he actually said that because that's a that's a real freedom of speech issue and uh i can see a
lot of shit coming to a head right now isn't it uh Charlie Sheen isn't he doing the movie uh uh
theatrical release of loose change 9-11 loose change uh he's doing the uh the narration i think it's
funded by um mark mark human owner of the mavericks of course and uh uh a super duper a-list blogger
hmm my wonder well this will be interesting to track so uh we're gonna pay attention to that
meanwhile over here in the United Kingdom the 7 7 terrorists of course we had the over 50
parish in the streets and buses and tubes of uh of London on July 7th uh i wasn't now it's not
two years ago it was a three years ago two years ago i believe uh they've brought the uh these guys
to trial and uh they're finding them guilty and there's all kinds of amazing stuff that has come out
and when i'm oh here's the only thing i don't understand so you know they they they
great detail all the papers today are going into um how these uh how they had blue prints of how to
make explosives they were doing it with liquids with like hydrogen peroxide and and other stuff and
uh i don't know if um if what is being said if these blue prints actually were dangerous enough
i'm just gonna presume they are and let's just uh say for a moment here wow uh if these guys
really were doing what is being reported good on ya to the to the forces here in the United
Kingdom good on you're forgetting these guys and bringing them to justice and i'd say relatively
swiftly no gitmo camps just bring these fuckers right up to the front boom here you are but what
really disturbs me is that they're denying it they're denying their guilty they're saying that
they were not planning to blow up planes in midflight that they uh we're not plotting
terrorist activities of any kind yeah so i don't understand if if you're truly um if you're truly
a terrorist if if you're radical and you want to get the message across and i think the threat of
terrorism is just as um just as bad if not worse than the actual acts itself and of course
excluding the loss of life wouldn't you say that you were they you were planning it and that you know
there's more common why these guys denying it that i just doesn't sit well with me and in a
way it discredits kind of a lot of what's being reported i want to know why they're saying they didn't
do it why i have you know they have videos apparently these guys shot uh you know like their
final jihad videos uh as they go off on their suicide mission and they're they're saying you know i'm
doing this uh of course they go through the whole uh i'm doing this for a loud deal and there will
be many more behind us and you slash shed blood and you know in our land and we'll shed blood in
your land and so they got all that down which also i had to say it's pretty damn incriminating if
you're making those types of videos in English no less but then why deny it savants called action
i would love to know what's going on with that hey i'm on this list in the number
guessing number 755 and book cherry it's probably about the last part of stuff out ever here you
say with all the positive music that we have to wait i know they're mainstream band and everything
and that's something you're kind of against whole we're reverend industry and everything but
well hold on i'm not against the record industry oh stop please i'm just saying there's a
better way and all i want is to be able to create content and and play people songs without getting
sued and that was the entire mission of the pod save music network i don't hate him it's sad it's
it's literally you watch eMI's in the biggest shit you they can imagine right now five billion
uh that there that has been leveraged uh against a failed business model and well not all
their business models are failed the some of the licensing will work for a long long time but still
i i just don't see the value uh certainly not going up and you know those guys are going to run
into some really deep trouble mark my words but i'm not sitting here on the sidelines you know laughing
or going or anything and i don't hate him i love it when people get switched on and see that hey
wait a minute this whole idea of a 360 record deal where the record company can in essence give
away the music for free and make money on merchandise concerts and other ancillary activities which
works quite well Madonna has a deal like that jazzy just signed to a deal like that and let the
people enjoy the music will buy if we have got proof time and time again proof that when people
really enjoy what you're doing and you've got a good offer right this is important a good offer
look this is the record companies of course their good offer was the CD because they package up 12
or 14 songs of which maybe you only like one or two very rarely do i think you like every single
track on an album you know that was shitty offer basically and these single tracks well it's just
not the same kind of income for these guys so they got a change but i'm not against them they understand
you get your music out there you give it away for people to play and people buy it and that's just
the way it is that's a great song and a love that is positive anyway bring here hope you win
love you no more and all that gets up yeah all right thank you very much well that's true
buck cherries on the pod sake music network and uh it's gotten lots of pod play i noticed and i
hope that article from billboard is coming out i don't know if it's gonna be this week and in fact
i would have heard if it was this week i think it'll be next week but uh wow man i really hope that they
give her some space this eve who's writing this article give her some page space or she can really
delve into it this could be an interesting turning point but then again you never know
the best this you think it'll be so hot it'll be so it's cold
you go everyone you go so you're not even it's up because it got the feeling
hands up you're the one we've been searching for
i'll tell your friends and tell your enemies because they are the souls and we
yeah what you think we do and we want to do so you're not even it's up because it got
the feeling hands up you're the one we've been searching for
you're the one we are
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
find them match the way played earlier, which I sourced obviously from the official
mashup supplier of the daily source code mashuptown.com.
All right, everybody so as promised, or as predicted, or as as shit as I told
John yesterday tomorrow, no jokes I'm going into what you know, I got a busy
day pick up the car, got to go in, got a couple of meetings, come and do some
stuff, Thursday Friday looks like it. So I'm, uh, hey, four, four day
Charlie week, a four Charlie week. Oh my god, what are we going to do
it? All right, uh, as always looking forward to your responses. We've got the email,
which is, is marginally functional for getting a message to me, Adam at podshow.com.
The show notes, of course, we can pick up all the information links, et cetera,
for everything I discussed and played in today's show at daily source code.com.
My weblog, which is curry.com, the, uh, the DSC drop, which is where you can upload
files, notes, pictures, videos, anything you want is uh, drop.io, Delta Romeo Oscar Papa.
.io slash daily source code. And of course, I would be remiss if I did not tell you to
live your life with passion, take that walk, Jan the earbuds in, turn left tomorrow,
get your synapses firing, and enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.