You're Adam, this is Tony and Joey, you know I've been hearing you talk about rubbing
out cancer and I gotta tell you, I mean the boys will be specialized in rubbing people
out, but what is it Joey?
Oh, what?
He's talking about being north, eh?
Ah, yeah, Adam, you're going to take care of that yourself, you know what?
You want to rub somebody out, you'll let me know, you want to rub out yourself, you
gotta take care of that yourself, you better explain it all on the DSC, 760, Capiche.
Wait, say, wait, I didn't wait, I'm in the same way, I'm in the same way, say, wait, I didn't wait, I'm in the same way.
You know the city can't sleep, you've all the secrets that keep telling the lights down, I don't know, all the fights, I don't know as a fix.
You'll be better than this, you'll be okay, you'll be okay, wake up, just wake up now.
No, you can't make me ...
Sorry, sorry, you're all going to be okay.
You'll be never able to pay to this, I'll be the way
You can't keep the side of what I've done
This thing will make your life real hard
I won't let you see me, I'll be the only one
You'll be never able to pay to this, I'll be the only one
Same way, same way, anyway, now that you're the same way
I've got you all figured out, it's just a fear
I'll take me over you
I'm a father of yours, I'm a girl, I'm a girl, I'm a video
No, sleeper, radio, don't try to let me know
You're every feel, but I'm home
And you can't wait, wait, wait, wait
Tell me where I'm gonna be, I'll be the only one
You'll be never able to pay to this, I'll be the way
You can't keep the side of what I've done
This thing will make your life real hard
I won't let you see me, I'll be the only one
Same way, same way, same way, anyway, now that you're the same way
I've got you all figured out, it's just a fear
And now that you're so far, I won't let you know
You're every feel, but I'm home
And you can't wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Tell me where I'm gonna be, I'll be the only one
Yeah, I'd say it takes all the boxes.
Crash Mothers, where did all the scene girls go?
Kicking off Danny source code 7-6.
Oh!
Coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey,
notice Gilford won the west side of G-town in the curry manner.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the program.
It's good to be back.
I had to show all lined up yesterday and was ready to rock and roll for you.
I almost ready.
I had most of the stuff pre-selected,
and I was ready to...
Ready to give you a good deal of the show there.
And then the teenagers started to act up a little bit.
As you know, we've got one.
A 17-year-old.
Oh, man.
You know, it's exam time.
That's what's going on.
And actually, I have to say that I think that Facebook is largely responsible for this kind of spiraling thing that we witnessed yesterday.
Not really good.
You know, these kids, they sit there and, you know,
how things can start to heat up in a forum where flame war starts.
That's essentially what happens all the time on Facebook between kids.
You know, it's like half the time.
It's, oh, I love you.
You're my best friend.
You know, the whole concept of branding.
And then the other half of the time, which may be even more than half the time,
this flame war's.
It's a modern version of it.
If you've got a kid who's on Facebook, look over the shoulder from time to time.
And you'll see exactly what I'm talking about.
Now, luckily, my daughter totally allows me to see her profile.
And everything that's going on there.
So I can kind of follow it.
And I don't interject, obviously, although my father Lee instincts really made me want to from time to time.
It's just a, oh boy.
They take some down this rabbit hole, the spiral.
I wound up actually taking away the laptop and I said, look,
leave this.
I printed out the book.
So she needed to continue studying from Gutenberg, Gutenberg,
Godorg, which was, let's see, the tempest and a Jane Austen book.
And she just got back from her exams and she said she did okay.
So I think she, she probably actually did better than she's letting on.
But man, was that a major trouble yesterday.
Just hysterics.
What can I tell you?
By the way, I read somewhere that Facebook's web traffic is down.
Something like 10% in their page views.
And I can totally understand why, because there's something new they've introduced into Facebook,
which is this concept of a chat window that kind of pops up in Ajax or whatever.
And that's now where the conversation is taking place,
most of the time except for something that they want to say that the kids want to say for
prosperity or want to publish the name.
You know, put it on someone's wall or do some kind of post like that.
But I don't see how, I think the model breaks with this, with this chat function.
You know, and of course it is taking over some MSM activity I can see.
I can just see it.
I can see what Christina is doing.
She's sitting there.
She's chatting.
She's no longer hitting different pages and looking at wall pages and refreshing.
It's interesting to see.
Because of course Facebook's model is built entirely on page views.
It's been, see this in the second, we're midway through through the week of the second week
that I've been doing this stuff in the morning for this Dutch classic rock station called Arrow.
And I got to tell you, it's been, except for the getting up early,
which on the other hand is also I have to say kind of nice because now I'm doing pushups in the morning.
I go for a 40 minute walk and listen to, you know, a selected show.
Basically, my channel lineup, which you can find at atom.mevio.com.
And I'm feeling, yeah, I'm feeling good and energetic and here we are.
Seven minutes past one in the afternoon and I'm already recording the show.
I mean, this is like two to sometimes even three hours earlier than normal.
So chuckle heads, you're in for a little ride today.
Is interesting though, doing live, live stuff on the radio versus the show.
And I think it actually inspires me for what I'm doing here because it's just, you know, you have so much more.
Freedom really isn't the word, but because I know that you guys will, here it is.
Okay, this is the basic premise.
So first of all, I know that you couldn't listen to the show whenever you want to.
You don't have to tune in at any specific time.
That obviously is something that I worked hard on figuring out in the beginning of all this.
But I also noticed that I'm much more prone or less reluctant, I should say, to play something really long.
Like we got a lot of comments about that poem I played on Monday.
You know, because I know that if you're not into it, if you're not digging it, all you have to do is just fast forward.
So it's, you know, it's a completely interactive, two-way medium and I'm really digging it.
Particularly, well, I'm just feeling good and particularly because my prostate cancer prevention quota went up by one count.
I'd say no more than 30 minutes ago.
Hi, Adam. It's been in Bond as you're how you're doing.
Good, man.
I wanted you to know, I just went through the grocery store, check out Lyme.
As I was getting ready to pay, the checker asked me if I wanted to donate it,
to help prevent prostate cancer.
That's what we're not working on on my own.
Just thought that was kind of fun.
Yeah.
Both on her face, like, told her that was like, fine.
Anyway, still waiting for my own jiggle.
Love you.
So homo.
Hope you win.
I think you already have all that.
See you.
Hi, man.
Thank you.
Continuing on the PCPQ, the prostate, the prostate cancer prevention quota.
John W. Kids says, Adam, does a larger emission volume require a lower frequency?
Can a large emission volume or a higher frequency then required be traded in just like trading in CO2 emissions?
Carbon credits.
Yes.
Cancer credits.
Absolutely.
I don't know, actually.
If there's any medical savants out there in the chuckle head audience, let me know about that.
I actually had a laugh about cancer for a second there.
Today would have been my mom's birthday, the 21st of May, is when I'm recording this.
And I think she probably would have seen the irony of this prostate cancer prevention
of laughter.
She's probably, you know, she's sitting up there and she's laughing down on all of us.
And she's saying, go boy, go!
Rob one out for cancer.
You could do it.
Oh, hello.
From Germany.
Oh, and Nick from Germany.
Couldn't I?
I've contacted you many times before.
I'm the host of the Schlaffers in München podcast.
Not yet.
I'll remember.
There are two things I would like you to talk about.
One.
Sometime ago, you mentioned that pocho was planning to come to Germany and we were all looking
forward to it.
And now, there's no news on that topic.
So what about it?
Will you be opening a German headquarters in Podstam or did you decide to go somewhere else?
Well, let me, let me, let me do something else.
I'd like to get in there ASAP, honestly, Nick.
I think I had mentioned this before on the show.
We really had to focus our energies in a couple other places first, which we reorganized
and those whole whole number of business reasons for that.
And so we just really, I think we jumped the gun a little bit ourselves.
We really weren't quite ready.
Myself certainly included because I would be largely responsible for getting everything up and running
and overseeing everything.
And of course, we still have the London office.
Now, the flying back and forth could be no chore, not even a chore.
In fact, it would be quite pleasurable for me because I'd be flying the Delta Shiera.
But we're just not ready for it.
But it is next on our list, the minute we can.
And that minute could come sooner than you think.
Watch this space, my friends.
And very curious about that.
And the second thing is, recently, you seem to experiment with live podcasting.
You seem to use talk show and live 365.
Live 365.
That's a new trend.
If you maybe consider producing a live podcast in the future.
And if you think that we all will be not podcasts, but private radio people.
Well, I think we already are a neat guy.
I think we aren't private radio people.
It's just the radio works a little bit differently.
Now, the whole thing about doing it live, which is kind of on hiatus for me.
Because there's some technical problems people weren't able to get the stations.
Even though there were plenty of slots available for different people to tune in.
And I really do like 365 mainly because it enables me to legally play some mashups and other stuff.
And the artist will get paid for that.
So there's still work on it. I've been back and forth with a text there.
But for me, really besides that one point, which is playing music that normally I would be pretty much illegal to play.
I like the instant feedback of people listening.
Usually there's like 50 people at one point there was more than that.
But as I said, we're having all kinds of technical difficulties.
I like it when people are then twittering me and giving feedback the minute I'm actually doing the show.
So it's not so much the benefit of giving a handful of people, certainly a small percentage compared to the entire chuckle head audience.
It's not so much giving them the benefit of hearing it live.
It's really, for me, getting the feedback loop.
That's what I enjoy about it.
Opening our own radio stations, maybe.
I was assigned the tasks to do some research on the topic for a German radio station.
Well, yeah, I know you have many press inquiries and that's why I'm trying to contact you this way.
Maybe that is the only way to get a hold of me.
You know that.
But that in your show, and then I can just use your statements from your show for my radio station.
Okay.
And you'll get paid for it too, right?
That's it for now.
Many greetings from Munich.
And then I'm signing off with...
I feel I hope you win great hair.
Love you, of course.
What else?
Thank you.
Take a picture.
Thank you, thank you.
Bye bye, Adam.
Oh, yeah.
You know you won't get naked.
Sorry.
Oh, she knows me so well.
Anik, guy, you'll be the first one I'll be looking for when we move into Germany.
All right, guys.
This is a big one.
I've been sitting on this for a couple days.
The news has already been spread out.
You've heard of it by now because it's something that's getting blocked all over the place.
Only unlike what a lot of people have been sending me, which has been mainly links from the BBC website that this would be happening in the UK.
It seems to be a European initiative, and I'll let Oscar our buddy from the Netherlands tell you all about it.
He prepared to be shocked to my friends.
Very, very shocked.
Hi, Adam.
This is Oscar from the Netherlands.
I just saw a very nice RTL news broadcast about privacy of, well, every European citizen mostly.
So the European Union has decided that they will archive all, all phone calls, connections, and all email traffic for, well, somewhere between six months and at least two years.
So listen to that folks.
This is a European Union initiative, which apparently the UK has already picked up on, has already working on, to archive all email traffic.
I think web traffic may be included in there, but see what the hell if you're doing it anyway, minus we'll do it right.
And also phone calls.
I don't know if they're actually recording the phone calls themselves.
I think it's phone records.
But this is echelon.
Okay, this is echelon.
Let me say it again.
This is echelon in case you're tracking me right now.
This is really, really, really bad.
And I know that there's people getting up in arms and protesting this all over the European Union.
We really have to stand behind this.
And I'm going to bite my teeth.
I'm going to sink my teeth into this one like a terrier, not of the Yorkshire variety, but of a terrier.
And keep on it because this cannot pass law.
This may not happen.
For everybody, this is going to be a European thing.
So this is kind of big.
So of course this is raised some issues and everybody, well, some people are shouting at least the left parties are.
But those are the only ones that really object to this well publicly.
Everybody else is just saying, oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
Chalheds.
We have a responsibility.
We cannot just sit around and say, oh, no, yeah, we've really got to actually do something.
I don't care.
I don't have anything to hide.
Yeah.
See about that when the real thing happens.
So this is just, so this is a million, a few million euros.
Well, probably more than that.
That's good.
For just a few cases of where they just miss out some, some bits and pieces of information.
And how about you?
It's hundreds and millions.
This is a big ass project.
This is something the Oracle is just, you know, salivating about because I'm sure they'll be using their technology.
No, no, no, this is big.
This is, forget the money, though.
What right?
It's not road to what rights do we have?
It's what rights do we have left over?
And you can have a long term archives for this.
So there goes privacy for you.
I think this is just fitting in from just better to even worse.
Anyway.
Yeah, that's it.
Great hair.
Hope you win folder repeal.
Well, between four and six times a week.
Oh, my goodness.
Good on that.
Good man.
Yeah.
I think that's it.
All right, I'll start.
Bye.
All right.
Good job, man.
Oscar from the Netherlands checking in with that.
Hey, guys, whenever you can, I love the links and I love the emails you send me.
Wouldn't it?
Whenever you can just call into the voice mail line.
Whenever you can record an audio comment, it's really, really appreciated.
And I think what's the change to sign off once again?
I think we should change it to they work for us.
Sign off like that, William.
They work for us.
That's the message we need to be sending.
In fact, there's a website now.
Lawrence McBride sent this to me.
They work for us.
They work for you dot com.
Although it is they work for us is the sign off here in the charity.
That's for folks living in the UK.
And you can even you can track your member of parliament.
You can track it down by your postal code.
And you can get RSS alerts.
It's really good.
I'm sure there's a US equivalent.
If you know one, let me know.
Send me a link and I'll be sure to publicize it.
But let's, let's agree on that.
Okay.
They work for us.
Sign off.
That is the new slogan.
Comic strip.
Once again in our EU, you correspond to Comic strip.
Comic strip blogger checks in.
Yo.
I don't know.
In music, carry.
They use this.
Yo, European Union correspondent.
Comic strip blogger.
So Italy is now considering
suspension of freedom of movement right of EU.
What is the very bet?
Because it's one of four basic freedoms.
Yo.
How are they doing that?
Comic strip blogger?
I don't understand.
What they're doing to restrict freedom of movement in Italy.
You know, if your life with passion and freedom or whatever.
The reason are gypsies from East EU.
But I think that no reason is good enough to abolish
basic freedom.
More info CSB.
More info.
Maybe your sister Willow, who lives now in Italy.
I could send some of your feedback about it too.
Being a gypsy, you know, right?
yourself.
No.
I knew it.
She is afraid about speaking out.
And fuck you.
Adam Kerry.
Because still there's no RSS feeds to comments.
Put the cuts in your company.
You.
Yeah.
CSB.
You know, I do that just to wind you up, man.
I said, whatever you do, don't put RSS feeds on the comments on the shows.
Whatever you do, do not develop that.
Please, don't.
I've given Express commands and instructions.
Yes, CSB.
When you call on that report, I am intrigued by this.
What Italy is doing.
I guess I could hunt around for.
But if you got a link specifically, send it to me because I'm very interested in that.
Some different, which, wow, I had no idea this was going to hit such a nerve.
This poem that I played for you on Monday.
Really, really struck a nerve with a lot of people.
They really liked it.
I got a lot of email response people.
Well, actually, let me play a couple of them for you.
Here exactly what I mean.
I hope you enjoyed it as well because I got another one for you.
Hi, Adam.
Eric from Portland.
I just wanted to chime in on Aaron Livingston's Accounting type home.
That is exactly the type of thing that I am coming to your info for.
It's the long format audio that I'm getting nowhere else.
It's the point of views that the magazines and newspapers I read do not provide for me.
The books I read do not do it.
Television is a waste.
The dichotomy of the United States with the red and the blue states fighting while we're bleeding in the purple center and getting no attention has got to stop.
Now, for my shout out, I got it to say that I'm a red, killed, folding, prostate 10.
You do!
Lovely.
Right on, man.
The bleeding purple heart in the middle.
I like the sound of that.
Yeah.
By the way, just looking at what's going on in the Democratic race, which of course is still not over.
I think I'm going to have to agree with John C. Dvorak.
I think Hillary Clinton is going to nail the nomination.
I know it sounds counterintuitive.
I know it's not the way the numbers are stacking up right now, but I think that's exactly what the party is going to choose.
Of course, we'll know in a few weeks from now.
More on this poem.
And this is a really good one.
This is almost a rant in the positive sense.
I love it.
Hey Adam, hey.
This is the sales weeds.
Again, back from two weeks.
Sales weeds.
I gotta tell you, I really enjoyed your 759.
I love the poem that was from Aaron Livingston.
I love her passion.
I love the fact that you played it in it's part of the artist out there that is not just music.
Even if a goofy guy like me that can call up and say, hey, keep it up.
Just keep it up.
Stay off the grid.
Stay off the stupid stuff that television have just mindless crap that we just see every day.
And if we can just keep the conversation going, just it allows us to be a little bit better.
And I think there's a growing, I don't want to repeat myself from a couple weeks ago.
But I do sense of growing young people that are going to get it better than we did.
And they're starting to, and they have got these eyes that are wide open.
And all they need to do, now that this is internet, if you want to call it, whatever you want to call it,
this media revolution that we're in, it's a worldwide.
It is something that slowly, but surely it's building skin and it's going to make things happen.
I see it.
And I just want to tell you, and why I'm saying this to you, thank you for your listeners.
They call in.
Thank you for the news that you play.
Thank you for all the stuff that you do that's even.
I know it's got to be hard work.
And you put your life in it and I can tell.
And those people that make that take it lightly, try it.
Just try it.
Try to do what Adam does.
That's what I have.
Yeah, try to rub one out one every day. You know, it ain't easy.
I bet you wouldn't be able to do it nearly as good, nearly as consistent.
And I'm not saying this could be on your show.
I'm just saying it because it is something that makes can't be.
To listen at the end of the day instead of watching the damn television.
Hell yeah.
Something different, expand the mind a little bit, expand the universe a little bit,
and appreciate the finer things in life.
Because once we can start getting to those things and agreeing and just getting off the
cramp, they put your stone and maybe maybe we're just
s yoken up a little bit and we keep our.
We're just going to be better.
We can just be better. That's all and that's all I wanted to say.
Oh man, thank you so much.
Remember, they work for us. That's the new slogan.
Okay, so here it is.
This is a new one sent in by Russell B.
And quality is not fantastic.
And it's not in front of a live audience,
but I really like the lyrics to this.
It's because it's that we call it a poem.
Do you talk about lyrics?
It's called sober America.
And I'm proud to present it to you right here on your daily source code.
To what ends shall become of us.
We children of this land.
A fighter, hate and misery.
We call upon command.
To smite those who have coden us.
To free them from their plight.
We'd rather bathe in luxury.
To stand up for what's right.
Who can be blamed for all our shame.
We swat them down like flies.
Forgetting all the roles we played that led us to these lies.
We cannot shame the world for chains that we did not use first.
The times too short, too worry worked.
The morning brings our hers.
In what regard do we now charge our brothers into war?
To blindly kill and pose our will forever wanting more.
We shall and cry for genocide.
But call it freedom's will.
Well, rich men, plain are future stands.
The poor men fronts the bill.
What can we do but celebrate our heroes have come home.
I'll drip the shades of peasantry.
The colors of our toll.
But need the flags and hickory.
The testimony fades.
Release from all their suffering.
Their victims that we made.
Can all we do is turn our heads when hypocrites are named.
The power of these words we give exposed when we are ashamed.
But rather than be washed by them that we might carry on.
Let's cloak ourselves in shuffessness and flee back from the dawn.
Do towers falling in our dreams still justify our hate.
We'll chain up those we took suppose to redirect our fate.
Do not blame me.
It's plain to see our motto and our prayer.
We give away our freedom's paid no longer do we care.
Well, we who live beyond the fray reach out to help the rest.
Those bound in change of poverty is to hunt us like a ghost.
Reflections of the lives we live remind us of the truth.
That we are bound by arrogance, a product of our youth.
I am going to take a saucecult.
I am going to get carried away.
This has got to be my most favorite song of the week,
maybe even the month.
Skinny Jones, spitters sweet tears on the Charlie.
Sit down and show it has been a while.
What did you do?
What did you hate?
I get lucky.
Living your love, have you finally found?
If you were trying to find?
Ever not a drink.
The night still young.
There's more one in the world only just me.
As your mom and dad, do you still go strong?
When your dreams are in the between and the wrong?
Bittersweet tears.
I cry.
When I think about this time,
a busy life,
and love,
to simple.
Drop the man I don't want to hear.
Of course I'm sad about what you want.
I just can imagine you being somebody's wife.
Feels like only yesterday.
I saw you alive.
Bittersweet tears.
I cry.
When I think about this time,
a busy life,
and love,
to simple.
I see you still do your hair.
Bittersweet tears.
I can feel them.
I just can feel them.
Back then,
show it up and live,
but the good things from now,
Raptain memories with some things
Yet I wonder if you feel so
Do you laugh about the best of all
So be the sweetest
You cry
When you think about this time
Or be the life
And love a simple
I'm be the sweetest
You cry
When I think about this time
Or be the life
And love a simple
This we teach you
You cry
When I think about this time
Or be the life
And love a simple
Oh, man, do I love this song?
Has a bit of the
Alessie Brothers
Oh, Lori vibes somehow
And it's song I can't find anywhere
By the way, nowhere to be found on the interwebs
That's a skinny Jones
You can find him at skinnyjones.com
Guy from the Netherlands
That one bittersweet tears
You can purchase the songs right there from the site
Without registering
Use credit card or PayPal
I think 99 cents
No DRM
Love them, love them
Let's see
What else is going to say?
Yeah, I was actually going to mention
This is clearly not a song
I could play on a classic rock station
Let's just take one as an example
And I really get enjoyment from playing it
For you guys
I just noticed that
I'm sitting here tapping my toes
Going hell yeah
I'm loving it
I'm loving sharing the experience
Crap, I'm such a damn hippie
Hey, this message is for Megan and all
From Celebrity Service
Looking to reach Adam Curry
Celebrity Service
I wonder what she wants
Let's find out
957-0698
It's regarding a medial quest
Thank you, Bobbi
A medial request?
Or a medial?
What did she say?
Why just listen to something?
I need it's regarding a medial quest
Thank you, Bobbi
Sounds like medial request
I don't want any medial
Oh man
I should have had a Skype to hook that
I'll follow that one up with you for sure
We'll see what else I have in the list here
Of stuff to talk about
Oh yeah
I found this awesome, awesome NPR show
On the drop
That's drop.io slash daily source code
It's called the giant pool of money
And it starts off with a bit of audio
From an award show
With a bunch of bankers sitting around
Give in each other awards
And they actually give out an award
For the creation of the CDO
You know this is the instrument
That was backed by all these fucked up
Lame ass mortgages
The guy actually received an award for it
You must hear this show
It's fantastic
It's right at the top there
And this brings me to the next problem
Because the drop is basically filled up
That's almost the drop that did it
Because I have one gig
Folks over there were kind enough to give me a gig
And I've emailed them
And I said hey I want to purchase another 10 gigs
Because I don't want to delete anything
I want to save all this stuff
It's so nicely categorized and organized
It's just like a blog
It's good stuff
And I don't want to get rid of it
But I think we only have maybe 50 megs left of space
And I haven't been able to get a whole of them
Or at least they've emailed me
And so I've used that email address
And said please please please please
Just tell me where I can buy it
I don't care what it costs
I want to keep everything intact
It's great the chuckle heads of love it
So maybe they'll hear this plea
And one thing I do want you to see
Required homework
Particularly if you live in the UK
But it'll work in the US as well
Because you'll see what's happening over here
And what can happen in our own country
It's really a shocking report
From current TV that aired on television
I embedded the video
About basic filming in public in the UK
And you'll see some police officers harassing this guy
And put a throwing on real attitude
Telling him to shut up
Telling him he has no right to film in public
Which of course he absolutely does
That he's acting suspicious
I mean it's really bone chilling when you see it
It's just duh
That's required watching
I won't take you too long
Then actually I think that the giant pool of money
Is also required listening
You can download it from the drop as well
And then thank you very much Glenn
From the city show which is
Or the city podcast I think
Glenn is in South Africa
And I said what is going on with the xenophobia
Which is the word to jure by the way
Killing people
And setting them on fire where they're live is what I call it
But okay, we'll give it the names xenophobia
But it's messed up in South Africa
And Glenn has all the details for us
Glenn, come on in
Hi Adam, it's Glenn you from Cape Town South Africa
And I thought I'd chime in regarding the
Terrible xenophobic violence that's been happening here
During the last nine days
Now basically it all started
In a township called Alexandra in Johannesburg
And actually has spread
As spread to many other townships around Johannesburg
In partying
I think that as a nine other eight provinces of South Africa
A very lucky so far not to have seen these
xenophobic attacks in the sense of the violence
That has been generated over the last nine days
Yeah, it's all because foreigners who are in
So who are coming when I say foreigners
I'm referring to people from other African countries
Yeah, I'm really glad you cleared that up
Because in Africa, indeed if you go to South Africa
And you're from the Congo for example
Or Uganda, you are a foreigner
It's a different country, you know
And clearly your view does a foreigner
And we specifically mentioned Zimbabwe
Of course we all know about the gross human rights violations
And absolutely anarchy that's occurring in Zimbabwe
Is driving a lot of
A lot of the population down to South Africa to seek asylum
And also not to forget other African countries
Up north of the Congo, the DRC
The names just gone
And of course they see South Africa as the land of milk and honey
Now South Africa is one of the one of the is a country that does allow
It's the silent asylum seekers or refugees to integrate
And of course a lot of them with virtually no money
And with the close and their backs have settled into
A lot of the townships around South Africa
And from what I understand a lot of them are even better educated
Than the South African themselves and speak fluid English
And that's causing a lot of anxiousness I would say
Clearly
And of course in this case in Johannesburg
And of course they've built up businesses
They have been able to get employment
And so forth
And basically the locals aren't happy
With the fact that they are taking their jobs
Their houses and their women
And this is sparked on a courageous violence
From the locals to these foreigners
I'm talking really 22 people have died
I mean there is a front cover page
In the times of a person burning today
I'll send you that link as well
It's really really sad to see this
And these are the images that we were very familiar with
During apartheid and that these images
Have to read their heads again
14 years later
And of course not to forget that we are going to be hosting
The 2010 soccer World Cup in
To very very short years
Time
So I hope that government actually pulls its finger out
It starts doing something about it
It's Glenn Veren from Cape Town South Africa
Great here, hope you won't blah blah
See you again
Yeah, I remember they work for us
Thank you very much Glenn
For reporting in on that
Sounds like a real mess
And man indeed only two more years until the big championships
Are being held in South Africa
Not good right now
I think it's 3 million
Foreigners have come in from other African countries
Oh, what a mess
Yeah, well we got a mess all over the place my friends
And certainly in the United States a lot is going on
And you know there is a call for a revolution
In my mind the revolution definitely is Dr. Ron Paul
Yeah, he may not be the Republican nominee
Remember he's only a heartbeat away from actually making a chance
But wow, do I want to thank Jeff Garlow for getting me a full blown version of
Amy Alex
Ron Paul Anthem
Wake up my friends
Wake up
They work for us
Let him know
We're in charge now
Wake up
They work for us
We're in charge now
We haven't followed the constitution and now for what we are to be done.
The system that we have today are ripping off the middle class.
In your matches, I'll go to the nation we have if we didn't have the federal reserve system
printing on as money.
We're not gonna give up the fight.
It's all about the message, not about the man.
And Amy Ellen has really done a great job on this one.
The Ron Paul anthem.
Thank you very much again for getting me the high-res version of that man.
It's good.
I don't know if it's available on e-music.
I actually should have checked that would have been the first place to check.
I don't think of it.
I'll go and see if I can purchase it there.
Of course, you can also get a great deal from e-music.com slash daily source code.
You'll get 35 free MP3s with absolutely no obligation.
And of course, there's GoDaddy.
I've got my codes.
DSE1, DSE2, DSE3.
I'll give you a little bit different deal.
The one that most people seem to like as seem to use the most is DSE3.
You're gonna domain name for $6.95.
You can't get a cheaper anywhere else.
My friends, definitely gonna do a full bar Friday show tomorrow.
I'm in deep in the city doing all kinds of meetings.
So it'll be a three time show.
Actually, what I should do is I should try and keep the prostate cancer prevention code
on the same track as the number of shows I do each week.
And that will be motivated to get to my five to have a 60 to 70% reduction in prostate cancer.
Huh? In that good.
They work for us, my friends. Remember that.
We'll have a great food bar Friday.
It's just around the corner
and we'll get into the weekend.
Until then.
Leave your life with passion.
And enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.