Delta Shara Charley's 7-9-4, today is September 30, 2008.
$60 million worth of airplane straps by us.
To the next generation, we need to cut any of my ears.
You need not sticky turds in.
I like to think I'm flying to the street.
Look, casting is a matter of curry.
We have the chance to turn and leave us all.
We're moving right from we want to ride.
We got to make us meet before we get much older.
We're all someone's brother.
We're all someone's son.
Hello!
We're getting each other.
Don't know where we're gonna go.
You're the one strand of standing.
Make the noise of making clear.
Wow!
We're not on the same side or less.
We're all someone will be alive.
It's a trend.
We know we all can share together.
We'll go out and tell you how we're born
We'll eat them, we'll eat them, we'll eat them
Oh, we're off someone's daughter
We're off someone's son
Help, give them a pretty child
Don't know where we'll go
Don't know how we're born
We'll eat them, we'll eat them, we'll eat them
Oh, we're off someone's daughter
We'll eat them, we'll eat them
Oh, we're off
Someone's daughter
We're off someone's son
Help, give them a pretty child
Don't know where we'll go
We'll eat them, we'll eat them
Oh, we're off someone's daughter
As I sit here, overlooking the San Francisco Bay
I'm proud to be an American man
You're the voice, and you know it
We won't sit in silence, we won't live in fear
And our voice will be heard because we all are the voice
Everybody welcome that is source code episode number 7
9 or 4 coming to you from San Francisco, Northern California
In the curry condo, it is Monday evening, 9, 30 exactly
On September 30th, 2008, of course, historic
We're going down today
I'm sure that a lot of you are at least keeping an eye out on some of the news over the weekend
I actually spend most of my weekend indoors
Watching Seaspan, which is just a fantastic
I love those fat hours
Fantastic initiative from the cable industry
Where's last night even I was watching
What was going on in the floor of the house
Watching everybody speak
And this morning I even set my alarm
5am, 8am on the east coast
So that I could see the continuation of
Well, it wasn't really a debate because of course this whole thing was railroaded
Ramrodded through I should say
And all set up to pass
And this is really the thing you have to understand about the way America works
We have a representative government
So we choose our representatives
We can't all go and vote on things all 300 million of us
So we choose representatives and they are supposed to go and represent
You know my brother represent
Which means they should be representing the general consensus of the constituents
That each representative represents
And not a single poll disagreed with the enormous
Percentage of Americans who did not want to see this bill passed
The bill by the way, which came out Sunday evening probably around
Or actually afternoon it was around 3 o'clock
So when I saw C and N had a copy of it
And finally got released and 166 pages
You know me
I was spending quite a lot of time looking at it reading it
Cross-referencing
This thing was like the Lisbon Treaty man all these cross-references
And language that really just goes beyond me
I mean it was not very understandable at all
In fact I was still parsing it when
When I got an invitation to join this week in tech
And I actually said I can't join you because I'm doing something right now
And I was just reading this thing trying to understand it
Wow
You know I wondered is there anything to talk about today
Is there any kind of news we should be discussing
Anyway, so you've got this representation
And very clear that the majority of Americans did not want this to pass
As is if we need time to think about it
We need time to parse it we were you know being threatened
Without any real
Real explanation of what the the choice of not passing this bill would be
Everyone said it would be horrible
Now when I look at the markets
And of course so you know by now that the
Emergency economic stabilization act of 2008 did not pass the house
By a nice enough margin
Markets particularly the Dow Jones that's what I would say most people are using as the bench mark or the bill weather
Down 770.77 points
Still well within Dow 10,000 territories
So it's not like everything crashed tremendously
I think a lot of this was probably already built into the price
The world did not come to an end and of course this is not over
Because there will be more
Trials at this they'll come back at it. They're going to do another round
I'm sure I'm not quite sure how or when or what but you better believe something's cooking
And let me just reiterate this was from in my mind this was not really ever about the money
In fact by all accounts from what I can tell the 700 billion dollars was just a big number pulled out of the air
I think it truly was about a power grab
And the power grab being almost a fourth branch of government and that would have been the federal reserve the treasury and their cronies
Where these guys all come from obviously and
I think that that is the thing that that we did really good on by by telling our representatives look you just you just can't do this
He just can't pass this owned by the way. There's all kinds of stuff in this bill that that I was able to parse out
And some chuckle heads helped out on the source code drop drop that I owe slash daily source code
The four instance for any further approval of funds that would only be a 10 hour period almost no debate
I'd probably these all the house committees were would be cut out again. I mean this is just it's a power grab
That's really what it is finally you know real control over our money
So I'm very proud that we let our voice be heard and we stopped this again. It's not the end all the be all the end all the be all
But at least you know, we were able to say unlike in the European Union I might add
Hey, you know, we don't like it. I mean this was almost as good as a referendum the way television and the internet and email and all these different pieces fit together
We let our voice be heard and right now we didn't want we you guys were trying to hand us and we said no and our representatives heard the call the majority of them at least
And it didn't take place
But I'm sure there's going to be a lot more to talk about a lot more to keep our eye on in the coming weeks and months as we move up towards the elections
I do have a couple of things that I want to play for you
Most of this obviously from from the drop. This is Representative Thaddius McCotter. He is a representative for
Believe Michigan
He's a Republican and I just want you to listen to this two and a half minutes about what he said on the on the floor of the house and this was today
Talking about the depending bail out. I think he really nailed it on the head
So let's just have a quick listen this of course coming from YouTube links in the show right today not to change anyone's mind
But to express to my constituents my reasons for opposing this bill
There will always be time and pretext enough
For people to compromise their principles and perform poor public policy that may in the short run be popular
But in the long run it will be detrimental to long-term interest of the American people
We learn this through history in the 1832 bank panic Andrew Jackson had the question of whether he would remove the bank of the United States charter
The people in the bank did not like that they threatened the prosperity the American people in the middle of a panic Andrew Jackson looked at these bankers
And he said there are no necessary evils in government the treasury to you gentlemen is closed
This was an act of courage on the park of President Jackson because he understood what was his stake was not merely in a femoral prosperity or a panic caused by the very people with their hand out
Andrew Jackson understood this was about majority in rule
It was about the faith in the people's representative institutions and those who inhabit the seats in which they are entrusted
Today we are in a global financial bank panic. It is the first of our global economy
We are seeing a leverage to bail out of the United States treasury
And in the end these interests that want your money are threatening your prosperity
And the choice you face is this
You will lose
Potentially your prosperity for short period of time
As the expense of your long-term liberty
Once the federal government has got you to take that risk and pass it on to you as a quote-unquote moral hazard
They will be in the marketplace and as the free market is diminished your freedom itself is diminished
And as your congress does not stand up to these and put forward a better plan that truly protects the taxpayers
It truly has the long-term interest of the United States is heart
You will be in jeopardy of losing both your prosperity and your liberty
The choice is stark and it was put forward in the book by Dostaeevsky
In the brother's karma's off the grand inquisitor came to Jesus and he said if you wish to subject the people
Give them miracle mystery and authority but above all give them bread
And it has always been the temptation and a crisis especially to sacrifice liberty for short-term promises of prosperity
And it was no mistake that during the 1917 Bolshevik revolution the slogan was peace land and bread
Today you are being asked to choose between bread and freedom
I suggest that the people on Main Street have said they prefer their freedom
And I am with them I yield back right on
Right the F on my friend
So this was very interesting to me as I was following all these debates and I'm hearing Republican after a public and after a public and a post
And a post this and which I don't maybe it shouldn't be surprising to me
Of course congressman Dr. Ron Paul or Republican
But I certainly have never ever felt that I was a Republican for any reason whatsoever
And I think I've been pretty clear that I don't connect with Republicans or Democrats certainly not the candidates
I'm pretty sure this is pretty much a professional wrestling where we've just got puppets who are making up a really big show
And it is a show and it's a huge huge show
But to hear all these Republicans oppose this
Told me that the Democratic Congress really is the ones that has been trying to sell us down the river
And it surprised me
Because you immediately think hey this is Paulson the Bernanke this is a Bush thing
It's the Republicans it's the evil the evil right
And you know it's just a pussy left
I think who just let themselves be railroaded or who basically are the the puppets of Wall Street
Anyway, lots more investigation to be done certainly on my part before I draw all kinds of conclusions here
Some very interesting stuff on the drop and I'm not quite sure because I really am a little tired
I am putting in full days here because I am here to work
You know, I've got a whole bunch of people we're trying to create something here in my view
But this was very interesting at least at first glance
There's something called the the Basel 2
And of course there's a link in the show notes a daily source code dot com
But it's an international banking standard or a set of
A set of rules or standards
That went into effect I believe officially in April of this year
And by October 1st which would be Wednesday
Every single bank that wants to participate in this international banking network
Or the ability to actually communicate and do trade and lend borrow transfer etc
We'll have to adhere to the Basel 2 standards left to comply
And somehow this may have something to do with the reason why this was
Blown in so fast and why everything had to had to take place
Lickety split overnight
If you want please have a look at the information
And see if you can help us deduct this and figure out exactly what's going on
Oh, by the way, before I forget Shana Tova
It is Jewish New Year officially
At least here in San Francisco and for those of you in Australia
Hope you enjoyed it
In the United Kingdom meanwhile
Wow, things not going too well there either
The after northern rock, I guess the the largest mortgage lender
Which was still a real company is now been nationalized
According to the telegraph it will cost taxpayers 150 billion pounds
To to nationalize Bradford and Bingley
One of the country's biggest mortgage lenders that's like almost 300 billion dollars
You can't tell me this is all just because of the subprime crisis in the United States
Clearly there's something going on
We've been through it many times
It's really a house of cards a big Ponzi scheme
The whole idea of how fractional or reserve banking works
How you can essentially print money out of thin air
And it looks like it's back to the real economy
Like we really got to get back to work and build stuff up
And keep a very sharp look out for what people are attempting to do
Some interesting feedback on the drop
There's a people now using it kind of as a comment thread
Which I'm not a big fan of a much rather you did that in the comments section
Of the show page itself
Title of this don't let Adams distortions fool you
And it basically debunks my entire
Theory as to why we should not approve this bail out
Need more economic savants to get in there
But that's too bad that
It's easy for Adam to say he'll comfortably ride out the complete collapse
In his mansion with fistfuls of cash in a bar of gold
You and I will suffer badly probably lose our houses and families
And many will die Adam will feel little pain
You and I will bear the brunt Adam doesn't seem to understand the stakes
Now I think I do and I've got 70 people here in San Francisco
who depend on me to keep this and not just myself
But all of the media management to keep this company running
Luckily during all types of economic downturns
Entertainment always seems to fare reasonably well
So a little harsh there on what I do and do not understand
And of course you can't look in my pocket book and I can't look in your wallet
So you don't know what I have and what I don't have and vice versa
And if I have a lot of dollars and a dollar goes down
It's going to be just as bad for me as it is for you
By the way the pound was down significantly against all kinds of
Different currencies such as the dollar
So anyway
I love this this was pretty funny
Buy my shitpile.com
Now there's a go daddy domain that or a good inspiration to hook yourself up with a go daddy domain
You got to take a look at this what happens on Main Street effects Wall Street
And you can basically upload your shitpile that you'd like to be bailed out from
And there's all kinds of funny stuff here
Broken heart
Million
Dirty video games 55 bucks
It's a cool site. You should take a look at that
And also if you want to set something up like that yourself
Then go ahead and use my go daddy code which will find in the show
Now it's a daily source code dot com
So over the weekend as I said
Saturday I just did some grocery shopping and kind of stocked up a little bit
Because as you know I'm staying out here for a while
So we get some stuff rolling which will be seeing
By the way, if not the end of this week the beginning of next week
We're setting some stuff up
The return of texture more on that later in the week
Or as I said beginning of next week
And I'm reading through this
Economic emergency economic stabilization act
And I get a ping from no actually
I knew that twit was coming on
And I'd never really had the opportunity to check out the live stream
And the chat room because it's always like one a.m. on Sunday
Or actually so Monday morning in the UK
So I think I love flip it on
And before they started the show
And John C. Devoreck was on he's
He's talking with Leo
And actually they were talking about
Sponsorship and financial stuff
And so I sent John a little Skype and I said
Dude this is like totally on the on the stream
And I don't know how many people in the chat room
But there's a lot
You may not want everyone to hear this
And then Leo said oh I don't even should join the show
And I still had a third of this thing to go
And he was expecting Patrick Norton to show up
And anyway so I finished reading this document
They're still going out at Patrick hadn't shown up
So I dial in
And I was fun
It was nice to be on to it again
Because of course I don't get invited
And then to get a spur of the moment
Invite was cool
And it was fun to talk about just some pure tech things
Although at the end after the show ended
We did continue and here's a comment about that
And by the way it was only so it wasn't in this week in tech
Which was what episode 162 I think
It was only for people who were in the chat room
And on the live stream at twittlive.tv
Who could hear that the conversation
Which was well known behold about
You know stuff that we chuckle had
It's usually talk about
Hey Adam
I'm not really a
Took a little head
But I do enjoy the head
I don't know agenda
I just got through watching
Foot live there
I went along and that the conversation
I had there with Leo
After the show was over
It was cold
And as soon as I 11 got mentioned
I knew it was coming
I just stepped back and enjoyed the ride
Yeah I enjoyed that conversation
I enjoyed that conversation as well
And what's interesting
I got several comments
But all around the same thing
For some reason people have the idea
That Leo and I don't like each other
And
John C. DeVorac actually said
Wow man you sounded like
You were really pissed off at Leo
I said what are you talking about
I was like I'm happy to be on the show
And then I started getting email from people
Saying wow Leo was really mean to you
I'm like huh?
Please people
And I don't know what it is
Maybe it's just the way we interact
When we're talking
I have no idea how you get this idea
That we have a problem with each other
In fact
Seeing all this type of commentary
Leo, you and I got to do a show
Man this will be fireworks
Even if we're professing our love
Each other people
So incredibly confused
I'm pretty sure that Leo and I
Just like each other
Okay
Yeah
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Game To Weasel
On this week's show
We enter a curious village
With a guy called Professor Layton
On the DS
I also play mercenaries
Two on the PlayStation
Three
There's copies of sonic
Chronicles
Up the Grams for the DS
And also a feature about the new
Spider-Man game
Web of shadows
That's all the gamesweasel.com
Alright Matt, thank you very much man
I promised
Myself that I do a better job
Talking about the sponsors of the
Daily Source Code
And what kind of incredible deals
They have to offer the chuckle heads
Let me just list them for you
If you're looking into
Getting a rent a car
If you need a rental
For a week or actually
You've got a deal for any amount
You can get 10% off of any amount
That you spend at budget rent a car
By using my code
You can just go to
The show notes at
DailySourceCode.com
Or curry.com
And you'll see the codes
Right there
30 dollars off weekly rentals
That budget
BrooksDone.com
If you don't know what BrooksDone is
It's kind of I would have to say
Well, it was still around
It was my second favorite
After sharper image
If you go to the mall
You know
My girls I'll be like
I'll go clothing shopping
Or whatever I say
I'll go find the sharper image
And hang out there
Of course
Sharp image
Went belly up
And BrooksDone
It's kind of like
A sharper image for outdoors
You know, they've got like
Barbecue thermometers
And automatic
Long lighting
Yeah, just kind of
Different kinds of pocket knives
A little more
Less techy
But a little more useful type stuff
But a very very cool store
And of course
You can shop online at BrooksDone.com
10% off of anything you buy there
With my code
Then of course GoDaddy
Several codes there for the.co.uk domains
We give you half price
You can't get a cheaper anywhere
Certainly not a.co.uk domain
And you'll get 30% discount
Off of anything you buy using
My DSC3 code
And finally
You can still get 35 free songs
At EMUZIG.com
With no obligation
Now that's not
It's very different from other offers
That are out there that may say
You can get more free songs
But you can literally cancel
The minute you get your 35 free songs
Again a code to be used there
And all the links in the show
No, it's a daily source code.com
And it's curry.com
I've been following
What's going on in the south
In the southern states
With apparently there's a gas shortage
And it's not really being reported
In mainstream media
Which is confusing to me
Because as I look into it
It appears that
The supplies are filling in
But yet again today
In Atlanta
The Atlanta Journal Constitution
This is
Yeah, the 29th
People are now calling 911
To get gas
They're running out on highways
And I don't get it
Because I thought that there was a supply
But apparently it's still going to be three or four more weeks
And people are getting pissed off
Waiting in these lines to fill up their tanks
And there's reports of some people
Getting out
There's someone cut in line
And you think that's bad in the UK
If you break the queue as they say
In Atlanta now
They just pull out a baseball bat
Start whacking your car
So I certainly hope that this isn't a problem
That it's going to last too long
Because you want to see some
Shit come down
And you want to take a look
When you can't fill up your car with gas
That absolutely
It's a day record
Let's put it that way
This is one you're going to see all over the internet
Guy by the name of Stephen Spoonor
And he is a security expert
Now there's a whole bunch of YouTube videos
And I'm just taking part nine
I think this is a it's 12 different parts
Maybe it's hours of the interview with this guy
Who's talking about how the election
I think this is even a dig
And I saw a Boeing Boeing
I mean if you haven't seen this yet
You might want to fast forward
Because I do want to play it just a little bit of this guy's audio
From this YouTube clip
Where he's saying that the whole idea of having electronic voting machines
Is just prone to fraud
There is apps
Just like thieves
Can use a man
The middle technique to steal your
Your ATM
We are credit card information
It all goes to a central processing
Or it all goes through central processing
In the so-called cloud
Well you know what
Let me just bring this up
You can listen to a little bit of this guy yourself
Fantastic to hear
How
How's our how fragile
Our our elections have become
With the
The entry of electronic voting machines
And he's actually calling the election
For McCain Palin
Unless of course those who are the true owners of the earth
Change their mind
I have predictions for the upcoming election
Should we do that?
McCain Palin
By 51.2%
And a shotgun
Probably winning by three of the tools
And you believe that's going to be
Because of course that
Now this audio sounds really shit
Now that I'm listening to it
It sounded a little bit better
When I was listening to it
Just on the laptop speaker
Let me try a little bit further on
Baby
We know
Now we're getting out
Oh crap
This is not good enough
I don't want to put you guys through that
Take a look at these YouTube videos
With this guy
He explains very clearly
How the only way to have a fair election
Is by paper
Ballets
No electronics
And that the system is too easy to gain
He says the last two elections
Have been game that way
And quite honestly now that we found our voice
And we have our power
Maybe we can overturn some of that
Maybe we can still do it in time
It's certainly worth consideration
Because I think that we're going to have a
A close election
And as you know
I'm afraid of both sides
I don't think that either one of the candidates
Actually is going to run anything
There actors
There front men
And it's people like
Well
Certainly on the Obama side
Zignu Brazinski
Who are running the show
The guys who McCain's got on his
In his camp are just
As evil and frightening to me
But there is something that
That is starting to bug me a little bit
And I was actually talking to Janet
The office about this
Because she's noticed it
And I would have to say it happened to me
Yesterday for the first time in person
Where I noticed this fanaticism about
Barack Obama
By people who are clearly
Extremely desperate
Very very upset with the state of affairs
And see
Not just the Democratic Party
But I would have to say
Literally Obama as the Saviour
As far as I'm concerned
Vapit and empty claims of
Change
And
The neighbor
I've talked about here at the condo
Like the horny millfee neighbor
Maybe a cougar would be
A better description of her
So once again
I'm going into the elevator
Oh shit
Hold on a second
Let me just
Sorry to do this to you
My cell phone alarm is going off
Telling me to take out the trash
Hold on
Stop already
All right
Of course that means it's six a.m. in the UK
I'm sorry
Seven because that's when I have to get up and take out the trash
I'm Tuesdays
I've got no people for that
Anyway
So let me just say that
I haven't seen her in a couple months
And she lives on my floor
Almost like across the hall
And by the way, she's very pretty
She's I think she's my age
Maybe one or two years older
And once again, I'm going over to the elevator
And the minute she hears my keys
And she's like
And this has happened so many times
And she's like come out of her apartment
And she'll have some kind of excuse to
With me
And so I'm like hey, you know, good to see you
And we're chatting on the way down
She had me like I'm going to put something in her car or whatever
Like that was a big necessity
And we're chatting
And you know, she's smiling
And we're just shooting the breeze
And then she says, well, you know, I'm really busy these days
Because I spend two hours a day
Doing call outs for the Obama campaign
I'm volunteering
But it was something
It was something about the way she said it
That just kind of struck me
And I know that she could see that in my...
And I didn't say anything about
How could I, right?
You can't launch it into the kind of
Stuff that we've been talking about for the past months
Or we're almost a year now
And I know she saw it
And she started to kind of get that fanatical look
And I have a feeling that the love is over
I really do
And I'm seeing this fanaticism
Which is somehow it's misplaced
In a way it's like a misplaced patriotism
I'm not quite sure what it is
And it's certainly not all Obama supporters
But there is a certain fanaticism that is frightening me a little bit
And I don't have to say that it feels
You know, I really hate to say it
But in a way it almost feels like the beginning of
Some kind of fascism
And by the way you have to really
If you're saying oh my God
What is you saying now
I'm not calling anyone Hitler
Anything like that
But why do you think that it looks
I know lots and lots of Germans
And I know Germans who were around in World War Two
And do you think that the Germans were born evil
Kill people and take over the world
No
It came from something
It's bottom-up some kind of grassroots thing
Where people are really afraid to
Speak their mind or say what they really feel
And they have a strong sense of nationalism
And then it's so easy to get them hypnotized
By a few people
And I don't know
I can't quite put my finger on it
But maybe it was exacerbated
By a posting Dave Weiner made on scripting.com
Which was so full of hatred
You know this whole idea of red states blue states
And I hate you and you hate us
That's un-American
And that is so fundamentally wrong
To be talking that way
We all can respect each other's differences
By the way
I don't see that much difference in what these candidates are saying
If you saw the debate
What were the differences
They agree on everything
That's confusing
Very, very confusing
So I'll just have to hold to my
Call it conspiracy theory
But I'll just have to hold to my theory
That actually what's going on here
These guys are just puppets
And doesn't matter who wins
The people who truly rule the earth
And by the way, their banks are still standing
Goldman Sachs
Morgan Chase
Definitely members of the
True Owners of the Globe
Going to the other side of the Globe
This is
I told you it was going to happen
Now there's
Flu shots coming to the United Kingdom
Already
Being administered in Australia
This is the
H3N2 Flu virus
Now remember that the dangerous bird flu virus
I guess is H1N5
So it's all meant to look and sound alike
But now hundreds of people have been killed in Australia
By the so called Brisbane H3N2
Where did this come from all of a sudden
And so
They're starting to
Vaccinate people
For the flu
And it's a very scary story
Look, I just don't trust them
I just have such a huge distrust
For these vaccinations
And
If you live in Australia, Brisbane
Let me know what's really being said about this
Flu
And let's keep our eye on this coming to the United Kingdom
And I presume we're going to see this all over the world
Once again, you know, this
It still feels like
Big pharmaceutical companies trying, you know
How many times have I not said this
If I was as evil as I think these guys are
I'd release them shit into the air
So that I could just administer this vaccination
I make money
These are big public corporations
They've got to do something
And I truly believe that this next comment
Which is about the
Guardazil vaccine
Which is
Ment or
Advertised as saving
Young girls from
cervical cancer
The way this person calls in doesn't sound like a true chuckle head to me
There's no identification of who she is
There's no sign-offs
Um
But the message is very clear
Let's dissect this one for a second
Hey Adam
This is the first time I've been moved to get
Really pissed off all listening to the daily source code
I'm kind of behind those catching up and you were talking about
Guardazil
You're actually raging against Guardazil
And
I have to say I've been very skeptical about vaccines
I can't say that I'm a big fan of them
Um
In fact I was extremely
Concerned about Guardazil when it came on the market
And then when
Some people were getting sick from it
Yeah, I think it changed my mind
Do some research
I hate it when people say that
I think I've been doing quite a bit of research about this
And as you get into your story
I'll see if I can tell you what I've learned
And
I'd love to hear back from you on these points
Yes, it's actually transmitted disease
But by offering up a vaccine
Against it is not encouraging people to have sex
Now see I don't think I have
I've remade a big point about this
So this is why I'm very highly suspicious of this comment
Because I know that there's a lot of
Schools and churches who are saying
This is promoting sex
That's why we should do it
I'm against injecting anything into our children
Okay, beyond
The vaccines which I I do believe
Are real and are working and have stopped
Death on a major scale
Things like polio obviously
But once big pharmaceuticals got into this game
And each child that is to be treated with this guardazil
Cost about $500
So it's a huge money maker
Now I've never really really made a big point
About it promoting sex at all
But you do point out
I say that it's a sexually transmitted disease
So as you yourself will reveal what
What the HPV virus actually is
We'll talk about other ways
That you can combat this without going the vaccination route
Whether we like it or not
I think the statistic is something like 80% of women
Will get HPV in their lifetime
Now
I have not seen this statistic
So I'm not too sure about that
But seems awfully high to me
Considering that this is basically
Genital wards you know you get it from having sex
And as far as I know
If you wear a prophylactic device
You
Will be shielded
From this
And that could be as an adult
Your husband could cheat on you
Yeah, would you could cheat on your husband
Good wind up with it
And it is the biggest cause of cervical cancer
And what makes the guardicill
In my mind even more important
Is that it is like one of the first vaccines that
It's not a cancer vaccine
Although it is marketed as a cancer vaccine
I've been paid very close attention to the news reports
I've paid very close attention to the commercials on television
It's being marketed as a cancer vaccine
Let's go on and tell me what exactly HPV is
But there is a direct direct link
Between the virus that is HPV
Which is genital wards
There you go, thank you, genital wards
Do you know that
The way you used it
This is treatable by the way
It is treatable
And you have to have a patch me regularly
And I believe that they can even
Detect it with like vinegar
It's this is not like something super duper
Yes, and by the way
I have two women in my immediate family
Who have had cervical cancer
And have had horrible operations because of it
And both of them say
You know you're right
There were other ways to detect this
There were other other ways to combat this
And the idea of a vaccination is weird
Okay, and when it's weird
I get suspicious and when I'm suspicious
I'm thinking someone's out there to make money
And when I'm seeing the statistics of girls dying from this
Of severe pain, nausea, illness
Because of this vaccination
I'm thinking BS
And cancer
So if it means that a generation of kids will have a far less chance
Is having cervical cancer
I'm all for it
In fact, they're expanding their label
And the coming year to
I believe include boys
And also inoculate older women
Yeah, I wonder how you know this
How do you know that
I'm on the lookout
All the time for information
I got guard to seal
Just sounds evil to me
I myself am almost 30
I was disappointed to find out that
I was not covered by insurance to get it
Partially it's assumed that I've been exposed to it so much
By the time I'm in my mid 20s
But it doesn't matter
Which is awful
It's also partially assumed that I won't have as many sex partners
And it's also because as an adolescent if you're exposed
Or a late teenager or in your early 20s
If you're exposed to HPV
You are a chance of having a very viral strain that contributes to that cancer
Is much greater
So
Looking into it a little bit more
I kind of hate it when people do that
You would look into it a little bit more
Do you re-threat
Savans I call upon you I need a medical
Savans to explain to me HPV
Is it indeed just pure general awards
Is this something that we need to be vaccinated against
Are there other ways to protect yourself?
I need some real information from a real doctor
And not from what I really feel is like a shield for the pharmaceutical companies calling in
Almost like she's reading a script
And yeah, there are risks
And the way that vaccines hit the market
Big pharma
Not always great stuff
Keep that skeptical I are
But consider it consider a little bit more
Especially where it comes to cardio
That's all
And notice she's using the brand name
And not the medical name
I'm hot
I'm sweaty I'm tired
It's been and that hasn't even been here a week
It's it's it's a rough man
Ah luckily I can play a jingle here
Because there is a
Comic strip
Time to move over to the European Union
Here's our correspondent
Comic comic strip
Hello Adam
So you say it's in financial meltdown
I would say the world is in financial meltdown
At least the banks are yes
And what is your opinion saying
Well, you know we're saying let's bail out for this bank right?
It's full of you say
It's because you say it was not regulating
Markets enough
Well, federal you says that's no federal measures
And this is how you knew
You know let me just tell you that now
This is actually a comment that CSB sent in before the fortress bail out
Which is kind of interesting to play it now
This is rampant
All right, this is not just the USA
Not just because of
That that there was fraud going on in the states
It's happening everywhere it happens
On the European forces it happens
The London exchange
I mean this is this was one big scan
Have you ever met a banker that you actually thought was a smart guy?
No, these are guys that go to strip clubs all the time
And hang out and drink and do drugs
Because they know the game it's simple
It's a really really simple game
EU is next
Planning to go wrong there look what the European central bank has been injecting into
Into the financial system
Oh, no, this is not just America
This evilness is all over the world
So I must say that I don't believe in anything
I don't believe in it and
Seren Paul said globalization works
Only if free competition is at work
And EU is too over-regulated
Too fortified
And EU fails to meet challenge
Of Asian economies like China
And others
So now let's enjoy the right
On the Titanic to downfall
Western civilization
So long and thanks for all the fish
Yeah, thanks for all the fish
I don't think it's going to be that bad
It's not going to be pretty that's for sure
I don't think it's going to be all that bad
I'm just looking at the markets and saying
Hmm, that wasn't you know these guys are eating each other up
They're eating their young
They're eating a banks they're being hijacked to bring in the deposits
It's a big roll-up strategy
I'm sure people made billions and billions today
With the way the stock market went down
You watch you watch
If we don't go into severe
Economic depression with people dying
Then it certainly wasn't as dire as it was sold to us
Is it good? No
Do we have to change things? Yes
I mean, while Gitmo Nation East continues to expand the United Kingdom this is this is just fantastic from the BBC
Children's web watch dog has been launched a new internet watch dog has been launched to help protect children from harmful web content
Such as cyber bullying and violent video games
So it looks like there's going to be some kind of task force that will take down these illegal sites
I haven't seen the legislation yet
I'm not quite sure exactly what this is going to be
But the strategy apparently A established a public awareness safety campaign
Notice safety
Establish measures to protect children and young people such as here comes taking down illegal internet sites
It's going to be interesting to see what is deemed illegal versus what is basically free speech
Which I guess does not exist in the United Kingdom
Promote responsible advertising to children online
And establish voluntary codes of practice with an examination of how websites handle videos
Or messages posted by users a lot of this of course it's about social networks
They're all going to take it down. This is just the beginning
This is the censorship of the internet
People who are so incredibly pissed off about the net neutrality
Here's your next focus, okay
Are these people crazy?
Are they absolutely nuts?
How about educating your kids?
You can't just do all this. There's nothing in the strategy here to educate children about how to behave
And what is socially accepted and what is not accepted and parents have a role in this
Taking down illegal sites
That's next a daily source code
No, no this guy's in sight. Oh, he may be using foul language. We should take down that illegal site. You watch. You watch. It's coming.
Proof is in the pudding
This is you got to read through this article about the European Union Parliament
Where there was you remember the three strikes you're outlaw that that France started up
Well, I guess this was last week the European Union Parliament voted to pass the telecom package
Which is a big overhaul of the European telecom rules which included
Basically you know a version of this three strikes you're out
And there was an amendment put in amendment I think 138
Which made it so that you know that it will have to go through a judge and a
Yeah, only a judge can really order a disconnection of your internet
Introduced by a French guy minister of European Parliament Gibono
I guess his name
And looks like Vivian Reading who actually we had on the show like she tried to keep that amendment out
That come to think of it. She looks kind of reptilian
Yeah, you think that's interesting. Check out this comment we got from Chris laden who works in our UK
I think he was doing an I think part of his intro there got cut off
But it's Chris laden. I recognize the voice anywhere
If I thought she'd just come across
Schools in the UK and now starting to thumb print children and in the month the school has the
The thumb prints in order for a catering system. So there's this third party company which goes into schools
Scans the children's thumb prints
And then keeps the biometric date on a database so that schools can have cashless ways of
Vending foods so the work so that the system is company comes into school
Can companies can children some prints children then go to cafeteria on pay for their food with their thumb prints?
So this is a couple things in one first of all this is already being implemented in big box supermarkets
Where you're given the option to pay with your finger print your biometric data so it's all kept on record
And like dumb sheep most people think oh this is really cool
Also it's really the move over to electronic money was just gives more credence to or more
Possibilities for people to to make up fake money
And I'm just a believer in in real
You could call it gold backed
But some kind of real valuable
Value not just pieces of paper and so removing even that piece and taking it on to the digital realm
It's just not a very good idea
Along with that comes the story of this
Information which by the way the UK is very good at losing misplacing dropping into the wrong hands. It happens all the time
And it's just another piece of the get-mo nation big brother cafeteria on pay for their food with their thumb prints
I mean this credit time is quite attached. Oh, so you can see if the kids eating you know
What the kids eating if they're eating right more reasons to take your children away from you?
That's happening more and more throughout the world
Parents being blamed for a number of things and this is proof
kind of things now
This is where I get really started to freak down because schools have schools
And now the government had access to children's
Some friends at the point this has been going on for years
Once that school is in reddish, it's called Trinity High
That's Trinity High to all took UK if you want to go and bomb art their website
There's also another one in Bishop's store for that thing that's Bishop's store food high school something like that
These are two that are come across
But yeah, there are companies that go around into schools take children's thumb prints and then keep them on a government database
It's with ridiculous
And
It's strange because some schools are based in nine children food. It's the case if we don't have your thumb print we're not gonna sell you food
Yeah, there you go. There you go. No thumb print no eaten
A school that did this is morally high school and leads
It is forced one of its parents to make their child pack lunches
This is school provided an alternative way for children to receive their dinner
There's either a case of we have your thumb prints and we serve you food
Or you're gonna starve
Which is absolutely ridiculous
This is a complete outrage. This again is a complete case of them not working for us
No then
Spying on us and watching our every move
It's the whole big brother situation all over again
It's biometric dates and the government has access to this just isn't generally good thing
Hey Chris really knows what he's talking about because he keeps getting searched randomly when it comes
Out of the tube station the the subway
Just you know minding his own business random search
And if you say you don't want to be searched, they rest you and the United Kingdom and you're taking downtown and
Then they really search you and they waste your time essentially it happens to him lots of times
He's a frequent travel on the tube
Get my own nation my friends get my own nation east
Either I hope you well right here
Hope you end love you. I mean at no home. Oh, they work for us
Yeah, we got to keep reminding him Chris we really really do a man
We really do
Where's the outrage in the United Kingdom?
It was so nice to see Americans pissed off and saying hey we're not standing for that crap
We need that same type of outrage in the United Kingdom. Here's something that might spawn it
This is from the times main stream media publication
Drivers will be banned after two convictions if they exceed the speed limit by 15 miles per hour in urban areas or 25 miles per hour on motorways
This is new road safety laws
So the way they do this of course is with digital cameras
The track average speeds over long distances rather than what they call the gatso cameras. I've never heard that term gatso
Basically those are the the speed cameras that record speed at a single point flash, you know, they get you
So this is now they're tracking you over long distances
And they look at your average speed and based upon so they don't even have you violating you know
I could have be teleporting for all I care
But they said look you you you start you were here at 10 a.m. and you were there at 10 30
I'm sorry you drove too fast and if you do it again, we're taking away your license
Ah
Meanwhile the true criminal criminals are
hard at work scheming to take away
more of our freedoms
Yeah
But you know what we're gonna stick it out chuckle heads
Because we do make a difference today was proof
And you know if you tolerate this
Your children will be next
So if I can't you promise then I can't you fash least
But let's follow a way too too
If you got it all I can
On a month's quick front and two people tells me it's what got this one man
Yeah
If you turn over
And that you'll be
And if you turn over
Then that you'll be
Who be next
Everybody keeps my heart down, always with my vision
A beautiful land being so big
Holding your heart to date
But I'm a pacifist
I've worked so hard for us, but now we're really in time
And if it's our reality, then we'll try and we'll be lost
We'll be lost, we'll be lost
We'll be lost
And if it's our reality, then we'll try and we'll be lost
And if it's our reality, then we'll be lost
We'll be lost
And if it's our reality, then we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try and we'll try
and they'll work for us. It's a good thing. Doesn't mean that I don't want to like just play some jam and songs on a show this week. Even I get a little tired of it all. Alright, I got a good all I got to go to bed. You know, I was just thinking. I'm gonna turn this into a positive. I'm gonna invite my neighbor Laku guy. We're gonna call her Laku guy. I'm gonna invite her to dinner. Maybe launch her dinner and I'll see if I can get inside her head and see what's going on. And of course, I will report back here chuckle heads on the next day.
source code or one in the bare near future here for the next couple of weeks in San Francisco.
Until tomorrow, the day after or maybe even to the footballer Friday,
enjoy your freedom because you're learning how to take advantage of the system to enjoy more of it.
But whatever you do, whatever you do, live your life with passion. Another fine,
and be the old presentation, stick it in your ear.