Dองest.
Delta share a Charlie.
Seventh five six.
I did fairly source code.
The $16 million worth of airplane went climbing strapped by ass.
Breathe, breathe°
The nexturing would reach me
Research themselves down the stage
We might not need nasty
Be strategic
honesty
I like the music
türk 많이 teach me
Your Go
podcasting is led neste
By the unreיבing of big, nice proteins
The street gotta be obvious
You've got to follow in your face
You make this bright
analyses
Kirkin Y
Survey
Pre- Shameless
I cover all you
But you're a young man, I'm not trying to get the three gonna take on the one thumb
They got blood on your face, your big discreet waving your thunder on
We will, we will, I'll you, sing it on
We will, we will, I'll you, I'll you, I'll you
I'll you, I'll you, I'll you
I'll you, I'll you, I'll you, I'll you
But you're a normal man, I'm not being with your eyes
Gonna make you something someday, you got blood on your face
Big discreet waving your thunder on your face
Your leg, we will, we will, I'll you, I'll you, I'll you
I'll you, I'll you, I'll you, I'll you, I'll you
Everybody we will, we will, we will, I'll you
I'll much of a mind mess up is that
You're ready from the scene and this thing something completely different
Paranoia, as like coming to you from these splice trips
These from homegrown productions, everybody is dead in source code 756
It's a food bar fried, so let's keep this vibe going
Non-matched up with your recognized and rainbow since you've been gone
For the Friday festivities, maximum music freight train
Same old dreams, same time every night
Follow the ground, never wake up
So I get out of bed, but I'm not shoes in my head
Don't fight back to break up
These bow holes are closing in
Look at the picture of me
Sit to the ground, sit to the ground
All of the head can't take it
Could I be wrong, or take it to the ground
You can't just bounce off, break it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Bitch, you'll be gone, so in that I stand
If it's the last dream, I'll be the world that you sent to me
I could take it after no good night
Time comes around just soon
You can't know what you need to mean
Your boys and ladders, you can't agree
Just go to show you don't care about me
Sit to the ground, sit to the ground
All of the head can't take it
Could I be wrong, or take it to the ground
You can't just bounce off, break it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Bitch, you'll be gone
All of the head can't take it
Could I be wrong, or take it to the ground
You can't just bounce off, break it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Bitch, you'll be gone, so in that I stand
If it's the last dream, I'll take it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Bitch, you'll be gone
The infallible Richie Blackmore and Rainbow
Since you've been gone
You know, I think it was some live album somewhere from Rainbow
I think it's live in Japan or something
I think it was Rainbow
We actually hear, actually hear Richie playing a solo
And you hear is a finger snap
I think it's like a pinky finger broke somehow
I've got to find out
Hey, everybody, it is the Daily Source Code
Coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey
Known as Gilford, we're on the west side of, or actually
We're on the west side of G-Town
Another beautiful day, Cabo case ceiling visibility
Okay, all the nine's was a little overcast early this morning
We're going to get to more overcast weather in the next couple of days
We're on the south, lots of people on vacation in Spain
And Portugal and Northern Africa and bummed out
Because it's a rain in there
Oh, shit
A bee just flew in the window
Hey, I've changed the setup a little bit
I don't know how it sounds
I have a different processing chain on the microphone
I hope you like it
Oh, my goodness, let me see
We've got a couple of things to get to
Today, I want to keep the freight train rolling
Because we are on a Fubar Friday Express
Which means lots of music, minimum talk, all kinds of BS
Come in your way, check out this cat fight
Ah, a little bit of infighting going on here
James, I was a frequent caller
The show here and Charles, who's a drunken Londoner
He didn't like me supporting Boris Johnson
Not that I actually endorsed him or anything
But I have to say I do like the fact that Boris Johnson is taking a stand
As a June 1st, no more open containers of alcohol
Permitted on public transport
I agree 100%
If this one thing I really despise is taking the train back home
At the end of the day
Usually I'll, in fact, I'll take a car because I just can't stand
All these drunks sitting on the train, bothering you
Making noises, you know
It's just like it's irritating
Absolutely, now is it enforceable?
I think that's highly unlikely
I have no idea
I have no idea how they're going to enforce that
The last thing you want to do is tell a Brit
Who's had a couple of drinks that he has to put his beer away
Okay, add to something you just don't want to participate in
Hey, and this is David from St. Carlos California
Quick question for you
This is the second day in real one
I download the daily source code right by iTunes
Downloads it for me automatically
I get two episodes
The same two episodes actually
One couple of times, and the other doesn't
What's up with that?
Is that a taking a system?
Thanks man
You know, this is something that's pretty irritating
A couple of people have emailed me about this
And I've seen reports around around the net
And of course, this is obviously directly related to our name
Change to mevio.com in the US
By the way, for those of you wondering
It will remain BT Podshow in the UK
There's a different vibe about Podcasting in the UK
Thanks to the BBC, they understand
It's not amateurs in basements with microphones
But some good crapman
Anyway, it relates to that
And I believe it's the way that iTunes handles
Your RSS feed
It's kind of a technical discussion
But there's such a thing called
Is the global unique identifier
The GUID
And regardless of what URL is attached
And in fact, interestingly enough
I believe the URL sometimes is the global unique identifier
You should never, once that GUID has been seen
Which is a part of the episode
It should never be downloaded again
And we've seen this problem from time to time
And unsubscribing doesn't help
It doesn't happen with every single show
For some mysterious reason
Another thing that I don't understand
So you could be getting shows twice
What I don't understand though
Hopefully this is not recent episodes
It sounded like it was
That makes no sense
There's no reason why you should be getting two copies of the show
Although of course, it is double the pleasure
And twice is nice
So I'll talk to Andrew Grumman again
He's the guy who knows the most about this
I think juice also had that problem
Not juice, but juice
Formally known as iPod or lemon
Also had some issues that early on
So thank you for the reports
Keep them coming in and I'll keep my eye on what's going on
And get the guys involved
Has this ever happened to you
Welcome to the rock and roll dinner
What will it be?
Hey there gorgeous, what's the special?
Nickelback with a side order of follow-up boy in 6am
Same old stuff
Yeah, really
Sounds like the same special from yesterday
Oh, it's something new
You too
Got anything I haven't tried yet?
No, chill
Well, have you tried the love and the club
With a side of some shot he get loose?
Yeah, give me gas
Have you got any independent dishes?
No
Yes, and the tavern on the green
You know, we've just got the same old same old
No, what'll it be?
Are you looking for something new and fresh?
Are you constantly bombarding with the beat
A love to repeat?
Well, now there's a choice
Indy radio chat new
We've taken over the FM airwaves
And internet radio every Saturday night at 10 p.m.
We feature interviews, news
And of course, the best independent music we can get
So hop on over to Indy radiochat new.com for details
And don't forget to subscribe
Alright
This one going out to Prime Minister Gordon Brown
who just upgraded
Cannabis from Class D to Class B
We got a lot to do
Don't criticize me
Do you want to kiss me to kiss me?
Am I not able, do I not?
I love you
not just deaf voices
All right题
Oh yeah
Come on, it's time for me
And a door to sit, sit
We're like six years
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, cinnamon, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Even the Lord, yeah
So you got to hear my life
And don't break his sight, baby
Go to the Father
Don't break his sight, baby
Yeah, now there's a concept
Legalize it and I will advertise it
That's right
It's that simple, it's so crazy man that this plant is being outlawed
Even further
When I read in the newspaper that the drug companies who are extremely worried about their patents expiring in the next three to five years
They're now going back to all kinds of natural plants trying to extract remedies
Oh my goodness, do the research
Hey, by the way, I've never met a guy who was stoned on the train who bothered me
I wonder what Boris Johnson asked to say on the matter
We'll certainly have to ask him if possible
I'm a little anxious right now
My daughter in right now in the UK here at the Curry Manor
It is 8 minutes past 4 in the afternoon at 4.24
My daughter takes her driving test and she's nervous
I went driving with her yesterday for about an hour
She's pretty good, you know, all things considered
Again, I've had the luxury of having to learn a skill similar to that
Not too long ago because of course when you think back to your own learning how to drive period
And actually when you got your license, if you've been driving for a while
Aren't you thinking to yourself, man, I drove for crap back then
Now I know a little bit more about what's going on
So I had the same experience of course learning how to fly helicopters
Then fixed-wing airplane, so I'm a little more laid back than most probably
And understand that the license to drive is kind of a license to learn how to drive
Of course, it's definitely frightening when you're on your own child
It's about to get on to the severely congested highways, highways, motorways
And with all the other idiots out there, which of course is what she has no knowledge of
That only comes with experience
Of course, a beautiful young woman in a snappy little car
Anyway, so I sent out the good vibes, my friends
She was definitely nervous about it and she's like, but for 30, it'll be rush hour and I was like, you know, dude
Just approach
Approach this driving test, the way you would Facebook, you know how you navigate Facebook and how you're fingers fly over the keyboard
And how you're in complete control and command, so you being controlled and command of what you're doing
Don't worry about little mistakes, just work your way through traffic other people making mistakes
I'm just really hoping she does okay, she would be so, so disappointed
So I have to I have to be done by I can only do another 30 minutes because when she calls, I have to be prepared for whatever is coming
So perfect timing, I would say to roll out
You know, well, that's his time
I'm counting casting
I'm hearing this, this is the head test
Young pole
Hey Adam
For a hit test again, then we're going to start right away with intro
Alright, one, here you go
Oh, that's right, please to meet you
Oh, easy one, that's a not uploaded, benefit of these six and nasty girl
I'm sure I got that one
Number two
Oh, what a day to remember
It's a
John Anderson surrender
Great song to play, I should open the show with that song one of these days
I'm clear about that one young third
Number three
It has a little bit of
Body heat maybe
And all of this we sensors are from
Answer number one
This is Benedict's nasty girl
Please to meet you
I think I want to be my neighbor
I'm living in a fantasy
I want to ask he loves
You want to come to me
Do you think I'm a nasty girl
And every moment
Dance dance
Is that it?
Wait me when you're done
That is the six
I guess you'll be the only one I've ever found
Next is the girl's answer number one
Oh yeah
And this is answer number two
This is John Anderson surrender
John Anderson is answer number two
And this is the final answer for just weeks hit this
Imagine
And I said body heat
I think I was thinking body talk
Which is another imagination song
It's not this one
Which one is this yeah
Oh, okay
And a hybrid
Heat is the night
Okay, do I get half a star for that or a quarter star
imagination in the heat of the night a sensor number three
And that concludes hit this number 100 and 21
So I'm on and she did this
Well, John the first two of course are pretty easy
The third one I had a little mix up there
makes up there. I think as you get a quarter star for the least.
Like always, hittest.mevio.com is the place to find info about the hittest answers.
And of course, the iTunes links if you want to buy tracks featured on the hittest online.
Adam, thank you for playing again.
Everyone else, thank you for listening. Next week I'll be back for another hittest.
So until then, F1, take care and remember to try to think with your heart. Bye-bye.
Your Honor, please don't bang that gavel. You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give a nod. To the harnessed work and lawyer,
He's Jersey tight in bed. He's Jersey tight in bed.
Oh yeah. Your Honor, what do you say? He might even fit with his case.
Yo, don't call to come back. How's it going, Adam? It's Jersey tight. The official music
kind of just of the chacha, except no substitutes. So hey, I know I've been away for a little bit
then real busy in the personal life. Things are good. Things are good. Hey, while I was away
the billboard article came out. I got to be honest. I was a little little annoyed that
my shining face wasn't pictured in the article. But hey, what you're going to do. Who was
featured in the article, along with Mr. Curry, was the other J.T. John Tagliari. Jersey's own,
the other J.T. And damn it, Adam, you can't just share a page and billboard magazine without playing
the guy. In fact, I went through his site on the potsafe music network and noticed that you've never
played J.T. This is indeed a mistake. John Tagliari has a wonderful, wonderful album and I'm
strongly encouraging everybody to check it out. Right now, this is Leap of Faith on the Daily Source Code.
To me, I'm trying to hold to these everyone else. I always put it myself as I'm trying to hold
to feel what they're feeling. I'm trying to hold to make it less but made that's what they're
calling for me. I feel so free now. I need no one you hold me down again. I'll leave of faith.
Well, look back at what I've done. Give up anything worth learning there. Only know it's time to have fun.
It's time to live without having a care. I do really, there's all heavy in there to this middle
fairy tale plan. Now I know I'll break it for a minute. I'm going to give it all I care
about. Now I know I'll break it for a minute. I'll break it for a minute. I'll break it for a minute.
You know, knock down the doors and throw out the roof of us. Nobody's coming for me now.
I'll hold my head higher and higher. I'm going to take my stand out and leave of faith. That's what they call it.
I'll leave of faith. No one you hold me down again. I'll leave of faith. That's what they call it.
I'll leave of faith. I'll feel so free now. I'll leave of faith. No one you hold me down again. I'll leave of faith.
There is nothing like the top-down driving around Jersey Sound, John Tagley here in a leap of faith.
Exportly introed by our very own Sir Jersey Todd, the official music college just up the shot shot.
Back on the footballer Fridays. I think I actually have played JT before Jersey Todd.
Somehow the reporting must have gotten messed up. I'm pretty sure I've heard the song before.
Hey, big topic. It's all of a sudden just blown up here. He's about nuclear energy.
I'm not one to just take what's written in newspaper as the gospel. I certainly believe there's been a structural campaign against nuclear energy for at least two or three decades.
There's a lot of misinformation out there. The whole nuclear atomic thing scares people.
There's a lot of information, perhaps misinformation about what the waste is.
Most of us think nuclear waste involves vats of green ooze. Nothing could be further from the truth. They're nicely stackable blue glowing cubes.
They are highly radioactive, but you can store them in places, and that of course is what it's all about. What do you do with the waste?
Well, I'm learning a lot about this. The first thing my belief is that he even have a discussion. We have to remove a lot of these preconceived notions.
I have to re-brand nuclear energy. It's just the wrong name. I've been working on names. I came up with moon juice, thinking that wouldn't be an interesting idea to put all the nuclear waste up on the moon.
I think it's doable. I think there's plenty of space up there. Wouldn't it be cool if the moon was glowing blue? Wouldn't that just be awesome?
So we could call it moon juice, and your life would be powered by the moon.
Well, you can imagine this insanity has brought on some commentary.
Hello, Adam. Go, man. They are not Bristol. We're naming all re-branding nuclear energy.
Well, I don't just fucking call it magic moon beams or pixie dust. I don't think that's easy.
People know what the thing is.
Magic moon beams would have to be there if you call it.
It's politically correct. Also, what a fucking BT pod show.
Are we going to get BT media?
I already answered that question.
Yeah, magic moon beams. I like that, man. That sounds even better to me.
Hey, sorry. Ross and Washington. One problem was sending nuclear byproducts to the moon.
We had some good ideas on the drawing board.
Morphs specific DT polygenic elements into the sun.
And nobody wants to do it because there aren't ones fearing of a dirty bombson area.
Where is the rocket blows up or there's airs to attack?
And all the waste is viewed across a large area.
And yes, not a good scenario.
Now, what we can do with it, well, the problem is we have.
What a thing.
All right, I think we should stop because there's someone the authorities are listening in.
Yeah, that is a point.
You want to make sure that space travel is a little safer than it is.
But then again, I'm sure that there's a waste, no, maybe not.
I don't know.
Well, then there's the option, of course, of looking at another heavenly body.
Hey, Adam, you don't shoot the nuclear waste to the moon.
You shoot it into the sun and you refuel it. It's all good.
Bye.
All right, all right.
So magic moon beams may not be a viable idea.
But of course, there is one savant out there who absolutely knows what's going on.
And he's done an interesting thing.
I want you to listen to this.
Here's our buddy.
All right, nuclear soma, atomic rod atoms.
Adam, atomic rod here.
Been appreciating all your commentary about rebranding atomic fish and you and your other listeners
have brought lots of questions that need a little bit more than a minute and a half response.
So what I did was put together an answer show.
You can find it at the atomic show.
URL is atomic.podcastnetwork.com.
And there I answer some of your questions about waste countries that produce uranium.
What we should call nuclear power,
how atomic fishing can help us answer the challenges of oil depletion, greenhouse gas emissions,
and the economic power of the oil producing countries.
The show is about 23 minutes long.
So it's way past my minute and a half time limit on your show.
48 two adult daughters with great careers.
One lovely wife of 27 years ever said to five plus for solo.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Love you.
I mean it.
Protect your freedom with passion.
Yeah, atomic rod atoms.
Everybody.
And you should listen to that show.
I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourceco.com.
I listened to it this morning while I was prepping.
It's about twenty twenty five minutes.
Oh, it is four twenty four.
One second.
Sending out good vibes to my daughter.
Come on, baby.
Come on, you can do it.
Don't be worried.
Okay.
That would you all please just put your hands on your iPod and think along with the pod daughter.
She needs it.
So listen to this answer show.
There's a lot of good information in there.
And I continue my quest to understand exactly what the pros and cons are of of of of of moon beams of
moon moon juice.
Crap.
You know what I'm talking about.
Don't you?
Hi.
This is How Witson from The Young Pants FM podcast.
Best of you, actually music.
Can't you live under bridging limbs?
We may house music.
I can't break it.
I can't think you like it.
On this month's episode, we're delighted to have in the studio since pop legends.
Howard Jones.
Now, Howard may be one of the most influential people in history of electronic music.
Please also not very good doing radio announcements.
It turns out.
Let's see what happens when we try to get him to do this podcast for a month.
Hello, this is Howard Jones.
I just want to tell you that I'm going to be.
I know.
Oh, this is Howard Jones.
I'm very happy to tell you that I'm going to be involved with the Young Pants FM podcast.
And we're going to be talking about things from the year.
This is rubbish.
I've got no improvisational skills whatsoever.
Okay, this is the real one.
Hi, this is Howard Jones.
And check out the Young Pants FM podcast.
While I've been talking about everything from prehistory to the infinite future.
Listen to this and many other episodes of the podcast ad.
www.TheYoungPants.com.
That's the YoungPants.com slash podcast.
I thank you.
This is the Daily Source Podcast.
The Daily Source Podcast.
Hey.
Oh man, get ready for another mind fun.
Sing along if you can.
It'll blow your mind.
It's going to blow your mind.
That's hot.
That's going to raise my prostate cancer prevention quotient by at least one before the end
of the show.
Just thinking about the accelerometer.
I was going through Heathrow, Tamil Nadu Five.
You know what happened?
Toilets in Tamil Nadu Five don't have toilet paper rolls.
But there's a tiny tissues.
So BA or BA are trying to convert folders to scrunchers.
No.
You.
That indeed is truly an outrage.
Come extra blogger.
Well, hopefully I never have to go through Terminal Five.
But now you know, bring your own TP if you're a folder.
The world has gone crazy, my friends.
We're all hating each other on the inner waves.
And you can't wipe your ass in Terminal Five.
John Campbell, John, tell me all about it.
The world is crazy, my friends.
Like it's always been on.
Make you want a life cry little die.
Fly high, as wide as I can breathe.
Because of the remains cost a million never a minute.
We're all hating each other on the inner waves.
Like it's always been on.
The world is crazy, my friends.
Make you want a life cry little die.
Fly high, as wide as I can breathe.
You and children, the name of your God,
can never be controlled as a sin.
Because the world has crazy, my friends.
Like it's always been on.
The world is crazy, my friends.
The world is crazy, baby
Like it's always been
Think you want a life cry
Little dive, fly high
As wide as I am
They pay a man with a shovel
To go underneath the ground
Last and a man with a pair
The world is crazy, baby
Like it's always been
Think you want a life cry
Little dive, fly high
As wide as I am
They pay a man with a shovel
To go underneath the ground
Last and a man with a shovel
Because the world is crazy, baby
Like it's always been
Think you want a life cry
Little dive, fly high
As wide as I am
They pay a man with a shovel
To go underneath the ground
Last and a man with a shovel
The world is crazy, baby
Like it's always been
Think you want a life cry
Little dive, fly high
As wide as I am
They pay a man with a shovel
To go underneath the ground
Because the world is crazy, baby
Like it's always been
Think you want a life cry
Little bit of change
Though the world is crazy
Like it's always been
But
And that
This inner web shit is brand new
We're still got the training wheels on
But how to use it
John Campbell John
I was dropped off
For the daily source code
Drop, you can find it in the show
Notes, drop.ail, slash
Daily, source code
Which was down actually earlier this morning
I think they've upgraded something
So it's working again
Go ahead and drop some stuff there
If you feel like
It's Friday
My day Tuesday
Wednesday Thursday
Food about Friday
I have a final fun
Your phone to read
Okay, so my almost final thought
As I hope my daughter gets her driver's license
That would be nice
But thinking about
The inner webs
I think we need a little more investigation
Into PR firms and public relations
Proplicity and press in general
Because my feeling is
We're being gained, we're being played
Next time you see an article
Don't just copy it
And repost it on your weblog
Think about it
For a second
Is it really true?
Have you been interviewed for anything
And was everything you said
Representing the article
That it seemed absolutely the truth
The way you thought it happened
Well, of course not
And take it from me
So my thinking is
We're being played
On some
I'm going to start looking into this
Because it seems like
Just like the reports now
Coming in from China
With all this huge anti-western sentiment
You know like
Dude, are we trying to help these guys out?
I thought we were
So clearly something is a rye
And we must look into this
So let's do that
And I think that the final thought of the week
Because you've got to be happy
You've got your freedom
But do you really
Are you jacked into the machine
Are you believe in everything
The man is now
Pushing into your brain
Through those pipes
24-7
Through Twitter
Through email
Through RSS
Do you really know
Or all this information is coming from
Think about that over the week
In my friends
Because that is my final thought of the week
Until Monday
Live your life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another fine
Media presentation
Stick it in your ear