If you have dialed the anti-terrorist hotline, please make your selection from the following menu.
See you next one.
If you would like to report someone who is acting suspiciously, see next two.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next three.
If you would like to report someone who uses a camera than a suspicious manner, see next
four.
If you want to listen to the DSC.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Hot casting is a battle curry.
Typically the only thing missing from the daily source code is a monkey.
Writing in a cycle, juggling, fling, bowling pins,
while smoking a cigar and singing Willie Nelson classics.
We'll see what Adam pulls out of his butt for the DSC 739.
If you would like to report someone who is acting suspiciously, see next two.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next two.
If you would like you to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next two.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see first.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next two.
If you would want to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next.
If you would want to report someone who owns multiple cell phone, if you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones,
1.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phone, see next two.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next two.
If you would like to report someone who owns several cell phones, see next.
If you would like to report someone who owns multiple cell phones, see next have enough in your sense,
3.
Okay,ã  that's why I don't answer,
Gilford asked tripping me out, man, and we didn't hear a single thing that must have been six
fire trucks, the guy said Friday night into Saturday, you know, we were home, and we were
watching TV hanging out, didn't hear a thing. Now, the houses aren't that close together,
but still damn. First of all, to have a burglary take place, and then have the place to
march. The guy's like, well, now you have something to tell Patricia, I said, I think not,
I don't think we're going to be doing that. Anyway, if you want to participate in today's show,
I got a roll over my wire, and we go. I'm still not going to do Skype calls just yet, but I am
watching Twitter and people are already feeding back, so that's how they appreciated. And I
listened back to yesterday's show, you know, there were some weird things with the sound levels,
which are technical and was my fault. It was very cool I have to say to be talking about
something, and about a minute into the topic, then all of a sudden some responses or some
input would pop up on Twitter. It works. It's kind of interesting, so I'm going to keep it at
this level for now before we bring people in. Of course, we always have people on the show.
It's just we don't bring them in live at this point in time, at this juncture. Of course,
the guy who does the opening for the Daily Source Code PD Love from Lovehouse Radio, we all know
and love him. He's a parent, and he does some daddy cast, and he's concerned about this DNA
testing and called in. So, of course, we want to hear from PD Love. Hey, Adam PD Love from Lovehouse
Radio, and the Daddy cast. You're talking about this DNA typing, and you're discussion with
about all this stuff that they can do with this. Let me just let me just interrupt for people just
tuning in either to the stream or the podcast. So, this is a guy from the Scotland Yard who said,
you know what, we should have a debate. He didn't say we should start doing it, but we should have a debate
about starting the test kids as a five years of age to see if they have any criminal behavior
DNA. And if so, then we can put them into special training. I think you just rip them out of the womb.
Doing an amniot. Why wait until they're five? Why bother? So, this, of course, is stirring a
lot of shit up, and that's what PD Love is calling about. You really get reminds me when you were,
you know, talking to the lady Patricia about, you know, that making you watching what you eat,
and then start dictating what you eat, and that's not a thing. You reminds me of a book I'd be
a friend of mine and I had back about 16 years ago, and we started working on it, didn't finish it,
but there's all doubts. At the time, all the different tobacco lawsuits going on, and some
of the same players from today, but Nationalized Health Care, that kind of thing, and our premise
was that the government had Nationalized Health Care, and now they had the right to treat every citizen,
almost like a fleet vehicle in a corporation. They got to tell you what you got to eat.
They got to tell you when to go in for your check-ups, so they got to tell you, you know, what,
you know, they basically owned the bodies of the people.
Oh, wait until they insert the chip dude, when you get your RFID chip inserted,
if you don't play by the rules, they just turn your money off. Oh, I'm sorry, your chip no longer
allows you to withdraw cash when making any payments. You watch. And I guess that's one of my big
things about all this talk about in your health care reform and Nationalizing things. Where's
it stop? Where? You know, they're taking DNA to figure out what type of person you are,
what if they get it wrong for one thing? Let's not, sorry, we've incarcerated 5,000 people
because we forgot to carry the one. But basically, if they're going to start doing these types
of things, if the government is going to start owning the citizens, then we've given up our freedom.
We've given up our freedom. We've given up our freedom. We've given up our freedom. We've given up our freedom.
Oh, dude. PD, start. If they're going to start, we will give up our freedom. Oh, man, please.
Oh, please. You're all ready working for tax money for gas money right now. That's what most of us
are working for. Just to be able to put the go juice into the machines, the audio owner's
dude. And it's not the government, okay? It's not the government. It's the banks. It's the rich families.
It's names like Goldman, Oppenheimer, Rockefeller, JP Morgan Chase. These are the people who own us.
Look at it. They own, they own all the mortgages. She got to work for that with a kick out of your
house. That's my definition of ownership right there. A lot, obviously. And that's what scares me about
these different things. It looks so good from the own setting. It looks like all they're protecting
me there. They're giving health care to everybody there. They're socializing medicine and to
make it available to everybody. But at the same time, they're owning you. They're owning the people
that you're giving stuff away. Nothing comes for free. And if they're going to own your body,
they're going to tell you, okay, you need to exercise more. So we're going to start making sure
you log exercise, you know, running miles every winter day. And only eating these certain foods.
And by the way, if you get sick, we're going to, you know, take your body and we're going to
rejuvenate it, but we're going to give it to somebody else. You know what, and you give your organs away.
We worried about it. So anyway, I think this whole subject is just very scary. And I agree with the
caller. Don't touch my kids. I think it would James have said. Don't touch my kids. That's the
same way I feel. So keep the DNA guys away. Anyway, love you, mean it. No homo, great hair, hope you
win, and try there's something else that they added to that. But talk to you later, Adam. Bye bye.
Well, dude, let me just tell you your kids are already in the DNA database, okay? When they're
born in the United States, DNA blood samples are taken. And I'm pretty sure that this stuff
remains good. You know, it's like you can look, there's stuff in the database. They have the DNA.
You know, so they may not have tested all the theories on it. But as far as I know, the DNA is the DNA.
It's in the database. I'm not a DNA expert. By the way, shout out, we could use a DNA
subont on the Charlie. That's for sure. I was talking to a buddy of mine last night. In the Netherlands,
there's this thing one week after your child is born, you have to go back to the hospital
for a heal prick. That's on the database, didn't it? A prick in a Dutch is a, is a jab,
is you know, a needle. Okay. We're in the tower of Babble today. So they, they jab your, your kid
in their heel. And what they're doing there is they're taking a sample for some no well-known diseases.
And this friend of mine, person actually had a slight DNA malformity, I guess it's called.
And they were aware of it and then he's fine, you know, it's just some minor, minor shit.
Of course, the minor shit in that area can be quite major, so I don't want to downplay it.
But they found out that their sons DNA had been added to a DNA database without their permission.
It had already just been done just by default. So I'm sure it's all in there. I don't know
when this started, I don't remember DNA taking place in the 60s. So I'm probably not in it, but
dude, it's bad. Let's see if you want to participate in the show today, then just
just shoot me a tweet. You can go to Twitter.com and sign up. It's Adam Curry, all one word. That's
we want to follow me and that's what we want to send direct messages to. So my
Dodds is listening to the live stream on live 365 and he sent me a link here about the bank
of England and the Federal Reserve denying a report that they're in talks over possibly using
public funds to make mass purchases of mortgage back securities to ease the global credit crisis.
However, the bank of England said it was considering a number of other unspecified
options to address the turmoil and financial markets, which is continued despite the injection
by central banks of billions of dollars of liquidity and cuts and interest rates. Well,
let me tell you, of course, they're going to use public funds. Oh, actually, technically they're not.
They're just going to print some more money. Okay? They print it up. That's what banks are.
Banks are money creation companies and they're all commercial. Particularly the Federal Reserve.
So yeah, and this whole thing with JP Morgan and with Bear Stearns, this quote buyout,
that was just they printed up $30 billion. So that effectively devalues the money in your pocket.
Thanks, guys. Hope you all had a nice weekend. So I'm pretty sure, uh, oh, John Arnold says it's
called a heel prick test here in the UK as well, off to all children born in the UK by default.
Well, in the US, he'll prick mean something completely different. So let's just stay away from that show.
It's one of the pod save music network. Jersey Todd sent me this. This is an Olympic gold medalist
winner who's now got a record out on the P.D. M.A. and Cardi Patterson, temporary life ordinary girl.
This time it just won't stop raining on my parade. Time has come to speck on me waiting for me to fade
away into the graves. And I tried to tell myself, it's not where I'm going to be wrong.
It is a time for everything that I've been in for way too long. I'm not as good for the world.
I'm just an ordinary girl but I'm a person yet out of this temporary life.
It can't be like this forever. Someday it's gonna change, but that someday it's coming too far
and I don't want to wave my phone let me pretend but I won't let this be the end of me. No way, no way
I might need somebody shorter to catch the sins I cry and even with no end it's that I know I will survive.
I won't break me in my take all I need to get back where I want to be. And I gotta tell myself
it's not where I'm going to be wrong. It is a time for everything that I've been in for way too long
I'm not as good for the world. I'm just an ordinary girl but I'm a person yet out of this temporary life.
It can't be like this forever. Don't exactly know where I'm going but any place is better than where I am.
This is not a permanent situation. I'm going back to where I began
Where I used to run for the world. It's a time for everything that I've been in for way too long
I'm just an ordinary girl but I'm a person yet out of this temporary life.
It's not where I used to run for everything that I've been in for way too long
I'm not as good for the world. I'm just an ordinary girl but I'm a person yet out of this house
I'm just an ordinary girl but I'm a person yet out of this temporary life
Well I'd say she's anything but an ordinary girl when she's not
Carly Patterson from the Potset Music Network links to that of course in the show notes today at resourceco.com
I try to put in links to everything in the show notes including songs that are not on the PMN
In that case I try to link to DRM Free MP3s and Amazon.com
I've been having a lot of good success there. A lot of this old stuff unfortunately is not available on e-music
You know we have a great promotion going on with e-music.com
If you go to e-music.com slash daily source code you will receive 35 free songs
No obligation whatsoever. It's the best deal anywhere that you can find for e-music.com
There's a lot of potsafe stuff on there so I'm actually considering
We've been to talks with these guys. We should link up the database that we have and if artists want to sell songs on e-music
With just it should be a check box, right? Something really really simple
Anyway working on all that
I often bitch about the audience and understanding the makeup of it. By the way, if you have not looked at the survey
I think it's actually it's time to do another results
You know we did got that nice graph that I put up on curry.com a while ago
But people continue to enter their information. I think we have about a thousand entries now
You can find the link in the show notes at daily source code.com and curry.com
Nicely cross-posted
And well sometimes I'm not entirely right about the makeup of the audience
And boy did you guys let me know all about it
Hey Adam, this is Gabe from San Diego, California
I'm just calling because I heard a couple of DSC's back ago that you said that only middle age and braille
The people just know the DSC will. I'm 24 years old and I like your show
So I'm also going to respond to the DNA story that you just mentioned
That I've heard that there's a movie called 46 that uses the DNA story as a background
To a future society where everyone has to be placed under insurance
And they somehow have these restrictions in this thing where you can't make babies
Because if you have the similar DNA to your father, mother, uncle, brother
And I'll insist all that stuff then it gets to crazy levels and all that stuff
So well I'm not sure how to end this call but I guess you could say I like to show
Remember you an MTV and um, okay
I don't love you no homo and
Hope you win. All right. Also please play based on your show
I've taken care of that part
Also this Friday I got a call from James of North
I believe on Channel 5 they're going to play the movie Gattica
If you're in the United Kingdom, you want to watch that
It's a very esoteric kind of new wave
Ardy funky science fiction piece
To put it mildly and it's rather long
But if you really get into the story and you're not disturbed by any outside
You know, this is the kind of thing you want to throw on the plasma
You want to crank the sound up, turn down the house lights
Light up a big split and rock and roll
And it'll trip you out. I just got a Twitter here from from PWb
Our satellite repairman
He says that for some reason live 365
He's not available to get it or it's off air or something like that
No, it looks like people run
So I don't know what's going on
I'm glad I'm still doing these tests. There's do this so much to
Look at and and think about
While there's also words supposed to be coming out of my mouth sometimes it gets very difficult
Yesterday I played this piece by a guy named Pat Condell
And he basically opened up from a British perspective
In a very typical British way
And just let loose on the whole idea of the multicultural society
And it was just it was just filled with with very
Very heavily loaded interesting stuff
And I asked you guys to perform some homework
Check this guy side out telling what you think about it
This appears to be
The type of talk that's going on behind closed doors
Not just in the United Kingdom but all across Europe
In fact there was a demonstration over the weekend
In damn square and Amsterdam against the Dutch politician
Heard builders who's coming out with this quote
Anti islam
Or anti-coron movie
A 15 minute movie is not a long movie by the way
And there was a big protest on the dam
Well it depends on how you look at it
You know there was a like 1500 people
Some say you know maybe it was 5000 but just looking at the pictures
And I know dam square it looked like it was you know
1500 maybe 2000 tops
And previous demonstrations that have taken place on dam square
Have been a million people
To stop nuclear deployment
I mean I've seen huge crowds there
So that leads me to believe that this indeed is probably a conversation
It's going on taking place behind closed doors
And hey if this is independent media and the mainstream media is not
Bringing this to the forefront I think that I should
Because I'm just a conduit
Parkie who's been really active helping me out with the show lately
Sending in good links and stories called in and had the following to say about Mr. Pat Condell
Hi there Mr. Parkie checking in from a rather noisy city of London
I just listened to the last show with Pat Condell
I just wanted to let you know that I've been subscribing to this podcast
For about six months now and I've been encouraged
And everybody you listen to 30 source code
To go and listen to his back catalogue of podcasts
And sometimes you'll do a bit of baking in the earlier shows
Just kind of mono-ish but you'll get there
Again, sometimes he's opinion about some opinion
But by the same token I think you're absolutely right
It doesn't take the pulse of a lot of UK British feeling
I don't think he's a racist I don't think he's got some very strong opinions
He lays into Christianity, Judaism, Islam
Almost everybody I think he just doesn't like organised religions
And yeah just get your guys to check out all of his podcast
Listen from number one because I think he sets a thing quite well there
All right, take out Tuesday
All right, and I park you thanks keep the good stuff coming man
Appreciate all the feedback and the input and of course
It always takes a couple of days before people really get into the swing of a conversation
Yeah, we're just now really getting into the DNA issue
And that of course is because of the delayed nature of podcasting
Which is kind of interesting
Let's try this out
Call
Call and calling
Call and call
Call
I give up
Call and call
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah right, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
uh for those of you uh checking it out on the live stream today live through 65.com don't
tell me you couldn't keep your feet still. Party Ben just makes you want to jump up and
dance, honey. Calling up the pieces. Be more remakes of course average white band mixed in
there with uh what uh what the hell is the name of the song picking up the pieces there you go.
Elio, Elio. Well that's just quite interesting. I must say I'm enjoying uh doing the show
knowing that there are people listening to the live stream. For some reason it gives me
something extra there. It doesn't feel like I'm just talking into Hild. You know, Hild,
Hild is the microphone I'm using to talk into. It feels like there's someone out there.
Uh and even though Pete Obs seems to have some kind of problem getting on uh to the live stream
everyone else says it's working fine. Okay. Hey, let me see. Oh, this actually I've been holding
back on this comment for a while is from uh our buddy Trucker Tom uh who has been doing a lot
with HD um and we have some HD channels uh they're moving through rotation so you can find those uh
at podshow.com uh they'll be highlighted on the home page as well uh but they are available now already
and uh you can probably find a couple of them through uh Trucker Trucker Tom himself um and he's
you know it Trucker Tom not just a Trucker dude the guy is a visionary which means he can see into the
future and can feel what's coming. Then I think he's right. Yo Adam. Yo Tom while's here aka
Trucker Tom. We're gonna talk a little bit about the Apple TV version 2 software. Right, this is the
the new version of Apple TV that came out uh uh a free update I believe. By the, I read somewhere
it's not available for the leopard yet but under tiger I guess tiger um under the previous version
of Apple's OS 10 uh OS you can actually download um something that'll run that software. It's
not available for leopard yet I can't wait uh when it is available uh I'm gonna be loading it up
you know I will. Just so I can screw up my setup again installing software dangerous business.
Update? Of course I was one of the original people early adopters of the uh Apple TV and it was so
so it basically uh turned your TV your home theater system into an iPod outlet basically uh but
the version 2 software is really cool because it allows you to forget about the computer, forget about
iTunes and surf your multimedia right on your HD TV set using the uh little remote control that
comes with the Apple TV. Of course you can surf through uh podcasts and not necessarily the podcast
I'm subscribed to an iTunes because I listened to those on my iPod but it lets you know I found myself
kind of surf surfing through other podcasts for topics I'd never thought about while I was in
front of my computer so it's a much better uh user experience and I think that it's going to
help out podcasting getting it out beyond that uh and getting it to the television
you know whatever we can do to get it to the television and get it to the home theater where people
can easily uh kind of surf through it with a remote control is a good thing anyhow I hope to see you
at the uh new media expo and later this year in Las Vegas I hope you're able to come
we'll catch you later all right yo talker time everybody yeah hey me give up at chance to go to
Vegas give up any reason to go to Vegas now I don't think so I think I'll be past drinking there my
front thanks for the feedback it's highly appreciated as always
you
dream a dream with you in view
better times and dreams come true
as what over tell me where's the door
there's this for the song
if you're from here, don't don't get it shout so clear in my mind
don't break in through time
dreams come true better times
so hold me close sweet to me
for the dreams we've yet to see
can't wait to see you when the morning comes
there's less for the song
so hold me close sweet to me
for the dreams we've yet to see
can't wait to see you when the morning comes
for the song
for the song Jimmy Bradshaw from the pot say music now word
restless for the song and yes indeed I played it for you
and you know who you are learning lots of great things here on on the Twitter feedback loop
again it's really cool because you know Twitter if it refreshes once every three minutes or
something and that's when it brings in new messages so I'm probably just at the
the cusp of changing the topic or in the middle of the song and just the timing is really
really interesting
Matt Millard or Miller said check out quoteably dot com quoteably dot com slash
Adam Curry you can follow the entire thread of all of what people are saying about you on Twitter
and of course that updates a little more frequently I guess than then Twitter vision
whatever the what does it Twitter was it in that one's called it's Twitter Rific
Twitter vision that's a good one too Ron Stoops says Tom trucker Tom is more than a visionary
he's a missionary a visionary sees the future a missionary makes the future that's the mission
I like the missionary position myself
alright one last rather long comment but well worth it so let's listen to you
hi Adam Scott here of Scott podcast.com I was listening to you talking on the latest podcast about
the security which you've talked about any number of times before and you're just like of a great
deal of it just on necessary and it sort of reminded me of something that I was thinking about the
other night I get a podcast which is nothing less and nothing more than the president's weekly radio
address to usually very short so I've listened to a few of these in the last couple
seem to bring forth what I'd call a common theme and that theme would be the theme of what I call
a Trump card that is for let's say for the liberals a Trump card would be a saying or something
that they bring forth that always seems to trump your argument and for liberals quite often that
would be well think of the children yeah yeah oh dude I hear you think of the kids it's all about
the children I believe the children are future yeah of course it's true but oh you're so right oh man
you should listen to Noah Jen if you have a if you have a chance Noah Jen that I'll podshow.com
a John C. to Boric and I all the time are listening for these keywords and these messages and
and this is a big one and I also subscribe to the president's weekly radio address that's what
it's called you could find it in my channels Adam dot podshow dot com you can get the whole channel
if you want so you can listen to and watch all the stuff that I'm listening and watching to
one a daily basis in my on the go channel it's the top one we can just subscribe to that individually
and put it to anywhere you want including in your own channel absolutely think about the children
but that's changed hasn't it's got you know that would kind of embody it in one phrase think of
the children what about the children right and that was the Trump card they'd play that to win all
kind of arguments well you know what the Trump card is for this administration I think you already
know yes it's not what about the children it's what about the terrorists yeah because I was listening
to two different presidential you know weekly addresses and in one he was well actually in both
of them he was trying to get different bills passed through the way he wanted to or in one case
he wanted to kill one off they were passing through a bill that would have kept him from
torturing and he didn't want that because he didn't say tortures and yeah this is all about the
water boarding yeah torture that interrogation techniques but he didn't want that because you know
the interrogation techniques sounds better that's good think about the children with your
interrogation techniques we don't want to torture children no wait a minute maybe I'm confused now
and then on the other one he was against the bill it was about allowing people to sue telephone
companies if they got too much into your privacy because again you know what about those terrorists we
won't be able to find them as well the argument on both of these podcasts or addresses was
exactly the same what are we going to do about those terrorists and I just thought about the whole concept
of you know Trump card you were also talking about the I think you're talking about where
terrorists come from or how they're formed what they're all about and I just wanted to tell you
about something that I used to see a number of years ago right so I think what I was saying at the
time which you're responding to is why why do people do this to us why are the terrorists doing the
things they're doing why and I just don't believe it's a religious thing okay neither should you
there's a lot going on there's a lot of reasons why where does it come from okay let's hear Scott's
version it was a gosh probably five or seven years ago I have a satellite dish and you can
watch stuff from around the world and one of the feeds it was up there was what they call
Masticila and it was a feed that was out of you know that part of the world we're all the
terrorists are coming from and what they were feeding on this over and over and over on Masticila TV
were videos showing people who were you know terrorists who were blowing themselves up and fighting
for the cause we used to call this musta killer you know we musta kill you anyway
something like that really is that still on because that's I I have access to some satellite
channel stuff and I can view that over here I wouldn't mind seeing what that's all about was that
it's for I'll kite a training channel in any case I've seen the kind of information that was being
shown to kids from a very young age made me wonder you know it does this work and you know
is this effective and would they be doing it if it wasn't effective but I just thought you know
on the argument of you know maybe where this sort of thing comes from how how they get people
to do stuff like this to blow themselves up and do all that that you know is this possible that
this worked I'm I'm just bringing it up for what it's worth and with that I guess that's pretty
much it I noticed that you signed off your podcast with something that I'm I very much believe in
myself he said live with passion I first heard that from Tony Robbins but I can't tell you how
much I agree with it Adam take care and bye for now yeah man well it's time for me to confess absolutely
am I influenced by Tony Robbins I've read his books I've listened to his tapes and I'm talking
about 80s now when he was on when you're the Gunty Rinker corporation was advertising all over
the place you bet your man and it's gotten me through the past 20 years and you know it's
important you always need to live your life with passion absolutely so I'm not going to end the show
just now with that I'll play it so I'm to music that goes along with what you just talked about
in 1967 it's important how can I not do a dream
how can it be the way to see what can I do she's the same
how well what will I try I still don't see why she says what you're done how can we make all
time and I can't really be the way to
what can I say she's walking away
from what we say what can I do still love of you it's all green how can we hang on to me
oh the words and music still hit home 1967 Tim Harden how can we hang on to a dream
that's it for today's show no program tomorrow because I will be in London doing multiple meetings
but of course we'll kick off the weekend perfectly right with a full bar can't wait for it get your
suggestions in ASAP maybe we'll even uh I don't know maybe we'll bring people in on the Skype
for do a proper up-sol maximum music football Friday something like that you can email me
at to atom at podshow.com my Twitter which is now becoming important to me at least is Adam Curry
and of course so show notes a daily source code dot com and all the latest crap from me at
curry dot com until we speak on Friday for the football addition of the program live your life
with passion my friends and enjoy your freedom please another podshow podcast stick it in your ear