You're Adam, this is Tony, you know I got a problem with this whole you work for us
thing.
The problem is with the word work, what government officials actually do work, you know
I pay all my taxes but it's all for them to afford that big house on the hill, work.
The other day I passed a grow crew working on the highway, one guy working, four guys
watching, so I don't know we got to come up with something new, like you get paid
by me, you should work for me, but I can't get on board with this whole you work for us
because that's just assuming too much Adam, maybe can clear it up on the DSC 768, Capiche.
This is the A-B-SoyScoon.
Hello, I'm Cody.
I'm a servant yelping chair, no-one's happy to write tonight's on the blockchain, I take off with you
discretion, sir, for 70, 60 here to read you, 7-0.
Copy that, take off from my discretion, you object into the right hand turn.
So, I'll check in, no-one's happy to write here, sir, you're right turn.
Okay, number 277, don't be sure, taking off from my discretion.
That's right, everybody.
Delta share Charlie 768 is not just on the air, will it, in the ability, let's go, we're going
to be a car, we're rather down, there we have airspeed indicators alive, we're 50 knots,
tease appease, everything looks good, let's see if she'll take off, and indeed, she's doing it.
Okay, positive way to climb, breaks, you're up.
Okay, number 277, don't be sure, find information, sir, number 277, don't be sure,
find information, sir.
Number 277, don't be sure, find information, sir, number 277, don't be sure, number 277, don't
be sure, number 277, don't be sure, number 277, don't be sure, number 277, don't
call number 277, don't be sure, you see, there's air, all the important stuff,
You lose, you're getting back, don't look back and I love you
You're doing sweet out there
I'll hit you, I'll just sit in your way
You've got the teacher that had a drop on you
You're doing sweet out there
Here you are
And I know all the way's yours
You don't let thation come
You don't let this camera go
You get it all you gotta try
You don't want the cover
You got the cover
You got the loaded on my stock
Ready, go
You feel like a cod we'll get out of the
We'll you're on a team
You look so funny, girls
You do it in your mind, girl
I'm a kid, y'all
And I know I'm a kid, y'all
I'm a boy, y'all
I'm a kid, y'all
When you're with me
While together
Losing your shoes, your stockings
You wouldn't even wear out of your head
Will you feel like a call
And go to hell, can't time to start eating
No
You'd be able to swing your mind, girl
Here you are
There were no rules, girls
But are you gone?
Here you are
Let's go and go
I'm a kid, y'all
When you're with me
While together
Losing your shoes, your stockings
You do it in your mind, girl
I'm a kid, y'all
When you're with me
While together
Losing your shoes, your stockings
You don't even wear out of your head
You do it in your mind, girl
Here you are
There were no rules, girls
But are you gone?
Here you are
Let's go and go
I'm a kid, y'all
Here you are
When you're with me, girl
I'm a kid
I'm a kid, y'all
You do it in your mind, girl
Here you are
You're a kid, y'all
I must do some inhibition.
I did it.
I will fire the 38 minute roll before the roll.
Thank you.
Remember the rumlla snow
And then go right off
and see if you know
then You know
Then Go
Right off
and you know
Needless
let us
And then Go
Right
Don't
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, sir, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I have some prawn in chat for a little bit because you are my co-pilot on DSC 768
Okay, we're a trim it at all off here. I've just passed the Hockham
The OR beacon for those of you who are
Following a lot may be on their Google Maps, of course. I
We got to bring along my other GPS tracker. I want to sucker. I am
All right, so we're just bringing along here. I'm gonna
Have a two seven seven to a few years or some time for people thinking one two nine this will fall over by
27,000 one two nine four. Thank you number seven. I'll be sure all right. That's off to being in hell. Here we go
Thinking approach number two seven seven. Don't the share of transit
Two seven seven. Don't just here. I'm picking a bridge. Get off the main path. I'm at it
I'm going to have to do a charming one eight two. You have far from Farrox to Rotterdam
Just release by Farrox radar. I am 10 miles to the west of your field
2300 feet request transit by the overhead. That's more than seven thousand number two seven seven
Delta share
Seven Delta share to come to Q and T school
Seven zero four seven four five miles around to the big and I have a head to Q and H
She's one zero one eight
Seven zero four seven one zero one eight and call you five miles number seven Delta share
But say that actually today the
Conditions are a little bit better up here than I thought there would be we've had a lot of storms
Thunderstorms rain. I can see that there is also
There is some rain in my
In my dream
As we'll
Probably find out as I start to cross the
In my channel
We need today for
Delta share Charlie number seven six and eight
I think that you know the one of those sounds seem to us. It's just me flying so
We're going across
The channel to Rotterdam
I have a little bit of business to model so it's the end of the day today
Um
There's a lot of interesting stuff going on as we get over the channel we'll talk about it
And we've got the Irish vendor taking place today
We've got a well and you sponsor of the show that I want to tell you about that
We pretty cool
We're also
Want to follow up and then code next element areas
Which is a whole mother's carry thing all together and that's coming from a guy
Flying solar with two thousand three hundred feet so
Bear with me for a second. I'll leave somebody already on and we'll talk in just a little bit
Number seven don't share them five you mean
I would have never share them all to the big and I would have had two thousand three
Overhead next two thousand three to number seven don't share
I just get a little bit bumpy here actually
Which is to be expected because I can see the storm but I'm ahead
But I'm being said the air will get a little bit more turbulent
But that's okay no passengers
And
You guys are actually getting the best of all
That was a nice little dip you guys are getting the best ride of all today because
You don't even have to listen to the boring bits when nothing's being said you get the
Monty where there's quite a crosswind blowing right now
I'd say well I got about to twenty knots so I'm 24 miles an hour and it's a bit blastery
Okay, I can see
You can hear a few which of course it's a real famous
Or it's
Bunction in the second world war so now I'm gonna set to deathling as my next
Destination here the next to waypoint
To take me cast a little bit left of the storm system which I'm obviously happy about
Looks like we're clear this nothing here in the pattern of course I'm well above pattern traffic
So some of Delta's here over it
I'm so nervous here a little dip I'll see it be in the town of seven I've found seven on top on next number seven don't be sure
Okay, so I can see a plane coming
My way he's about 400 feet below me
And
plenty of clearance there
Don't I just want to make sure I do seven ohs properly now there's a little bit of
If you can hear that beeping that's my
Traffic collision alert system
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to steer a little bit to the left today
It's said are going directly to
Deadly which is my normal waypoint
Because in my path in fact directly in my path
Is
Little bit of the storm system here which is
Delta T and something else
Delta N key
Delta L and we're 0.3
101 to 01
And
Okay
Can you say, hot my favor and shoulders?
Watch us know our 277 Delta sheriff, lighting commation service.
I can have to do and Tony 1, a two VFR from Faroh again.
I like to stay with you for a little more lighting
service and I'll be passing you with the currently in 2,305 to
number 7 don't share.
I'm going to get a ticket, I just want to go one in the right for the
event after the event.
I want to get a coupon for the event.
1017 and I'll have a short look at the traffic.
Thank you to number 7 don't share.
Okay quick scan temperature pressures, everything was good, fuel sufficient, everything's not
not worried.
I don't know if I could believe you man, but if you wouldn't be good.
I don't know if the people will serve it, you can hear off and at the
payment program.
Okay, so don't all the calls we need to make, I'm going to set
mess and I'm going to talk to them in a few minutes, but let's just get the
time from BBC World Service and let's see what the headlights are.
Before we, before we, before we talk to them, let's see what the
headlights are.
I think we have to debate it in you, Alfa.
Let's hear it.
It's for a clock.
It's English in your first language.
You might want to check the news in a different one.
We report global and regional news in 33 languages.
BBC World Service.
This is the BBC in the BBC.
Don't you believe it?
Post here, or for any.
Where are you?
Over here, in the BBC.
There.
Just a few minutes.
Here.
Over here.
There.
Over there.
In addition, the US Supreme Court rules of business being held at Guantanamo Bay as the right to challenge their detention under the US Constitution.
We go live to Washington.
And to Southern Africa, where two leading opposition leaders in the Far West are detained by police.
Here in Britain, a senior opposition politician designed some parliament to mount the challenge before the voters to the government's anti-terror policy.
Oh, that's another big, man.
What a big shabang.
That is this extension of the polling term suspects in the UK for 42 days extended from, I believe, 28 days.
Man, that's been a big deal over here.
Hold on, I'm going to talk to you guys one second.
Let me just, okay.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I want you to number 277, double share of changing frequency demands to 1,265.
Okay, thank you, bye-bye.
I love her.
That's the number 277, double share of transit.
Actually, I should have said, quite a profession service.
That's the number 277, yeah.
That's the number 277, double share of Charlie 182, be a far from Farrowster Rotterdam.
Not currently 2,300 feet sponking 7,000, and I'd like to stay with you for fight-in-for-face and service up to the 100, please, number 7, double share.
277, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double
share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotterdam, double share of Rotter
You know, the best account of people's feelings across the world.
Well, you listen to news reports and they go around the world and they speak to other European citizens and, of course, the Irish.
You know, they do a very fair and balanced view.
So you really don't know which way it's going to flow.
You know, you've got, you know, both start off with someone who's against and they've got a someone who's full and then against and then for.
And so you're really, you know, you really can't tell what's going on or what the sentiment is.
But it's going to be very interesting to think completely new, free Europe.
And the discussion is out there.
The discussion that we've been having.
People saying, hey, you know, this is, uh, this is all fine at Dandy.
But, uh, we didn't get to vote on it.
How come, uh, I just kind of got railroaded through.
So, you know, my stand point on that.
By the way, right now, we're doing about 150 knots to air speed.
A little bit of, uh, a little bit of wind to the, uh, crosswind and headwind.
So, I've got 142 knots ground speed.
And, uh, for those of you who are playing a lot of people with, if you, uh,
find Manston and you, uh, trace to the dawn of Manston.
Uh, you'll see a wind farm, uh, which is pretty funny because, uh,
I thought of it as wind farm many, many times.
And quite often, uh, they're not turning it off.
So, I'll give you a direct eye in the sky report.
One thing for sure, there's enough wind for those things to be turned in,
some form of electricity that I'm confident of.
All right, come up on the wind farm.
Okay, so I'm just going to count how many,
how many wind bills I see here in the water, which, of course, is, you know,
heavily debated topic about putting,
many more wind bills in the water to generate power around, uh,
the entire British aisle.
I want two, three, four, five, six, uh,
this is about 12, 24, 24, 25, 35 wind bills here.
And I'm going to tell you how many are actually turning.
Uh, I see one, two, three, four, five, six.
There's one that's not turning.
There's one that seems to be broken.
Uh, that's pretty interesting.
Looks like a blade is ripped off without one.
Now, actually, they all seem to be turning,
and that also shows me kind of where the wind is coming from.
I have what we call a, uh,
ordering tailwind, which will blow me a little bit off track.
If I don't adjust, I do have the autopilot on,
but it's not slaved to my GPS,
so I do have to adjust a couple things manually,
but still it's better to find complete manual.
And, uh, let me just see where we are in respect to Manson.
I think I have another, uh, couple more miles to go.
Uh, about to eight more miles until, uh,
you've been Manson that I don't know where I am.
Yeah, all of them, they'll see me working,
except for one that's clearly busted.
Now, two, two roof busted.
Not turning, and actually looked busted.
That can't be cheap.
It is beautiful though, and I'll have to say,
the, uh, and a little bit of vomiting.
Just, uh, coming out of the lamp,
and now that I'm overseeing, boy,
it makes all the difference in the world.
And, uh, it's loud to know broken about me.
I couldn't, uh, I could go up to, uh,
you know, 5,500 feet if I wanted to,
but again, I'm pretty sure with, uh,
he would do nothing.
Yeah, for the speed, you would just slow me down.
Number 277.
I'll just share an order for me.
No, let me have no share.
I'll run you to an LL by entering.
About her next, no number 7.
I'll share.
Okay, so that means that, uh,
we've got about, uh, it's not even that long now,
about 7 minutes until we hit the, uh,
the boundary, which is literally a boundary
and a line drawn on a map.
Uh, uh, that's where, uh,
the United Kingdom flows into either, uh,
uh, Belgian water and airspace.
Uh, or in this case, Dutch airspace.
Uh, and then I'll be, uh,
handed over to, uh, Amsterdam information
before we, uh, inland,
and then eventually, uh, talk to water dam.
So, uh, a lot of crap going on in the UK, uh,
uh, and it comes and up with Europe about the, uh,
about the place of fuel.
There's, uh, a very important day coming up in, uh,
just a, uh, just a couple weeks,
which is, uh, as of July 1st, across Europe.
And this is, uh, I think pretty much,
happening in every single country.
It seems like it was almost a European director.
I'm not too sure of that.
But certainly some form of agreements were made
where, uh, the, uh, tax on diesel is going to be raised by 3%
that's what the, uh, truck drivers in the UK were, uh,
protesting about and there are people,
protesters, uh, protests, uh, right now in Spain,
truckers are, uh, blocking, uh,
supply is getting into supermarkets.
Uh, there was a minor protest in the Netherlands
this morning with another one planned for next week.
And, uh, this is the big, you know,
this is the big topic of conversation.
And, uh, the European Commission, uh,
released a statement today, which I, uh,
printed out abroad with me.
Uh, of course regarding this, uh,
the situation where people just really can't afford
the fuel anymore, and they, you know,
they're all, and everyone's pretty much free
down about, uh, having to, uh, pay even more
with a 3% rise, uh, on the horizon.
So, uh, this is what the protests are about, you know,
not that people can necessarily, you know,
that the place can be brought down, uh,
well, of course, could be brought down by the old companies,
but, and I've got to just 3% rise by the way,
turns out, in most countries,
was, uh, installed and agreed upon,
as a carbon emission tax.
But, um, now, and I think that's probably wrong these days
because the diesel engines are much, much cleaner.
But anyway, here's the, um,
here's the big deal that came out today,
which was on the, uh, uh,
European, actually, it's one of the headlines
that, uh, you wrote that.edu,
if you take a look at it.
But this is from the European Commission,
it was not elected body by the way,
but they hold a lot of weight.
Uh, the European Commission agrees that
member states, and provide targeted support
when justified to those households
experiencing the most serious impact
of the cost of fuel, while ensuring
measures taken to alleviate the immediate impact
of vital oil prices, our temporary non-destroying,
which is, of course, a tricky little word there,
and do not inhibit longer term adjustment to higher prices.
So, they're taking it seriously,
and that's good news, but now all the individual
member states have to actually do something about it
and get to it.
And right now, I'd like to play something for you
from the pod tape using that work.
I found this, which is pretty appropriate for you today.
It's really proven here's gas money on the Charlie
in the air, on the air.
Everywhere.
I need some gas money.
We'll take some, need you know that
that ain't funny.
We'll like nothing better than to give you a ride
on a year.
But first I'm gonna give me some gas money.
I'll play over Texas.
Me and my van.
From the red river.
To the real red.
Gas prices so high.
I don't know who to think.
But I get to my next gig and may after I'm nearby.
Because I need some gas money.
We'll take some, need you know that ain't funny.
We'll like nothing better than to give you a ride
on a year.
But first I'm gonna give me some gas money.
Maybe someday.
As I want to find a way.
To make the wheels roll without having a bay.
As I'm a rap chic.
They don't really dig our sea.
But till then you spare some change for some gas money.
Because I need some gas money.
We'll take some, need you know that ain't funny.
We'll like nothing better than to give you a ride
on a year.
But first I'm gonna give me some gas money.
Well I ran out of gas.
I was walking down the road.
This truck driving out came by.
Here in I have it low.
She was a big old guy.
But she looked me over.
She said you look pretty good to me.
But it's as gas or grass.
Nobody rides for free.
And I mean nobody.
It goes on.
Need some gas money.
We'll take some, need you know that.
We'll like nothing better than to give you a ride
on a year.
But first I'm gonna give me some gas money.
We'll like nothing better than to give you a ride on a year.
We'll first I'm gonna give me some gas money.
And now my favorite moment of the flight.
I would like to climb to 3,400 feet.
I'll never have no idea.
I'll just call me on a selection report.
I'll reach you next number.
One of my favorite moments of the flight over the channel.
It's nice and calm like this.
It's a have a nice little pre-rolled tobacco here.
I believe me.
It's only tobacco.
It's one of my vices.
I've got two asteroids on board here.
So what can I tell you?
I'd love to make use of them.
You know, every once in a while.
Just get that urge.
It's kind of cool.
The reason I asked to climb up to 3,400 feet is because I see a cloud layer of head.
It looks to be broken, but it was pretty much exactly my altitude.
So I'll just climb up above it and see if we can stay above it for a while.
Until we have to start to descend down into as we get ready to coast in into the Netherlands.
That, by the way, was a really broken gas money from the cloud safe music network.
I have a couple of minutes here just to tell you briefly about a brand new sponsored action.
It's sponsored.
This is an awesome device that I want you to take a look at.
It's called the Durobo.
If you've never heard of this thing, the Durobo.
If you'd deal with big files on a DuroboStore.com, then you'll really understand what this thing is about.
It's essentially an external hard drive.
It never runs out of space.
It's completely hot, stopable.
You can pull drives out, push drives in.
It's like a bay.
It's like a drive bay.
And you can just keep expanding this thing with terabytes and terabytes and data.
It grows as you grow.
You can put almost any standard ATA.
I think of any standard ATA based drive right into it.
And it just works.
Now we've got a special deal.
I've already worked with this.
It goes into this.
Now if you deal with the files like I do, the audio files or video files or 80 photo shop files,
you know what this thing.
Don't think my work for it.
Just go work at DuroboStore.com.
If you think it's up for you, you want to buy it.
But now until June 30, you can get $50 off of DuroboStore.
It's unit bundled with a Western Digital Green Power 1 terabyte hard drive.
For a 2 terabyte hard drive or a 4 terabyte hard drive.
And across about 500 bucks, go check it out.
DuroboStore.com.
It is definitely something you'll enjoy.
Now if you please excuse me, I'm going to get the hand off between Manson and Amsterdam information.
And we just climbed up to my intended altitude of 3,400 feet before I call it.
And so I'll do it all on one go right now.
It's 3,200 feet.
We're climbing at 500 feet.
For a minute.
You can hear that please get a little bit quieter in the cockpit.
I can actually put a little thinner oxygen up here.
And add a little bit of manifold pressure, which basically means more and more fuel on the fire.
Love that.
And here we go.
And number 7 Delta Share is at 3,400 feet.
And that's the boundary.
You don't find no change frequency to Amsterdam information.
3,6 decimal 6,5.
And down to here in Roger.
Now now I'm going to try to catch my 10 feet on Amsterdam.
I have a little trick.
I thank you for the service.
Number 7 Delta Share.
Here we go.
Okay.
Another advantage of the height here that I just put in is.
I'm going to get better range of the radio because I'm going to quit.
Don't quit away.
Let me see 42 minutes from a destination or water dam.
There you go.
I don't know.
I don't know what the wattage of these transmitters.
But it's, you know, it's something like.
Gosh.
15 watts, maybe.
I've got the beacon now.
The hotel share.
Delta beacon.
I'm right on track.
So that's all good.
Let's give Amsterdam a call.
Amsterdam information.
Number 277 Delta Share.
Flight Information Service.
Who to meet up?
Charlie 182 VFR from Farrow to Rotterdam.
Just across the FIR boundary.
And we'll be routing in via hotel share.
Delta 7000, the box.
3,400 feet with even flight information service.
Number 277 Delta Share.
Please pass your message again.
Did not read?
Number 279 Delta Share.
And IDoting.
It's just walks up a thousand.
Just trying to find me now on the radar.
Here.
I'm sorry, I'm reading YouTube, can you read me?
Yes, it is, it's reading 3300 feet per trail, but two now.
Oh my god, you're getting all the easier, you're a 90, that's a moment.
Currently reading 3400 feet at 1017.
That's correct.
Ready for a Q9, just a little bit of off the screen.
1013, number seven, self-chair.
Well, that doesn't happen very often.
I guess Rado wasn't reading the end then.
I really had the tune into a voice.
Now, I said I was reading here too.
That could mean that in my radio is breaking up, which it wasn't, but just your voice.
I really had the tune into it for a second there.
Anyway.
Okay, so we are now officially in, yep, we're officially now in Dutch Airspace, cruise no long,
and everything's all set.
I was going to talk to you just briefly about the codex elementarious.
You should take a look at this.
I put a video on Korea.com.
I didn't get a lot of response about it.
The codex is something you need to look at because it's something we're going to be dealing with in Europe.
It probably will be harmonized into more by December 2009, and then now talking about making this law in the United States.
And if you haven't heard about it, it's basically the law, or it's set up by the World Trade Organization
of all people who would should be responsible for your health.
And then going to determine what can be in your hood and what kind of food you can eat and under which conditions are which circumstances.
This is, I'm unusual already in the United Kingdom.
We've heard complaints of people who can't buy certain vitamins and supplements,
and only a pack of stuff may become outlawed.
And what I understand, and this is the thing I want to think about and research and look into,
is they may actually start orientating a water again in certain places in the world.
And that is, you know, that's just not what I'm not really too comfortable with.
Hey, you know what, there's some, I'm going to get a little busy here to take them about to fly into some clouds
and not quite sure how far the cloud cover is.
So why just follow along with me as, as we, let me see.
These are, I know, cumulus clouds just a little bit.
Nothing too severe though, but I'll do it a little bit to the left of it.
And I do see the tops of the clouds and I can't see the ground, which is part of the visual flying rules.
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to take you in all the way into Rotterdam.
And just before we hit Rotterdam, we know I've had a ton of landing.
I got one more sock to play for you.
And, you know, tomorrow, I'll be flying back and I'll be collecting somewhere near the end of the day.
I'll bring you a football party because that is definitely definitely in the cards.
So, uh, hang back, sit tight, fly with me for a little bit.
But, uh, see how we do, uh, with the weather at the conditions here.
If I want to stay above the clouds, which seems to be reasonably okay right now, or if I want to drop down below.
So, hold on.
No, let's check the BBC World Service while we're at it, shall we add?
I'm going to let them down.
We don't get off to go.
I remember seven don't share a go.
Yeah, what do you do to hide three don't?
Three don't have six under this seat.
Uh, yeah, that's correct.
I'm just going over the top of some clouds here.
Is that okay for you?
No problem.
Thank you.
Yeah, she's worried about shit.
I'm only, she'll go hide three.
Oh, then I'll hide.
Okay, hold on.
Let me try and, uh, the means to recycle the whole thing.
We'll try to get it.
Okay.
Okay, she sounds a pop.
Oh, it's good to be on radar.
Is that any better of an absurden ambient fall
than ever seven don't share?
I don't have a deal with her.
Uh, I want to even know what I did.
Okay, that's, uh, that's confirmed and are you receiving altitude?
I'm out of these with altitude, slow, cold green eyes.
No, I don't appreciate that radar.
Probably made in China that I don't know.
I don't mind being involved.
Okay, let me turn it off and then on again with the one more recycle.
Okay, that's that.
That's that.
We're here.
We have, uh, also here.
Oh, we don't appreciate that.
Shut up.
On the little side because they're all, but it's all the same.
I hope to see those.
Okay.
We'll remain at all.
And number seven don't share.
Prechates the other station there.
We're back with the, uh, squawk seven zero four seven.
Uh, I'm sending information.
Number seven don't share.
Make a second.
We have to be careful.
This is squawking seven thousand.
Uh, I've got one over here.
She walks through her next step there.
Three, four.
Thank you.
I'm Dr. Medell, but you're looking now.
Uh, I'm least keeping your, uh,
uh, identification.
And the fault, but it's only long.
Very cool.
Okay. Well, I'll have to have that.
Take a look at them.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay for you, uh, for the information you have at the moment?
On the time.
On the, uh, you, you're on the church, uh,
We're meeting you.
On.
Uh, yes, correct.
It is currently 3,600 feet.
Actually, we'd like to descend down to 2,000 feet at this moment.
So you want to follow along.
Number seven don't be sharing.
Okay, down the channel.
I don't understand who problem.
Uh, so the reason why I'm descending now is because, uh,
There's some nice clouds here that, uh,
have been keeping us in a formation.
Uh, which, uh, they're not high enough to be worried about it,
but they could be a little bumpy,
and they could be filled with some crap.
So we're just gonna descend.
Lots of beautiful going to these clouds.
Absolutely fantastic.
I don't understand what she's not seeing now.
Okay.
So we're gonna be on runway zero six.
Information fox truck.
The wind is, uh, cross wind from the left a little bit.
Uh, about zero, three zero degrees.
So should be, uh, just fine.
And we've got about 12 minutes until we, uh,
We've got about 12 minutes until we, uh,
We land, uh, this is just, uh,
basically, uh, some kind of strong system that we're flying underneath right now.
It's a thousand feet.
Yeah, it looks like it's gonna end just before we hit the shore,
which is nice.
And then we have four thousand feet cloud days.
So it's all good.
Actually, only about five, well,
a little choppy here, only about five minutes later.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Come on, baby.
Keep it together now.
Yeah.
No one's been doing that.
Number seven Delta Sheriff at Hotel.
From a seven Delta Sheriff, virtually,
for the wiki.
Whiskey next to number seven Delta Sheriff.
Right there.
Number seven Delta Sheriff Whiskey.
From a seven Delta Sheriff, we've got one thing called.
Take a next, number seven Delta Sheriff.
Okay, get ready close.
And you can definitely feel the wind here.
It should be exciting.
Number seven Delta Sheriff, take a note.
Number seven Delta, join the left and share the knowledge in a section to a thousand.
Take number two.
Send me one thousand feet number two for zero six, left and number seven Delta Sheriff.
Okay, fellows, here we go.
Come on, come on.
Okay, up a beautiful exercise again.
It's up a beautiful and equally important wiki.
One thousand five hundred feet for landing.
A beautiful exercise, we're sure.
Hold on, I will show you the six same formations.
Hold on.
I will.
Here we go.
Number seven Delta Sheriff, down with zero six.
Number seven Delta Sheriff, number one.
Number seven Delta Sheriff.
We got three greens.
Uh huh.
We got some pretty strong winds up the two states of floods today.
I don't think I'm going to be able to do it.
I don't think I'm going to do it.
OK.
This is definitely going to be a pretty exciting.
OK, I went down.
OK, I'm landed now.
OK, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
OK, let's do it.
Let's do it.
I don't think I'm going to do it.
All right.
That was kind of interesting.
A little bit of bounce there at the end.
That was quite a bit of wind.
They catered big to two.
I don't remember seven notes here.
It's a mixture of lunch and a...
Richard, why don't you take a two-key to get center here?
Okay, don't you remember seven notes here?
Wow, that was a massive, massive gust of wind I got there.
At the very end, wow, that was probably one of the sloppiest landings I've ever done.
It's undecflained exactly what happened, but I got a huge gust of wind just as I was touching down.
You know, from here, it's over over here, there's six clear to land.
23, 0, 1, 3, 2, 0.
Yeah, there you go, go, go, go, go.
So I got a huge gust of wind at, you know, about 25 miles an hour.
Just pop me back up, so it's really struggling there.
I get it down, you may put the engine rev up a little bit,
as I adjusted the speed.
Good landing.
That was certainly...
...somewhat exciting.
So, any landing you can walk away from is considered a good landing.
We'll say that was a great one.
And with that, I'm going to wind up this edition of the daily course.
Great.
Number 768.
It's an important thing though.
Leaving you with Tom Smith and something I thought was better profile for today's show.
I want my flying car.
And you know what?
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow on this for one Friday.
As long as it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
And guys live life with pleasure.
And gals too.
I want my flying car.
I want this to be attached to hell out of my garage.
It's my station wagon to a star.
I want my flying car.
They told us we have robots and portable fusion.
So our bodies so we wouldn't stay dead.
But I have to doubt because it didn't come out.
The way Mr. Asam off said.
My coffee bruises self every morning.
My shower seems itself every night.
But twice a day I'm caught in a traffic knot.
I'm growing older at every red light.
I want my flying car.
You know it just ain't fair.
I want to hit the air.
I want my flying car.
If I'm making a mistake, I can use my air break or grab a phone line with a spar.
No more waiting and hate in the church tail.
Gating when I'm levitate and over the town.
Parking fees wouldn't matter.
I drive a road ladder or a side climb right down.
No barrels of cones or construction.
The zones no blessing radios in the next lane.
I'd put on a stethon and make my church kitchen.
If I've got a flying car, I can get a girl like James.
James, stop this crazy thing.
A thousand miles of the gallon.
It never rides fucking your loud.
When the weather gets nasty, I make a real fasty,
positive climb through the clouds.
I never worry about signs of signals.
Those who's gonna take me to jail.
We've what's that sign?
Any someone else flying?
I got pigs on the wing on my tail.
Up in my flying car.
I want my flying car.
I stay on the ground when you can drive around.
In a Chevrolet shooting star.
I want my flying car.
Will I don't care how cos I'm ready now?
The future can't be that far.
I want my flying car.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.
I want my flying car.