Delta Sierra Charlie, a 0-4.
$16 million worth of airplane straps by us.
To the next generation radio contenting my ears.
We don't need enough digging trees.
I like to think I'm signed with you this year.
I guess it is a foodie.
That's right, everybody coming to you from the Big Apple.
New York, New York, it's a daily source code.
I'm Monday, November 10, 2008.
I'm going to roll it.
With a hotel room.
I'll take it off.
I'll run this money on the left and the right.
I'll just need you to try and sign my name.
Yeah.
Tell me I'm ready until the same old sign.
Tell me I'm talking, tell me tell me,
The way the weather went down.
All the time, we said, let me tell you my name
And now it's time to fuck it
And get the squad and come out
They take the money, they're the same
Everybody's ready to turn away
The money, they take the money, they're the same
All we do, we want to take the money
From the way to the play
They take the money, we'll see
They take the voluntarily, somebody
They take the money, we see
They take the money, people are the same
All we do, we want to take the money, they're the same
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah you love me. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah you love me, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah
Change the world is in the same
Now we will be able to change the way
The world changes the world is in the same
Now we will be able to change the world
Now we will be able to change
Yeah, Tommy Keith and the boys
Cinderella
The more things change the more they stay the same
Kicking off daddy source code episode
No. 804, coming to you from a hotel room in New York City
Traveling with my friends
I've got the the true mobile set of
We haven't done this in a long time.
A show from a hotel room.
It's been, man, I'm trying to think now.
This may actually be months and months and months.
And this has happened.
Well, here I am back in the United States.
I might want to add to that.
It's been very easy for me to get into the country recently.
I'm off the list, which is nice, not quite sure what happened,
but apparently talking shit about it for months
on end has some kind of result.
And apparently, you actually can get off the list,
not the no-fly list.
This is the customs and border protection agency list.
So we're here for a week of sales, not my favorite
or a way to occupy my time, but this is actually
it is a perfect time to be in New York to do this
just before Thanksgiving is a lot of activity.
And we got a lot of good stuff to sell.
We got a lot of awesome shows on our network.
If you haven't seen the new moveyupmiveo.com,
there's a lot of changes.
We've got our four networks, men,
media, women, media, tech, media, music.
I've been doing some of the home page channel stuff.
It's been a lot of fun.
And advertisers responding very positively do it.
It looks like there is money flowing out
of traditional media into our world, which is good,
because we need some of that.
Thanks.
I gotta tell you, just listen to that song, Cinderella.
And man, I think I have one of their,
I think somewhere, back at the manner,
I have a Cinderella, either a gold or a platinum disc on the wall.
I mean, we used to hang out a little bit back in the day.
I wonder what happened to Cinderella?
They still around, or they still performing.
Someone sent me an email that's living color,
which I played the other day.
And I'll also talk about, I know, a gender.
They're still out gigging around, gigging in Germany right now.
So they're nice to know that those guys are doing OK.
But that was going on with Cinderella.
And when I listened to that song, I'm thinking, oh, man.
Yes.
And it's really great.
And on the other hand, it's really difficult for me,
because everything is so crystal clear right now at the moment to me.
It is, you know, particularly when it comes to what's going on
in the financial world, which hits all of us one way or the other,
it just seems so obvious.
And we've got this big summit coming up on the 15th,
which really would be no more than a photo op as far as I'm concerned.
Just taking out the, you've probably heard about this Bretton Woods
to this, of course, as Bretton Woods refers back to the 70s
when they created this, the current global financial system,
although it wasn't really advertised as global.
And now that's completely where it's going.
I'm just going to read off a couple of links, of course,
just about everything once again, sourced from the wonderful source
code drop.au slash daily source code.
I read this page, this website, many, many times a day.
It is truly where I get the news that I'm interested in.
And sometimes, you know, there's like a naked picture of an
internet or at least a Photoshop, you know, then that, that helps, too.
This is all good stuff.
So this came out today, this is from Reuters,
and just listened to the language that is being used.
In his annual speech at the Lord Mayor's banquet, Gordon Brown,
the unelected Prime Minister of the United Kingdom,
I just want to point that out that the, the good people of the United
Kingdom would not elect their prime minister, their so-called leader.
They, that happens within the party, which is very typical and very
different, of course, from the United States, where we think we have
a choice between parties, but really, which is voting for the better
actor, you know my stance on that.
Anyway, Ron, who is spearheaded calls for reform of international
financial institutions, we'll say, as he did today, that
Brittany, United States and Europe are key to forging here.
It comes a new world order.
Yeah.
Finally, finally, they've done it.
And it all is starting to click in my head.
It's like fireworks.
The synapses are firing.
Remember, we were talking about the Lisbon Treaty.
And this also, you can find on the source code drop, I'll see if I
put a link in the show now in today's source code.com, crossposts that
at curie.com, the latest communication from the European Union.
So let's just go back to the Lisbon Treaty.
The Lisbon Treaty was supposed to be the actual constitution of the
United States of Europe, been talking about this for over a year.
You know, remember the actual constitution, the constitutional document was
voted down by the French and by the Dutch in national referenda.
That's the plural of referenda or referendums.
Well, more than one referendum, each country, they had referendums in
their country and they could vote.
And they both said, no, thank you.
We're not interested in in this.
We don't think we needed, of course, the EU started as the European Commonwealth
as a, basically, a trade union.
Then we kind of got duped into this idea of, hey, you know, let's all have the same
money.
Yeah, that's a pretty good idea.
Since I can go to Germany or France or Spain or any place in Europe, and
I can use the same money.
That makes a lot of sense.
That makes things easier.
But then they started coming out with all this stuff.
And they wanted laws and possibly an army and, you know, taxation and
all this complicated stuff and no one liked it.
They just didn't like it.
Whether we understood it or not, we didn't like it.
And of course, the representative governments true to form said, OK,
then we'll just create a new document.
We'll take out all the constitutional stuff.
So it doesn't actually mean you have to have a referendum on it.
And we'll ram that through.
And there was one country out of the member states of the European Union,
who did have a referendum based on their local constitution,
that being Ireland, God bless the Irish.
They took one look at this document, which we've discussed many, many times
on the daily source code, right down to the basic fundamentals of human
rights, where there's all kinds of funky shit going on in there,
where they can take your children away.
And the death penalty is OK, as long as you're trying to run away from law
enforcement, then a kill would be considered legal and clean.
Not just some of that minor stuff like that.
Though, and of course, you can always be incarcerated if you're an alcoholic,
a drug addict, a vagrant or mentally insane.
Well, I think I hit just about every single one of those boxes,
except for the alcohol bit.
And they needed to have this done by October.
What was so significant about October?
Well, it all starts to come together.
When you see what's happening now, of course, with our global financial crisis,
they clearly knew this was coming.
By the way, not just the leaders knew this was coming.
We all knew this was coming.
I've been saying this for months.
And now when you read the latest communication from the European Commission,
an unalected commission, kind of the Starfleet Command,
as I like to call it, their October, think 28th or 29th,
the community, they say we will act according to the Lisbon principles.
Well, it's not interesting.
The Lisbon principles, basically the way I read that is,
we're just going to go ahead and hold ourselves to everything we set up
in the Lisbon Treaty.
This thing was unreadable, except for the actual bits that I took,
you know, weeks to figure out to understand and all these different documents
that are referenced all over the place and protocols.
And all kinds of crap, basically, hiding what the true intent is.
I presume that this all comes down to this new world order,
this new financial order that Tessar Kozzi and Merkel and Brown,
and, of course, the United States and everyone's getting together.
And the banks essentially are going to control the way things roll.
And as you know, once you control the money, you don't actually need to be in charge of the law.
And a couple other things started to click for me.
This was a news report from, actually, this one is from Fox News,
but I've seen it on many other news sites,
some somewhat more credible.
This is actually from 2005.
Now, AIG is in the news.
This is the insurance group, American International Group,
who we bailed out the United States citizens for 80 plus 80 thing,
85 billion dollars, and for that we receive something in exchange,
80% of something not quite sure what.
But now, looking back to 2005, I didn't know about this.
Someone pointed this out to me.
I'll just read this from the news story.
billionaire investor Warren Buffett was questioned by regulators Monday,
in connection with federal and state probes into the insurance company, AIG,
saying afterwards, I told them everything I know.
And if you read through this article, it seems like there was,
and this also involves, Ellie, it's Spitzer, who was doing,
who was conducting the investigation, who, of course, completely got boneed,
when they set them up with the hooker scams.
And which, of course, is really stupid.
I mean, if you're going to be going around shouting in everybody,
you'd at least better be pretty clean or com-clean about the things that you're doing.
But basically, Berkshire Hathaway, which is, which is, sorry, just lost my page here,
which is Buffett's insurance, so, or his investment vehicle,
they're really big into reinsurance, mainly through general recorp.
And I don't want to get into the technical details of it,
but this has been, there's been all kinds of shit going on between
the regulators between Warren Buffett and AIG.
And now just think back to a couple of weeks ago, when Warren Buffett,
all of a sudden, put $5 billion into Goldman Sachs, Goldman Sachs,
of course, just, just connecting all the dots for a Goldman Sachs, of course,
Hank Paulson, the current secretary of the Treasury, was the CEO at,
at Goldman Sachs, do you think that there's, like, a payoff going on here,
and the things had to be settled out, or someone had to be made whole in the end,
that's exactly what it feels like to me. And, you know, as I said, I'm seeing more and more of this stuff,
more and more of this stuff that is just, it's all coming to a head right now, as we speak.
Everything is starting to click together.
Now, something really weird that I have not seen in mainstream news at all.
And actually, you put this on the drop the other day. There were two stories.
One was from CNN, where CNN said that the U.S. Treasury was now making bonds available.
So, U.S. Treasury bonds starting, I guess, today, selling $550 billion worth of bonds,
trying to raise money, obviously, because, well, look, you know, we've been shelling out
trillion, so we got to go get some, we got to go borrow it, otherwise we have to print it.
But what's interesting is that the BBC reported on the same story, only they didn't have
550 billion, they said 55 billion, which also these days, you know, by the standards we run with,
it seems almost an insignificant amount. So, I'm a little confused about what it really is,
and why that's not being reported on at all. In the meantime, Bloomberg, the news agency
has filed a lawsuit against, I guess, the Treasury, I'm bringing up the story right now,
for some reason, the bandwidth here sucks is really slow. For some reason, it's a hotel for
crisis, what do you expect? Everyone download and pour in the middle of the night.
Because, yeah, we have the 700 billion that was approved and went through the Senate and through
Congress. What is it? Why is it all sudden? I hope my microphone batteries aren't
emptying out here. Sounds a little crummy, I'm sorry, just have to live with it, I'll see if I can
fix it later this week. Here we go, the Federal Reserve is refusing to identify
the recipients of almost $2 trillion of emergency loans from American taxpayers,
or information about the trouble assets that the Federal Reserve Bank accepted as collateral.
So, the 700 billion we all knew about, big to do, big who, you know, we all know how that went down,
and of course they'll tell us something about what they did there, but that the Federal Reserve
is saying, I'm sorry, we're not going to give you this information. It's none of your business,
you cannot file a freedom of information act to request against us. That $2 trillion, we don't have
to tell you. And it just blows my mind that this is going on. Blows my mind, it's our money
and they're just taking it and giving it away to their buddies, and I'm seeing all of this unfold,
and I'm seeing, now we had, was it China just put it, and it seemed like every single
massive continent or country is kind of at the half trillion to a trillion dollar mark in their
stimulus packages, Germany is done at China's done at the United States is done at, you know,
kingdom is done, and still not going to be enough. All of our money is systematically being taken away
from us and given to these banksters and they're not passing it on down the line.
So that means, of course, that somehow there's going to have to be more money pumped into the economy,
that'll come in the form of stimulus packages. We're going bankrupt. We're going bankrupt,
and the banks are controlling this, and the timelines make sense the way it's all coming together
now this week. Again, in my mind, it's just a photo op. This has all been completely set up in
advance. They knew about it and God knows and God help us what's coming.
Hey, Adam, how you doing? I'm not this. It has number 146. All right. Start right away.
Oh, y'all, I think I'm going to like today's hit test.
That is, of course, the incomparable banana ramma with Robert De Niro's calling.
Talking Italian.
Number two.
Okay.
It's good to be that mid-lear, but I think it's the Rolling Stones version of Beast of
Bird and I, y'all, good songs.
And number three.
Billy Idol, I was about to face, oh, will he get six out of six today?
I think so.
Let's hear the answers.
On hit test 146.
And that's it in its time for the answers.
And this week they're all from 1984.
The Rolling Test.
And this is answer number one.
This is banana ramma, Robert De Niro's rating.
Do I say calling?
Right.
I'm not waiting.
Robert De Niro's rating, banana ramma answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
That mid-lear, right?
It's the burden.
That way, that now.
I'll never be your beast.
Bird and I, y'all, all this to you, to me.
Go to me.
Bird and I, y'all, to me, I'll never be your beast.
Bird and I, y'all, to me, that mid-lear.
As answering number two.
On, this is answer number three.
This is Billy Idol.
One more Pat, Grey.
One moreкус, Rig Frouper.
I have a lot of days,
And so number three Billy Idol and I's without a face and that concludes hit this number
one four six
So Adam yeah, how did you do this? I'm looking at the judges and I think I'll let me slide on a couple of
imperfections here. I'm just gonna say I got six out of six. I got names, titles, everything
all right this time yeah. I'm ready thanks for playing Adam. Thank you. By the way this
hit this is made and created using a new version of soundbites. Oh, it's a three duck
seven and it has the new features implemented that were put in the better version I was using.
So check it out. All right. If you want to buy these tracks so you can hear more of them
please go to hit this.meepio.com because the iTunes links are there placed for your convenience.
Yes, or you can be all right. Next week I hope to be that for not to hit this so until then take care
Have fun and remember try to think with your heart. Bye bye. Bye back to test that she
mail.com info.
Oh, man, just hearing all that being in New York makes me think of so many good times
particularly those songs Billy Idol, man. That was big when
just about the time when I was over here
kicking at MTV
and to be
in New York and then here a day Fox there that fantastic voice who does the ending of the
of the of the hit test imaging
but all day working at Z100 in New York hopefully able to hook up with him this week because I'm going to be here all week
leave Friday night. I'm going to see if I can miss you my good buddy Steve leads over it to
serious. So actually serious XM these days
wonder how that's going over there, man. Those guys are losing like a billion dollars a year.
Literally. I mean, look it up. A billion dollars combined
serious net XM and their stock prices like a 20 cents completely destroyed by the FCC or whoever
in the government was responsible for slowing down that merger.
And I got to check out the new version of Soundbike.
You know, I I used live able to live for the most of the production of the of the daily source code
but I do use soundbite as kind of like a cart rack and I got to go check out what those new features are.
I do recall that popping up saying, hey, yeah, there's new version available.
Do you want to get that? And I think at the time it's like new too busy. Not going to I like it when they ask
a speaking of updates, by the way, the the Google G1 Google phone that I have, which I brought with
me to the States, seeing as it has my U.S. SIM card embedded. And so I can make and receive
cheaper phone calls here. Of course, this thing runs out of battery and about two and a half hours now.
Something that is very cool about the phone twice now. I've received an update
where you you turn on the phone and it's say, hey, there's an update available and you say,
yeah, I'll take it now and then it literally downloads the update right there on the phone,
which is what I guess most people would wish their iPhone did. You don't have to be tethered. It's
pretty cool. Still quite useless as a phone. Really messed up news from the lowlands. This really
cuts down to the core of who I am and and and and my roots and where I come from. A lot of articles
coming out now that by 2010, the current ruling Christian Democrats have said, you know what,
it's over and done with. We got to get rid of all these coffee shops in the Netherlands.
Now, if you don't know what a coffee shop is in Holland, at least it's not where you go to buy coffee.
It is where you go to buy weed and it's kind of a weird situation because although it's legal to buy
and legal to smoke, it's illegal to supply to the coffee shops. But of course, that's that's
it's just being allowed. There must be, what's the word? I know the word in Dutch. I don't
know the word in English. It just remember that. It's a dog which means basically they kind of
look the other way. And as far as I know the policy's been pretty good, you know, it's to work
out well for decades. But now they're saying stop, not going to happen. The thing that really
interests me is that in the current coalition in the Netherlands, the Labor Party is also rules
with the Christian Democrats. And the guy that I know for almost 10 remons who is the Secretary of
State for Economic Affairs, or is it European affairs? I think it's economic affairs.
He's come out and said, hey, you know, I don't think that's such a good idea. We go,
you shut up, you a Christian Democrats. And he has told me this personally before,
by the way, France Timberlons, he's a builder-berg group member, total member of the New World Order,
Illuminati, nice guy, just because he's involved with all that doesn't mean that his personality
at the surface, at least is a nice. And he said a couple things to me in passing,
which, particularly when I was doing the Dutch radio show at Arrow Classic Rock, I had him on,
how do I actually have him in the studio? I remember him saying, you guys are doing some really
important stuff here. I think that this is one of those guys who he's wrapped up in it all.
He doesn't see a way out, but he does actually know that what is happening is wrong.
Or maybe he's just thinking, hey, this is a big part of our economy. We don't want to blow that up.
I don't know, one way or the other, but it's sad that this noise is now taking place. We've been
hearing these rumblings for many, many years and it looks like it actually might happen.
It is a fact now that you cannot sell your coffee shop. If you sell it, it can no longer be a coffee shop.
There's only about 150 left in all of Holland. Most of them, I believe, probably in
and around Amsterdam. I'm keeping my eye on the situation, but I'm obviously quite sad about
what's taking place. Meanwhile, in the United Kingdom, this is a great story. I mentioned this
on Noah Gendo over the weekend talking to John Jackie Smith, the home secretary. She's in charge of
everything that goes on in home. In the UK, and she says, hey, you know, we're going to have national
ID cards for everybody, which is basically the precursor to the chip in your head, biometric data
on the ID cards by 2012. But, quote, I regularly have people coming up to me saying, they don't want
to wait that long. They can't wait. They love the idea of the ID card. They really, really love it.
What a lie. What a crock. They're really, really pushing this stuff. And in the meantime,
we have all this change taking place based upon our hope. And we have lots to look forward to as
the soul member of the office of the president elect. President elect Obama will be coming. And
right now, we've just got this big reality show taken place on television. We're all looking there
at the wrong things and all this shit is happening. Lickety split. They're going to, the banks are
basically going to run the world. That's the way I see it. We're all going to have ID cards. The
internet is being censored from Australia. Well, obviously China, but Australia is really taking place
now that United Kingdom, it's unstoppable. You know, why? Because we're sheep. And we're just
letting it happen. Just staying in the Netherlands for one moment. And also just staying with the
radio show. You know, one of the big problems that started off the demise of your wake-up call,
which was the show I was doing on the in the mornings for Holland. Only did it for like three and a
half months. Is when I got a reporter on who has been following the case of the Secretary
General, George Demink, the Secretary General of the Netherlands. That's just about the highest position
you can have in the Justice Department. He is pretty much the bomb digger. He's not the minister of
of the Justice System, but he's the Secretary General. These are the guys that really do most of the work.
A well-known and documented pedo-sexual, not a pedophile, although he's that as well, but he's a
pedo-sexual, meaning he has had and probably still has sex with children. Now, in this case,
15-year-old boys, it's well-documented, multiple television shows, have tried to
have tried to blow this case wide open. They keep getting shut down. This particular reporter, Mikha
cult, he actually is now operating from Thailand, because his life is in danger, because he keeps
on howling this guy. It's not just this guy. I just, and I'm bringing this up because A, this
was part of the demise of not just my show, but I believe now the whole station is in trouble,
the government is trying to take him down. But this just shows you how deep this shit goes.
There is such a huge pedophile network in the Netherlands, and it spreads. It spreads from the
Netherlands to, if you haven't never heard of the due true case, D U T R O U X, the X files. You can Google
all of this stuff. I'm not going to put links in the show notes. That's, believe me, it's two
dangers, just for even for me to be doing that, because it stirs up so much shit. These guys have
been locking down any complaint, any news article, anything that's come out about this case,
and many, many more. I personally believe that the Isle of Jersey is connected to it. Remember,
we don't hear about that anymore, of course. Remember, the bunker next to the orphanage, where they
found, was it bones and teeth of tens of, it may be 20, 30, 40 kids who had been sexually abused
and killed, and just left to rot. I'm pretty sure that Madeline McCain, I'm sorry, Madeline
McCain. That whole situation is part of this network. There's lots of testimony and to some
degree evidence that the former heads of the Fortess Bank were involved in these networks,
royalty, Belgian royalty, Dutch royalty, British royalty. It's a true network of degenerate crazy
freaks, and they're running the justice system. Man, I'm happy I'm New York,
while I'm talking about all this crap. So I put a link to a hive site, which does nothing for you,
if you unless you speak Dutch, but I just wanted to bring it to your attention. First of all,
we have a lot of listeners and the Netherlands tuning in. We have to continue to spread this
information to get it out far and wide, because once we crack this nut, I believe these networks
these crazy ass nut jobs actually will go all the way to the White House. Many, many, many
documentaries, articles, and I'm just going to leave it at this, but it just, it makes me so mad
when I see that these guys are getting away with horrible, horrible things, and they are the
justice system. They literally run it, and they can do whatever they want, and they are.
Makes me, you know, it just makes me, it makes me angry, makes me sad, at the same time,
I'm really happy that we have alternative, distribution, alternative media where we can get the word out.
And we can talk about the nut jobs who are going to run our lives, run our monies, run our
governments, and get away with literally murder. They all want to root of the world, nothing new there.
We will want to run our lives, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our mon
moving our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, oh my ком 축 structure and darkness have to begin the monies, and lost our own monies, run our monies, run our monies, run our monies, no monies,
Thank you so much for watching this video, don't forget to subscribe, like, comment, and share this video with your friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends,
friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends
friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends , friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends, friends
I had really such a shame those guys wasn't to curtain roll and never got their shit together
I'm trying to get one of the other albums, it's never worked up, they broke out
Tears of fears everybody wants to rule the world, ain't that the truth
Ain't that the truth
I just feel really bad you know, it's like
The radio station couldn't really help it, you know, they knew what I was going to do
I knew what I was going to do
And just maybe I took it a bit too far, but I just couldn't stand it
I just couldn't stand what was going on
And so now looks like the government is going to take down the entire station
So there you go
Let's get back into the markets
In this case not the true financial market, but this would be the carbon credit market
Which is crashing down
I love this, the whole idea of what I wrote, I think I had someone wrote it on the source code drop
That buying carbon credits to fight
Global warming or climate change or whatever you want to call it
It's kind of like being fat and paying skinny person
To help you slim down
You know, it's like it's just so you understand how these carbon credits work
If you have a factory
And you want to produce stuff
The CO2, remember that's the stuff that you exhale
But it also comes out of chimneys
It's a lot of other shit that comes out of chimneys, which is definitely not good
The CO2 in that so harmful in my opinion, but let's not get into that
You basically got to pay for it, which means that somewhere down the line in the future
Someone who sold that carbon credit will have to produce less
Less carbon, so it's really it's not solving anything
It's just moving the future further and you know, moving the problem further out into the future
You know, into like my daughter's era
Once you'll be grown up and then you'll have to deal with it
That's kind of what the idea is in my humble opinion
In July, one ton of CO2 would have cost 29 euros and 33 cents just the other day
It was down to 1825
Sudden collapse of carbon price mirrors the route in wider commodity markets, no kidding
So that market may just go away, it's crazy
Trading on carbon credits
Whole thing is BS
Total BS
Hey Adam, it's market snowball here
I've been listening to a lot of stuff you've been saying about this whole like carbon tax and carbon credits thing
And I just want to agree with you that it's bullshit
Oh good
You know, this whole idea that you're going to convince people to do something by finding them basically
Yeah, that's the idea
And it's not, now it's for factories and industry
But you know, we're already being conditioned to look at our own carbon footprint
And that's the future I see, that's what I see coming with the
The greening of the economy
Is it just lots of stuff you won't be able to do?
You want to do something you have to buy some carbon credits
Tax basically
Extras special taxes
Pay in more money to do stuff we've been doing forever
You know, I'm pretty sure I want to compare it to basically speeding tickets
And if I remember right, you had a lovely experience with that sort of thing
Actually, that was the lady Patricia who has a heavy, heavy foot on the accelerator
But I took the rap for twice, I took the rap, I got the points
I said, I take it, baby, don't worry about it, I'll take it for you
A while back, like I said, it was a while ago, so I'm not sure if I remember right now
Oh yeah, no, believe me, she's learned since then
This whole thing, well it's hard to see what 30 miles an hour is on my spedometer
I couldn't tell, yeah, of course she really was only going 32
And then she gets snapped the photograph
Nothing dangerous about what she was doing
Just the way to get money
As like a 65 pounds per shot, something like that
Exactly, but supposedly the idea, of course, behind getting tickets for committing
Moving violations while in your car is that this supposedly a deterrent
But it really isn't
Oh, it's a game
It's pretty much all these tickets do is basically give more money to the police departments
You know, if they need more money, they've got us where they can get out
And the hassling people who are going five miles over the speed, I'm sure
Anyway, just wanted to throw in my two cents about that
Great hair, hope you in, love you no homo
And of course, and they work for us
Yeah, they really should, but they don't, they work for the banks
They'll work for the banks right now
We're working for the banks
Oh boy, let's see, Chris from Nashville
You know, actually, I did want to say
But I'm going to stick to my guns on this stuff
Okay, I'm going to stick to my guns about
It's irrelevant, it's just not, it's not productive for us to have a conversation
about whether global warming or climate change exists
Or not, one thing is absolutely 100% clear to me
The entire world is based upon oil
Well, actually, based upon oil, golden drugs
Those are the true commodities, the true currencies that make the economies run
And everything comes from energy
We have to have energy
And can you just imagine
If there was a way
You could wave a magic wand or rub your hands together
Or snap your fingers and you could basically produce energy
Energy to, well, to provide you with transportation
Energy to heat your home
Energy to make stuff
Because, you know, really make and stuff
You need energy, you need either tremendous heat for steel
Or, you know, other forms of energy to manipulate
Other types of materials
Imagine if, if you didn't have to buy that
Imagine if you didn't have to come off of the grid
Or if had to come out of, you know, some global system
Where it comes out of the ground
And then is, is processed and is finally comes to you
And the form of gasoline or diesel
Or other forms of petroleum
Imagine if we have that
Imagine if there truly was
A form of energy that everyone had access to
First of all, if I knew about this
Unless you say maybe I knew about it a hundred years ago
Because Tesla probably invented it and it was suppressed
You would keep that shit quiet
You would keep people dumb as long as possible
Because the true power comes from harnessing
The energy
From having control over the energy
That's really where all the power comes from
So I am going to re-dedicate myself
It already started with the hydroxy booster
In the jag, which is still to this day is getting
Since I had that thing built into the car
Just yesterday before I left
It's only the third time I filled up the gas tank
The third time in what?
Four months now or something like that
It's outrageous how much gas this is saving me
Just by putting a little bit of science to work
And you can, people out there who said, oh, this is not possible
And you can't get more energy
And this is against the law of physics fine
All I know is I have empirical proof for myself
It works
I put less gas in my car
It's about to the averages 29%
Depends on where I'm driving, how I'm driving
Anywhere between 25 and 30%
Less gas goes into my car
Because of this basically
He's a plastic with water and electricity
From the battery that I have
Jacked under the hood
Thing works
And you can go ahead and look around online
And I actually put a link in the show notes about
Another crazy thing that's been happening down under
The Australians, I don't know
And they seem to be coming up with more and more cool shit
Where you put like
One volt in and ten volts comes out
Yeah, they say it's impossible
But they're doing it with magnets
And all kinds of crazy stuff
I'm really dedicated myself
Which means I'll have to go and visit more and more
These new age sciences
So we're discovering this stuff
And making it and actually coming up with results
And we have to get this stuff out to the people
If it's actually viable, if it works
And that's what I'm going to stick to
That's what I'm going to stay right on top of
Instead of because we know what
We'll solve my issues
And we'll solve your issues
If we don't have to burn fossil fuels
Then everybody should be happy
Right?
Because by the way, your government
Is not looking into the true alternatives
They don't seem to be clamoring all over people
Who are coming up without rages
Or seemingly outrageous claims
You don't see them
Yeah, actually you do
You see them going up to these inventors
And killing them
I'm a Christian Nashville again
First of all, it's a thank you for playing
The comment on 802
Oh man, I don't know
Thank you for contributing
You guys put the show together
I mean, all I do is spend a couple of hours
Pulling stuff off the drop
And then I got a show
And I agree
We shouldn't argue about a bigger
About all this stuff
I just wanted to also just add that
I agree with you as well
I mean, carbon credits, this whole scam
Or whatever
It's not the best way forward
Which I'm pretty sure is set up by Al Gore
By the way
I don't know if he's in all the carbon credit
Trading schemes
But I know he has a lot to do with it
The best way forward is to look
Different forms of energy
I agree with you
You know, this whole triangle hold
That they have on the oil industry
And so on
I think that's definitely the way forward
A great counter to the whole
Drill baby drill
Or whatever
I mean, how not lets invent something
It says drill
It's insane
Really
And you know, just wanted to throw that out there
Let's not argue about it
You know, we're obviously going to be working on it
Obviously disagree on it
So I just wanted to leave a follow up
To that comment
Still love the show
Love you a minute
And right here in Houghtyland
And we'll talk to you later
Thanks man
Thanks Chris
I'm not going to make it too much longer
For today I'm going to try
And since I will have a couple of evenings
Fring and I'm going to see if I'm going to do
More than one show this week
What do we got right now
We're at feels like about 40 minutes
What do we got?
Oh geez
Man, time flies when you're having fun with friends
48 minutes already
So in the I'm not going to play the YouTube video
But I did put a link in the show notes
DaddySourceCo.com or crossposts
That are curry.com
The Lutec Magnetic Amplifier
Which is yet another
As I said, another crazy Australian invention
These guys are making stuff
They put 210 volts in
Like five times the energy comes out
I mean, can you imagine you could run your entire home on that?
Oh man, it'll be so beautiful
You know what?
I got to go to Australia
That's it
It's settled
Okay
This is a trip that I this is now
I finally have a real besides
Well, we know that I'm not going for the porn
Down Under
Because the links that have been showing up on the
Drop are of very low
Excitement
Quality
There's not a lot of good porn going on down under
I have been to Australia before
I love the people
Love the place
Work hard, play hard
I need to go visit some of these folks
Maybe that's a whole series
I don't know
But I am going to make time in 2009
Hear me now
Believe me later my friends
I'm going to come to Australia
And I'd like you to start helping me out
I need to map out
Where I need to go to
Obviously it's a huge country
I can't go everywhere
But I do want to visit some of these folks
I'm not quite sure where they're all located
But I just got to go and see some of this for myself
And we've got to bring this to the forefront
There are some truly spectacular stuff going on
Meanwhile, just going back to something that
Totally insulted me, made me incredibly angry
From the Washington Post
Airports across the country
Will have designated security lanes for families
To move through pre-flight inspections at their own pace
Just in time for the busy Thanksgiving
Travel season reports the Washington Post
And so essentially you'll get the experienced lane
That would be people like me
You just want to zip through and know by the time you get there
You've got your laptop, you've got your belt off
You've got all your shit and your jacket
Your jackets and the tray
I got my shoes off because of course
The expensive shoes are the ones that have the metal
And it turns out
That's what they always say
Take off your shoes
They're too expensive
They've got metal in them
Crazy
Expanding these lanes
Every airport and directing families and passengers
With medical necessary liquids
To them increases passenger convenience and security
And here it comes, here's the thing that pisses me off
In August of 2006, the TSA changed its screening policies
After officials foiled a plot to use liquid explosives
To blow up commercial airlines headed towards the US intelligence
Well, I'm sorry towards the US
Intelligence officials remain concerned
The terrorists could carry liquid explosives onto the plane
And of course the government is testing equipment
That scans liquids for explosives
And hopes to lift the restrictions in the future
So I just want to remind you that the British courts
Could not convict them of doing this
There was absolutely no, it's a story
It's a fabel, it's fake, it's bullshit, it's a lie
They could not convict
These so-called terrorists
For actually plotting to do that
They had no tickets, they had no passports
There was absolutely no indication
They were going to blow up airplanes
And yet the stupid laws still remain in place
We're still taking our shoes off
Because of some guy who had
Like some kind of explosive in his shoe
And I love foiling
Once again, this morning at Heathrow
I love doing this
If you've ever flown international out of Heathrow
First you go through the regular screening
And then there's a secondary set of paths
We have to have your passport looked at
As you leave the country
Right after that
There's another security checkpoint
That is only for shoes
And you have to take your shoes off
Put them through and then go put your shoes on
And then you're finally out by the way
They drop your right off in the tax-free shopping
I mean literally inside the store
How convenient is that
But every single time I love doing this
I go through the passport
I always go to the right hand side
If you're traveling out of Heathrow
Try this
I go to the right hand side
The most far right passport control
And then as I come out
There's always the person trying to hurt the sheep
The sheep people into taking their shoes off
And I always kind of stand
I look at my passport fumbling
I might do something with my bag
And then the minute the security person is not looking
I just walk right past on the right hand side
There's so-called security checkpoint
Proving that that is bullshit as well
Because they don't mean it
They really don't
One thing that has been cropping up that
God I hope this is not true
But as you know
911 and 777
911 of course in the United States
On the day of 911
There was an actual drill taking place
A drill that
An exercise
Military actually was a lot of different divisions were involved
The delts specifically with hijacked planes
They were doing a drill
And it happened for real
July 7th
In the United Kingdom
At that very same time
They were doing a drill
A security drill in London
Where they suppose that there would be a number of explosions
In tubes
That's the subway
And buses and they were almost exactly the same spots where these explosions took place
You can call it coincidence or whatever
But starting tomorrow in Los Angeles, California
5 million people will be subject to the Los Angeles
Shaken-Bake drill as I'm calling it
They're going to simulate a 7.3 or 7.5 magnitude
Earthquake on the Richter scale
I think this last for three or four days this drill
And of course this stuff popping up on the internet
Everywhere's in people saying hey, wait a minute
911 that had a drill it really happened
777 in London
They had a drill it really happened
My buddy John C. Devorex said that he thought that the cycle was time once again for a so-called
Terrorist attack and he was talking about Los Angeles
I don't see how we can quite corroborate
Or combine the an earthquake with a terrorist attack
But I'm just saying
So if it does happen, God forbid man
I got too many friends in Los Angeles, God forbid
At least we'll know that there's a pattern to this stuff
So let's hope it doesn't happen
Then finally
What company is doing great in these times?
What company do you think is just doing a fan?
Just knocking it out of the park
When everyone's in trouble, everyone's going crazy
Everyone's losing money, the markets are crashing
McDonald's
8.2% up
In actual revenue
Because of course
With food is too expensive
We're starving, we're eating crap
Absolute crap
Same store sales
Same store sales, 8.2%
And how do you like this?
The company's popular dollar menu
And its annual monopoly promotion
Also drew in value hungry customers
How interesting is that that we've been talking about
The move from paper to plastic egg McDonald's
As well as in the monopoly game
It's just making it easy
Path of least resistance people
Please
Try and eat something healthy
I know it's really outrageously expensive
But this is how we really are killing ourselves
By eating absolute crap
We've really really really really got to take care of ourselves
And I'm going to do just that
Which means let's see it's a nine o'clock here in New York
So my body clock is saying 2 a.m
Time for me to head off to bed
After we hear from the master John Lennon
As soon as you're born
They make it feel small
By giving you no time instead of at all
Till a pain is so big you feel nothing at all
Working class hero is something to be
They hurt you at home
They did do it school
They hate you if you're clever
And they despise a fool
Till you're so fucking crazy
You can't follow their rules
Working class hero is something to be
When the tortured and scared you for 20 odd years
Then they expect you to pick a career
When you can't really function you're so full of fear
Working class hero is something to be
Keep it dope with religion
Sex and TV
And you think you're so clever and class-less and free
But you're still fucking peasants as far as I can see
Working class hero is something to be
There's room at the top they are telling you still
But first you must learn how to smile as you kill
If you want to be like the folks on the hill
Working class hero is something to be
If you want to be hero
Just follow me
I'm not the only one saying this shit has been going on for a long time
A lot of people have been switched on to this
And we must not forget
As I said, lots going on this week in Nueva York
Good to be in the city though
It still is the city that makes me feel very much at home
I haven't really been able to taste the atmosphere yet
So tomorrow I'll get a good dose of it
And I'll probably be in a New York state of mind which is always fun to be in
So take everybody remember
It's your freedom
Enjoy it while you can
Use it responsibly
And whatever you do
Live your life with passion