This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Delta Shara Charley 717
edges
It was $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
To the next generation concealed content in my ears.
It takes me a few minutes to fix my turn..
On Google Icecan
on Google Icecan
When I got it, when I got it, when I got it
The most crazy night, a full moon in the city
She wants to be reds the best way that's back underneath
She wants a passion, needs that for me, yes, no, no
She blew me into the Senate, she blew me away
The water's here, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, where are you?
I want a shower, what was that dream?
She got a dream, checking, hell cave in the roof
When I should keep you down and think about someone to apologize
Surf off the streets. I need to listen to you
Show them, you all are news mum
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, hey, oh,
I need a rest of my life, I need a for you
I need a rest of my life, I need a rest of my life
Now you're here, it's been a year, it's been a year
It's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year
It's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year
It's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year
It's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year, it's been a year
Singing off the bar Friday with a hot rock, little redstone at all from the pot
save music network.
Everybody how you doin' is the Daily Source code episode number 717 coming to you
from the curry condo,
wrapping up the week here in San Francisco
and the Russians are definitely checking in on
as my friends, listen to this.
Bravo, Bravo, Edno, V, 3, Bravo, Bravo, Edno, V, 3,
good night.
Now I don't know, man.
I don't know, Probo, Probo, sound, it could be Italian,
but this is pretend it's Russian, okay?
Ha ha ha.
Oh man, wrapping up a week,
I've got a whole bunch of cool music lined up for you.
I think we got six songs ready for today,
five or six, got a hit test,
got some other sub-on stuff in buy,
like my pal Amy Mack,
who has been evaluating my ass throughout the week,
well, I've been in San Francisco.
And of course, while I'm here,
people are passing through G-town.
Hello Adam, my name is Joseph Carradis.
I've been living pure podcast for quite a while now.
And about this my first time that I'm calling,
I was just rushing through G-town
and I said, like, well, the hit,
let's say, let's call and say hello to Adam.
I love you, they're normal, right?
Back at you, my friend.
Too bad, too bad you were a passenger G-town
and it wasn't there to meet you.
And of course, you know,
it's not a live phone that rings anywhere.
So call me an advanced next time,
man, we'll hook up with the Starbucks.
Hi Adam, Eric's important to me.
I've been trying to get my wife interested in podcasts
for the past two years without any luck.
Well, last night she was feeling kind of down
and I walked to her computer and downloaded DSC 716.
I'm in it later, we were listening to natives
of the new dawn, this day.
The mood changed instantly.
And then her young kids came in
and we cranked up party like a rock star.
We were all danced around with Dan
like a bunch of lunatics.
It was a great time.
And I think you have a new listener.
Love you, bro.
Go home.
No, man, love you back.
No, homo, you know what it's like, right?
Uh, see, I had a, uh, someone sending a question
about that.
It must be somewhere, uh, hmm.
Maybe it was this.
Hey, Adam, how are you?
It's probably for my first.
How what's going to your back?
You if they're saying no homo means that you're not homo.
It's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo
it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo, it's not homo
Trim up, put down the seeds
I shed the light on the brand
The day I stretched my own to give a sigh
I watched the grass fight out of my eyes
I hit out, down all the town
No shame at jamming up the ground
Rolled on, just to the shore
All these girls ain't knocking on my doors
The worries won't against time
But I still didn't even tell the night
I get so tired to say
Get the same old shit, just a
Driven day, let the boogie loose
And let the boogie loose
Let the boogie loose today
Did any old layers of weight
And let the boogie loose tonight
And let the time even feel it all right
Feel it all right, yeah
It's not a one of those tracks just makes me feel good
Dancing around like idiots in the middle of the night
The brain buckets
And let the boogie loose tonight
Yeah
All the girls ain't knocking on my doors
And let the boogie loose tonight
Yeah
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, no-no-no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah
Oh my god
You know I got admitted
It's been
Someone
Challenging this past week audio wise
I've
You know been working without the mix
I've been working on Ableton Live
It's been anything but easy you know
We go back to your via
You've got about on a Mac and on
Yeah
Thank you for the comment. I took that into account and specifically beefed up the microphone and I think we're doing a little bit better there
Brain bucket that the movie loose from the pod save music network at music.podshow.com
Hey Adam how are you? It's Pablo from headquarters. I was going to ask you is there saying no homo means that you are not homo or you are not short
And if you say you are not short or you know what you are
Okay, if I hold that
You can understand that question. Love you. Love you mean it
No, man. It's I picked that up from
From Tony over at costas world
He and the boys would sit around and they had this one long conversation one day about
About about guys who hug each other and say hey man, I love you and then they say no homo, which is
It's only in America. Do you need to say that really? I mean I I don't think you need to say that anywhere else, but it's just because actually we have yet for someone to call in to say I love you a homo
Which is fine, too. So to answer your question
It's just a way of
Mainly American males feeling more comfortable about saying I love you
Any kind of playing it off. You know how guys when they hug they like hit each other on the bat that pay attention to that when when males hug
Particularly straight males. They'll pat each other. You know sloppy child on the back that often there is no embrace. There is no
There's no warmth and no love transferring. Which is a shame, really
Of course, to answer your question. Honestly, I don't know
God
Hey entertainment of the week. Thank you very much. This is one of those links that a million people actually did send to me
And I appreciate every single one and it really turned into just my favorite past time over the past
Over the past two days, apologies, of course, we're not bringing you a show yesterday
I'm not even going to tell you what it is. Just listen to the comment. It's it's fairly obvious and it's wonderful really is
Yeah, I'm this is Scott from Sonny, South Bend, Indiana
First time one time
Right now
Hey, I was listening to you for quite some time and
Just thinking about all the travels you've been having with the TSA and getting stopped in airports
This evening on the 31st is a lot of stuff on around the net
Let me just stop you there for one second
Even though I appreciate the thought about TSA, it is not actually the TSA that are giving me
Well, it's not even a problem now. Now it's just become a joke. It's the CBP Customs Border Protection Agency
Still part of Homeland Security
We're pretty much identical uniforms although these guys
They're packing heat
The customs guys they got weapons TSA
Thank god almighty. They got no no led to shoot it.
TSA actually having a blog of all things. It's at tsa.gov slash blog
And if you look at it, it's actually pretty funny
So whoever wrote it or put the page together actually has a sense of humor
On the net. A whole lot of posts and responses on it
And you can't look at it. It's hilarious
The people that are running it, writing it and reading to the comments
Some of the TSA are actually acting like human beings
Kind of interesting. Like to see what you think about it
Yeah man, thanks. As I said, total amusement, total entertainment, love every single second of it
Not gonna post it. In fact, I shouldn't even I should be reading it through a proxy server
But the idea is good TSA.gov slash blog
And I am not alone. We are not alone my friends. That's for sure
What I haven't really seen yet though is some really good responses
They're starting to clean it up. They did kind of a classic mistake
Well, I just the whole idea of using WordPress comments
For a weblog, for an agency of
That has hated this much actually
It's just a mistake in the thinking process
So that's gonna tell me that this is a pretty genuine effort
It feels like at least
So they're gonna have to do a lot of cleanup on the comments
And of course, you really should be doing a forum when you think about it
But fun initiative, still, still not loving the TSA
Even though you're showing a little bit more for human face, it just doesn't cover
Hey, speaking of human faces, I happen to be wearing my hands
Are my shoulders
Hey Amy, bring it to me, let's do some exercise
Hey Adam, Amy, man
Okay, so I've seen you running around the office all week
And yet we haven't had time for a proper butt squeeze and evaluation
Yes correct
What happened to us?
Where are our priorities I ask you?
Okay, so maybe some things are more important than having a great ass
Well, but I don't know what that would be
Anyway, today we're gonna be standing, so do you gotta do
I'm gonna take the mic with me, okay, I'm standing
We're doing reverse lunges
So place your right foot in front of you and then put the left leg behind you
Left leg behind
You're gonna put it in a deep lunge
Then bend the back of the leg and take the knee almost to the floor
Keep that upper body up tall and straight
And then bring the leg back up
And again, six more times
Ben, and straightened
Squeeze that stomach
Down and up
Last one
Good, switch that
Left leg forward and right leg back
Now bend the right leg
Knee almost to the ground
Up, up, up
Six more
Down and up
Come on Amy
Yes, I will hear it
Is that where you want to hear it?
Hiders
Now take a deep breath
Last one
Go back off for this week, so until next time
Jesus, Jesus, Jesus
Whoa, what's going on?
There we go
Sorry, overloaded the system there
Amy
Now I can't wait to get home
Now I'm all worked up
You know, I'll be honest with you
When you're away from home for a long time
I don't care how old you are
If you love your partner
If you're in love with your partner
Particularly if you're a couple of time zones away
You know what happens?
You get crazy ass sex dreams
About five or six in the morning
They've actually been waking me up for the past two days
I mean, I mean these are
Sex dreams with my wife by the way
But there's all kinds of other people involved too
Which is kind of naughty
Adam, it's ginger from the day
If you haven't met with a couple of things
First of all, the word literally
I think you have no idea what that word means
Because I've never heard of you
Correctly, at least not in recent memory
Literally means actually or really
You just said
Nokia E61 is literally indestructible
And if it were literally indestructible that means
There would be no physical way on earth
But wait
I have to stop you there
I truly believe
That's why I said it that way
That is an incorrect use of the word
In most cases
In case of the Nokia E61 I
That thing is literally indestructible
It's a brick, you can't break it, you can't mall it
It just keeps on working
Which reminds me, if you don't mind me
Interrupting this English lesson
That you can get
Well, you can purchase
Unless you now am really self-conscious of my English
You can purchase the Nokia
And 810
Internet tablet
I mean, I talked about it so often
But now you can get it
I believe it's pretty much worldwide
At a 15% discount
You can't get this thing cheaper anywhere else
I haven't found it
And believe me, I looked
If you use my code, daily source code
When you check out, it's a promo code
Or discount code, I think they call it
So you want to go to
NokiaUSA.com slash n810
Or go to BTpodshow.com slash n810
Or podshowoffers.com
slash n810
And when it asks you for the promo code
Just a type in daily source code
And you'll get your 15% discount upon checking out
So what you actually mean is it's not literally
Indestructible, it just seems that way, sometimes
So that's less than number one
Okay, number two is the word amount
You say things like the amount of podcasts
What you should be saying is the number of podcasts
You use the word number when it's something that can be counted
Like the amount of love in the world
Water is the number of podcasts on my iTunes quite
Anyway, just some English lessons
And driving me nuts, thought I might as well educate you
Thank you, no, I appreciate that, please feel free to do that any time
And I really like the way you did that, you were just really cool about it
Fantastic, thank you, thank you very much
Well, thank you very much everybody, it's a football Friday
That means it's time for young plets
Fantastic, with Adam Curry
Adam, who are you ready to be stumped
Because he is the fantastic guest
Hit me baby
Adam, this is hit us number one or seven
And this week all the tracks are from 1986
Yeah, with him crown number one
That is
That's the Sun City record
Oh, crap, I give up
Number two
Y'all
Is that
Lady and red, maybe
And number three
Oh, shit
I know I'm gonna hate myself when I get these answers
I can't believe it, I haven't done this bad in so in a long time
And time's up and this is answer number one
Yeah, you're not in the guest
That's it
That's that one, right?
Well, kind of
I'm one place on city, is that it?
Ah, hey, we're gonna play Sun City
And what ever happened to that?
I guess it's okay now to play Sun City
Music for a good cause
Artists united against the fight hide with Sun City as answer number one
And this is answer number two
What is it, what is it, what is it, what is it?
This is Kak Robin
I'll remember the promise you made
We
Kak Robin
Kak Robin is answer number two with when your heart is weak
And this is answer number three
I don't know this one
This is total contrast
Because though it's gone you say
I wouldn't have known that one
Total contrast is answer number three with hit and run
And that's it for hit this number one, no seven
Not easy
So at him, how did you do?
I would say I suck Bollocks
Like always, don't just hit this and also the links to iTunes
So you can buy these tricks online or to be found at hittest.fotshow.com
Next week I hope to be back with hittest number 108
So until then take care and bye-bye
Hittest at gmail.com
info
Now that this is of course the hittest
Now is the hittest, the football Friday I mean
I was just thinking about my wife and I thought you know what?
It's right, I got to go home with clean laundry
Take one step
And I'll shoot
I don't think I'm afraid of you
You held me back
So I tied you up
The only way you got it
I almost fell down the stroke of luck
Because no one
gets away from me
Till I say leave
I'm on the beach on the moon
Take your words that hurt
You dirty shirt
Walk your ass back out my door
I say go
I'll be OKy by myself
When you go, you will ride
Because every night we will make it look
I was thinking of somewhere else
The tables have turned
Then your goose is cudd
And judge me they has arrived
If they're ready or not, here I come
You're gonna pay for what you've done
And I get to watch you square
There's no one
Get away from me to let's say leave
I don't need your number
Thank you words that hurt
You dirty shirt, walk your ass back
Come back to us and go
I'll be okay if I'm my friend
Let me know if you were right
Because every night we were making love
I was making up someone else
You chased your tail for too long
You're a girl, a girl, a girl, a girl
And I guess that's the price you pay
When you let something this could get away
You're gonna pay for what you've done
Yeah, let's try baby
You're all
You got clean shirts, boys
I said take one step
Come on
Take one step
And I swear I'll shoot
You're here on me back
So I tied you up
The only way you got out was the bell
So come and look
Because no one
That's the way for me to let's say leave
I don't need your number
Take your words that hurt
You dirty shirt, walk your ass back
Come back to us and go
I'll be okay if I'm my friend
Let me know if you were right
Because every night we were making love
I was making up
I don't need you anymore
Take your words that hurt
You dirty shirt, walk your ass back
Come back to us and go
I'll be okay if I'm my friend
Let me know if you were right
Because every night we were making love
I was thinking so well
You are
Oh, Laura Clap
Man
Haven't played her in a long time
Of course you'll find links to all of the songs
On today's show in the show notes
A daily source code dot com
We'll just go through the a Gmail here for a second
Oh yeah
Lots of comments of course on the offer to Chris Moiles
Lee said for hi Adam just heard
Your show where you officially offered Chris Moiles
1.2 million pounds
To come to work for BT Pod Show
I swear that Chris had a conversation with this crew
Either this or yesterday morning on air
And the topic was
Would you leave if you were offered double the money
I can't be 100% sure though
Because I was still in bed
And semi-conscious listening to my clock radio
You still have one of those
They all pretty much concluded that radio
One is a dream job and they wouldn't leave
Oh yeah
Well Chris was pressing people that everyone has their price
Absolutely
And by the way
I expressly did not extend the offer to his crew
To what is it comedy day
And whatever the girl is on the show
And the reason why is
Sometimes
Sometimes you might want to change your crew
Basically
So I wanted to give Chris the opportunity
To essentially make that decision
Lots of stuff going on with this
I'll be back
I'm going to go to Amsterdam on Monday
And I'll come back Monday night
And in the office the rest of the week
So I'm sure
I've got super Keith, super agent Keith
He'll be hooking up with
He's going to
He's going to give me all the load down
And I'll pass it on to you
Who knows?
Who knows where this could lead us?
Could be very interesting
Actually I know where it can lead us
It gave us an interesting comment
Greetings Adam Curry
This is Lindsey Curre
Freelance Broadcaster
And I have an offer for you
Why not offer me the job
What job?
Well Chris Morales is job
Being the habitual listener to the Charlie
I nearly pissed the bed last night
When I heard you offer 1.3 million pounds for moils
Now I accept that the man is good in small doses
But is he really worth that much
As a radio presenter
Now Freelance
I have an offer for you
Higher me
Onto your network
And save yourself
And your company
Major Money
I'll have to do the gig for
50,000 pounds a year
After all I do have eleven years
Broadcasting experience
Both with commercial and BBC
So come on Adam
Give me a shot
What do you say?
I'm challenging you to give me a paid real money shot
Our proof that I too can get listeners
I'll leave it to you
Oh by the way
I'm a scrunching folder
I'm male
I'm 35
I'm married
Love you
In a non gay way
Love your hair
Hope you win
And keep trying in your shoes
He's made of baby
Shining so easy
Car
Just for the fun
Of it the linty career
You're sure
Oh
Look by my
Adam
Come on
Take your sauce cold
Adam
Come on
Well Lindsay
Thank you very much for for for sending that to me
You know working freelance for mainstream radio BBC
I mean you need a lot more qualifications
If you want to work for me you have to have a you can't be over five foot one
You have to have a flat head and that ears I can grab onto
Flat head is for the beer
You know what
I really appreciate it and I wish I could pay everyone 50,000 pounds
You know obviously
Chris Moiles has an audience of seven right million people that listen on a daily basis
The thinking here is that he could it it means like a Howard Stern deal
You know like he could at least bring a million people per day to his podcast
I'm quite caught he already has you know almost a quarter of a million
I think on a daily on a daily basis
Who are listening to the podcast
And if you come away you know if he comes over to the death star
First of all he'll be able to play music with that be refreshing
Because of course the podcast version of the Chris Moiles show they have to strip the music out
And of course you can play awesomely cool music
And I'm quite convinced that he would be able to bring a million people over
That's that's really what makes it worth it
So
Honestly anyone who can bring a million listeners a day can make a shitload of money
I will help you with that
I guarantee it
Hey, I'm thank you by the way for ending your comment with sub demographic information
Lots of people calling in lots of people emailing in men was I wrong
Was I wrong about who's listening to this show
I thought it was guys who either 20 years old or 40 years old
Whenever you call in with a comment just finish up with just a quick demographic profile
So we're kind of introducing ourselves to each other
So it would be love you, mean it or
Is that it's a love you know homo great hair hope you win
Middle age middle class white dude something like that, you know you can do any variation you want
And here's how wrong I was
Hi Adam, this is Audrey
I just wanted to comment you know that yes, there are women out here listening
I've been listening since 2004 and you finally got me a call because I'm tired
If you think that there aren't any women
I absolutely hate making phone calls though
So this one for you Adam
I'm 40 I live in Florida
I'm a data analyst and I do listen have a great time doing the show
And thanks for doing what you're doing
Bye
Audrey you know me to thank me thank you so much for calling in
I really appreciate that
And if you're a if you're a woman or a girl and you're calling in
I think you should also tell me where you listen to me what you're wearing when you listen to me
I listen to me how you're feeling when you listen to me
Hi Adam I'm calling to give you some of my demographic information
I'm Solange I am actually from Argentina
But I live in Belgium
I am a philosophy student here I'm 24
Yeah
What electrical device do you have running in the background?
I am actually from Argentina
But I live in Belgium
I am a philosophy student here I'm 24
More like most students I'm usually broke so I don't know exactly where I fit in
Yeah
I'm just my family would be middle class
Folder
Red pill
Well
Great hair hope you win
I love you Adam
I love you too
And I really do mean it
I really do mean it
Hey Adam my name is Rich Seigo
Call and give you another demographic
I'm a 60 year old physician calling from Gloss to Mass
And if you hear noise in the background that's the ocean
I'm a podcaster
I have a podcast called Pediatrics for Parents
I've been involved with computers in 1966
Back when it will punch cows and paper tape
And I'm a Mac enthusiast calling on my iPhone
I have three Macs in home
And run my office all on Macs
Keep up the good work
And with your family history I sure hope you quit smoking
Yeah
Thanks for a great show
Bye
I quit that shit
Pediatrics for parents
I like that
Drop me an email, William
There's a lot of people who are interested in sponsoring programming
Like that and I'll have an email
Just let me just hurry on over right now
Let me see if I can find your show
I found that we went into alpha today
With V3
God this thing is going to be so cool
Hold on PDATrics
And we're starting to integrate some of the new search functionality on the existing pod show
And it really does work
Okay, last time I posted January 31st
Excellent
Okay, I'll have a listen
I have a queue up now
So I can't lose my place
Let me just see if there was another
Any more comments that came in
Something about internet bandwidth
I do want to talk about that about the meter bandwidth
Well let's do it
Well, here we go
I thought it was a 20 year old and 40 year old white guys
We got some women
We've got a 60 year old physician
And
I had a
It's Chris here in Nashville
I did call you once before
Ages ago
But I'm a long time listener
The listening person
Some of them are arched out of five
You were I just heard this recent GSC
Or you were talking about
You only have 20 year olds and 40 year olds
So I'm 32
And I guess you could consider me middle class
And I'm Hispanic in origin
I am a work in construction inspection
So just a little bit more
That's your demographic information
Keep up the good work
And I will be listening
Excellent
That's him
That's our Spanish listener
He's there more out there
Besides a whole bunch of white guys
A couple of white girls
And one Hispanic guy
There's got to be more
You can add up this is John from Dallas
When you call in about your demographic
Get a survey
I am currently on the road
It's 6 to 11 in the morning
I'm driving to Austin for meeting today
I'm 43 married, live in a suburb
North of Dallas called Frisco
I am a electrical engineer
By a profession who has migrated over into
The state-of-the-school world
I am currently a school
I am currently a school based on the engineer
For a large Japanese and a construction company
I also have an MBA
And I'm a part-time musician
So hope to tell
Love you in the unique right there
Hope you win later bro
Alright man, awesome
Thank you so much
You know that's really this is
It's not just the comments that blitz me up
When I listen to you guys calling in
It's what you're saying
I feel
I feel like I was a man
I know I was wrong
That's for sure
Now this track is so perfect for a food bar Friday
It is classic Matthew evil
Even though it's a new song
It's got his vibe
It's got his sound
And some of the lyrics from when Sally went down
But now she's going down
So
What I'm saying
I mean like
Down, down
Nashville's finest on the Charlie
On a footballer Friday
But even country girls
They don't want to run
Because the pride of the night
Till the city is night
We're laying down like a curse on a small town
The music's swinging and bringing it
The greater girls
Tell the fellows
Get up and get up and get on the train
Going down
Down
Take me down
Don't tell
The Sally couldn't see a future past the end
I've never known
I said I'd fall
The stars with some confidence
And I'd beg for the flow
Don't you say the sight
Some of the night
Shading at you on the show
The Sally never made it to the world
Now you drive the legs
My body's looking for sex
And cheap whiskey in the back
For the happiness
And suck you in
When the city's to clean
And a stick pan
And a spoon that you go
And a way to keep going
Down
Take me down
And take me down
Down
I'm gonna go home
You fishin' that's looking mass, but baby
You better sell your daddy gonna raise that
Wow
He's your money, but honey don't daddy don't give it down
Unless you gotta tell him you're gonna win down
Tell him I wanna get
We're all alone here
Take me down
Ah Matthew Evil
Down town
From the pod save music network
Music.potshow.com
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Awesome tune for a footballer Friday
Loving it
Okay, one kind of serious thread we've been going through
The conversation about metered bandwidth
Which is going into trial in Beaumont, Texas
Time Warner cable is checking that out
You know, and I believe that this has the possibility
The capability to actually wind up becoming cheaper for a typical internet user
Which that may not be us by the way
Robert writes in
Robert Bob
Oh man
Kawarotani
Bob Kawarotani writes in
Dear Adam check my band with usures for the podcast
Audio and video
I'm over one gigabyte per day
Luckily we haven't been hearing any noises about metering here in Japan
Ah, hence the last name
Living in suburban Tokyo
We have the choice of two fiber optic systems
From company electric power company
The cable TV system and several ADSL vendors
Also there's one pure data vendor offering seven megabit wireless data as well
I usually joke that this one, this is one case where Japan took some good advice from the Clinton administration
Okay, I don't quite understand that one
Anyway, the interesting part here is the one gig per day
So a 30-day month would be about 30 gigs
That should cost you at a really, really high price is about 30 bucks
That's about if you just take a dollar a gig right
So knowing that that price can on the other end of the pipe
We pay under nine cents for it
And I'm contractually not allowed to tell you how much under nine cents
But it just sounds better than under ten
You can see where you're only using so much
And as long as we don't hold on to the model of overage and charging then per megabyte
Which I don't think this is about
I think we might actually be in good shape
Hey Adam, it's Sam from Bushman UK
I'm listening to episode 715
So you're talking about meated bandwidth
The cool thing I think it was just in
Saying you know, you pay for unlimited, you just have unlimited
I think that's a crock of shit
You think about your electric connection coming into your house
I have a hundred amp mains feed from the electricity grid into my house
But I don't sit there drawing a hundred amps of electricity constantly
If I dare I'd be paying a fortune for it
You know, I use more electricity when I want to use them like a cooking
But at night I don't use them much
So bandwidth is the same
You pay for a DSL line at whatever rate megabits
But you know, you shouldn't be maxing that half constantly
And that works just don't work like that
Anyway
That's all for me, I love you
Great half if you win
All right, thank you
Exactly my point
This is very very common
It's common with your current phone service as well
At least according to me
Maybe not to some lazy French fucker
Hi Adam, this is an afternoon from Silicon Valley Frost
I'm sorry man, just doesn't with you
I'm calm
And I hope the AT&T signal quality is better
Better this time, yeah
I told you that anyway, so I'm not just a meter bandwidth thing
Sure, I won't for it as well
The problem is, well, was the last time that your telco
Actually lowered its rates
I don't know
Sakabla, are you making a joke with me?
And Jolie
And I remember my first cell phone
Cost like three bucks a minute
That's gone down
Roming charges gone down
I mean, you cannot argue that
That
Phone calling hasn't become consistently cheaper
Worldwide, aren't they?
Sever
When was the last time you actually paid less
Or telephone or internet act
Oh, Jean-Douille?
I mean, seriously, think about that
When was the last time you did
And I'm talking about, you know
Since basically the mid 90s
I'm not talking about prior to the 90s
Well, man, I had a 64 kilobit frame relay
That I paid, I think, 700 bucks a month for
Are you kidding me?
I don't know
No, no
It was really expensive to have an internet connection
So, that's the problem
I think that even if we get to a meter bandwidth situation
We're not going to pay any less than we do now
What's going to happen is that the templates
It's just going to raise rates
For the people who, you know, are being with dogs
Basically, but we, you know, average users
They're still going to pay the same
Maybe even more
So, that's it
All right, love you
Love you man
No, no, no
No, there's anything wrong with that
30 years
No, Oma
Uh
Tonset
California
I don't know, mercy
No, man, I think you got a completely wrong there
I really do
Anyway, it's fun to talk about it
And of course, all of us just talking out of our poop shoot right now
Because we don't know what they're doing
Where are the people in Beaumont?
I reach everyone around the world
Surely within the power of my voice
Within the, you didn't mean it that way
Within, I'm so conscious now that I'm getting these English lessons
Anyone within the, the reach of my voice
If you know anyone in Beaumont, Texas who might happen to be
In the time Warner, meet her ban with trial, please give me a call
Hey Adam, this is Dean from Morgan Hill
And hey, I was in this
DFC 2012 and you were questioning how I did the hybrid while
Let me explain it to you
It goes like this, you're full of toilet paper off the roll
And you fold it
And then in the process of using it, you're scratching
That's how you end up being a hybrid
Hope that clears it up
Hey, love this show
Love you into home
All right man, the home
Thank you very much
Thank you, thank you
Thank you
Let me just see what are we doing on time right now
What about 40 minutes?
Being a, wow, 50 minutes
Oh, well, you know what?
I want to play a song that I talked about earlier this week
Hey guys, thank you very much
For reminding me, not I specifically said
Could someone please just shoot me an email
Remind me to play this song and no one did
Luckily, I've been really active this week
And the brain has been firing
And all the synapses and everything's working
So I remembered myself
This was the song I was talking about when talking about
Chris Moiles earlier in the week about how
I feel that I am a dysjockey of the, you know
When they made dysjockey like me, they broke the mold
It just doesn't exist anymore
The, I wrote, not only do I romanticize
Being on the radio
I actually believe it and feel it
And this song
Every single old school dysjockey in the world
Knows this song
Anyone who's been in the radio business
As a dysjockey
Knows what the song is about
It is completely to the tea
Exactly the life of a DJ
Not very glamorous
And the lowest rung of the show business ladder
Is Harry Chapin to tell you about it
In W-O-L-D
Hello honey, it's me
What did you think when you heard me back on the radio
What did the kids say when they knew
It was the long lost daddy, oh
Remember how we listened to the radio
And I said, that's a place to be
And how we got the job is an FM job
The day you married me
It was two kids and I was into a rock
But I just had to run around
It's been eight years since the left you paid
They've been tell you about what's gone down
I am the morning DJ
And W-O-L-D
When all it hits me up
Wherever you may be
The great good morning boys
Who's hurt but never seen
Feeling all the fun of fire
Knowing I'm 15
The drinking I did on my last baby
It made my horse go low
They said it didn't like the other time
When they let me go
So I drifted on down the toes
Of the home of the delete night talk show
Now I've worked my way down
Home again near the boys
And I know that's how this business goes
I am the morning DJ
And W-O-L-D
When all it hits me up
Wherever you may be
The great good morning boys
Who's hurt but never seen
Feeling all the fun of fire
Knowing I'm 15
I'm making it come on and do
It has to go to suck up
It's not the big time
It's the same
It is a crazy way
I just step on the top of my head
Just make it more with getting too late
There's a caramel that got rumbrar
From setting up
But it's never gonna go away
Sometimes I get these crazy dreams
And I just take off in my car
But you can travel on 10,000 miles
Still stay with you all
Thinking that I should stop this junk
And start that record stall
Maybe I could settle down
If you can take me back once more
Okay honey, I see
I guess he's better than me
Your older understand
You don't have to worry, I'm such a happy man
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh
I am the morning DJ
Head to the U.O.L.D.D.
Lay in all the hits we owe
Wherever you may be
The great good morning voice
Who's heard the never seen
Feeling all the fun if I
Going on 15
I am the morning DJ
Head to the U.O.L.D.D.D.D
You know, it really is that lyric
The great good morning voice
I've never seen, I am the morning DJ
I'm W.O.L.D.
Of course, this is a fashion, right?
But the vibe is the same
And that's what shows like ours are doing
Call it podcasting whatever you want
That's what it is, we're connecting again
I love it, I love it, I love y'all
And that'll do it for Fubar Friday
For first of February 2008
And I thank you very much for listening
I can't wait to get home
So Monday may be tough for me
Because I'm traveling
But you know me, I'll find
So I mean, like you like you're listening
To this on Friday, here we are right
Hey, drop in email
AdvertwoodPodshow.com
DailySourceco.com
And have yourself a great week
And live your life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
And a happy anniversary
To a Dr. Ron Paul in his wife