You're out of my thinking making this money thing a little too complicated I think we need
to explain it a little easier so I'm gonna say like this let's pretend that there's a
neighborhood and see the neighborhood has a bank it's called the bank of Louis people
come to Louis when they need money Louis lens a money people pay Louis back with a little
extra for I interest people don't pay Louis people getting broken legs see it's
pretty simple don't understand it's on the DSC 746 let's try to keep it simple
compete I knew you were a good guy there and I'm carried this is the daily source code
the daily source code
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped my ass in the next generation radio content in my
years I like to think I'm flying to the street
I've been telling me what it means and it's coming to an end
Please be next to me
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no not, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, is just going to be the strike, I'll beat it, I'll beat properly, I'll beat it, I will be beating it, I will beat it. And,
Oh, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it
it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, yeah, it's me, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah there's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, I'm a free one, till all, all, I'm free one, I'm free one, I'm free one, I'm free one, see ya, good name ya'll, ex me, depth strength yes let's see ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll yaa ya'll ya'll ya'll ya ha we'll yaa won ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll yaa ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya'll ya
from back in the day when they called us swinging
different word for making love, right?
Of course, it's only 30 years old.
Now they're entering to the soundtrack of our lives.
Jim Gilstrap, not to be confused with...
Gil-Jockstrap.
I don't know.
Everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode number 746 coming to you
from the curry manner in a very wet Gilford.
It's coming down way a little bit of hail earlier on.
It does not look like it's gonna be a very nice week.
We just got more of this April showers,
which are supposed to bring me flowers.
And I'm late today, it's already 10 past three in the afternoon.
I spent an entire morning getting car insurance for Christina's car.
You know, I got Shanghai the other weekend.
And of course, you'll have her license any day now.
All things going according to plan.
And well, so I had to go figure that out.
And got her a Renault Twingo, which is a really cute car.
It's a great, you know, first car.
It's reasonably sturdy, I'd say.
It's safe.
And I don't want to have any hassle, so it's new.
And very interesting, though, trying to get insurance.
Just even to put it on my name.
Because I learned very quickly as I spoke with our regular insurer,
Jaguar, which I think is forward insurance.
It's a forward anyway, right?
I said, well, you know, so I'll get this car now.
And then when my daughter gets her license,
I want to add her as a named driver, as they call it over here.
Ah, yeah, hold on a second.
She came back, she gave me a quote of 4,000 pounds.
What are you talking about?
The car only is a little bit more than that.
She's like, no, well, you know, we don't like ensuring anyone under 25.
Like, what the hell is this?
She said, well, it's the global credit crisis.
We have to be really careful.
Say, well, I have two cars insured with you already.
Combined, they're not even a quarter of that.
No, it's all about adding that third.
I said, all right, thank you very much.
Goodbye.
So I called up the dealer.
I said, you know, dude, here's the situation.
He said, you know what, why don't you just get it on your name?
And then add your daughter later, because it's a hassle
explaining she doesn't have her license yet,
and she only has a provisionals.
And okay, no problem.
And I call up the Renault insurance, right?
Renault itself.
Like that should be okay.
That's why I got the Jaguar insurance for the Jag.
So I call up, we go through everything, and you know,
she asked me all the, all my details.
And she says, what do I, are you employed?
I said, yeah, so what do you do?
So I'm managing director, which is kind of what I am over here
for BT Pod Show.
What's the name of the company, BT Pod Show?
What is it?
Oh, it's internet, audio and video.
We do television production.
I tried to make a little more understandable for.
So media and entertainment, yep.
Okay, hold on one second.
She comes back.
And she says, I'm sorry.
You've been declined because of your job.
You mean, said, well, we find that that sector of business
too risky to ensure what the hell is that?
I was dumbfounded, I don't even know what to say.
This is the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
So then I think, you know, why don't I go to confused.com,
which is what I see advertised all the time on television.
There you go, there's advertising working, TV advertising.
And I had no idea what confused.com was, but obviously,
you can get different quotes from different insurers.
So I start feeling this all these forms out.
There's a lot of them.
And I get to the very end.
And it says, okay, we want a username password, okay.
And then it says, you have to do a reminder.
So always, for the type of stuff, I have a password
and I know what the reminder is going to be.
And then those interesting line that caught my eye that said,
some sites that we'll be registering you with require
your mother's maiden name, I'm like, wait a minute.
These guys are going to go out and they're going to,
I guess, automatically, or they're probably
tied in three APIs or whatever, I'm going to give all
of this information, I just filled out.
Oh, this entire huge, oh, my life is in is what I just gave them.
I'm going to give that to hundreds of insurers.
I don't think so.
So cancel, got out of that.
Hopefully the stuff they captured before I submitted,
going from screen to screen has been destroyed.
But wow, what a scam that is.
No wonder those guys have enough money to buy
television commercial airtime.
If you're calling that much information,
that's a very valuable list.
Thank you very much.
Don't want to be that much on the grid.
I'm out of that.
Voting you guys off.
And so I call the detail back, says, you know,
I just tried test codes.
They're the biggest, that's easiest.
And so, you know, worked, I didn't say I was in media.
Although I was being truthful, I said,
well, you know, we're kind of in telecoms.
It's BT Podjo.
So there was no question about the occupation there,
but man, what a big pain in the ass.
And still the quote was reasonably high
because we have our international driver's licenses.
And in this case, Tesco or whatever they represent,
they will count that as just a zero experience driver,
even though I've been driving for over 25 years.
So the quote was still high.
But, you know, like 300 pounds.
But that's still a rageously high for a car
that has a 1.2 liter engine.
I mean, just, God.
Oh, anyway, those are just my temporary problems.
Not the problems of the world
because that's where we're here to solve my friends, right?
Well, let's start in, let's see,
why don't we move on down to Florida.
We've got Dan, our ex-pat from New York.
And, you know, this is a voice of Dan,
expat New Yorker here in Fort Lauderdale.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
I'm just wondering, fly boy,
already today's commercial airline is designed to operate
in an environment where oil is $100 a barrel.
And, are these FAA inspections and the grounding of flights
just to excuse perhaps to cover up
because of the whole agenda, the hidden agenda
of decreasing the lifestyle, the standard of living
of the US, a read-down and sing of little wide wealth
as a world directed by the powers that be dictated
by the Bush training regime.
Yeah.
I've been receiving these about.
No kidding.
Anyway, my two cents, have a good one.
No, thanks.
Alright.
Dan, expat New Yorker and Florida.
Yeah, I talked about this over the weekend with John C.
to Vorac on Noah Gendell, briefly.
Well, let me just try and address your question
so the people who listen to both shows
will get some new information.
You know, civil aviation started off
being subsidized by the male.
Okay, you remember that the first transatlantic flights
these planes were bringing male and it was air male.
And that was a really big deal
because now we had a really fast way to send letters
and packages, et cetera.
And so these flights were already pretty much paid for.
Let's just call it subsidized by the postal system.
Postal systems worldwide.
Many of them, which, of course, were government
controlled and owned, which most of them still are.
Although there are lots of alternatives
to the male system to the postal systems now.
And so in addition to male, they started to add on passengers.
But over the years, the actual male carriage,
you know, that whole business has been broken open.
We've got careers, we've got all kinds of alternatives.
And of course, aviation has, you know,
there's just so much more possibilities.
So we have, you know, the capabilities are so much more vast
that I would be surprised if if there's any U.S.
and of course government contracts are great, right?
They are always the best.
They're not necessary.
The sharpest market driven prices.
I would be surprised if there's any type of subsidy.
Probably not because, you know, these airlines
still trying to operate under,
you know, oh, man, it's such a tough issue.
You know, we need them, particularly in the United States.
And in Europe now too, we cannot live, you know,
business cannot take place without all of these reasonably
priced flights going all over the place.
And the only way they're going to be reasonably priced
is if they stay reasonably priced, you know,
so no, the airlines were absolutely not set up this,
and it's a spreadsheet business.
I've owned an airline.
An Air Operator Certificate, a very small airline
with only two helicopters, but I certainly know how it works.
And it's complete spreadsheet business.
You know exactly what is going to cost you per hour?
You know, your crew costs are the variables
are, of course, oil, which and fuel.
So a derivative, of course, of oil.
And yeah, that's outrageous.
And I believe that we are paying more,
but probably these airlines have been, you know,
cutting it really, really close for a long time.
Competition is not made it very easy in this regard.
And some would say maybe we should regulate again.
I don't know, man, but airlines sure are sucking.
Of course, we got the FAA's pulling their spot
in inspection, grounding entire fleets of aircraft.
Now, that's a whole separate issue.
That's between the FAA inspectors or the FAA, really.
And the government, they've got to get their act together.
They've got to open up a little closer dialogue.
Because, you know, those types of inspections,
that type of work, it should just be built in.
You know, if they're already skimping on that,
then, of course, they're bankrupt.
If they're not already going bankrupt,
then we've got British airways.
Oh, man, what a mess.
Terminal five is, you know, they don't expect
to even bring over the rest of their long haul flights
until June messing up everything over
to terminals one through four at Heathrow.
No, it's an absolute mess.
And I think what's happening now in the US
is probably the only right thing to happen is,
you know, you've got to have carriers going out of business.
But of course, the existing carriers have to have
a business model that will take them, you know,
into those new markets that can help them expand.
And I just don't think they have it.
And, you know, we're going to be paying a lot more
if we want this convenience of flying.
I just don't see any other way.
It's either that or we go to a, you know,
government sponsorship or subsidies.
It's probably, when you think about it economically,
it's probably a great time to get into the airline business.
Oh, hey, Vey.
Let's see, last time we spoke together here
on the Charlie, we were talking about the protest
in San Francisco, which took place last week,
people trying to douse the Olympic flame.
Of course, we had the pro, to bet protesters
and the pro Chinese, converging on the streets of San Francisco.
And I guess, you know, there was something else,
what I read today.
Oh, my point on Friday, at least, was that, you know,
we're so gung-ho to take up someone else's issue.
Also really important, but look at all the things
we have at home, you know, we're at war,
we're in economic crisis, you know,
where our family units are in crisis.
There's all kinds of stuff that certainly could be improved.
And, you know, by the way, I don't want to be a downer.
I mean, it's not like it's all that bad, but still.
It seems like there's a lot of stuff we could be working on
at home, and we're just not doing any of it.
You know, how long have I been calling for people
to protest the government here in the UK?
Can't get anyone to move yet.
It seems that it was very easy for a whole bunch of people
to create a flash mob and do a Rick roll
with Liverpool Street Station the other week.
I'll put a link in the show notes to that BBC news item
about that.
I mean, that's not just, that drives me nuts.
It's like, oh, we can all do a Rick roll,
which is fantastic, and it made the news.
It's on YouTube.
This is exactly the type of thing you want,
but there's no payoff, it's dumb, there's no payload.
So how can we take the concept of getting everyone
to do a Rick roll, and then put some payload in there,
like, hey, you know, by the way, Gordon Brown,
or whoever you want to protest against, oh, man,
we need to, where's Abby Hoffman?
He's dead, isn't he?
Crap, how we need to do the new steal this book
when we need to help people to explain
how we can really get some good protesting.
I got to think about it too.
It just drives me mad.
It drives me absolutely mad.
Now, apparently in San Francisco,
this is protesting for things other than what's going on
in San Francisco or in the rest of the world
seems to be pretty much the norm.
I had, and this is San from Palo Alto.
So you were talking about the protests
you were seeing over the Olympic flame in San Francisco.
So what's interesting about that, you know,
you were upset that they were protesting over something
like Olympic torture, the Olympics instead
of something that is really important.
Well, you have to understand is that that's San Francisco.
San Francisco likes to protest over anything.
They protest over, and one of the reasons
why I don't read this San Francisco Chronicle
is they love protesting and complaining over every little
minutiae you could imagine.
And for the most part, no one listens to it at all.
Anywhere in the world except for other people in San Francisco.
So I agree that Sergio is really great
and they should be protesting over things that are closer
to home and matter a lot more about.
But they never done it before.
So maybe they did it in the 60s, but they haven't
in the last 20 years, and certainly not since I lived here.
Anyways, good luck, great hair, whatever, I'll be with you
and bye.
Yeah.
I, that's funny because I did hear a couple other people
mentioned that to me.
So that's San Francisco, man.
That's not typical any town USA.
Maybe it just has to get a lot worse before people will
wake up to it, maybe that's what it is.
Maybe we really have to really, I mean, I can see this
coming to a head, this global financial crisis is not just
something on the news, okay?
It's not, look, it's even affecting me.
I, people don't want to give me insurance because they can't
take any risk anymore.
They have to have low risk.
And so they're tightening up everything.
You know, that's why I get a 4,000 pound quote on a 6,000 pound
car.
It's just outrageous.
So maybe it has to really come down to it.
It has to really come down to a crunch where all really
pissed off.
The world bank, it's it today, I think, called, that there's
a worldwide crisis with the food.
And they handed out $10 million, where was it?
I had to hear the handed out $10 million to a Haiti, I
think.
Let me see, I'll just bring up this news article because I've
found that fascinating that how can we still have famine
in the world?
Can that just drive you nuts?
Crap, okay, this link broke.
But I saved it, too.
Now, well, anyways, the, the point is the world bank is calling
for immediate action on deepening global food crisis.
And that's mainly because of the cost of stuff like
rice and wheat.
You watch, and it's going to start affecting YouTube.
Start counting your money at the end of the month.
And when everyone's ready to party and get down and yell and
make some noise, I'll be here.
You know, people in other countries know exactly what to do.
And they know exactly what kind of feeling you have to have.
And they understand the vibe because they've been living in
less prolific circumstances as we have.
I am just shortly from conclude, Mexico.
A long time easier, I just go to tell you a few things about your
goodbyes.
The daily source code, you say, leave your guide with passion and
your freedom.
I think you need to change that.
Okay, so just, because I've already heard him say this all,
you know, he's from Mexico, he's talking real fast.
What he's saying is instead of your usual sign off, which is
live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom, you should try the
follow-up.
Now, for if you're led with passion and fight for your freedom or
demand your freedom or spend up for your freedom, something like that.
The way things are going, he's not looking to do it.
At the end of that, the thing I wanted to tell you is that the
future is on the third of the world countries.
Because our government, it's also spying on us, but they don't have
to turn out that technology or the money to do it a bit
right away.
And you can find the fear, cancun, male, 52 to kids.
Love you, no, almost great hair, hope you win, folder.
Darling, thank you.
Thanks to appreciate the folder coming too.
Yeah, so there's a very good point.
It's kind of like, it was a jenga.
Is that the name of the game where you pull those little blocks out and you put it
on top?
That's exactly what's happening.
The third world countries have a lot more, you know, they have growth,
everything's ahead of them.
And so, you know, you pull one of those third world country blocks out and you put it on
top, guess what's happening, to happen is that new us, so
called at the top of the, at the top of the chain, you're going to start
moving down.
And that's okay.
But I think we could equal it out a little bit more.
Oh, it's going to be really interesting to be in the minority living in
underdeveloped country.
I've always wondered what that's going to be like.
We're all going to find out.
I had a bit of a map from Game's Weasel coming up on this show.
We have a review of Rainbow Six Vegas 2.
Metal Gear Solid portable opt platform, the PSP.
I'll show you how to fix the next box 360,
sort of, and you can win copies of Viking, battle pass guard on the 360 as well.
That's all against Weasel.com.
Games Weasel and also games Weasel TV,
and check it out for sure if you want to know what's going on.
Particularly in the UK, I think we're working on a U.S. version of that as well,
with U.S. release dates that the show is really, really kicking.
So I did want to mention that even though I had a hard time here,
comes, you can feel it.
Even though I had a really hard time getting my, my car insurance,
life insurance on the other hand, which at the rate I'm going,
I'll need some, that's really easy.
In fact, I can get 70% off on life insurance.
And so can you, if you use my code at Acute Quote.
So if you don't have life insurance, go get informed, okay?
And by the way, no one's called in about this.
So either you're all buying it, or you're not investigating,
you're not even thinking about it.
And I think it particularly, if you're the median age of the charted listener,
you might want to have a quick look at what life insurance really means,
and what it can do for you.
And particularly for the beneficiaries, because of course,
it'll do nothing for you once you're dead.
I love selling life insurance.
Go to Acute Quote.com slash dsc online.
The dog's going to need some life insurance, if you didn't shut up,
or, and this is kind of cool, we set up a custom phone number
for you to call.
It's 1-800-410-7214, obviously, for US residents only,
Acute Quote.com.
I want to come back to the China Tibet thing, but first,
and I'm thinking about this throughout the entire prep session
in the morning this morning, because it really is only for Wednesday,
that I'm supposed to be playing this call, but I'm pretty sure
that I'm not going to be able to do a show Wednesday,
and I'm very worried that the person who this call is intended for
may not hear this show until Wednesday.
So I decided to play it now, so it may come through a day early,
but it's such a beautiful thing that I wanted to make sure that it got through.
Hello, my name's Susan, and I'm the second Dutch vice
of Dutch sales guy, you please, and Germany.
Okay, so this is Susan.
I love this, the pregnant wife.
I love the way she loves it, the official pregnant wife,
of sales guy, you, who lives in Germany.
I'll just listen to your voice, Susan.
I think we need some naked pregnant pictures,
and she's calling in.
I was surprised when I heard this, but it's really nice.
I think it would be some noise, but I'm not sure if these kind of messages
didn't hear a show, but I thought I'd give it a try.
This coming Wednesday, April 16, is my husband's 31st birthday,
and because he's a big son of your show, I thought it would be a great surprise if I would appear on it.
Then I would like to say to him, Lisa, I can't even ask that.
He's dead, much A&F to be at it, and that's for all the way from a Sudan
and this one or last, I was right away to this.
You have it to best, and that's also not to really sound about you.
Bigger this way, I know this is a bit of a lost minutes request,
but I hope you might be able to squeeze this into your show on Wednesday.
Thank you, Adam.
Nah, Susan, that is so incredibly sweet.
You know, hey, guys, does your wife do that for you?
You know, she went through the trouble of figuring out what this guy is talking about,
because of course you're saying, oh, is this into the Charlie,
this, the Charlie, that, she's probably at home while I'm out.
The podcast, I don't give a shit.
What is he talking about?
And so she takes the time to listen to the show.
She gets the phone numbers from the show, no, she calls in.
She's already, you know, she understands kind of the format of the show,
so she's listened to it, and she says the most beautiful thing to him.
She's even thanking him for all the things she's done.
He's done for her over the years on his birthday, which is Wednesday.
I'd say, you, you are in for a big ass, lay my friend, congratulations,
and happy birthday for all your chucklehead friends here at the Daily Source Code.
Here's a song for you to love birds to get into the mood together from Crystal Gale.
When you go, I'll describe all that long, say that it's all true,
and don't it make my bad eyes tell me no secrets tell me some lies,
give me no reason to give me out of the box tell me love and don't let me cry.
Say anything, but don't say goodbye, I've been meaning to treat you bad,
you know, just what I have, but I'm in now,
and don't take my brown eyes, don't make my brown eyes, don't make my brown eyes,
don't it make my brown eyes, don't it make my brown eyes, don't it make my brown eyes,
Don't it make my brown eyes, don't it make my brown eyes
This is a daily source code
On December 1, 2007, the portal opened.
Hell's Army came forth.
The demon said on world domination.
No one is safe.
No one is free from the wrath of the underworld.
Except for one.
One man can save the world.
One hero can save mankind.
One son of a bitch who can kick some serious demoness.
He's faceless.
He's fearless.
King.
His black shadow.
From the mind of Davey Patti of Bogothar, Steve Sailor.
And brought to you by Pod Show.
Comes a story where the only thing standing in between total destruction.
And peace on earth is the craziest and most kickass some of a bitch to ever wear a costume.
Where the superpowers meet the supernatural.
One to learn more.
Head to Steve Sailor.net now.
And subscribe today.
Black Shadow.
Way to be finds the demons first.
Before the demons find you.
Steve, the official albino of the Charlie.
Go over there and check out Steve Sailor.net.
That sounds pretty good.
Of course, that was Nemcoff.
He always sounds good.
I just wish I had more time.
These days on my flights, my transatlantic flights.
I'm just sleeping.
I got no time to listen to anything.
I try.
I listen to a couple of audio books, audio podcasts, books,
audio books.
I guess I called.
And I'll just wind up falling asleep with your buds jammed in my ear.
I wonder if the whole book plays out.
Did I actually hear it?
You know, it's not in my ears or clothes.
But that register in my brain will I be able to pull out passages from these books?
Interesting question, huh?
I'm surprised.
Come extra blogger didn't call this one.
Being our official EU correspondent.
Alan, the Britain Basel sent in this wonderful piece of news,
which I presume is correct to EU Parliament.
Nearly throughout a vote that would have banned files
sharing by private individuals and decided against
banning copyright abuses from the internet.
This, of course, is a three strikes your out rule.
With the idea is, if you're caught once caught twice,
the third time you get caught fasharing illegal files,
or sparing files illegally because it's copyrighted material,
you would then forever be cut off from the internet.
You would not be able to get internet service.
It was a very narrow vote.
314 to 297.
Wow.
297 idiots still thought that was a good idea.
But the way this has been instituted, or similar laws
are in place if anyone's in France.
If you listen to the show, call it.
Let me know exactly what the rules are.
If you do have this three strikes your out law.
But it looks like for now, for now.
We're in good shape.
Let me see, what is it end up here?
It's expected that you'd expect to have this,
oh, this is France.
Of course it's expected to take advantage of it coming
presidency of the European Union.
And the second half of this year to have another crack
crack it, creating this law. Okay, let's be on the lookout folks, because France is going
to try it. They're going to try and push their law through to the rest of us, and clearly
this is not a good idea. And if they do push something like through like that, you know,
well, then maybe I want to have some files banned. Maybe I'll call all kinds of stuff copyright
that you can't touch. Ah, an crazy world, aren't we? Hey, let's come back to the Chinese
thing because the PD love sent in something really cool that I just wanted to play for you guys.
Yeah, and PD love from the daddy cast and love house radio. And I don't know, can I be
called the official introologist on the show? Yeah, I know. Yeah, Louis, the judge.
Anyway, I wanted to comment on the push to stop buying products made in China. If you're
indeed going to protest China's oppression of Tibet. Yeah, and before you get into it, a lot of
people misunderstood what I was saying. You know, I got a lot of emails saying, you know, you're a
Mr. Gadget guy. What are you talking about? You're a horrible example. Look, I'm yelling at myself here
as well, right? If we really want to protest what China's doing, then yeah, the Olympics is a
great way to get some public stuff on the public forum, but really the way to do it is to boycott
products that are coming out of China. And unfortunately, stuff like your iPod comes out of China.
But I just picture a big pile of iPods on fire, like the burning bras of the 60s.
But a question, who's actually going to have the guts to do this or the the pocket to do this?
I mean, what are the alternatives? You know, you mentioned the Taiwan iPods,
well, that would be one alternative, but there's the older ones. Well, the hold on a second,
PD. So that would be Apple's decision, right? And I'm sure that Taiwan can do perfect manufacturing.
Yeah, they did the first gen iPods, but I don't think that's, you know, that all their iPods
were look like first generation iPods. But it's Apple, you know, it's like, so you're right,
your point is, who's going to boycott Apple? Can we really stay away from that new iPhone 3G that's
coming out? No, we probably can. Are there other MP3 players made in the US or somewhere else?
Yes, most definitely. I'm sure there are. If not, let's start making some.
You know, what about our PCs? How much of that of our just our computers are made in China?
So all of it. I just wonder, you know, can the anti-China protesters give up? Can they give up
convenience and the investments in what they've already got? Can they give up the convenience of
finding things? Once they decide to stop buying Chinese products? Hey, kids, he's talking to you, okay?
And to me, because this is the question. Are we really willing to look at the label on everything
and say, hey, it's coming from China? I'm out. Because that's the simplest. That's within your
power. You don't have to go on the street. You don't have to demonstrate. You don't have to yell.
You don't have to cause unrest. At least not civil unrest because this will hurt the entire
system. Just stop buying products from China and tell the companies that produce products in China
that you're not going to be their customer anymore. It's not easy. But I bet you're most of
your all-talk. Or did too many people just, you know, take up the cause for the cause, you know,
say, oh, I'm protesting the China for Tibet, but don't really know what all that mean. Yeah, I call
that the Nup the Gay Wales syndromes. And, you know, are they willing to trade in their luxury for the
cause? I remember, back when I was in college, a comedian came in, stood up on stage and said,
who out here is a vegetarian or a member of PETA or anything that's one girl enthusiastically
waved her hand? He was taking you stand up for a minute, you stood up, he goes, yeah, nice leather
belt. So it just kind of, I think sometimes people state their fur cause, but really don't have
the heart behind it that it takes to stand up for that cause. But anyway, just wanted to throw
in my two cents of that and to see what you thought about options to actually boycott products from
China and how that could be accomplished. One other Nup, I have your attention on the Daddycast 146.
I had a special co-host and with CC Chapman, we had a chance to talk a little bit about fatherhood
and so forth. Yeah, I think it was a great time and hey, if you ever get a chance, feel free to let
me know. We'll get you on the show as well to talk about all of your challenges as a father.
Yeah, sure thing. Anyway, great hair, hope you win everything else. And I guess I've never really
given you my stats. I'm a dad 38 years old. I'm a general manager of a software development company
specializing in the brokerage industry. So some of the financial costs are really interesting and
actually makes sense. Anyway, that is my bio. So in short form, I will talk to you later at
him. Bye, bye. Hi, man. Thank you. Appreciate the thought. Absolutely. And I'm glad you brought it up, man.
That's totally totally spot on. Now, I would have to participate in this as well.
Okay. That's why the first thing I want to find out was what's going on between China and Tibet.
But you know what, when you look at the grand scale of things, you know, all of the things we're accusing
the Chinese of. We're doing too. You know, we totally have slave, slave labor here.
Slavery and here is well, probably. But in the US, we detained people unlawfully.
There's all kind of, we do all the same things. Except we have different words for it.
You know, we invade other people's countries. So, you know, is it
popcorn the kettle black? And maybe the best way is to change behaviors to show it through
leadership and to do it, you know, to lead by example. So I would love to hear from you guys.
Are we willing to give up all of our products from China or not? You've got the voicemail lines
right there on the in the show notes at dailysourceco.com and at curry.com.
I'll do nothing. The Charlie said, love you. No home move. I mean, it's big here.
Oh, they were there. Okay. Catch you later.
Oh, a chemist, chemist. That's the way you pronounce it. Sorry.
Yeah. Unfortunately, that promotion is coming to an end. Today is actually the last day.
You can go to pachowoffers.com slash n-800-10. You can just find it at pachowoffers.com.
And you want to use my DSC checkout code for a 15% discount. I was actually I was playing with the
N-800-10 over the weekend. For two reasons. One, I wanted to, you know, I was looking for a way
to get my aircraft flight tracks on to Google Earth and there's an application called Memo
Mapper. There's a couple of them, actually. That's why I was fooling around testing a few out.
And of course, this has a built-in GPS receiver. So it's exactly what I need. You know, I
easy to get the file off into Google Earth. So I was a mess around with that. And then I really
got back into Gizmo. And Gizmo is a VoIP client. And it uses the Open Standard and IETF standard,
which is the SIP protocol SIP. Excuse me. Which is, you know, so basically Gizmo is, you know,
a version of software that you can use with the SIP protocol. There's tons of service providers
and software that you can use and install. And I have to say, I'm pretty impressed. There's
lots of really good implementations of this spec and of the software that really surpasses Skype
and quality, which is why I'm interested in it. Because of course, you know, I'm doing this show
weekly with the, with the VORAC, no agenda.podshow.com. And, you know, so you have all the, in this
particular software Gizmo, which is available for Mac PC for the internet tablet from Nokia,
even on your, my E61I, you can get calling out minutes, you know, get inbound phone lines,
it has chat, it even has video, which is on the internet, what a great implementation. It does video
and voice, you know, spectacularly, even on the built-in mic and speakers with no echo. And I was
really, I was playing with the Candy Man Luke. Yeah, let me rephrase that. I was playing around
with Gizmo, calling Candy Man Luke. And I was, I was quite surprised. I'm going to keep
by using that for a little while. And what I'm looking for now is a client that I can actually plug
into my, into my setup. The Gizmo itself doesn't do it. I have to be able to choose a different
sound device and have to be able to route it through Jack router. If that means anything to anybody,
you'll pick up on it. You'll send me an email, I hope. But most of these clients aren't,
aren't good enough in a crash or they're not fully developed. So I'm still kind of hunting around
for stuff. But in general, just as a voiceover IP client and system, I'm very impressed, far superior
to Skype, although of course, of course, no one uses it, which is another downside.
Let me see. I got one more here that I just wanted to play. This is regarding drop.io,
which I've been cleaning it out. It's not an archive, even though it does have a handy
blog type format, but it's just a great way to put files up. Drop me a note, send me a link to
something. It's a perfect place to do all that. And I'll put it into the show notes regularly now.
It's drop.io slash daily source code. And Eric added something that I left up there. You definitely
need to check out. Yeah, I'm Eric from Portland. I just want to draw your attention to it. Email
exempts you today. Thursday. On the sub-prime mortgage message, it brings to a Google notebook
and 45 slides of little stick figures. And it's almost yet how a sub-prime mortgage is originated.
How it becomes a AAA paper. And why we're all fucked. I think I like it. And click over to it
and see if you want to add it to the show. Love you, Ben. Bye.
Good evening, I would like to report on the state over the war against American people.
We're mounting a sustained campaign to crack down on every American and every person of every
faith in every nation and to bring them to justice. All missions are being executed according
to plan without warning or provocation. Americans are being swept up in the international
drag net. Thousands of FBI agents drawn to 12 of other citizens here in abroad. It has everything
to do with aid and evil. And murder in prison. America's strong strong strong strong strong.
I see a message from the government like every day. I'll watch it and listen and call them all
fuckers. They want to be about a summer or whatever. Pitching me behind the scam I said never.
You went through a hard tool, so just beaten. I'll stay committed, gives up to that loose commission.
It's all about a fight and never state my control. And all about the battle for your body,
mine and soul. And now open you don't tell your mind, so they shape you. Don't forget they made a
slave, gave a say, then rapist. Another push season, mean another war for profit. All the
secrets of the public never fit to stop. The aluminum and nutty triple six all connected.
Throw the post, take control of race and take elections. It's the stolen bones, remakes and kill
committing. See the dragon get shitty or in every city.
Now ask yourself who's the one with the most again. All I love and motherfuckers couldn't
stand his name. Not even Dickens waving flags like they all stay mine. Everybody got opinions
but don't know the time, because America's been took. It's playing the seat. The oldest
trick in the book is making enemies. A phone to evil, so a couple makings to his dirt. And take
okay your freedom, knocking low in search. And then change one more fellow people locked in prison.
He's picked still beat us, but it seems we forget. But I remember folks that pimple
hide his devil's do it. Fucked truly, honey. Asked y'all a while he's doing. We in the streets
hall a jail to the people. Follow, fuck, wave your flags, bring his back and sit a knees.
Boy, oh, blood, honey, make these killers ride cold. I'm suspicious through with five people dying
never told. It's all the part of playing cards, so you think we need them. I'm being ash
cross, take away your rights to freedom and bail goodness to the sickness of these
tiktakers. Hope you want to stay in the time, brother, because this makes you.
So now you ask and why my records always come the same. Keep it real in the fillers,
motherfuck a blingin'. My eyes seem to gory at a comin' up the beast. So every story, every word I'm saying,
fuck peace. If you could witness to your lumen, I'd be by the count. Don't be surprised. These
levels that I'm talkin' bow. You think a couple thousand lies mean shit to killers. And they got spread
of God. We're the ones ain't no villain. Or any other world they think to demonize a country. And
don't tear it threaten us. I prove we're waiting slumping. So I'm a sayin' for the record. We don't
want that plan. Ain't no one in the country, took upon a head of hand in. Just a way to keep
your scary. So you think you need them. Praise and push, why not kill or take away your freedom.
How many apples got discovered, but ignore the symptoms. Nick is talkin' loud, but ain't nobody
saying shit. And we're the four of them ain't gone. I was all in the first. That's why I'm spitting
side of night, each and every verse. I see the corn loud, poopin' Harris, make a count. I see
them be the fifth, each and every session now. And why I stand burn, see the public by it. I see the
profile, and see the media is compliant. The war's good for business, see the vicious, make a
safe. I hope you understand the time, but the cutters' rage.
You can't imagine how much money they've spent trying to silence. Good people who put their lives
on the line to fight for change. Hell yeah, I think this is going to be the new anthem.
You know what, if you have a podcast, you must play this song. The first example I've heard of
someone actually just laid it out there saying it in every single lyric throughout the entire track.
That is Paris. What would you do? What would you do, my friends? That's the question
and we'll be talking about it later on this week. So until we speak again, email me,
adamotpodshow.com, drop some files into the drop drop.io slash daily source code. And of course,
daily source code.com is where you can find the show notes for this program. Until we speak
in next time, my friends, live your life with passion and fight for your freedom.