It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
And now the man willing to march on DC all the way from the UK, it's Adam Curry and the
DSC 723.
I think that's what I did, drink out and buy me
When am I on the road?
Love, love, hate, hate
Love, love, hate, hate, hate, hate
Everything, we'll never run between
Those are the my interests, need, affordability
And the war has took us by, I'm the world that has built us in time
Set the head of heart, take it from major heart
Can't I do, girls to get through to you?
I can't tell that you, crazy
The standard here, about what's the normal
This, you tell me is, you tell me I'm going without your help
Add some๑wwSh, get some gold
No, if you're me, if you're me, believe me
Okay see
Yes, see
I got my bubble came out
I can't be vision is all
I got the violence in hand if I'm too real is all
I love this great nation
I got my fish, I got my hair, I got so far away
This dance for me, you see it's in the club
Really like to feel nice
You see it's on the floor
You'll be watching all night, we need a look about it
Oh, sit down
Boy, you turn me inside
And round me round
Oh, sit down
Boy, you turn me inside
And round, round
Round, upside down, you turn me
You give a love instinctively
Round and round, you turn me
I say to me, you respect for me
I'm upside down, you turn me
And you give a love instinctively
Round and round, you turn me
Say to me, you respect for me
I got the problem, you know
I got my fish, I got your hope
I got my fish, I got my fish
I got my violence in hand if I'm too real is all
I got the problem, you know
Isn't it so easy to teach?
I got my problems, you know
I got the intuition
You're so holy, I got matter
I got the demon all the time
I asked you just come home
I got my violence in hand if I'm too real
I got my violence in hand if you're being lost
I got the idea
I got it, you turned me inside
And round, you turn me inside
Man, all's as good as this
I stradion, ageal
I'm upside down
Mm, ah
Come on
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh,
Françaisiantly
THEY ARE H mio
Dear god!
DJ Lobster Bus kicks it off
With a hood
What is he saying here in his show notes?
Not since you were saved for Africa
So I had such a collection of mega stars
nuggets been assembled for musical cars
Michael Jackson, Paul McCartney, Rihanna, Nellie Frutato,
nine-inch nails, Mary J. Blides, Dan Ross, Rick James,
and the temptations.
Hick an off-dirty source code episode number 723.
Everybody how you doing?
Late in getting the show started again today, because I got some goodies
came in and I had to hook him up and configure him.
And of course, that screwed up just about everything.
You know, I've been working on the ultimate set up
to have the, like this ending here.
I've got my fist, I've got my pair, I've got some followers.
You know, yeah, working on, uh,
working on setting up the ultimate all-in-one studio for portability.
And I told you that I'm using Ableton Live.
I'm using soundbite as a cart rack, but Ableton Live
because of the low latency factor, because of, um,
you know, the power of the MacBook Pro, essentially.
It all handles it so I can listen to my voice and real-time processing.
And I told you I was really getting into this MIDI stuff using a MIDI controller
to control the software.
And so I got a, um, a beautiful, um, just in love with this device already.
A beautiful little, little MIDI control, um, well, they call the control surface.
But I think this is a control device.
It's, um, from Thader Fox.
How you can find them at Thader Fox.de.
And essentially, it's a, it's a little mixer.
It fits almost on the palm of your hand.
It's, uh, it's shaped just right.
I'm going to put a link in the show notes.
You got to see this thing.
It's shaped just right.
It has nice little angles.
So you can, you know, so the, the way you'd expect a mixer to be,
it has, uh, one, two, three, four, six channels.
It has a cross-fader, which I won't use.
And it also has a number of color-coded buttons.
So I can use those to fire up, uh, different, uh, sound effects or songs
within Ableton Live.
Really loving it.
But of course, I had to configure a new MIDI interface.
And I got a, a little, uh, what is this, uh, an Ederol MIDI interface.
I did a little geeky here, but folks who give a shit, uh, the UM-1 EX.
Uh, so essentially, there's just one wire, uh, going out of this fader Fox into my computer.
I've got the headphones plugged in.
Got the microphone plugged in and I'm done.
And see now when I move this little fader here, kind of, uh,
here, I'll move this up and down and, uh, controls the volume.
And I can see the, uh, the fader indicator on the screen moving.
What was really weird is when you start to configure MIDI devices and you're novice like myself,
um, you know, you have to teach the MIDI device, what controls it's going to handle.
And everything you add to it essentially adds up to the processor, doing more work,
both with MIDI, but also with audio.
And if you have another, uh, MIDI device or interface that, uh, that isn't attached.
It might be looking for that and it could, anything.
All of these different moves can essentially raise your, uh, your processor speed.
And then able to live starts to crap out and so yeah.
And I hunt. What's that?
Oh, thank you.
Peanut butter.
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, peanut butter sandwich. Thank you.
Um, oh, no, I should probably lower this threshold a little bit.
That was the lady Patricia who just walked in with some nice,
set peanut butter sandwiches.
Love it. Hey, happy Valentine's Day. By the way, if you're listening to the show on February the 14th,
don't forget his Valentine's Day. There's something you should be doing.
Uh, I spent this morning of Valentine's Day, um, at the dentist.
Man, the older I get, the more this should just starts the fall apart.
I hate it. Anyway, so it's not entirely configured properly. And I've, you know, it was just getting so late
that I figured I just got to get going. Maybe I'll be able to make the show a little bit shorter today.
Just because I don't want to be messing around. But you guys are in effect kind of guinea pigs
for this episode 723 of the Charlie, which of course is coming to you from the curry manner and the
affluent suburb of Surinone is gilford. Crap weather out today. It's, uh, we've got to overcast
guys. It's going to stay. This is what came in from continental Europe. They had that weather yesterday.
And I did do about it. Anyway, good day to be inside playing around with some toys, huh?
Yeah. I had them this is Stephen Boston. I did do demographic survey on the website and I found out that
there is no option for zero kids. So thanks to you. I now have one kid and I hope that you're helping
to pay child support on that. So I'm male 41 on a teacher. So I guess you call that middle income.
And, uh, let's see, I have great hair. I really hope I win and I love you, meet it.
All right. Then, oh, well, thank you. I'm sorry about that. I fixed that by the way. That should be
working now. It was kind of dumb. Everyone had to have at least one child on the survey. You should
take a look at it. It's very interesting. Still, I'd have to say predominantly a male audience, but
a couple of very interesting female listeners in there. And of course, that's the only reason I did the
whole damn survey. You know, Adam, Nathan Centaroza, um, 27 today, uh, male obviously, uh,
Mac user folder, but until, um, whether they're demographic, you want nothing. Get to it.
Uh, 6.6. Whoa. Um, libertarian. Anyway, I was trying to work with Podshow, subscribe to
your op-salt show and I can't find a way to subscribe to it in iTunes. Um, Podshow seems to be
all self-contained and I can't find any fucking feet. Um, so, uh, well, um, love you, no homo, uh,
great hair, hope you win. Um, whatever. I hope you want.
Emma, bye, bye, bye, bye. Dude, I hate it when people don't look. If you go to op-salt.podshow.com
right there on the home page, you'll see there's an RSS link. And of course, if you click on any of the
episodes, you'll see RSS links, links for iTunes, links and their icons. It looks like an icon, uh,
for iTunes. It's not that hard to recognize. But yes, in V3 in the new version of Podshow, which, uh,
I think we're going into close beta in next week or two. It seems to be moved along quite
quickly. All the functionality is built. Now we're strapping on the UI, which, of course, is always
the hardest part. Um, oh, we're going to be surfacing those links, uh, a hell of a lot better,
so you can, uh, so you can find it. Okay, so I have to call up screaming at me.
It's all football, man. Here's one for all the gigs. You know who you are.
Every one is so vulnerable. I'm there busy, except for me. The world wide web is so insecure,
town aside, but I'm so glad. I am fireworld in every single way, nerds can't bring me down.
And I run anti-virus every single day. Yes, nerds can't bring me down. No, no,
ain't gonna bring me down today.
To all you moops, you're delirious, your brows are closed. You're so exfoliating, yeah. You're trying
hard to fix that awful mess that used to be. Your precious piece, see to you let that
virus in, but I'm unhackable no matter what they say. Let's get and bring me down.
My fishing filter told me that this is not eBay. Yes, nerds can't bring me down. Oh, no,
ain't gonna bring me down today. You get your money, space, head, to get your money.
There's gonna come anti-virus, you're delirious, your brows are closed. You're delirious, your brows are closed.
It's all matter, I'm again, you gotta lose, clean in your face. You'll be sees a big disgrace.
Fire since he comes back, you probably should have bought a knife. I am fire walled and never sing away.
Let's get and bring me down. Oh, no, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I've got spyware blast. Turing in my train. Yes, please get bring me down. Oh, no, no, oh, oh, don't
Oh, how beautiful is that, huh?
For all the nerds.
That's Bob Riching.
I've been out of to call the Fump Unhackable.
You'll find out on the Podscape Music Network a night.
Of course it is.
Today.
Of course it's a cover, which is always a gray area, but under the auspices of fair use for satire.
I'm sure it's going to be okay.
I hope.
You know what?
I don't know if you're listening to the track, or maybe even DJ Lobster does at the opening of the show.
With the say, say, say, isn't the all-star jam?
I could hear some anomalies going on with the audio.
So I'm going to make today show a little bit short because it's just going to drive me nuts.
Hey, if I'm paying attention to it.
Oh, this is really good.
So this is kind of cool.
It's been going on for this is the, to just 720, 720.
So the fourth that actually within three episodes, we were able to solve a pretty interesting problem.
The one of the chuckleheads had with his Nokia, not the 810, but the 800, but he did have the new internet tablet software.
And his flash plug-in apparently stopped world flash.
The hell is going on.
Stop.
His flash didn't work on his browser anymore.
And we couldn't figure it out.
And we had another chucklehead call up and give him some advice.
And check and see if the plug-ins had mysteriously become disabled and low on behold.
Thank you so much for the fix.
Work with a dream.
Turn the plug-in back on.
Drop rate flash and work like a dream.
You want to talk to Nokia people and tell them the text and not be such asses.
I mean, the guy I'm technical at Facebook and told me, well, you're screwed.
We're not doing any updates.
So live with it.
That's quite literally what the guy told me.
And all he had to do was tell me to turn on the plug-in.
Thank you very much.
You have a call for a game with the fix.
I really appreciate that.
Yeah, man.
That's how it's supposed to work.
Absolutely.
You send it in.
We fix all the problems.
And let me see.
I got a whole bunch of count coming about the Snoop Dogg nation notice the United Kingdom.
The surveillance state.
I'm thinking, now, I'm not going to play those.
I want to save those for tomorrow.
Or maybe on Monday, I'm going to San Francisco next week.
So it'll be the true test of the mobile setup on the road.
Oh, well, I really want to tell a port.
It's funny because when you think about flying that distance, it's like 10 hour flight.
You think about it's like, oh, man, it's going to take a whole day.
It really doesn't take a day because you leave around 11 am and you arrive around 130 pm.
So you don't really miss all that much out of the day kind of because of the times on changes.
And then actually when I'm flying, I kind of enjoy it because it's so nice and calm.
But, you know, it's kind of sucks.
Particularly, I just don't want to go.
I want to be with my family, my girls.
We got to.
We got some stuff going on with pod shows.
We got to rock and roll now.
We've got to start doing it while the iron is still hot.
So I don't know what you're doing for Valentine's Day for your loved one.
A lot of people think it's just a commercial bunch of who we.
And so they don't participate in it, but I'm a sucker that way.
And actually Christina gave us a Valentine's card this morning, which was very sweet.
You know, I think for, well, Christina's 17.
So for at least 10 years, maybe 12 Patricia's always bought her a Valentine's card.
And she didn't do it this year.
Patricia bought me one, of course.
And then.
So she didn't buy one for Christina and Christina had bought one for us with the best mom and dad in the world.
I'm like, oh, that's so cool.
So of course, Patricia felt like shit was just pretty funny.
All right, so we're going to play Valentine's song for you.
And this is actually, you know, this is, I told you it was really easy.
If you want to get your song played on the daily source code, all you got to do is
preferably be female.
Cute is good as well.
And do some good songs and send me a comment.
That's that easy literally.
What the hell is that?
Oh, man.
I got the wrong one.
Hold on a second.
I hate it when that happens.
It was all set up to hold on.
This is the right.
This is the one I want.
Whoa.
No, that was interesting.
Huh.
I was dragging a file onto the sound by the application.
Oh, this is turning out to be a real geek fest.
And I passed over Ableton Live.
And boy, didn't like that.
I thought it had to import a song just because I passed over it.
Sorry about that.
Okay.
I got a bit into it.
Basically, I had to restart and pick this up.
So you missed a minute of my life.
Doesn't that suck, huh?
Hey Adam.
It's a little straight from Holland.
It's when I was always singing and dancing and listening to music and loving your show.
Now, I got to tell you something.
A few weeks ago, I was around in my bike.
When my head up in the clouds, all in love, and I got this melody.
That doesn't she sound awesome.
Doesn't she sound full of energy and yet something very naughty behind those words?
Mind.
And I just sang a little bit.
Got a few lyrics in my head.
And I got home to a friend of mine, Karen.
And she was just playing a little bit guitar and I started to sing.
And we're just jamming, just playing around, fooling around.
And we wrote this great love song.
It's called Amazing.
And it is amazing.
It's got a whole love vibe going on.
Yeah, baby.
But before you're going to play, I just have to say,
Will you please stop sending me a request about naked pictures?
Okay, I really don't like it.
And lady, just call me.
She doesn't like it either.
So you better stop, all right?
Okay.
So I would love it if you would play the song.
And you'll love it too.
I'm sure.
For everyone else who's going to love it,
check it out on LuluMusic.com.
Amazing.
Oh, by the way.
Yeah.
Love you.
And I'm mean it right here.
I'm going to cook you in.
I love you.
I'm mean it.
Great hair.
Oh, you mean it.
I love you, mean it.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Thanks, baby.
I love the way you start to smile.
When you look at me,
A grateful look so full,
It's like there's no one else to see.
The way we said together,
feels like the world is ours.
The things you said the way you left
I know that the world needs ours.
Cause you're so amazing.
And you're so truly in love.
Yes, it's so amazing.
How you've got me in love.
I love the way you stroke my hair,
but it's a shame to speak.
The care you share through your hands
with a tennis show me.
We lay together,
feels like the world is ours.
The things you say the way you look
I know that the world is ours.
Cause you're so amazing.
And you're so truly in love.
Yes, it's so amazing.
How you've got me in love.
Cause you're so amazing.
And you're so truly in love.
Yes, it's so amazing.
How you've got me in love.
I love, I love, I love, I love.
It's not just a beautiful story.
Right in her bike, feeling in love, went back home.
I wrote some lyrics with a friend.
And recorded the song.
And here it is, in the, well, I can say hundreds of thousands of years.
How awesome is that, man?
I love what we're doing.
I hate the fact that my sound system sounds crap,
but otherwise I'm pretty happy.
As Lulu, and you're so amazing, the DSC bonus edition,
for which, of course, I'm very grateful.
So I'm going to work on this stuff.
Tomorrow we'll do a proper food bar Friday.
I'm going to be home tomorrow.
If time to prepare for it, get everything set up and ready.
I'll fix all of the crackles.
And we'll be jamming it out with some great songs.
Hit test, maybe Amy Mackle, bring the,
ostracized by.
And we'll talk with some angry brits who are both angry at,
the state of affairs in the UK.
And also angry at me.
So how much fun will that be, huh?
All right, everybody.
Thank you very much for listening.
I appreciate it.
Remember, Adam at potshow.com is my email address,
daily source code.com as we can find the show notes and links to everything
across in today's program.
Of course, the links to the music on the potset music network.
And please, live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom.
Another potshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.