Delta's here at Charlie, 7-5 so...
Travel around the city, everybody, let's go be something
Tell me more music, show me more music, use God for you
Tell me more music, show me more music, show me more music
Tell me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more
music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music
show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show
show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me More music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music, show me More music, show me more music, show me more music, show me more music
DJ La Clown is back with Evangents.
You're in the Sweet Dreams, rocked up, and messed up with the Rock Lobster from the V-52s
as called Sweet Lobster, mashed up, but of course, source for mashuptown.com, the official
supplier of mashups of the Daily Source code, and that is the program you're listening
to.
Right now, episode number 757 coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford,
we're in the Curry Manor, where it's just a little past one, a clock, another beautiful
day.
There are clouds in the sky today, and I'm expecting a thunderstorm here or there.
But otherwise, ceiling and visibility, okay, we're cavo-k, my friends.
Hey, I did the, I did that Dutch thing this morning.
I've been talking about first time.
It's actually a holiday today in the Netherlands, which was kind of chosen on purpose.
If anything messed up with the communication lines, no one would hear it.
And it's almost like, you know, it's, it's, those guys over there, they're equivalent
of almost like a pirate radio station, although they have an incredible coverage.
And the music they're playing, they call it classic rock.
I don't know if this format exists in the States, but it's basically it's rock, but
it's not just classic from, you know, like 70s or even 60s, it goes all the way up to
today, as long as it's rock.
And that's, it's almost like sitting in the soundtrack to my life, and then being permitted
to talk.
I got a way to go with the audience, you know, I'm trying to migrate some of the, somewhat
I've learned here on the daily source code, see if that works in a live format, stuff
like the phone calls, et cetera.
I have a little bit of work to do, but it was fun.
And man, that technology that ISDN point to point, why can't we get these codecs on like
a Skype or whatever, it's like I'm using 64 kilobits going one way.
Now my upload speed on my DSL is 300 kilobits, so there's certainly enough to do that.
And why do people always call me silence when I'm really busy?
But the delay is like there's like 60 millisecond delay between both ends.
And, you know, it's just the codec, you know, I don't understand why we can't do that
over the internet.
You should be able to actually, I AB compared it against Skype.
Skype is about, I'd say the delay is probably 600 to 700 milliseconds, you know, between
the time that I speak and it reaches the other end of vice versa.
And so this is a tenth of that.
Oh man, would I enjoy no agenda that much more if we had no delay?
It's always funny, whenever something funny is said on a no agenda or almost any show
that does Skype between multiple parties, the laughter always comes a little, just that,
just that couple of milliseconds, too late after the punch line, you know, that's kind
of a bummer.
And boy, the quality, I got a convinced of where I had to do that with me.
Hey, you guys have really filled up today's show.
Michael Heads, you've got a lot to talk about and let's kick it off.
Hello Adam, this is Mark Zinkle.
I just want to let you know, I don't think anyone has told you this, but at least with me,
I'm getting each episode for quite a while to vice in my iTunes seat.
And I'm scrolling down right now and the cheese, I am ever since ever since I've
just episode 223, it's been happening.
So, so I'll let you know, maybe it's a problem you're aware of otherwise I'll stick it.
All right.
I think you're out of love.
Yeah, I love you too.
I love you too.
I'm 16.
Six, 10.
Bye bye.
All right, 16 times is that your prostate cancer prevention quota for the week?
Yeah, no, I'm playing this specifically because a lot of people are having this problem.
And it's of course it's related to the the name chain from podshow.com to mevio.com.
I believe it's the way that iTunes handles the global unique identifier.
I think they do it in a funky way that basically this is the result.
And probably what's going to happen is it's going to try and read download every single
episode.
Believe me, no one is pleased with this.
You're not liking it because it's a slipper up your bandwidth.
We're not liking it because it's slipper up our bandwidth that we pay for it.
But Andrew Grumman is on the case.
He's he's back well rested and is all over this.
Of course, it doesn't help just as another data point that I released show 7.56 on Friday,
which was the Fubar Friday edition and aptly titled it 7.55, which was, of course, the
episode before that.
I'm sorry.
That didn't help at all.
But people did enjoy the Fubar Friday regardless.
Hi, Adam.
I'm Steve from Boston and I just got done listening to paranoid, mashed up when we
will rock you and then you straight into it, you read right into rainbow since you've
been gone.
And my friend, you have pushed all the right buttons today.
I am a chronic scroll wheel guy.
I scroll through everything that I even think I might not like.
And just this Friday, this Fubar you got me.
Go and you pushed them all my friend.
Way to go.
I am loving it.
You have a whole lot of it.
That's why I do this show.
That kind of response will get me up every single time.
It will get me out of bed.
I mean, you know, well, you know what I was, you know what I was, you know what I'm
going to say.
Adam, this is Ron from Philadelphia, just finished listening to episodes 7.55 of the
Charlie.
I could not stop laughing when I heard you play the team of America world police
I remember when I saw that in the theater, I would laugh so hard.
I think I was caught up alone.
It was so funny.
Great episode.
One of the say that I understand exactly what you meant by the comment that you
played about the individualism and you know, being so American.
And I think a lot of Europeans and Asians, they see that and they think that we
Americans are a bit off a rocker a bit crazy.
But that's just how we are.
That's how America was founded on crazy off the rocker people.
Individualism and focusing on, you know, making ourselves great.
However, it's, you know, not all that we do.
We do care about the rest of the world.
Although our current policy of President Bush is so crazy.
You don't even want to think about it.
But just to let you know, there's a lot of grass roots ever going around.
There's a lot of us in my area and my neck of the woods that we have support the
troops and the war.
We have signs on and along.
People know where we stand and what we believe.
So keep up the good work.
Thanks so much.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
No homo.
And unfortunately, only two times this week.
Hey, there.
I got my, my first mark on the board last night, actually, which technically was Sunday,
but we'll just count it with Monday.
So I'm one for five.
That means one down four more to go in the prostate cancer prevention quota, which, by the
way, is quota not quotient.
I was corrected on that just recently.
You know, five times a week, Jens, that will reduce your chance of prostate cancer by
60 to 70 percent.
Yeah, I do, you know, since you brought up the Bush administration as it still happens,
St. Clarence, sent me a link, which is from the LA Times.
It's called the government in secret.
And I'm going to put this link in the show notes at dailysourceco.com.
I really want you to read through this because as it turns out, there's a whole bunch
of laws that are being put into place that we have never seen or don't even have the
right, literally, to see these laws, a lot of it is executive order stuff.
And basically, if I understand this article properly, the president doesn't have to listen
to Congress at all based upon all these opinions of the Constitution.
I mean, this is what's really killing, killing us is these, you know, look, I, lots
of lawyers and my friends, J.T. Jersey, Todd, I hear you, all right, but bear with me.
But there's all these, in fact, what was the, was it a debate?
I can't remember, maybe it was even, it was Mitt Romney or someone said, oh, I have to
get, I'll have to consult with my attorney about that question.
It was probably about the guns or something like that.
But, you know, so the Constitution is being interpreted and reinterpreted and looked
at in so many different ways and I guess eventually you can find some kind of legal opinion
that will let you skirt around certain issues, fourth amendment is a, is a big one.
But please read this article.
It's too lengthy for me to, to get into it now, or even to read quotes from it.
But I think what we totally are getting screwed, it's not right.
Anyway, oh, here's the sound of America for you.
We're just having a deep choice.
You know, I don't, we're trying to explain last week, everybody was right in the New
American history and the Middle Beach.
Yes, you know, yeah, Sharon, I don't give a shit for you.
All right, Ravada.
Yeah, you don't give a shit now, man.
Wait until it's seven rate bucks a gallon.
Then you'll start talking.
But yes, indeed, the sound of Detroit
and Milwaukee Thunder, that is what America is built on.
Hi, this is PWF, I've been doing digital flats
them for more than three years now.
And as unbelievable as it might seem, I have never made an official promo.
So this is my very first.
It is digital flats him about, oh, I don't know, about 25 minutes or so.
Check it out at digitalflatsom.org.
I personally guarantee it is the finest podcast you will ever hear, called Digital Flats.
Of course, one of my favorite shows available on the Mivio Network, obviously.
For those of you who've been listening, I've been more than a couple hundred episodes.
You'll know that mode Jones is one of my favorite bands in the whole wide world.
And this is one of them.
I sit down in a child, I've spent a while.
What did you do, where did you hang on?
I get lucky, living your love, have you finally found?
If you were trying to find, ever not a drink, the night's still young.
There's more one in the world only just me now.
As your mom and dad, do you still go strong when you see him say you've never dreamed of me wrong?
Bit of sweet taste, my cry, when I think about this time,
a piece of life, and a life to simple.
Drop the man, I don't want to hear, of course, it's sad out, what you want, shit,
I just can't imagine you being somebody's wife, feels like only yesterday,
and I saw you a life with a bit of sweet taste, my cry,
when I think about this time, a piece of life, and a life to simple.
I see you still do your hair, you're beautiful.
Is that, you?
This lack I can feel in.
I'm stuck in love.
It's your living room but the good things from now.
バня 이렇게裡je Something sure, yet I want no, to feel so,
if you laugh about it, that's another soul's, thickest.
When you think about this time of easy life
And love a simple
A bit of sweet taste
And I cry
When I think about this time of easy life
And love a simple
A bit of sweet taste
My cry
When I think about this time of easy life
And love a simple
Oh man
Is that a great song or what?
Skinny
Bit of sweet tears
So what I was going to say is that
I don't think mode Jones is broken up
But you know just listening to this track
Man, Skinny has gone off and done this solo project
And I'll put a link in the show notes
It's not on the podcast and music network
I'm trying to get them on
You can purchase actually about the whole CD
Which almost second is titled
My heart beats the moon
It's like five tracks, five or six tracks
But man, just awesome
And really it sounds like skinny
What really was the guy in mode Jones
Because you could have put mode Jones on the label
I wouldn't believe it
But wow, do I love that song
Bit of sweet tears
Okay, let me see
I got some really disturbing UK stuff
I want to get to
But first
This is me kind of important
I trust once to talk about influence
And what we can do in our lives
Hey, Curry.
Rust now I've seen been just thinking
But in the war I've said
I know agenda here about
Your influence
Effective about two people that seem on the Charlie
Yeah
If you haven't heard no agenda
No agenda.mevio.com
Episode was at 30
The one we did on Saturday
And talking about changing the world
And how we can we can make a change
With media
With our own free independent media
And the format was
A highly skeptical
And just eyes me saying
That there's only two people that I influence on this show
I beg to differ
And it's point I think is valid
You know, I mean I've tried to do my part
It's a couple of edge motivated
But you know, really what we consider success
You know, how much touching of people
But the songs are all
Do we really want to do you know
Before we got to count being successful
You know, I'm a writer
And I'm a poet of my spare time
And I've written several poems
About the state of America
To the state of the world
I've written
In a tourist
You know
People have agreed with some people
I've just agreed with them
You know, yeah, and I've had an effect
But you know, how do I measure that
To what standards am I living up to
A senator you living up to?
What can we define as
Yeah, we've touched somebody
But you know, that's a very good question
And I'll say that I
Consider it's success
If I reach out and touch
One person
If I can open one person's mind up
I'm not trying to convince anybody
If anything
I just want you to start thinking
Because man we are
The matrix
The movie was so right
Except of course not really
I don't think
We're not really jacked in
Line and pods
And our brains have just created
This imaginary world
But look at how
How far should we've become
We really are, you know, we're
We're obsessed with the celebrity gossip
And not with the things
Happening around us
So I measure that by one person
One person at a time
You being one of them
Rust by the way
And you should send us some of your poetry
I'd love to hear that
You know
Not enough of you
You thought about it
But they don't do anything about it
I don't think it does make him accountable
And unfortunately kind of
Believe it seems to have
Very little weight in this modern world
So
Where do we go from here, dude?
I think that's a good question
That these to be looked at is
What do we consider success
And what are we doing wrong
If all we've done so far
It's not motivated people
Like it's not it would
So that's my two cents
Yeah
No sign off
No prostate cancer prevention quota
It's switching gears here
This is
Let me send this to me
Philip Clapham
He said me this awesome link
About this project that's going on in Australia
And you can find it
Let me just find the address for you
And via mission.com.au
Obviously I got a lot of links
Put in the show notes today
It's a new solar project
But it works a little differently
Than what I've seen so far
Essentially
There's this tube
I don't know what the diameter is
That sticks out of the ground
And it looks like it goes up several hundred feet
And it has
Some solar panels all around it
And when you see the diagram
Then you really understand what's happening
Essentially
The heat is being generated at the bottom
And then being pushed up through this tube
Because it's a tube
It's going up with a significant force
Enough to actually power turbines
And what is it?
200 megawatt power station
They have
I guess this is the first prototype
It provides enough electricity
To power about 200,000 typical Australian households
Of course I don't know exactly how much
Australian household uses
They might be a lot less than we use over here
But it really looks cool
And I think it's an awesome look
The force leads into
The search for all forms of alternative energy
Including nuclear
Which I am desperately trying to re-brand
To at least take away the negative connotations
As we figure out what we can do with the waste
And how safe is it?
And how much for turn an investment do you get?
And what are the pros and the cons?
Hey Adam
This is Marcus Novel who is the
Stokeshouse protest
And all of the 100% novel
It's more to a real quick space
Something about your wanting to re-brand nuclear energy
First that thought it sounded like a real cool idea
But what you think about isn't that really what
It's a politician view all the time
You know take some piece of legislation that they're really in favor for
Oh yeah, I know where this is going
Of course it's what politicians do
That's the whole point of branding
You want to give someone something to think about
Something that will stick in their mind
Obviously the idea of mushroom clouds
When it comes to atomic and nuclear energy
Isn't not exactly what we'd like people to be thinking about
If we decide to go that route
It's the public behind them
It's some really cool sounding name
They're taking it behind
You know, sort of like the old war on drugs
Yeah
For the same
I mean how about
We're just taking more factors
And educate people about what
If you're energy really isn't nice
It's not really an advantage you might think
Yeah
We're doing that
I'm trying to I just give you a
Education about these stove pipes in Australia
Hey Adam
This is Brian Chicago
I just wanted to give you I just had up on something
I want to want to recognize here a nuclear
Or radio act of discussion
You might want to check out a show
It's here in the States on show time
It's called 10 hours bullshit
And they have an episode about
Kind of a nuclear energy in your career
And create a huge number of videos of
How safe nuclear waste really is
I guess the storage of it
I don't check it out when you get a
Chat
Oh better way to get a good information
To them through the TV
One time listener
I might still say
Fuck you out
Oh oh oh
That hurt
Thank you
Yeah, I'm very familiar with the show
Haven't seen it in a while
I think it was running here in the UK for a bit
And then I kind of lost track of it
Of course I have show time in the condo
But I'm sure I can find that on YouTube
So I'll definitely have a look
And I'm not going to put that link into the
Into the show notes
You guys can find that one on your own
So the concept of rebranding
Was to
You know kind of coincide with the question
Can we put the nuclear waste on the moon?
And then of course rebranded moon juice
Because that's exactly what it will be
Turns out this is not a new idea
And the outcome and the results
Are pretty much predetermined
As is defined by the following comment
Hey Adam, how are greensteen from New York
Calling in about moon juice
It's amazing to me with all the sci-fi geeks
I listened to the daily source code
That no one busted out anything about space 1999
Well this show showed from 1975 to 77
In the U.S.
Was about an accident that occurred on September 13, 1999
Where nuclear waste had been stored on the moon
A catastrophic explosion sends the moon
Out of its orbit
And the 311 inhabitants of moon base alpha
Arturately
Uncontrollably into outer space
The series star Martin Landau
And Barbara Bay
Who had been stars admission in hospital at the time
Were married to each other
And this was a very popular show
But it was only shown in syndication
In various different markets in the U.S.
The music was cool and I have to say the effects for the time
Were very cool and I remember as a kid
Watching it on channel 11 in New York
So don't store nuclear waste on the moon dude
It's going to blow it up
Send it out of its orbit
And send all the people who are there working on the nuclear waste
Off into a mission in outer space
So they didn't want to go on
Just say it
All right
Folder
Whatever times a week
It seems to happen
Great hair
Love you
Mean it
Hope you win
Catch you soon
Bye
Are you tired of the so-called
This of the 70s, 80s and 90s shows
That will play the same songs on and on
But do these tunes
Some nice background music for doing your work
Households, sports or just when relaxing
Start listening today to the Sunday sundown
Where I bring you the best, easy listening in independent music around
Every episode
At least an hour of the best music
Nowadays you don't need to be finiatain
More to hear some refreshing and good music
Play it in your home
And go over to www.sunday sundown.com
And subscribe to iTunes
Or to direct link
Listen to it on your phone
Your MP3 player
Or just from your computer
Either way, you will hear the best about the music
Like you hear me in the background now
www.sunday sundown.com
And start listening today
To the Sunday sundown
Oh yeah
Yeah there's something for everybody on that pod save music
Now work I've noticed
That's pretty cool
Sunday sundown
We'll check it out pod save
And it chill out so
Today the source code episode number
I'm the 757 we'll be talking to an advertiser in a moment
Who's got something to say?
Which should be interesting
And this is also for the pod save music network
Loom your way to see these guys show up
And I am a woman
Oh but I know
Collective soul on the charlie
These ladies he days
I barely see myself through
While they hit cold up
My thoughts wrapped around you
I've got a lot of my thoughts
So I should never try
You're all that I know
You're the sun you're the star
When the sun comes and run
And I never will be
You're the sun you're the star
You're sure to show
I'll be sure to show up
You're the sun you're the star
It's what I want to do
You're all that I know When the sun goes down, you're all that I know
When the sun goes rise like the devil in the heat
And when tomorrow I'll waste the shed to show
You're all that I know
When the sun goes down, you're all that I know
When the sun goes rise like the devil in hearing
What the word is, it's just a show
You're all that I know When the sun goes down, you're all that I know
When the sun goes around like the devil in the heat
And when tomorrow I'll waste the shed to show
I really want to thank the Promotions Company, the record label, and of course the
band themselves was supporting the pot-save music revolution, shared that shipman, and actually
sells more records.
I think the Promotions Company, the same one that put out the book, Cherry, record on the
pot-save music network.
So that is of course highly appreciated and love and a great great song.
Today's source code is brought to you, and part by E-music, you know, you can get 35 free
songs, absolutely no obligation, if you go to E-music.com slash daily source code.
You obviously can buy this track there.
They all have M-P-3's, no DRM, you couldn't use it on all your devices.
If I got to email from David, aka the Pimp Daddy, to add to my found thick freakness
and exotic dancer blues on E-music after I heard your recommendation of the service
on the DSC, I've been downloading tons of songs since then, thank you so much from the
Pimp Daddy.
Yep, another satisfied customer.
Not so entirely with the life insurance offer that I made for you, which was, I've been
talking about that for a couple of weeks now, accuquote.com slash DSC.
A lot of feedback, I was wondering why people weren't buying life insurance if they didn't
like the concept, if they don't care about life insurance, if you already have it, if you
don't like the sponsor, I'm just trying to figure out what's going on, because I thought
the uptake was very low when I thought a lot of people would be very interested in life
insurance, and maybe we should learn more about that.
I've got some, you can get up to 70% discount if you use acuquote.com, but let's get into
this, because there was some pushback and feedback that I want to talk about, specifically
as it relates to acuquote.
Hey, Adam, this is great from Minneapolis, first time calling on to the comment box.
Is that comment about the actual feedback you're looking for?
For me, the difference with this campaign, I was a felt a lot less like the advertisement
that I've been along the part of the show, the more I just took this small advertising
with some sale, even though it was a social sponsorship, and more recently, the Nokia
and the 110, I told him, engaged by the ongoing conversation about the products, how
was the natural part of the show, you talk about how you were using it, and it's so like
advertising.
I could just tell you the plug, anyway, that's my two cents, and I do already have a
couple of policies, one of the part of it, or at the other, my life set up, actually trying
to send me a message, anyway, here's my sign off, 34 years old, Mary, one kid, older,
girl, Fluggie's, we need it for her, for the one, and I currently pass it down to people,
too.
So, I prefer a word in the process.
You've got to hurry up, man, I think I was sent in last week, so hopefully it's a little
bit higher than that.
You've got to have at least five a week, dude, let's stay alive, protect yourself, okay?
So, now I feel kind of bad, you know, I'm thinking maybe I didn't do this right, because
I agree, you know, I try to make it advertising, and I like that phrase you use there.
I think that's a good way to integrate commercials and monetization, ways to make money,
ways to keep people going on doing this stuff, and yeah, I'm, maybe I'm, I am perhaps struggling
a little bit, you know, I'd love to hear anyone who's purchased life insurance recently,
what you're looking for, someone an expert, man, in fact, I have an expert, it's Mr.
Acute himself, who called into the voicemail line, let's hear from Shanchani from acucode.com.
Hi Adam, this is Shanchani, I had up all of the marketing for acucode, and I was just
listening to DSC 754, and there was a caller, Shon, who had gone to the site, had, you
just Jersey Todd's link, and when he went to the acucode site, thought that we were a referral
site.
I'm not sure exactly what he is interpretation of a referral site, I can't tell you that
acucode, we actually sell insurance, we sell life insurance from a variety of different
carriers, no matter, you know, whatever one is going to make the most sense for the consumer,
and we only represent the top rated companies that are price competitive, so he had a concern
that whatever company he uses for his auto insurance didn't show up in the comparison, and
the reason for that is most companies where you get your auto insurance, they're usually
significantly more expensive on the life insurance side, so for that reason we don't even
bother quoting them, we're only going to focus on the ones that are top rated from a financial
standpoint, and also price competitive, because if you're not saving money and getting
your life insurance from a top rated carrier, there's really no value proposition there.
So just wanted to clear that up, been very happy working with you guys over at Mivio,
a little bit about me, I'm age 35, married to kids, and I love everything you're doing
great here, and you're a winner.
Well, what is your prostate cancer prevention quotient?
Can we get a discount?
Okay, all right, here's your advertisement, Sean, Sean, Sean, if a daily source code listener
checks in, and it has to be the honor system, but I feel if we're doing five releases
a week, you know, keeping up the prostate cancer prevention quota up to five, we should
get a guaranteed 70% discount.
I mean, we're basically working for you then, we're trying to stay alive.
So let me know if we can set something up like that, where if you have, if you can prove
that you have a quota of five, you'll get a hit, I'll give it to you for free, if you
have a way to prove that.
All right, I got a wrap, I got so much to do tomorrow is a huge day.
We have a big party in London at the Shoreditch House, which is, it's really, it's late
in coming, but it's our coming out party as BT Podshow, which we are over here in the
UK, Mivio in the States.
And of course, this is where the partner British telecom, it's going to be a huge party,
all kinds of sea liberties and de-leberties, cool bands, we got cool DJs, we got free
booze, and lots of beautiful boys and girls.
I want more do you want?
It's going to be fun, but then there's all kinds of interviews and stuff I'm doing tomorrow,
so probably won't be able to eat out a show tomorrow morning because I got to be there relatively
early to start, I mean, it's a whole list, I mean, we got this PR from over here, that's
really been kicking ass, Kazoo, Kazoo's in the name, I'm sure there's a trademark issue in
there somewhere.
So I just want to leave you with one more for today from sales guy, you?
Hey Adam, so thank you, Chris for your.
My wife's telling me I'm starting to look old, get wrinkles, you know, tags on the my eyes,
so she told me today that I should go to a beauty shop somewhere and buy some products,
some cream, some moisturizer cream, whatever that's all gold, that could help me or help
my skin to rejuvenate.
Now I know you're a big product guy, you know, just, I think you, you've got a cream for
pretty much everything, any suggestions, any tips, you know, what should I buy?
I have no ID, man, the only product I use is the odorant and shampoo that's about all I got
right now.
Let me know, man, and don't give me those products that cost 500 euros, you know, for
you, the soup's bad, this, I need good quality products for a good payable price, you know,
what?
I think I'm turning into a Metro sexual, we're doing it, so.
Yo, sales guy, you, I'm so happy you brought this up because this gives me the opportunity
to bring out that old jingle, yes, ladies and gentlemen, Metro sexual, Metro sexual,
Metro sexual, Metro sexual, it's Adam Curry's Metro sexual moment, yes, everybody.
The fabulous Jeff Smith and the Jeff Smith.com, thanks so much, man, I still love this thing.
Sales guy, you, yes, I can tell you exactly what products you need, and you know what the good
thing is, you don't even need to go to the store to get them, my friend. No, you could stay at home,
you don't even have to take money out of your pocket, what you do is you go to your wife's medicine
cabinet or wherever she keeps all of her little creams and stuff, and you go in there and you look
for anything that says facial or moisturizer, combination of the two is even better, and the
smaller, the container, the more potent that shit is sales guy, you, so that's the stuff you want
to be using, and every single evening after you've washed your face or taken your shower,
whatever you want to moisturize your face, particularly under the eyes, with the excess,
you want to use that on your elbows and your knees, so you don't start cracking up,
and you repeat the same process in the morning. That is the official Adam Curry
cheap Jack asked tip to look in young and stay in healthy.
All right, everybody, that's it for today. Again tomorrow, big party, so I will be Twittering,
and I'll be posting stuff with the camera to the blog that'll be fun, so we do some live
blog and for you from the event at Shortage House, which is on the east side of London, where
everybody's weighed down with that, and back on Wednesday for a hump day show, so until then,
live your life with passion, it's certainly the weather for it, and while we still can,
enjoy your freedom. Another fine, medium presentation, stick it in your ear.