We are all with a program with a special boy.
America is now under martial law.
All kinds of people right have been pathetic.
Take your home.
Do not attempt to contact.
Love one is for an agent or attorney.
Shut up.
Do not attempt to think or depression may occur.
Stay in your home.
Her view is at 7 p.m.
Start after work.
Anyone caught outside the gate to prepare some divisions.
Sectors after curfew will be shot.
Remain call.
Do not panic.
Your neighborhood, what officer will be by to collect urine samples in the morning.
Anyone caught interfering with the collection of urine samples.
Will be shot.
Stay in your home.
Remain call.
The number one enemy of raw grass is a question.
National security is more important than individual will.
All boy's raw test will proceed as normal.
No more than two people may gather anywhere without permission.
Use only the drug required by your boss or supervisor.
Shut up.
Be happy.
Obey all orders without question.
The comfort you demanded is now mandatory.
Be happy.
That's why everything is done for you.
$60 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
The next generation brand new content in my ears.
We don't need us digging trees in.
I like to think I'm flying into this jar.
Fantastic.
It's a battle curry.
In a world where you have to remind politicians that they work for us.
Where the need for nuclear energy has never been greater.
Where money drives the wheels that turn the engine.
When all around you seems too barred beyond what you can handle.
You need to take a moment to catch your breath.
Look at DSC.
7.
61.
Crank up the tunes at them.
We need to imagine the light.
About a home.
Or a country to call you alone.
We'll thank God.
The girls here who gave their last to make this.
Home of the brave.
Hey, here come in.
The only energy that you feel free.
If I feel release, raise your head on your heart.
And share the fear of the U.S.A.
Today.
I'm used to bow.
We've fought our way.
Give us all we have today.
Graves souls.
Mark it.
Graves treasure you can.
Hear them say.
Hey, here come in.
The only energy that you feel free.
If I feel release, raise your head on your heart.
And share the fear of the U.S.A.A.A.A
to D.
Remember that.
Survey day sunshad down allorphs fade
Gails clear when the place came down
Parajas low world thron the ground
Watchin' this朋友in' cry
owanns in some of world's다는
Fear won't run all the day
Pinky tidak pride a way
If they don't know about
Find a day from town to town
We paid the price
Freedom to save
We'll ask to show
Still eat the way
Freedom to save
Oh, who can forget that classic?
Listening to the heart and soul of this next one, you'll know he's singing straight to the Lady Patricia.
All the greatest is brought to you as only Adam Creak in.
Just listen to this.
Yes, now we can all hit the dance floors AC's done.
Buy your copy now because you know they won't last long.
Yes, for limited time only it is Adam Creak sings by now.
It's Adam Creak sings.
Don't give me source code.
I don't give me source code.
D, mashed up for you on D, S, C, 7, 6, 1.
Wow, I've got a musical sound auditory collage,
all set up for you, my friends.
Not too much content.
Gotta keep it low on the content.
Gotta keep it real high on the music.
I just feel like it's a Friday.
And I just want to play some awesome tunes for you.
Got some great feedback.
Remember when comic strip blogger
lashed out at my sister, Willow, who lives in Italy,
in reference to restriction of freedom of movement,
apparently the, quote, gypsies and no longer
allowed to travel around freely around the country.
And it's a lot wrong with Italy.
But when you say to any curry, when you say,
oh, I bet you you won't say anything,
you probably won't stand up.
You're gonna find out that we are made
from the same wood comic strip blogger.
Here is my sister Willow,
checking in from Italy on the football Friday.
Oh, Adam, it's your sister calling from Italy.
Of course, I'm calling in response to CBS.
Oh, fuck you, CBS.
Of course, I'm not afraid to speak up.
The other thing is, country is so fucked up.
It has so many issues.
And of course, the whole Romanian and the role
of my Egyptian issue and it's a positive question.
Like so many other things.
I mean, I'm not afraid to speak up.
I'm just trying to do the best I can
and my Michael environment.
I mean, I'm just trying to live my life
with the values I do right.
And I'm trying to read my kids with those values.
And even people who can get all these people
into the streets and like the comedian,
that they do though.
I mean, you've got hundreds and thousands
of people on the street protesting.
What was the result?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
So basically what I'm trying to do is
just trying to be part of the solution.
Because now, if you're not part of the solution,
you're part of the problem.
So anyway, I'm trying to do the best I can.
I'm not afraid to speak up.
I will agree and not afraid to speak up.
You see, yes.
I mean, what's your real name?
Do we know your real name?
I mean, are you afraid to speak up?
Or do you all speak?
I'm in the name of comic strip blogger.
Oh, oh, that one hurt after she had CBS a couple times
and then CSB, then she finally struck home.
Yeah, comic strip blogger.
How about you, man?
What's your real name?
Come out of the closet.
Anyway, I think that was about what I wanted to say.
Oh, by the way, Adam, you know, how do you
do you want to picture me in the bathtub with a note here?
I don't really like to picture you with your prevention quota.
Anyway, that's all.
They work for us.
Hell, they do.
Yeah, no, I can understand that is kind of weird.
You know that, so the prostate cancer prevention quota thing.
That's really, it's playing a mind trick on people.
You know, we've done a lot of mind tricks, Vulcan, mind tricks I might add here on the
daily source.
You'll recall the the burping association with the Senseo coffee machine,
which I think by now most people are pretty much deprogrammed.
I hope I have no way to really deprogram the other than just to stop doing it.
But this rubbing one out for cancer for those of you just joining the program in the
community.
Welcome.
You're now in official chucklehead.
Studies and studies have not survey studies have shown that masturbating five times a week,
a minimum of five times a week can actually reduce the chance that you can contract prostate
cancer by, I think, up to 60 or 70%.
But just me talking about it has, well, it has a couple of different results.
One is people are taking note.
They're keeping track.
By the way, I'm at three so far for the week, so I'm a little bit behind, but we still
have Saturday and Sunday.
And sales guy, you put certain savant.
Oh, he's got a whole other problem with this deal.
Adam, sales guy, you're Germany.
You just got back from a beautiful holiday in Italy, Serenzo, Costa Capriña.
Oh, it's beautiful there.
Scott, talking about masturbation on your show.
I'll tell you why.
Okay.
Each time I try to have fun with myself, pleasure myself.
You know, run one out for the team.
Now, I get this visual of you sitting in a barbedrope doing the same thing at exactly the same
time.
It's not stimulating.
It's not helping me.
So, quit talking about it or have a lady talk about it or have somebody do a cute
or do it.
It does not help when people like yourself or CSB or the candy man or nylon talk about masturbation.
It gets in my head and I want to think of beautiful blonde chicks when I masturbate.
Not of overweight, shall be computer nerds.
All right.
I'll meet a snitzle from beautiful Sunny German each out.
Yo, man.
Absolutely.
Oh, okay.
So, female chuckleheads.
Your work is now officially cut out for you.
I can no longer speak about this because it's definitely harshened.
The male chuckleheads mellow.
What we need is we need some helpful reminders from you.
Just record them.
Send them in on MP3 or call the voice mail lines.
Remember, you're doing this for the mankind.
Bettering mankind and to help prevent prostate cancer.
Nothing is all right till we decided it is.
Just get away from me.
I'm going to make it right tonight tonight.
I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down.
I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down.
I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going, I'm going down.
I'm so lonely in my pocket
I'm lonely in my pocket
I don't remember where I got it
I gotta get it to you
So please answer the phone
Because I keep falling but you're never
What am I gonna do?
I'm so lonely in my pocket
I'm lonely in my pocket
The way we want to chase, we know
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
And you'll be telling me you're gonna have me
You're gonna have me
But you don't have me
But now I'm in too deep
She's gonna be so that I just can't sleep
Loving me out of here
Please get me out of here
And just help me out of here
You're busy
You're just home
You're gonna have me out
Tonight I'm home
I'm gonna make you the right
Tonight tonight
Tonight
Tonight I'm gonna make you the right
You know, honestly, I really don't know where I sourced all of the tracks for today's football
Our Friday edition of the Charlie from that lot of it came from
The source code drop the drop.io slash daddy source code
Some of it from the
Podsate music network
It's just all over the place
I don't even know if I can do the show
Notice for this
But that's the
The final name is the clip tones
24 hours crazy tonight
Strong teeth
I'd say a massive mashup right there for you
Oh my goodness
And we're like 25 minutes into this
And I still have so much more to go
Because it's Friday of course
And we haven't done a football Friday in two weeks
It's a very special hit test line now for you
Because it is episode number 123
Typical young palettes
Send me one says it's a special one
Because it's one two three
Let's go
We're all in casting with
I'm curious
This is the hit test
Hit it test
Young bowl
Hey Adam, how are you doing?
I'm good man ready for one two three
Meet us again at this one special
Because all of the songs are from 1987
So here we go
I'm here for a good
Okay, I'm gonna suck for one two three
I have no idea what that is
Number two
That sounds like
Level 42
I don't remember the song
I think it's level 42
And final one is number three
That's definitely level 42
That's
Runs in the family
I don't know what the second was
And times up and here are the answers
Who is it?
Hi Adam, this is Mark King
This hit test is all about level 42
Mark is awesome
How the hell would you do that young?
I love it, Mark King
My favorite bass player
They're all three level 42
Young second with the hits
Answer number one in this week's hit test level 42
And to be with you again and this is answer number two
Hi, this is Mark King of level 42
And you're listening to the daily source code Adam
Mark is the hit test with young polled
Awesome
It's a level 42 special
I can't believe it
Answer number two
To be with you again and this is answer number three
Hi, this is Mark King
This is the daily source code with Adam
Adam
What's in this two
I believe the voice
He said that he would thank you
He'd make you so miserable
He wrote it in the family
Answer number three
Also by level 42
And all of them are from 1987
This special hit test all of them from level 42
That concludes hit test number 123
So how did you do Adam?
Well, you surprised me, on of course
Eventually figured out it was level 42 for 1, 2, 3
Excellent, thank you so much John
Like always hit test up mefio.com
Is the place to find the answers to this and any older hit test
And also the least of iTunes
So you can buy the tracks featured on the hit test online
Thank you for playing Adam
Thank you everyone else
Thank you for listening
Many thanks to Mr. Mark King for helping me out with this special hit test
Hello
Thank you Mark
Next week I'll be back for the next hit test
So until then
Have a very nice week
Take care and try to think with your heart
Bye bye
I'm almost done
I'm almost done hold on let me just put it in
Let me put it in
I knew I had it somewhere my iTunes
Well, shit if we're going to do a level 42 special
We might as well play a full track by the band
One of my absolute favorite level 42 tracks
The one that we played over and over again
To the vinyl was literally grey
A decimal radio and half spam at the early 80s
This is the live version
Which just takes all the boxes
Thank you, John
Thank you Mark
Here's love games
I can see my life you're by
You mean everything to me
Just can't take no more
Throw smile my way
As a pain I feel inside
Just to love for you
And I'm yours
I'm yours
If you want to show your heart to me
Said a new way
Once I hold you back
You love me and your friends
But in time can't do the game
I won't play the whole
I believe I'm right
When I say you love me too
But it can't go on
You're okay
I'm yours
If you want to show your heart to me
Said a new way
As a pain I feel inside
Just to love for you
And I'm yours
Said a new way
Saying a new way
Marking is awesome.
Oh man, give me some more of that face.
Ah, yon, so of course in acquiring mines when I know how you hooked up with Mark King.
It's a small world man. Let me tell you that.
I love 42 love games. I think that was from 83, maybe 84, which at the time I think we dubbed the year of the base in the big smoke city of Amsterdam.
As I said, we played this song over and over and over and over again. Just loved it so much.
Another thing, you know, talking about long versions.
As I said, you know, there's so much cool stuff that you can do that you can't do on traditional radio.
And one of them, or actually a couple of things I've been doing over this past week has been playing poems,
poems that people have recorded, either other people doing it or themselves,
and the data source code drop is a great place for these. There's a new one up there.
It's nine minutes.
So I haven't even listened to it myself all the way through yet, but you might want to go have a listen.
And these things really are striking accord with people.
Adam, it's Marcus Noble again.
I just wanted to tell you, I just was finished listening to your latest episodes.
Yeah, see, I'm on my lunch break at work right now.
And I just want to say that I love these poems that you're playing out love can hear more of some, you know.
As I'm sure others have said before, but I just want to make sure you know this.
Yeah, this is very good, you know, very moving stuff you're playing here.
And this is sort of stuff you won't get on TV, won't get on radio.
And exactly.
Yeah, this is the kind of thing that people really need to hear regardless of, you know, what political party or for, or anything like that.
So anyway, um, great here.
I love you, you know, homo, I hope you end.
I'm a folder, 23, and I'm single and college doing so.
I'm lucky enough that I'm able to get to take care of my prostate cancer prevention quotient twice a day.
And they work for us and they don't fucking realize that soon.
Yeah.
Hell yeah, hell yeah, they work for us.
New sign off everybody.
They work for us and you know they do.
And we got a new savant who is this, um, spontaneously presented himself to the Charlie with a beautiful MP3 recording.
Please welcome Charlie.
This is the Bruce here.
Ah fuck.
What does it Charlie when it's Bruce?
Oh, I see why.
Uh, please welcome Bruce.
Um, I'm a fan first time calling.
I know your show is a guy show.
Not necessarily a guy show.
We've got some ladies out there.
I show.
I think.
But I like it too.
And I'm gay.
I listen here from T. West Florida.
And a lot of my friends listen to you too.
Um, as a group.
Anyway, here's an idea.
A little silly.
I just got a visual of that.
A little idea, just for fun.
But how about me being your homo, Saman?
Use the homo, Saman.
Awesome.
Bruce the homo, Saman.
You're in.
I don't need to hear the rest of the comment.
You're in my friend.
I can tell you there's some real science behind homo sexuality.
Um, just for instance, did you know that extensive homo sexuality is found among seagulls
off the coast of California, like almost 15% of gals are gay?
Yeah, let me guess.
Are they in San Francisco?
Um, I think that research was done in San Francisco.
I'm not sure.
Yes, really.
Listeners need to understand us.
Obviously, some already do.
But we're in the minority.
I'm sure.
Okay.
So homo, Saman.
That is unless you're anti gay.
I mean, no homo is simply a declaration, right?
Um, not like implying bad juge or something, right?
Um, or you could have me as Charlie Savage's avant whatever.
Oh, and here's another idea.
How about Adam Curry's homo sexual moment?
No.
But I thought really, you just really might really like me to provide regular insights
as installments of information and understanding about that.
That's weird.
Wait.
Did you say inspiration?
No.
Let me hear that.
To provide regular insights as installments of information and understanding about us
queer, we're human too.
Is there a genetic component or not?
Um, you know, I could tell listeners about stuff like that.
Let me know, bye-bye.
No.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Love you, mean it.
Platonic.
Uh, yeah.
Homo and my quotient is anywhere from five to 12 per week,
depending on various circumstances.
Rachel.
Let me know.
Bruce.
Oh, man.
I hope you're for real.
And for a couple seconds, I don't know.
This is for real enough.
But of course, you're more than welcome.
Everyone's welcome to be a chucklehead.
And yes, you are here by the official, uh, homo savant.
Whatever that means.
Um, I think, you know, probably when we have some questions about the topic
is when you want to weigh in, not just jump all over the place,
but happy to have you on board, my friend.
And please enjoy your food, my friend.
There once was a song called The Rest of President.
Contemporary music.
It was the kids.
It was a top 10.
I wasn't popular, so I missed the bus a bit.
The politics was on everybody's heart, the summer list.
The cool kids were all rocking votes.
I shit you knuck.
I was pistol whipping cops for hip-hop.
I'm a slow-box.
Y'all in into mega-fones.
The killing hard-box.
Using cartes and the stepping stones.
I had a thermostat except holding my marches.
The day that Chris Columbus got crucified and called the marches.
My pen is still as too tall to climb off.
And in fact, that's the reason for the hot-haw.
And I went up here and seen the reason on my side of course with.
I'm the dog to win the pros and a push-up contest.
All for the sake of military refruiting.
The fellow can't stake the way they targeted the students.
I got a ball.
Whistling Ohio.
It's the rest of us.
I'm doing a stand-up at a cricket convention.
Who was they thought?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What they thought?
They've made a machine that leaves the quality of black gold.
And a prominent look at the quality of black gold.
They've got the quality of black gold.
They've got the pie, so all that.
But they can't paint it.
First, the time taken from minimum wage paper.
I don't care how that's making it all fake.
She looks.
She smells like dirty cash in each paper.
So what's your time with your time?
We'll downbody you killing them.
Slow downbody you killing them.
Now it's with the low versus the pistol holder.
Case dismissed.
The lock you up and throw away the key witness.
Just this is the whim of a judge.
Check his chest density.
It leaves much room for error.
And the rest left a death thing.
The West Memphis Re-Loss Paradise.
It's death penalty.
Versus suicidal fantasies.
All I wanted was a fucking Pepsi.
Institution.
Making you think it crazy is a billion-dollar range of street.
They could sell sanity in a bottle.
They'd be charging for compressed air.
They're marketing healthcare.
They're demonized welfare.
Middle class eliminated.
Rich kid.
They're poor kid.
Educated.
What's from the y'all still having grown into your face?
Are you face something quite match your head?
And I'm waiting for a brain to fill the dead space that's left.
Your own kid.
Me ethnicity.
You'll give me dread.
Just a funny and rebel.
Without a cause for a long.
Cause when postures the shove.
You jump into your forefathers home.
Sees a banker.
Your part of the system.
All throw the tread blocks.
And comes in.
Come briefcase.
Free space.
Significent.
Own a camera star.
Hold and say to fuck out of the picture.
Bill Royce.
Free space.
Significent.
Own a camera star.
Hold down.
Under your killing.
Mr. Save the world.
Spares the details.
Save the females from losing interest.
And misstate the universe.
You're a damsel in distress.
Tie down to a track of isolated incidents.
Generalize.
My disease.
I need a taste of what it's like.
Living off the fat of kings.
I play the scab at your hunger strike.
The strike.
Slow down.
Under your killing.
One love.
One life.
One too many victims.
Republic rat democrat.
One party system.
Media goes in a frenzy.
The stripped of their credentials.
Presidential candidates.
Can't debate over this instrumental.
Let them freestyle.
Winter takes all.
When the music settle.
Have Ted Newtons head hanging on my wall.
Kill one of ours.
We'll kill one of yours.
A friendly fire.
That's a funny turn.
Like civil war.
Sixth in the morning police have my crib.
Now my knife consists of two, two.
Sixth in the eyelids.
The cruiser fixed in vitamins.
Music that is pirated.
Newflaid.
The food made of mutated hybrids.
Oh.
They tell me that it's not that bad.
Who fucked you up good.
But it's not that bad.
They hold on to these tales.
To list the door that wax.
God save us all.
Let be list the cattle.
The foul.
We're the blame for the strain.
A muggle.
Of course.
Who can kind of hate.
But prep a can.
Hold a sword.
It's the same.
Who can complain about the muggle more.
A can.
Oh.
Four.
They call the shots.
But they're not in the line of fire.
I call the shots.
But they break in the line of duty.
Let's call the shots.
To the abuse of authority.
The truth keeps calling me.
And I'm a lift to tell the story.
So let's not true.
Crits begin forgiveness.
You need to cut the news.
But you don't believe in scissors.
Use the words of truth.
Over here in yellow ribbons.
Just bring home a mother fucking brother.
This is this.
Cuz they don't call the shots.
But they're in the line of fire.
I'd like to call the cops.
Let's they break in the line of duty.
I call the shots.
You're beautiful.
You keep calling me.
And I'm a lift to tell the story.
You hear that brook.
You hear that Hillary.
You hear that George.
America's youth is pissed off.
Bring our brothers and sisters home.
Stop the madness.
We made a super star.
That is what you are.
Coming from a farm.
Rating with your own.
Come away with me.
To another inch.
We can rely on a tree bread.
Your honor.
I'd like to make a motion.
To rock this mother out.
Your honor.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's don't give a night.
To the harness.
Working lawyers.
Jersey's dying.
Yeah.
It's Jersey's dying.
Oh yeah.
Your honor.
What is.
Yo.
How's it going?
Adam.
It's a special musical of the Chacha.
So I got something beautiful for you tonight.
I'm really, really digging this track.
The guy's name is JJ Appleton.
And he's really, really good.
He's been huge in Europe.
And I think he's going to make it here in the United States as well.
I love the song.
The song is called today.
Today.
And it's just beautiful and hopeful and wonderful on your football Friday.
Hey.
Danger dream.
A little bit longer.
Just for the heat.
A little bit stronger.
Heavy hours.
You've seen the rough and tumble.
A long the road.
We've had a few stumbles.
And when you can't believe we're lonely.
She wanted everything.
To me.
Yeah.
It's Jersey's train this fast ride.
Tomorrow's every day.
Tomorrow.
But it always comes on time.
So we've got a today.
Today.
And the weather else.
The rain.
But here.
Today.
The rain.
You.
對.
Being sorry for everything.
Every path.
We're still struggling here for tomorrow,
tomorrow.
And a race.
Here.
competed,
gonna die.
Tomorrow's a dream, but it always comes on time
So what we got is today, today, today
No where else can we live in the edge of day
No where else can we live in the edge of the edge of day
I know about you, but music truly started to mean something to me again.
It's like a awakening game.
Expertly, source by Sir Jersey, top the official musicologist of the Charlie, the G.J.
Uperton, today, today, today from the pot-safe music network.
Go ahead and find the music on Potchio.com.
We're going to miveo.com and just search on a music you'll find it no problem, what's so ever.
Oh man, another matchup for you.
We're going to run along my friends, that's for sure.
It's going to be probably about an hour and 10 minutes today's show, but well worth it.
What do you get when you put any wine house together with Ella Fitzgerald?
Well, this would be the result. Enjoy this.
We're going to run along my friends, that's for sure.
Kind of a funky mashup that made me wine house versus Ella Fitzgerald, Marky Boy brings
you back to the Ritz.
On the early source code episode number 761, the Maxo Music Fubar, Freitrain Experience.
You know, the daily source code drop was you can find a drop.io slash daily source
code is wow what a fantastic tool that is I had loved it so much and we already had filled
up pretty much a gig worth of stuff one gigabyte and so I'm hunting around right I'm
trying to find a place to upgrade to buy more space because they gave me the one gig for
free which was really nice so I sent a couple emails finally I get an email back so like
I did we upgraded you to 20 gigs because we're still in alpha you can't really buy anything yet
and then it's been fantastic because you guys have been dropping all kinds of cool stuff in fact
some of the stuff has even been dropped in twice hey Adam this is being down here and good old
Houston Texas hey that's a big pool of money uh so that you're talking about is from this American
life which is a great little NPR radio show they also have a podcast that's how I normally
listen to them and they use they have some great stuff on there so if your listeners want to
check it out uh this American life dot board is the website and I will talk you soon have a
great day bye bye you killed in the traffic here oh don't do that and they work for us my friend
yeah this is what I was talking about on Wednesday uh this is the show uh we you it starts off
with an award show where all these banksters are handing each other out of awards including in
award for a CDO which is the pretty much the basis of the the credit crunch oh by the way and this
is something that will definitely bring up with John C Devoreca tomorrow I know agenda front page
of the financial times yesterday um the ratings agency that rated these uh these uh funds I guess you'd
call them like the CDOs which of course were backed up by by mortgages that were flaky to say
the least if not completely shot in worthless these um these financial instruments were getting triple
A status from moodies and obviously moodies was wrong because well you know they weren't triple A they
were maybe triple D double D at best so there's been a lot of investigation into this and uh yes
they front page financial times moodies the guys who are I think really um not fully but
certainly partially responsible for this whole mess their answer their reason why this all went wrong
it was a software error yeah we had a coding problem and they discovered this a year ago these
guys are so full of shit I say lock them up in the brink every single one of them hey Adam it's a
go our full of mic here I was just reading a pretty interesting quote from the American Institute
of Architects and said building the account for 48% of US energy consumption and generate
far more greenhouse gas emissions than any other sector not thought that was pretty interesting especially
with our recent discussions on nuclear energy you know it seems that it will be pretty easy to
start building nuclear power plants to replace those cold burning plants we have now to fuel these
and if we take it as further and say the people start to split you over to electric cars
where are they getting the power for those cars uh huh that's right the same nuclear power plants
that are fueling our buildings I don't know just a thought oh yeah don't forget those douche
bags are people just like you and me and they work for us oh yeah oh man you got me on that one yeah
I'm getting more and more interested in nuclear that's the kind of energy that I think we can really
do something with but we've been pre-programmed for some reason this is bad and you can't get rid of
the waste and and the waste is green ooze goo this oozing all over the place um I think we've
we've really been taken for a ride I think the technology is improved and we have us a Vaunt to tell
you all more about it is name of course is atomic rod atoms and uh specifically specifically
Rod's gonna talk to us about nuclear waste remember nuclear it's the way to go it's the way of the
future powered by nuclear hey Adam it's atomic rod I heard you play you the last comment and you
keep asking about the waste let me tell you the waste is a valuable byproduct the
is recycle not sensitive and just recycle it usually again and use a viable material and
oh by the way during my day job I work for you I interesting that's not my didn't know about atomic
rod he apparently works for the government ah he's just risen more notches on my list excellent
so wait a minute so we can recycle nuclear waste we can recycle it we can reuse what can we reuse
it as could we put it back in the reactor or what can we do atomic rod please do tell me more this
is exciting news yeah there's a discussion group that we have amongst the the mevio producers
oh I don't okay sorry about that once and a while the the map just gets to excited on a food bar
Friday um and we have all kinds of discussions and there are some of them are um out not right
flame wars which is always fun and a lot of them are very personal and I've talked about
Robin and Suzanne who do the show inside works more than one song the daily source code
and the Suzanne has been going through a couple of health related issues and you know they had
a bit of a scare going on there and you know Robin shared that with his friends and if I'm very
happy to say that all the producers are his friends in a way and we send a lot of positive energy
a lot of love and things definitely seem to be looking up and I could not be happier because
they certainly need some tailwinds and I think they got him hey Adam this is Robin just want to
call and say I am a lucky man I'm humbled by my friends and my family and especially thankful
for my friends and my family so that does make me a lucky man so rock on with the food bar Friday
ever what you made me had white horses and ladies by the score all dressed in satchin
and waging by the door oh what a lucky man he was
who a lucky man he was
whitelist and feathers they made up his bed
I go over the mattress on which he was led
he went to my horse for his country and his king
pop his honor man's glory the people who are lucky man he was
the problem is nothing but rude as he played nobody laughs
And I know I love you man, he was
Oh, I love you man, he was
I told you we go about an hour and ten minutes looks like I'm just about spot on.
Emerson Lake and Fomer, what a lucky man, he is
For Robin, and of course, Suzanne.
Oh, I love that. Oh, man. Yeah, I got one more track for you.
Well, actually, we should wind up the week with something we haven't done in a while, which is of course.
What day is it today? It's Friday.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Food about Friday at a spinal fund for the week.
As everybody is time for your final thought of the week, you know?
It kind of struck me as I was going through the show.
We need to think about over the weekend as our final thought of the week.
You see how easy it was for me to accidentally program people's brains like sales guy you.
But I have heard this complaint from a couple other people, just by talking about the prostate cancer prevention
and people thinking about me doing, you know, like, you know, hand-to-gland combat, polish the pope.
Stuff like that, that freaks people out. So how easy is it to be programmed about stuff through, you know, simple things like the media?
Do you think we're being kept kind of dumb, perhaps? Do you think that they're really happy with all these reality shows?
You know, the people I'm talking about, the ones that work for us, they work for us.
So maybe there is something to new clear when it comes to energy.
Maybe there is more to be done with it.
Maybe we've been programmed through imagery of atomic explosions that's not going to be good for us.
Maybe the answer is right underneath our nose as only there's financial gain for others that is holding us back from the true solutions.
That my friends is your final thought for the week.
And now the song that I've been waiting for to play for you for at least four years.
I was unable to find it in the iTunes Music Store, unable to find it anywhere online even at
Seepa.com, which is where I rip all the best stuff.
Finally, I found out through a message on drop.io slash daily source code that it is available for sale
at emusic.com. And of course, I'm signed up emusic.com slash daily source code.
I got 35 free songs. This was one of them, The Alessie Brothers.
I'd like to stay in love with you all summer and after fall.
I'll keep you warm through the window.
I've made it one day.
I've made it
one day.
I've made it one day.
I've made it one night.
Oh, this mark's really long,
You danced for me while you're at me
Because I know after you knew
When we knew I'd made love to reach out to you
When I'm glad to see you
So I wanted you
Love you
Gimme brands and braces
Baby make it to the heart
See the  icy
Love you
I've been born again
Oh yeah
I think it must have been the summer of 75.
I was a wee boy, maybe 11, 12, maybe 13 years old,
madly in love with a girl at school and just thinking about
riding with her on my handlebars through the middle,
and really didn't be in.
That's from the soundtrack to my lives.
Have a good share with you on the source code.
Oh, man, perfect way to finish off the week.
As if we are from our Friday maximum music freight training
experience, the LSE Brothers of Glory.
Bruce, Bruce, I need help.
Okay, everybody, I will be back on Monday,
which is a bank holiday here in the UK.
I think it's a memorial day in the States.
I'm not quite sure anymore.
In the meantime, get your voice mails in.
Send in your MP3s, Adam and me, vio.com, get your music requests in.
Drop stuff and the drop.drop.au slash daily source code.
And of course, keep up on the blog at curie.com.
Until we speak again, have yourselves a fantastic weekend.
Live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medial presentation.
Stick it in your ear.