It is August 26th, 2008. It's time for the Charley, gaining source code episode
number 785.
The next Charley's radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying to this jerk.
Everything is broken, everything is breaking down, breaking down.
Everything is broken, everything is breaking down.
Everything is broken, everything is broken, everything is broken.
Everything is broken, everything is broken, everything is breaking down.
Everything is broken, everything is breaking down.
Everything is broken, everything is broken, everything is broken.
Everything is broken, everything is broken, everything is breaking down.
Everything is broken, everything is breaking down.
I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close
I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm
Gilford, G-Town on the West Side. Hey, how you doing? I hope you had a nice weekend for those of you in the UK, a bank holiday
Which means we all fucked off on Monday. I didn't I had stuff to do. I worked. I got busy
But it was and of course, I made a big mistake of putting the trash out today on Tuesday is normal
Get my ass out there at seven in the morning because we're first on the run and after my long walk
I try to take one every single day about what a long walk half an hour 45 minutes just to get out get some exercise have you know
basically movement and oxygen
You know when I listened to
Some some shows. Well, I listened to I listened to it today. I hadn't had listened to it yesterday
And they're the bags the trash bags are still there dammit. Now. I got I don't know if they're gonna come tomorrow or sometimes
They don't come for a whole week. Then you gotta wait until next week
And of course if I just leave them out there the animals will get into it anyway, who cares talking about politicians
Actually, I did have a pretty good weekend. I did some flying finally. I looked at the log book and I hadn't flown for almost two months
Which was kind of surprising
Wasn't the best of weather on Saturday? I was scheduled to go visit some people up in the north the very northern part of the Netherlands and
Roaning in
Elport of never been to before actually I've been there, but not certainly not solo and certainly not as a pilot and in command
And certainly not a use since I've had my flatless license
So I really didn't you know, it's kind of it's always kind of tricky when you go into a big airport that
Potentially has really big airplane to come in and out and you know, it's just unfamiliar territory, but it was fun
And
flew back yesterday
Which also wasn't just wasn't the best of weather all round. You know, we have a relatively low cloud base here in the UK
Man, I just wish I had two weeks two weeks. I could go to Portland within two weeks
I can finish my training for my
Instrument rating get the ticket and then be flying in a whole different airspace, but two weeks. You know, where am I gonna get it?
That's just not enough time in the day
Particularly since everything seems to be changing and moving so fast and all kinds of stuff happening
We're in the middle of the
The convention the democratic national convention out in Denver and I'm trying to follow what is best as possible
If it even on the way back in the Delta Sharia yesterday had BBC World on which I can get on six four eight AM
And we have a
Directional finder which is kind of the the World War II technology
Which will tune into that frequency so instead of in fact
I know exactly where the transmitter for the BBC was located because that's where that thing does is basically a needle
With a compass heading around it, which you can set and then you just tune into a frequency and the needle will point in the general direction of where the
Where the signal is coming from and it was of course kind of pointing towards London. I think yeah, yeah, it was pointing towards London
So I was listening to some of the coverage on the on BBC world, which is kind of cool
On the it's about about 45 minutes over the water and there's really nothing else going on
There's no one else up usually. There's no one else up there anywhere that I'm flying
That was kind of fun
So this is the daily source code where we specialize in aggregating aggravation everything source today from the drop data drop.io slash daily source code
Just sticking with the politicians theme for a second and of course all these links to be found either on the drop
Which you can subscribe to the RSS feed is a whole bunch of ways you can get to that or just go to the individual show notes a daily source code.com
Look for today's episode 785
Also cross posted on curry dot com
So this came from Japan today
Which kind of blew me away
The story is they're quite well the claim is coming from a one-time
Manichi Shimbun journalist
Who
Pooh was posted in Seoul
and says
North Korea's
Came John Ewe he died in 2003. He was replaced by a look like
Which now they think about it. I've never heard this guy talk
I don't I not that I can recall not that I would understand it
According to the stories actually, you know the the look alike the standin is actually two and a half inches taller
Then the original can you know the OG Kim Kim Jong-il. I think what I'll do is I'll send a note to Uncle Don and ask him if he's familiar with the story
And because he's met him and he's had many dealings with him and so he would know
So we'll see if we can debunk this story just thought it was pretty interesting that that that popped onto the radar screen
More political stuff
And probably because we talked with you know I've been talking about how messed up certain circles of
Government and justice and the police force really are and so here's the story
Xus diplomat who admitted taping his sexual encounters with teenage girls apparently some under the age of 16
While I was stationed in Brazil in the Congo
Was sentenced Friday to 20 years the maximum possible prison term
It's guys 42 is younger than I am
It's our leniency claiming a lot of the things that cultural differences in those countries made sex with teenage girls more acceptable
Okay, you know the guy clearly doesn't need to be in jail. He needs help
This is what always kills me about
About this situation, you know and obviously most people want to kill guys that do this
And maybe that is the only solution that we decide on as
As human beings and brothers and sisters that we should kill our ill and weak. I don't know if that's
the right
track
But certainly locking him up for 20 years is only gonna remove his problem from society for 20 years or until whenever he can get out on parole
Kindies help
Let's see if there's anything about any any help while he's in jail
So of course the link to the story and in the show notes as usual
But it just kind of shows you know that more and more of these stories start bubbling to the top about politicians
And in this case, I don't know what was this guy. He was
Just says an XUS diplomat. Doesn't I can't find out what he was
Maybe some kind of ambassador type
And this kind of stuff. It just you hear more more about it and the real problem with it is
Outside of the obvious is that it makes these types of guys and
Women perhaps I wonder if it's only men who do this stuff. That's another question for you
It makes them you know susceptible to blackmail which only fox it up and makes the whole
rabbit hole deeper and brings in more of these people
Psychopaths and ill people that
Well, we have to kind of I think we should make a uniform decision. What we do with people like this
But it seems like it's rampant among these circles
If that weren't crazy enough
This is I guess all 50 states in the US have what they call a safe haven law which means
And I didn't know about this until I read this story which is a story from the Huffington Post
Excuse me, which is probably cross posted from somewhere else
There's a safe haven law which allows parents to abandon and unwanted children at hospitals with no questions asked
I didn't even know about that
And that by itself is certainly worthy of discussion and and troubling
But in Nebraska they and I don't know if this wasn't really intentional if someone didn't think about it
But it is interesting to note that the safe haven law for Nebraska
Um, goes beyond babies and the story says potentially permits the abandonment of anyone under 19
teenagers
Well now you're talking my language
I definitely would like to abandon my teenager from time to time
Who by the way turns 18 tomorrow big party here in G-town?
Oh god, where's the time gone
But the stories certainly things to be looked at and followed up on
Just uh just crazy
Hey, I wanted to give you guys this since I got a lot of notes about this about my E71 in fact
It doesn't seem to be available everywhere
I must have been such a total fluke that I was able to pick this one up and what has it been now?
It's been almost a month ago. I think yeah it's been
Yeah about a month ago when I came back from from holiday and instead of buying the iPhone
I picked up the E71 from Nokia
I've been an E61 fan and of course
Actually, I've walked the entire upgrade path with Nokia. Have an eye I started with the a with the
E60
E61 I think and then the came the 61 eye yeah
So I wonder if there'll be a E71 eye if you're not familiar with it. Please take a look at this first of all
This thing it's sexy and it just feels right
It just feels really good in the palm of your hand
And I think I've mentioned in previous show all the things I like about it
There's and you know, just a couple of things I wanted to mention that I don't like about it
Really the tomb the the main feature that bugs me the most is the physician of the headset and the angle of the headset jack
So the actually the the headset jack on the phone itself is on the the top right not on the top
But on the right-hand side near the top
which is
Regardless of what kind of plug you put in there is not
groovy for
Portable use because you want to slip the phone into your pocket and
If it has something sticking out the side it's you know, it's either gonna catch on the on the side of your pocket or it's just it's uncomfortable
It just doesn't make any sense it should be on top or to be on the bottom so you can put you know the phone in your pocket upside down
I'm sure there was just it's a lack of space or whatever it was but an ergonomic nightmare and then the
The headset itself has an angled plug which makes sense because it's coming out of the side
But that it catches on everything and you know it gets jerked out
It has one of those behind the head
Special headphones
You know, so of course has a microphone built in and it has one long
So like the left the left ear wire is a shorter than the right ear wire because you're gonna wrap that around your neck
Which I actually kind of like that system so that you have the wire off to one side and not in the middle like like an iPod headphone
So that's okay, but just the combination of that that the hooked jack and and the headphone jack on the phone is is it's really irritating very very
dumb
Because I use it as you know as my iPod now and
And I love yeah, I love the the the podcast and client of course. I've loaded up my my mevio channel
The on the go channel in there and that you know that's fantastic. It seems like the the whole machine is just so fast compared to the
The 60 or the 61 the 61 I models and it seems to be some improvements to the software itself some extra features
Which of course is the simbian operating system
then the only other thing that is noticeable
if
And you know I like to typically I for some reason I like to close applications
I'm starting to learn how not to do that
But if you open up the address book and you have a large a number of addresses now
I don't even have that many I'm looking right now. I have
764 addresses in my address book and firing up the address book
Takes minutes
So you what you don't want to do is ever close that one out if you have a big address book
I don't know what it's doing. I don't know why it's it I've never seen it is the same address book I've used on
On the 61 and that had no problem. So it must be doing something parsing something figuring something out but
Extremely irritating and then
I think that's actually it that's those are the only the only things I don't really like what I haven't figured out as if
Since it has built in GPS if I can actually encode GPS information into the pictures I take with the
Lovely 3.2 megapixel auto focus camera with flash Yahoo, and that's still like the
Test out the the video calling feature which because it also has a little camera on the front
Which is probably a VGA camera, but I'd love to try that out. I just have no one to test it out with and and by the way
I don't have I don't actually get a 3G signal here at the house. I have to
Go off site so to speak
But otherwise still love on this device battery still unfricing believable
How good the battery life is of this thing so there you go
Love in it quite a bit
I wouldn't want to trade it in for an iPhone for anything which may sound kind of weird coming out of my mouth
But these days I'm just completely into functionality and wanted all to work
Uh
tracking the world finances as the
All of the Europeans oh the European all the central bankers got together
I think it's an annual thing they all hang out in Jackson Hole Wyoming
Excuse me those sippety there I've heard other things about other conferences taking place that I can't quite recall what it is
But they basically came out and said well yeah, it doesn't look too good and
Is a story here from CBC Canadian Broadcasting Corporation and it looks like you know
You can almost they're talking about taking bets on how long it's going to take for another bank to fail the Norwegian bank just failed the other day
The rock tealed we sound a lot like raw child to my to my ears
So the Norway Norwegian Central Bank had to step in there remember that you know all of the stuff this whole system is
As far as I can tell it's just coming apart at the seams you know by primarily by greed and
um
debt just too much a debt for the for the American system to handle and I think that's just spread
drastically throughout the rest of the world of course the
The mortgage crisis uh we went from subprime to the mortgage crisis now just the damn financial crisis
And everyone's got a theory on it, but at the end of the day it's the central banks including the federal reserve
Who are to blame because they're the ones that create the money so
Whether it was intentional or not whether they knew what they were doing or not it's it's coming from them
So the guy we got to look at them for for helping us out in in this mess or into this mess
Here's a couple of the high profile bankruptcies that already have taken place in 2008
I just want to say it again because we get so used to the word billion
And you only need a thousand billions to create a trillion and the US has nine trillion
I mean these numbers they they seem pretty outrageous and big, but after a while
He's just like a billion million trillion whatever, but you got to realize the the scope of this how how big this is
So in August we had first priority bank of Florida taken over by the FDIC after incurring significant loan losses
Of course July we had the 32 billion
Dollar failure of indie Mac bank of Pasadena, California
That'll cost the taxpayers in the US for or eight billion dollars
Of course in March JPMorgan Chase and company bought Bear Stearns, which was brokered by
The federal by the Fed by Bernanke and all kinds of loans are made available for that
And then of course we have Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac which is as far as I'm concerned are virtually bankrupt
And they've got at least half of of the 12 trillion dollar US mortgage market
And that's just the mortgage stuff that we're looking at you know what what you read very little about other than people pleading for
Transparency in the marketplace is these derivatives and you know if we have a I'd love for a financial
Subvant out there to call in and please do me a favor and and use the the phone line on the on the source code drop
You know there's a phone number there and then there's a pin code the after use please use that because that's just all in one place
I get everything from there. I've even changed the show notes to reflect that
To call in and leave a message explain to people what a what a
A default swap is something you know like a vanilla
Deal which I think is what most of these deals are I mean it's been explained to me
I understand that I'm not a good ex you know, I'm not good at explaining how it works
But consider that it's probably about four or five hundred thousand billion dollars
Which is five hundred trillion. Yeah, so something like that some astronomical amount of money which is or yeah
Money which has been swapped and traded but it's only maybe two or three percent is actually covered and
You know this is because you have two parties and there's those transparency as to if that party can actually pay
One you know when it's it's it's more credit stuff that is just vague and unclear and if that shit starts to unravel
Well, I think it could actually just fall apart. It really could big discussion with John city work about that
I don't know agenda he disagrees course
But it's just it's just it's just kind of freaking me out to see all that
Again all of these stories sourced from
From your suggestions your links so
Either that's going to make everybody happy and make the audience very small or these stories are just
You know interesting stuff. It's all reports from mainstream news. That's why I'm saying aggregating the the aggregation maybe the aggression
Because this stuff never really floats to the top it just doesn't
Although I have seen this report around but no one's really fallen over themselves about New York City's new
High-tech defense perimeter which includes and this is this is nuts
If you haven't read about this again link in the show notes
16 million dollar plan. It's the LMSI the lower Manhattan security initiative
It's centerpiece an array of 3,000 cameras that will turn the entire area
Into a 1.7 square mile of observation deck
Let me read some of this for this funny and contrast to London surveillance system which we all know about
There's a several cameras per inhabitant of the city the so-called ring of steel
New York's cameras will do more than identify terrace after they struck the new cameras will be fully networked video
Intelligence algorithms that aim to spot potential attackers before they perpetrate their crimes
Wouldn't be used to track anybody would it
Electronic license plate readers
New software can sound that alarm when it spots suspicious behavior like bags left on a platform truck circling
People entering a building through an exit
Please don't go up the down staircase
We truly truly are prisoners, aren't we?
And just and no one's complaining about this stuff maybe what they say about chem trails is true
You know, we're just completely numbed out and don't give a shit
But
All right one more for you for our friends over here in the UK
I think I saw the store the story maybe it was even on the BBC
It was on news night or something but now it's hit the New York Times
So it's definitely an older story for those of us over here on the aisle
But it's basically about
Crete the island of Cretan grease and
That's where a lot of young Britons go to
Go to vacation. It's not just Greek there's a couple of but it's around the Greek islands, but also I beef Spain
You know couple different places
That that are reporting that you know the Britons
Well, yeah, I have the code for you. This is how how most foreign countries where the Brits go on holiday view
I'll just say us
They scream they sing they fall down. They take their clothes off. They cross dress. They vomit
It's only the British people not the Germans or the French. This is
Malia's mayor Malia, I guess is a town in Crete
That's nice. They scream they sing they fall down. They take their clothes off. They cross dress and they vomit
Yeah some statistics for you
British behavior abroad is the British Foreign Office as reports 12 month period
2006 and 2007 six hundred and two Britons were hospitalized 28 raped in Greece alone
1,591 died in Spain died
1500 people died in a years time
Jesus
2,032 were arrested
Does anyone else see that this is an issue
And and I'm telling it's because
What happened to the thin white dupe type Brit who you know would stand up to his government?
I know Margaret Thatcher broke the unions and and and and the minors, but I'm still looking for that spark where is it?
Where's the you know all we're doing is just getting hammered and
cross dressing and puking
and it's just the complete
Numbing of our of our consciousness
This is just not okay and definitely not good
It's the youth of the nation
TOD a source code favorite
Let's stay on the rest of my life
I wish I wouldn't know cuz I didn't kiss my mama goodbye
I didn't tell that a love there how much I can't a thing
I'm off to all the talks and all the wisdom we share
Where I just did what I always do every day to stay with team for us
Get up to school but who knows that this day wasn't like the
Wrapped instead of taking the test off to cooler the chat
Call me by my dad to see it come and everybody was running
but I couldn't hear nothing except
Don't lose and you have to so fast
I didn't really know this day to rise apart
Class maybe this kid was reaching out for love
Or maybe for one money he forgot who he was
Or maybe this kid just wanted to be her
Whatever it was I know it was because
We'll be our
We'll be sure we'll be our
We'll be sure
We'll be sure we'll be
We'll be sure we'll be our
We know we are, we know, you're the nation.
Who's the blame for the life that drags this claim?
No matter what you say, it'll take away the pain that...
...and that I feel the side of time to mobilize...
...or nobody, nobody's the blame, we need a cryer.
You said the way that the story goes, will it ever make sense?
Somebody's got to know, just gotta be more to light than this.
Just gotta be more to everything I thought exists.
We are the eye.
We are the nation, we are the we are.
You're the nation, we are the we are.
We are the we are.
We are the we are, we are the we are.
Drinking ourselves to death.
Entertaining ourselves to death.
Eating ourselves to death.
As right?
We are the youth of the nation.
Now to my talking about, I'm almost 44. Next week.
That's playable on death.
I like that.
Some reason a lot of, I'm into a lot of like real heavy, heavy music lately.
But we do have some other stuff coming up on today's show as well.
And I'm pretty sure it's going to be another show that's over now.
I think I can kind of handle this or at least the vibe I'm in right now as we aggregate aggravation.
Maybe aggravate aggression.
It seems like I can do two shows a week with the rest of the schedule.
I'm still on early mornings and early mornings for the Dutch stuff and late nights for San Francisco.
So I don't know, but my asthma elbow as we would say.
You know, and I'm a man pissed off because, I guess as I said was the bank holiday.
So I knew it wouldn't have kicked off, but today we kick off a special promotion in the UK.
We now have, and I'm very proud to announce, go daddy.co.uk,
which has pricing and pounds.
And in addition to that, you can get.co.uk domain names.
It's cheaper than in, I mean, by far cheaper than anything else that's being sold here in the United Kingdom.
But I didn't get my special code.
Of course, I have DSC 1, DSC 2, DSC 3 for go daddy.com for dot com dot net dot org etc.
But not for dot code at UK.
So do me a favor.
Check out your favorite other brick, brick castor, brick podcaster.
Get their code. If you're going to buy a dot code at UK domain name, use their code.
I think we're down to like, it's somewhere like £3.50 or something.
It's literally like the $6.95 in the state to get for dot com address.
I think it's the equivalent of that in pounds here in the UK.
So the best deal better than any other dot code.uk domain name deal.
If you find something better, let me know immediately.
I'm sure the good folks are go daddy will go out and top that.
So very proud to be supporting go daddy in their UK rollout.
You know, I've obviously, you've seen me shift.
I'm used for those of you been around for seven hundred seven hundred eighty five episodes.
Clearly you've witnessed a lot of transformation of myself moving from.
Interested in technology to somewhat trivial to podsafe music.
All the way through to where I am now, which is is much more than just what I'm doing with me.
What I'm doing with with the source code, but really what I'm doing in life, I guess, and that must be.
I'm sure it has something to do with my age and where I'm at right now.
But I've pretty much decided that I really have to remain very open for all kinds of possibilities of things.
And that, of course, was a big part of the awakening show seven eighty one.
Because this can't be all there is.
And you know, that I just don't accept.
And of course, with a lot of things I've been talking about.
There's been some, you know, a good amount of ridicule, which, you know, was to be expected and I'm definitely careful at how I am.
At how I phrase things and, you know, I think the chuckle heads out there, you know, no one I'm talking about.
But when it comes to.
Some alternative beliefs, like, well, like, 2012, there you go.
This is a big one. This is the number you see everywhere. It's the Mayans, the Mayan calendar ending. It's a so much information.
And there's been information about this for thousands of years because they basically wrote it that long ago.
But now comes an interesting twist to all of this or at twist something, just interesting.
This is from National Geographic, a lab earth filled with stone temples and pyramids and 14 caves.
Some of them underwater has been uncovered of Mexico's Yucatan Peninsula.
And they announced this just last week. This is exciting stuff because, you know, if you're, if you're into this and you're into the concept that we are all just brothers and sisters of the galaxy and that there's a lot more out there and that we just haven't transformed into the dimension where we can actually see what else is around us.
Instead of this reality, which has been created and carefully maintained for us primarily by the news media.
When something like this comes along, that seems like big news to me and I'm quite surprised, frankly, that I hadn't heard about it until, of course, the trusty drop came along.
According to my and myth, the souls of the dead had to follow a dog with night vision on a horrific and watery path and endure myriad challenges before they could rest in the afterlife.
Sounds like Indiana Jones.
In one of the recently found caves, researchers discovered a nearly 300-foot concrete road that ends at a column standing in front of a body of water.
This is cool, man. Any more info on this stuff.
Hit the drop with it because it's, is it just coincidence? Is it all just kind of coming together at the same time? I don't know.
What I will say, and, and I hadn't really, I've never really looked at crop circles too much because, you know, I have cares.
And of course, I'd been kind of hit with a meme that, well, you know, those original crop circles, you know, some college students did it or whatever.
And then I found this site called cropcircleconnector.com, and just go take a look at this site.
And, and, and, and they track crop circles throughout the world. And very interesting is that if I just look at their tally here, um, the world worldwide, they've got 50.
I don't know when they started doing this. I, crop circles, 2008. Okay.
So 50 in this year so far around the world, which haven't looked at yet because my eye was immediately drawn to the 65 for the UK alone.
And you look at these crop circles. And this is, you know, this is not just circles. This is like really major, uh, geonomic shit geometric shit, which is just, and, and many cases, phenomenally beautiful.
And a lot of them seem to be located in a wheelchair for some reason. Oops. Hold on. That actually, you're probably not here in that, but it started up some music. I didn't want to do that.
Um, so in, uh, and, and like every single day, there's a new one almost every single day. And here's what I like about crop circles.
Because it fits right in with 9-11. You know, if you even, um, broke the topic of 9-11 with someone saying, hey, you know, it seems like there was a lot going on there.
Some people must have been of all, somebody must have known something. What you normally get is that's impossible. Someone would have had, well, someone would have come out and said something by now.
That's so big a secret. You cannot keep it in, uh, it just cannot be kept quiet. Someone would have to, that talk about it sooner or later.
Okay. So I'll accept that. But then you have to kind of say the same would be true for crop circles. Because these things are so intricate, so huge. So many of them that if it's actually done by people hoaxing, first of all, I'd hire them for an architectural firm which had start tomorrow because they really has some awesome design sense.
Um, the same has to hold true. Well, then, you know, so many people would have to know about this. And of course, it would be college kids that someone would eventually have to say, yeah, I did it.
We all know about the two old guys who claim that they did, uh, that they would do in crop circles for 13 years, but they're not doing to a day. Every single day. It's just, it's amazing. And some, and, and the symbols, who does it? How knows what they mean?
Well, I think that just like, it's some thing or someone or some energy, just send and shit to make us happy. Just saying, hey, we're here. Take a look at this. Here's another beautiful drawing for you.
Yeah, crop circle connector.com fantastic. And again, I'm just bringing that up because it makes so much sense, uh, if you, if you want to say that 911 could have been an inside job, then there's the same holds true for this.
You know, this can't be an inside job or a fakeery because too many people would know about it and too many people would be talking about it. Interesting know that you, I mean, considering that certainly in the UK, where they do love a, you know, a good scandal or something wacky or some UFO stuff.
This year's scale of how many of these things are being created is certainly not being reported in mainstream media mainstream media primarily the big ones, of course, owned by a Rupert Murdoch here in the UK, which reminds me actually this story that I'll talk about that a little bit later on.
So there's one other thing that I do want you to take a look at, since this was left on the drop. If you want to learn more about the Mayans, what the significance of these caves might be, but really about the transformation.
The transformation that is being talked about about the earth and there a lot of this is is well known, you know, there's an increased son activity every 11 years.
That's was been taking place for the probably the past 70 years has been more than the more son activity than ever.
But it literally as far as I understand it will affect the magnetic energy of the of the poles and we're not talking about the guys with the missiles near Russia.
And, you know, there's all these different things that are supposed to happen.
And what I'm doing just personally is I'm trying to get a little bit more in contact with as corny as it sounds.
With nature, with mother earth trying to reconnect a little bit trying to open myself up to a possibility of anything else that might come our way.
And I was given some advice to try and sync up with the I think it's called the human resonance.
So this is a frequency and I've heard of this because I think in, I think one of my helicopter books that actually talks about the human resonance because which is a I think it's seven hertz seven.
And they talk about the ground loop effect.
If you, if you're on one skid or you lift off on one skid and can't exactly, I've never, I've never, it's never happened to me.
But if you pull too much power or you actually, you put it into the exactly the right RPM the rotor.
The ground loop will occur, so then you've got not made, maybe it's seven hundred RPM who knows I should look it up again.
Then it starts to interact with the, with the actual resonance of the earth and then basically what happens is the helicopter spins around tips over and it's a day record.
So what I'm from what I understand the resonance this seven hertz is actually elevating in some spots and is moving up to 10, 11 and some places even 12 hertz.
And so I'm trying to connect to that and actually try that with, with the audience on the Dutch show on arrow classic rock the other morning.
Then you know, here's what you should try, so I'd like you chuckle heads to give it a go.
You know, whenever, whenever you're the opportunity, when you have some time to just chill out for five or ten minutes, just sit on a chair or lay down whatever makes it feel comfortable.
Basically, try and put both of your feet flat on the ground.
I think if you do this on the ground floor, it's probably best, but it shouldn't make any difference.
Visualize that you are literally shooting root through the bottom of your feet down into the earth and trying connect with this seven hertz vibration, this energy.
And try and channel that just in your imagination up through your feet through your legs, you know, the bottom half your legs up through your thighs up through your, your groin area, which is essentially your lower chakra.
And this is not shit. I'm just making up, you know, it's been around for a long time. I think people used to actually learn about chocros and school. We don't do any of that anymore.
And see if you can move that energy up higher. And things start to happen. You certainly feel very rested, a lot of people fall asleep.
But three people after trying this only once, three people saw things in the night sky, which they could not identify, which was highly interesting to me. So I'm, I'll do that. I can take five minutes a day and do that.
And I think you chuckle heads, you just might want to give it a shot as well.
How are we doing on time? Because I got about half a list left of stuff.
Well, 42 minutes. Okay. Let's move along.
Another link for you to check out referring back to to 9.11.
This is, you know, we've talked about, you know, really how mainstream works perfectly well with independent media, but more in editorial function.
Because there are some great journalists doing some great journalistic work in mainstream media, but either they're not placed poorly placed or, or just filtered out.
And if there's not enough of, of quote, fact about something, it just doesn't make it into the mainstream consciousness.
So this is the highly credible people who question 9.11 blog 9.11 summary dot blog spot dot com. I'm not going to go through this whole list.
But it, it starts right off with the co-chairs of the 9.11 commission said that the 9.11 commissioners new military officials misrepresented the facts to the commission and the commission considered recommending criminal charges for such false statements.
It's a mainstream media article on the Washington Post dot com. That's just the top one.
Give that a look. It's in the show notes a daily source code dot com.
And then this thing.
This really, uh, this really freaked me out when I heard this.
I did want to share it with you. And I'm not quite sure what the origin is. It came in on the drop drop dot IO slash daily source code title generation kill.
And it sounds like two marines either in Afghanistan or in Iraq. I'm pretty sure it's Iraq.
And it was an OG G file. So I had a trans code, which also kind of made me think that maybe it was a portable recording device or certainly something.
Even if you listen to it, it sounds like they're handing a portable recording device back and forth amongst themselves. So it sounds extremely legit.
But it, it really does say something about what's happening over in the desert, where our brothers and sisters are children, our boys and girls, 19 years old, killing other children.
Other brothers and sisters. And for what fucking energy, I can oil drugs and gold. That's all it seems to be about.
And, you know, it troubles me so much.
And we don't even, you know, we're such hypocritic fuck wards controlled by our mainstream media that we don't even want to acknowledge it.
And when you listen to these guys talk about their lives and comparing it to the lives of, in this case, American citizens.
And what's important to them and what their days are like and what our days are like.
It's just, it's just unconscionable that the true facts that what war really looks like and what's really happening except a daily body count.
Well, that's all you get. Body count. Just a couple numbers.
No one even checks if they're for real anymore. There's no pictures. There's no pictures of the coffins draped in flags.
Man, we would be so much more pissed off. We really saw what was going on, which is the only thing that was right about Vietnam as the press, at least had free reign in reporting on it and showing what was really happening.
And it was scary and it affected people. And now we're all just drugged out one way or the other.
We're completely asleep, apathetic, and don't give a shit.
Listen to these two marines. I think about what it means to you and what you should be meaning to them.
You're gonna remember 1775. I was born and a bomb graded. My mother was in him 16 and my father was the devil.
Each moment that I lived is an additional credit upon your life. I ate concertina, this napal, but I could shoot around through a freeze ass at 300 meters.
I traveled the globe, first year on anti-americans everywhere I go, for the river of Mom, Chevrolet, baseball, and apapai.
I'm a grown, I'm a dirty nasty, sticky, sweaty, filthy, beautiful little son of a bitch that's kept the roof roof in the board for 225 years.
On the United States Marine, look like soldiers, top leg sails, slap the shoot at a boat home.
So the eagle from the earth was the roofed on an anchor from the Navy, and on the 7th day in God rested, whoever ran his perimeter will run the show ever since.
Whoever by night, joker betrus, who my God, stood for the best.
The Social Sacrifice of day-to-day military personnel, especially combat veterans, is under-appreciated.
And you got the American Society, when it run, the fastest they can to the counter stop, to the fucking new stance, and grab motherfucking us weaklys, and fucking people magazine, just to see what fucking Jake Jillonfall did on Thursday afternoon.
You know what I did Thursday afternoon? I put one of my motherfucking Marines on a plane. I put that motherfucking bird to fucking know where.
I picked his lifeless ass up body, put him on a stretcher, and put him off.
I'll put that while that being a motherfucking magazine.
Or how about, let's put a day in a life of fucking any average Marine out here, going through the streets of our body.
Their biggest concern is that, you know, they couldn't buy a local latte at fucking Starbucks because it was under construction.
Our biggest motherfucking concern is getting blown up on fucking 29 or 5 in Michigan.
The women go home and they're going to say, wave your little flag and say, welcome home, thanks for serving all like to go on, not get in the fall.
There it is, folks, we're sitting here fighting for your freedoms. You got the right to say what you want.
We got the right to much of your fucking mouth, we disagree.
We got the right to much of your fucking mouth, we got the right to much of your fucking mouth, we got the right to much of your fucking mouth, we got the right to much of your fucking mouth, we got the right to much of your fucking mouth.
Some of those that work for us is, draw the thing that works for us is, oh, you're the name of, you're the name of, you're the name of, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you.
Now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you.
Now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they
told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you
do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now there you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what you told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you, now you do what they told you you do what Didn't even wrong
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, ready, jump, go,
I can't believe you can't tell me
I pray for those boys, I all children, the Iranian children, the Georgian children, the
South, the city of children, my own child, all of them.
Christ, man, this is just so wrong.
It's starting to really bother me.
So anyways, I was saying earlier about Murdoch, great documentary called Outfox.
It's a Rupert Murdoch's war on journalism.
You gotta see that.
A whole bunch of ex-fox news reporters.
It starts with WTTG, I think it's in Washington, D.C., and they tell you, they'll show
you exactly how it all happens and how the manipulation of, you know, the media takes place.
They will explain to you exactly how it goes and it's not like journalists are dumb, journalists
are great, most of them are, but it's the decisions that the editors make and that comes
from up high and you gotta see this documentary and that's all, that's gotta be homework.
You gotta take a look at that.
Got Ray on the Charlie coming up for you, which means we'll have something hokey going
back to 19.
I don't even listen to them anymore because they just want to be surprised by whatever
Ray puts together some kind of song from the soundtrack in my life and usually some
embarrassing moments from my past career.
So we'll get to that in a second, here's another one.
Here's how we, here's how much we love our kids, San Antonio, Texas, court authorities
will be able to track students with a history of skipping school under a new program requiring
them to wear ankle bracelets with global positioning systems monitoring.
Oh man, this is what we used to call play in hokey, right?
And you played hokey, you got the tension.
And what is this now?
Because we have the technology, we're going to slap an ankle bracelet on our kids with GPS
so we can track them anywhere.
Oh, of course, at least one privacy group is worried.
The ankle bracelets will infringe on the students' privacy.
Yeah, no shit, this is lunacy.
And maybe we should stop trying to put GPS based band-aids on the problems and find out
maybe these kids are just too fucking intelligent for the idiotic schooling that we're
giving them.
My daughter's on to it.
She's totally, and she's like, man, they teach me crap at school.
And you want to hear what the, what she liked the most was English literature because
she could just go back to old stuff and read it and interpret it.
And you know, that's just, but it's literature, it's not history, it's ridiculous.
So now, you know, now, of course, she's off to college starting in September.
She's going to study drama and photography, which is specialized courses, but as a base,
a base level.
Dude, she learned a shitload more from just traveling around the world with us than
anything she learned in school.
So maybe these kids are just, you know, the next generation, maybe they're just extremely
brilliant.
Ever think of that, that this whole ADHD that all of a sudden became an illness and
gives us reason to pop riddle in on our kids and, you know, in some extreme cases, give
an electro shock therapy that, you know, maybe that's just because they're fucking brilliant.
Is that possible?
It seems certainly seems possible in my mind that there's a next step of evolution
in these kids.
Certainly, certainly feels that way to me.
Yeah, so instead of actually trying to fix the problem, there you go.
That's what you got to do.
Slap a GPS based ankle bracelet on.
Boy, the soundtrack to my life, let's take a look at the landscape on a road trip through
your life.
These episodes and queries, the soundtrack to my life, brings us back to my team for
our good.
The most 20 years old remember his parents in an illness and tried to make living
fubbying a winter in restaurants.
He also did some Dutch viral radio work on that radio, as certain moments and certainly
the escalation letter together, the videotape of himself to be boss of the world we
are talking about in the broadcast station of the Netherlands, from the car.
And can this be breaking broadcasting as the host of the team, the music television program
countdown.
So, if you want to be the media star, you also have to do some radio.
So, the first time with everything can be very scary.
A home for show or national radio with an out-free or malicious, and you still know what
your first record was on the national radio.
Yes, I do.
I remember very well.
I remember a flashback to May 25, 1984, around a 30 p.m.
This was an unspeaked break on national radio, star of his confession.
I don't remember.
Here we go.
We move through.
This is a hobby.
When you hear some, well, wake me up before your go-go, maybe something drew that into the two forming.
I won't.
All of that's right.
They want me to do the show in English.
I remember that.
The explain what I'm doing here actually I'm filling in for start to bat.
Laying work, part of the truth is bitter, I think, being a boy is not the wilder.
It's a fact.
This is embarrassing.
I think there's a lot of fun, hot-plane records here on radio Veronica.
It's really scary.
Go above in the beginning.
Give me five, 60, let's go.
Wh elsaheem!
Are they ready to play?
It's really scary.
Get up!
Oh yeah!
That's a dyro!
I hope the website will even find everything about two short-term on-lines.
Hey, what's this?
Hello?
Alright, now for a while.
Hey, Tom, good to hear from you.
I'm late, I did.
My head is in the green of the night,
and I see the love of you,
been visiting and re-cast again.
The A-own guilty,
had a check-as for some old A-use material,
that of me.
What the heck?
Why I got you in the line?
Can you upload the full episodes without the editing?
I need you to know the truth that I've come on.
I don't want to get in trouble with the man.
About the music rides man.
Come on, man.
It's on music.
40s for old tapes.
No one's going to complain.
Alright, man.
I've been left.
What do you do with you like the first?
Well, we are looking at 984 as a moment.
I need you to work.
He's got all my old tapes.
I've got all my old tapes.
40 flash.
Thanks Tom.
No problem.
Thank you for being late.
Thanks Tom.