We are the DSC 749 amidst the construction for the huge gala that will be the DSC 750.
Cruise are hard work building a large stage for all the pot safe bands that will be performing
as part of the event.
It'll be quite an astounding occasion with podcasters known around the world, present
to all wish the podfather himself, a wonderful show.
He is three quarters of the way to a thousand shows, it's just remarkable.
While the work air continues for the big event, please enjoy in the meantime, the DSC 749.
The DSC is the daily source code, daily source code.
The 16 million dollars worth of air playing strapped by us.
To the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying for each and each turn.
Podcasters is no great.
Every watching is what you do.
Every looking at you.
Every wonder will come out tonight.
Every time you get it right, get it right.
Everybody's working for the weekend.
Everyone's working for the Sundayinga's working.
Everyone's working for the weekend.
Everybody's work for the weekend.
Somebody's working for the weekend.
Everyone's working for the weekend.
Everybody's working for the weekend.
Everybody's working for the weekend with the weekend.
Everybody's working.
Everybody's more working for the weekend.
I'm sorry now, let's go over.
Oh man, you guys have sent me some awesome stuff to share today.
It's New Day, I feel alone.
Oh, all love the city, you just can't appreciate your love, sir.
Your love, sir.
You're the new day, I'll be your one.
I've got my suitcase, screw it all down.
Pull it to get away in my hand.
But no more, you'll be like it, no less in my hand.
You're the new day, I feel alone.
I've got my suitcase, screw it all down.
Can't take it so late, all the problems of the day.
When the people here were told, just don't need you anymore.
What if that it wasn't all?
Could you make it on your own?
Got my shoes, you want to spend it and play some time with me.
And you stand without a rule.
As people love it, you, because you can't communicate.
Why am I so busy?
And I can't love the most days you got around more.
You'll dreamer, you'll dreamer.
And you'll be as we go.
I can't love you.
You'll see me so late, I feel alone.
You're the new day, I feel alone.
You'll see me so late, I feel alone,
I love you
And I love you
You're a day
I feel alone
And I feel I don't know
I'm a little angry today
I'm a super super super motivated
You guys sent lots of awesome songs
From me to play
Both through email
Links to the pod save music network
Links to mashups
Stuff that's been dropped in
Drop.io slash daily source code
Oh man you guys got some great stuff
And a lot of complaints
But particularly today we'll be talking about
China
I think I have to turn down the
The heater here in the studio
It's making a lot of racket
And I got whatever outside
I think I have a helicopter
I have at least one fixed
The wing aircraft flying by
It sounds like there's a lawn mower
And still people have reasons
To call in and listen to this show
Adam, hi
It's Brenny Jones
How are you?
Reasons why I listen to the daily source code
I'm in a part from your
Dullsit tones
It's a channel
And now you have a thing about channels
BTpodshow.com
You've mentioned it quite a lot
For me the daily source code is
I'm mini channel
I get a bit of entertainment
Bit of music
Bit of discussion
Bit of thought provoking
And it's good
So for me it's one of the podcasts that I listen to
It brings his own form of entertainment
And it's just about what I'm looking for
In the morning when I'm driving to the office
So hey, have a great day
Keep up the good stuff
Love you to bed
Yeah, I love you to bed as well my friend
Actually I just found out turns out
That's a lawn mower outside
That's making this incredible racket
Want to say hi to the people
Checking me out live now on live
Trucker Lou is in a broken truck
And lumbered to North Carolina
Young pallette
Unfortunately having truck
Not actually he looks like young pallette
And the Netherlands got through
We've got Phillip Job
We've got see Oscars
Haven't some trouble getting through
Richard Hyde is checking us out
Tom von Art
Luke from the helm
Parkie can't get through his firewall
Of course, obviously I'm reading the Twitter messages
Which is kind of how this works
You guys provide the feedback
I provide the freight train
Mr. Curry
Jamaican in York here
Just figure out calling and tell you why I listened to Charlie
Okay, Mark
Well I've aside from it being quite informative
And entertaining
You know
Let you know in the club about myself
I'm a program, you see
Programme great many things
Quite a few languages actually
I know
You know, also a planner owned iPhone
Proved iPhone double
You know, I'm talking about iPhone beta right now
Just testing out some apps that I built
They're going to be a great online
You know, I like to tinker
You know, I'm like you in a lot of ways
We like to mess around with things
But you're firmly believed that
In this world where
We're all in this world to go
You know, we're all connected
Now pay attention to the Rostaman everybody
Because he's got something really good to say here
So you know
Give you a little example of how this takes place
How it plays out in my daily life
You know
Walked into the office the other day
And I saw a box next to the coffee machine
And you know when the box said that
I'm said PG tips
Oh my
Bell
I'm drinking a drink
Jamaica
Being a form of British colony
You know, we in Jamaica
I like to have a spot of tea
Everyone there
And I think I'm, you know, I've been here
And I'm talking about this PG tips thing
There were a few Britain officers
Obviously somebody brought it in
Well, I must say I don't
I try to cope with this PG tips
I let it steep for about three minutes
Like you suggested
And I will say that
I think good tea, I don't
That's really really good tea
Now I'm trying to get a whole lot of this PG tips
Gold, no
I hear that's a little hard to find
But I'm, I'm sure I'll track it down
You know, it's a big city, you know
Just wanted to let you know this
So life is, you know, we are all connected
Things happen
It's just a matter of us noticing
These little details in life
I, you know, you talk about the PG tips
The PG tips show up in my office
It's a beautiful thing, man
Just wanted to let you know
While it's, it's about life
It's about connections, you know
We're all, we're all one
One people
Absolutely
Jamaica
In New York
That's right, New York
Back on the show that you make it in New York
Boy, man, it's true, we are all connected
So I'm for you, my friend
Because, you know, you just don't hear enough reggae
Anywhere on mainstream media
Certainly not the hybrid, like this one
Y'all fire on the Fubar Friday freight train
A revolution never comes with a warning
A revolution never sends you an open
A revolution just arrived like the morning
Bring the alarm, we come to wake up the storm
They telling you to never worry about the future
They telling you to never worry about the torture
They telling you that you will never see the horror
It's been it all today, and we will believe in tomorrow
Three people
And bank accounts in Bahamas
Walls keep, I will never spend you through this time
I'll tell all the children in Bahamas
I'm something I must dance
In this, I'm a side of Bahamas
Maybe commercial for a Papa pill
Cold shot, the drug companies
Suck a little like a full shot
And Emirati babies would be GI Joe Father
10 years from now is anybody
Call the party up higher
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yeah, hah,Indoo, yo, woah, y'know, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo yo, yo yo, yo yo yo yo yo yo yo, yo, yo yo yo yo yo yo yo, yo yo yo yo yo yo, yo yo yo yo yo, yo yo yo yo yo yo yo, yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo, yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
Everyone addicted to the same nicotine
Everyone addicted to the same gasoline
Everyone addicted to a technical screen
Everybody trying to get the hands on the same green
The banks on the river to the banks of the greedy
All under it just taken back by the needy
We come from the country and we come from the city
Play us on a record, you can play us on the city
All the shit you keep in us
It's for the lives of the needs of your payment
You can never go to lies
It's out of cooperation, you can never go to lies
It's like beer and toss it
Legalize it, burn them boy's in the base
Time to travel, rumbling the speakers in and making you want to rap
It's for your hands, don't take a two another level
And you never have a ever-maCare team
Shall you buy another name?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no sorry, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, okay, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, yeah, no, no no, no, no, no, go we're, no, no you'll no,
SP describe glory
you finally
oh man love that sake
you were never e Chrongenes
maybe you were never eC
never eC
just the rice like the moon
come here
love you come away
don't you stop
faian
I've got to send these guys a note and let them know this is unacceptable.
99 bucks a month and people can't even get on and there's plenty of room playing a room for
more listeners and still it's messing up a little bit dimple monkey says oh man I feel like
jumpstarting my old lawnmower yeah boy I tell you what let's play some crazy shit right now
because of course there's the football friday freight trains this is where we let our hair down we
led loose we throw our pennies on the stage johnsey de Warack sent me a note the other day and he
said you you remember that guy that you played on the daily source code pad condell who had a lot to
say about the multicultural society in Britain he sent me a link to what he calls the US version
of that guy and although he's not quite as refined I fall in and love with this guy with the
things he has to say not everything because some of it is is really out there and some of it
downright racist but in general in general if you're talking about a good old boy from Brooklyn
New York from Brooklyn who's got some to say he was got some on his mind the kid from Brooklyn
is the place to go the guy to listen to hey the big man's back WWE that the kid from Brooklyn
that guy the old people out there realize it's six years six years were fighting his war
and I wrecked we went in there under the presumption they had weapons of less destruction
we went in and we found shit we found nothing will tell me how come when Saddam Hussein
ran I wrecked you had no terrorist there no out kinda no has balla no nothing he didn't have no
terrorist of anything soon as you got rid of Saddam all these terrorists all of a sudden
they come and direct where the fuck did they come from out of the fucking sky the world's
come and do it and remember remember when we invaded I wrecked and all the TV cameras was in
there and every night we can watch the world live live we can watch the U.S. soldiers
and vending I wrecked well tell me how come today they don't have TV cameras and I wrecked today
is the government afraid to show you something I mean come on give me a break put some TV cameras over there
don't you think the American public deserves the right to know the truth and what about the
think cheating he was on a talk show and the host asked him 64% of the American people are against
the Iraqi war you know what his answer was so so get the fuck out of here ready dick you mean you
fucking be as a fucking dollars you were all in fucking corporate rent bases you represent
tell the American public the fucking truth it's like shoveling horses and it's the fucking
time we came and get the plane simple truth how do you American government put the fucking TV
cameras over there and I wrecked I got the right to know as a taxpayer what the fuck is going on over there
anyway they come panic this is a big man don't worry don't worry shut up people
ain't think cheating you made a lot of fucking money fucking rent bases and a break man's always
had me to say yes this is a daily source code a daily source code all in casting with
I'm sorry this is the head test get it test young Paul yeah yeah it's a test number 118 and we're
gonna start right away with intro number one oh young the hell is that man how am I supposed to know what
that is nice getting me matter I have no idea number two oh you don't that's not that's not
regassely is it you're not gonna regrow me on my own show man that's you're sounded like it
and number three not Madonna okay but no idea what that first one was I think he was regrossing
a number two and definitely Madonna's Vogue a number three look at the answer and time's up and it's time for the
answer number one it's from 1985 I'll be the cutest to be here
it's my car number one genie by the BB and Q-Bass and this is answer number two
seven that's just regassely that's not official reggae what ever you need somebody you need somebody
regassely is answer number two and this is answer number three strike 90 it's Madonna Vogue
and that concludes hit this number 118 hell yeah so I don't mind if you do this week
well I got regassely I didn't get the title of course I got Madonna and Vogue so about two stars
out of three you couldn't keep up I want to check out the answers to this or any older hit test
or if you want to buy one or more of the tracks featured in the hit test online through iTunes
go to hittestupartshow.com there you'll find everything you need I'll write the end I'm
thanks you for playing everyone else thanks for listening see you next week for the next hit test
have a very nice week and remember try to think with your heart bye bye
back hit test that she built a gun in full young bullet that's come today and be a wealthy
teacher hey afraid trains got to make a stop because I'm run out of juice yeah an excellent man
I never would have gotten BB in Q band and I have to say I don't think whenever you need somebody
by regassely is an official reg roll uh nice try though hey how about the kid from Brooklyn huh
that guy is so funny uh he's actually charges for these videos that you can you got to see him you
have to see him on on the video he has a whole bunch of previews available at the kid from Brooklyn.com
I love that though hell yeah we should have some cameras over there and I rack so that the
taxpayers can see what's happening with our money got damn it fuck you dick chaining I love it I love it
hey Adam it's a Tim binder from the century media podcast first time calling in GF and I got to tell
you I am hooked and a conversation came up about why people are listening and checking out the
DSC and of course no agenda and the growth of that and I got to tell you you know you every day
sign off with a live your life with passion and you can hear the passion coming through on the podcast
idea with radio promotions and deal with a lot of stations and you know in that game and definitely
one thing that your podcast has that a lot of content out there on on radio lacks is that passion
you know and you can hear it I love listening to the music uh love the mashups love love the
buck cherry the other day it's great seeing bands like buck cherry on on the DSC and plenty other
great bands too that I've actually discovered and purchased from from the DSC including black lab
which you played a while back other than that just want to say keep up the great work wanted to join
the conversation I'm looking forward to the billboard article and for anyone else that also works
out there on the record side of things I definitely suggest the pod safe music network we've got
a bunch of bands up on the pod safe music network and like to think of course Michael Butler
in your San Francisco office he's been a huge help for us and yeah so if you get a chance check
out some of our tunes a couple of our our bands that are up there right now include in this moment
the god track called beautiful tragedy and a new one from firewin called mercenary man just went
up the other day and yeah just joined in the conversation thanks so much for the great content
always look forward to the DSC been listening now pretty short time for about three months but
that's about it 31 record rep living in Los Angeles great hair hope you win love yeah no home
all right man thank you thank you very much fantastic hey you guys sent a lot of really cool stuff
and I was going through the voicemail and as I said got a lot of china stuff to talk about
a little bit later on as we slow the freight train down for the footballer Friday edition of the
daily source code but you remember that guy guy running for senate in the garden state state of
New Jersey Murray Sabron and I think one of his aids called in and said you know Murray would
like to talk to you and I never honestly I never really got around to it and then I started looking
into this guy and he's Ron Paul is a big supporter of his and they do all kinds of things together
and low and behold coming through on the daily source code voicemail lines just this morning
Murray Sabron himself hello Adam this is Murray Sabron long-time friend of on all on the
sea to meet with him for the freedom rally of if there's something about our past situation
that's a story of liberty in our country one coming up in the dirt around April 20th to have
a lot of events for my campaign for the United States Senate that just like to give you
free free on it on it to a one yeah okay so I probably shouldn't play the uh probably shouldn't
play the phone number but how cool is that huh now look forward to seeing you thanks for my
excellent all right so now here's a guy going for a seat in the u.s. senate calling into the daily
source code after I ignored him which things they really want to be on the show I love that
okay definitely I'm going to call this guy we'll do that on Monday
comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip the member states of the European Union
are very own uh European Union savant the one-only comic strip blogger with a financial up
yeah I don't we go carry film on here's your EU correspondent csb yes you wrote that
against three strikes piracy policy okay so just to let you know what this is about
this is something that I believe is already in place in France and the UK has been looking at it
and it was just voted down in the uh in the in the European parliament the idea is if you're caught
downloading or uploading quote license content I think they're particularly talking about music
you get three strikes and after the third strike apparently you can no longer get broadband service
anywhere in your country and of course they'll kill your children but as you know I was to late last week
to send comment so this week a financial story the European investment bank EID is a EEDU
version of word bank and interestingly it is directed by such people as politician
Alistair Darling from UK and bankers like Frenchman Pierre Richard and Italian Reiner Mazera
and Brit Tim Stone EID is lending big money on very good conditions to fund so caught private
finance initiative schemes including hospitals and privatizations some other investments but
these directors at the same time work for banks and financial institutions that actually are doing business
with EID that keep it KPMG, Dexia and Le Mans brothers do you realize what it all means
you're on the conclusions you yeah yes as if European citizen I must stand and
probe up at my hand over my heart all right yeah yeah man there's all kinds of stuff going on
don't think that we're immune over here in Europe to what's going on in the global credit markets
Gordon Brown prime minister of the United Kingdom has said this is an amazing thing he said
the I guess the bank of England or certainly the government is going to issue bonds
to banks in exchange for the shitty ass loans that are out there and make no mistake particularly
in this country a lot of shitty loans were made and so basically the taxpayers going to guarantee
that money so that the banks can spin up trading again which by the way from an economic standpoint
maybe a very good idea I I really am not qualified to say if it's good or not all I do know is that
it's pretty risky for us guys the taxpayers because we're now guaranteeing all the the
shoddy business that was done and it really gives banks no downside to taking huge risk because
we're too big to fail scares me my friends how about you it once was a place a wonderful
wonderful place where listeners to go and sample some of the best music podcasts
on the worldwide we have a place where those with tattoos and piercings
we live in harmony with those interfered ranger jeans and telling lava boots a place where one minute
you would hear the calming sounds of the stratavariates and the next gear piercing cords of a
prosthetic caster unfortunately on September 27th 2007 that podcast gave its final goodbye
didn't six months later music podcast for listeners now have a new place to come together
it's called music remix music podcast is a chance to show the world where you've got
go to music remakes dot com some in a five minute clip of your show and once it's past a good
house keeping silver approval we'll be scheduled for an upcoming show on listeners
are you tired of listening to the music remakes dot com or we promise that you don't like
what you hear on the show we'll double your money back wait a minute is this script bright
it's a free show music remakes dot com that's in this i seen are you m y s dot com we wait too long to
get the right spilling so soon all right yeah sounds like a good one
here's one you got a crank i really like you're listening now on your computer through
speakers otherwise jams ear buds deep in guess who when the band was saying a shaking
when i'm like this before i'm about 10 years time ago
when the band was singing shake it all over
now they give a huge illusion we did the world to see it all rock and build a
roof way too
once you don't know how to even know how i just said i got to tell my bitch what in the
now it's not a magic it's not music it's not all right i don't know i think i won't
i'm not just one time before
i'm about 10 years ago
when the band was singing shake it all over
now it's not a magic it's not a music
it's not a music
when the band was singing shake it all over
definitely an entry to the soundtrack of my life to guess who when the band was singing shake
all over
by the way if you're looking for some cool tunes to fill up your ipodder and be free player or
you're on these days you're cell phone head on over to emusic.com
courtesy of the daily source code and the pod show network to get 35 songs for free
absolutely no obligation just go to emusic.com slash daily source code
music dot com slash daily source code for that 35 song no obligation offer
all right so lots of calls came in about my statements about china and i just want to make
something uh really really clear i am not saying that i'm protesting i'm not saying that you should
protest i'm not saying you should throw away any products you have that are made in china
because you'd probably be going walking around outdoors naked um what i am saying is it seems
like there's a huge amount of hypocrisy in people who are protesting the Olympics
being hosted in Beijing in china because of their um violations of human rights which is
right there is just a question by itself or they the only ones violating human rights or do we
do a fine job ourselves it just depends upon your perspective i guess and uh is
dosing a torch really an effective way of um protesting and does anybody really care well
according to james are friend here in the UK no one gives a shit james
i don't know what this thing again for the protests you're not here and anything there's
nobody's interested it's got it all came with it's just all of anything more of a god
it's just being greedy but not being tortured we're not solving a death people protests
the people who are being punished in this life and nothing and we're not being punished
which is being the extent more and more and more of nothing it's as simple as that and nobody's
protesting nobody's interested in what you're saying because it isn't important what's important
i'm trying to get to equity in the world simple bye all right get some equity in the world
but interesting statement there james and obviously uh excuse me someone does care because
we're out trying to douse the Olympic flame as an ineffective pathetic means of of protesting
you don't see uh oh Gordon Brown's not going to attend the opening ceremonies oh wow meanwhile
let's take a billion dollars from the sovereign wealth funds from the chinese let's import all kinds
of products i'm not saying it's good or bad i'm saying that it's just full of shit
it's hypocrisy is what it is please make all of our gadgets and our clothing and all of our
little plasticine things in our toys please make them really really cheap
and we won't say anything about that but we're gonna go and protest the Tibet
some country far away yeah i know it's such it's a horrible what's happening horrible what they've
done to tywan and others are we any better uh just feels like hypocrisy to me man and where's
the where you know what i'm so happy i'm so happy that finally the protest is starting to come
in the music and it's not coming in the form of music that i expected it initially to come it's
coming in the form of hip hop it's uh coming in the form of of real urban street art that is being put
out there in fact i what i want to do is i want to take you back in time back to the early 80s this
is uh it's a mashup by djbc we've played before in the daily source code but the the main theme
of the song of course is the message from grandma's to flash you remember i'm actually it's uh
i guess it's melly mel who's doing the rap uh and you should have a listen at how we protested
in song in the 80s this was about the state of america in the 80s black people and this
got you's got your one power to determine the own destiny and the own black communities
are way over their resides in the confines of america
a boys born in hard time Mississippi surrounded by for those that ain't so pretty
walking glass everywhere people pissing on the stage you know they just don't care i can't take
smell can't take the noise got no money to move on i guess i got no choice right in the
front room all this in the back jump giving the alley with the baseball bat i try to get away but i
thought i could get fuck of the man but i thought i'd be possessed my car
i think don't wish me cause i'm too scared of it all the same i'm trying not to
want to my head like a joke with the time for me right now i want you to know when i'm
like a joke with the time to make me wonder how we're keeping the woman
like a joke with the time to make me wonder
abandon on the front screw hangin out the window watching all the cars go by rowing as
the breezes blow a crazy lady living in the bag now the car failed to beat the beat
extension that's a tango to give the life and anger with their car printers in the
last sunset down at the beef show watching all the grief so she can tell us stories
to the girl back home to win to the city and got salsa did it she had to get a
ticket and make it on all things don't put in me cause i'm too scared of it
i'm trying not to use my head like a joke with the time to make me wonder how we're keeping the woman
it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how we're keeping the woman
brothers doing bad for my mother's TV says she watched it too much it's just not
healthy all my children in the daytime down the night can even see the game
well the sugar rate fight the bill collected the ring my phone and scare my wife
when i'm not home got a bomb education double digit inflation can take the train to the
job there's a strike at the station need on king constant number that can't stop to turn around
rope a second earlier rate my green cancer never raise in times i think of a bonus thing
i swear i might have jacked it but it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how
i keep the woman it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder
my son said daddy i don't want to go to school because the teachers are jerky
must think of a fool and all the kids won't read for a thank you beat cheaper
if i just got a job learned to be a street sweeper a dance to the beat
jump for my feet wear a shirt and tie and run with the creeps because it's all about money
ain't a damn thing funny you got to have a car in this land and milk and honey
the push that girl in front of the drain took it to the doctor slow the harm on again
stamp that man right in his heart gave him a train for core brand and started
can't walk through the park was crazy if rocked my head on my door because they got me on the
road i feel like an outlaw over last last door here there's a you are some more living
don't put it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time
to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time
to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with some time to make me wonder how it's like a joke with my memor
who are normal
he's like a diesem chan
come down
DJGG sees mesage for the city
That's how we did an old school, back in the 80s, mashed up in a nutty package.
Nice.
You know, I'm just going through all the Twitter stuff here and seeing where people are
saying about being able or not being able to get on to live 365.
I think we've uncovered something here.
I believe it's false advertising.
See, the way it works, the highest packages they have available just to sign up online
is you get 60 people who are not VIP members, which, of course, means you're signing up and paying for the thing.
60 simultaneously.
And I've never seen it go above 35.
It's like 35 seems to be that, no, actually, I have seen it at 40.
But certainly not 60.
So there should be room for 20 other people to get on.
And a lot of people are not even seeing the stream as being live at this moment.
So I think that we've discovered because we're doing this in a live environment where I'm broadcasting live,
you're feeding back to me live.
I think we've discovered that they're full of shit this company.
And I'm going to write them a very stern email.
And I think you should do the same.
There's absolutely no reason why this should be happening.
Other than that they have tricked out their system to not actually deliver what you're paying for,
and that's really offensive.
So let's get all over this shit.
Because I do like the fact that, and of course, who knows of that's true,
that they actually give a piece of that $99 a month to artists to pay for license music that is played.
Ask at BMI Harry Fox type stuff.
So I'm very, very suspicious of what live 365 is doing these days.
All right, back to China for a second.
As I said, a lot of people misunderstanding what I'm saying here.
I'm just opening your eyes and waking you up to what's happening.
I'm not saying we need to protest China at all.
And I'm not saying you need to protest it by breaking your iPod.
Now we have the French frog from Cupertino, Arnold.
He called in.
I believe Arnold still works for Apple, who, of course, makes all of their Shite in China.
Hey man, this is the French frog.
So it's in ValleyFrog.com.
There it is. I've learned that anyway, I've been catching up on the TSC.
I've been listening to 746 the other day.
And you mentioned, you know, by cutting, I mean, the whole China, by cutting a concept.
And that's a bullshit.
That is so stupid.
I'm sorry, that concept of by cutting products made in China is stupid.
Especially if they're made by the company you work for, right?
By cutting fathers from country that is not a democracy.
Where the citizens do not have access to, you know, to free media.
I cannot know exactly what's going on.
And then why people are cutting those products?
It never works.
The Chinese, those one point, whatever, billion Chinese people, they are not fortresses.
You know, I mean, they're just people trying to make a buck.
They're finally, you know, a lot of them are finally, you know, buying a car for the first time.
You know, they're doing what the rest of the developed world has been doing for decades.
They're finally, you know, a lot of them finally can feed their family.
They're not responsible for the abuses, the horrible abuses of their government.
In fact, a lot of them have no fucking idea that it's, that's what's going on.
Yeah, because they're chained to their machines in the factory.
What are you talking about?
This is, look, we can't have it both ways.
You know, we can't be protesting just the government.
Which, by the way, I think is the biggest cop out in the world when people will say to me, they'll say,
I don't dislike Americans.
I just dislike your president.
I just dislike your leaders.
You know, a country gets the government that it deserves.
So we voted Bush in, you know, and if you stole the election, we deserve them to steal the election.
We let it happen.
So, you know, come on.
I mean, you can't have it both ways.
You can't protest and then at the same time say, well, you know, but we're really hurting the people of the country.
You know, the point is to get a message across and the quickest way to get a message to anyone is to hurt them where it really hurts.
Which is usually their pocketbook.
Everything else is futile.
Now, does boycott in the Olympics hurt?
I don't think so.
I think that's a, that's a big financial ring right there.
The international Olympic committee, my ass.
Yeah, you guys are probably sleeping with the bankers as we speak.
So, okay, I get your point, I don't know, but I don't think it's correct.
You know, how are we supposed to, to let China know that we don't agree with what they're doing?
My question is, is it even our place?
Pot-cattle, black, maybe?
I don't know.
They shouldn't be penalized for it.
It's impractical anyway, because I defy anybody to live a life without having owning any product or service.
That at some point is made developed, designed, whatever, somewhere in China.
Okay, but so just help me understand, I know why are leaders of the, quote, free world boycotting,
because they're not calling it a boycott.
They say, well, I wasn't, you know, Gordon Brown, prime minister of the United Kingdom.
I wasn't intending on, I wasn't planning on attending the opening ceremonies anyway.
Now, horseshit, he doesn't want to take the heat.
But at the same time, on the back end, they're taking billions of dollars or pounds or euros.
Or I just read this morning that China is now saying that they're going to dump about,
I don't know, about a trillion dollars worth of currency, US currency, back into the market,
and they're going to exchange that for more stable currencies, like the euro and the Canadian dollar.
Here, that people in North America, the Canadian dollar, more stable than the US dollar.
We should be protesting outside the White House.
It's impossible.
So, good luck with that.
And, you know, this is coming from a guy who tries his best to, you know, buy, meet in the US or meet in France,
because in French after all, products, when it's possible.
But, you know, I also believe that, you know, it's impossible,
and you like YouTube, you buy products.
I'm trying not.
You gotta be realistic.
This is not the way it's done.
You know, it's not the way it's going to work.
Anyway, great here.
Hope you win.
Love you.
And, uh, take care.
Well, alright.
So, I don't know.
What doesn't work for me is, of course, calling and complaining saying,
I'm wrong and I won't work and not offering any other solution.
So, maybe there's two questions here.
A is a boycott of products and effective boycott,
or does it hurt the people of the country your boycotting too much?
And, B, should we even be boycotting other countries?
And, that would be my personal question.
Shouldn't we be making our own house a little bit cleaner,
get some order in the house, and then lead by example?
I'm thinking it's a good idea.
Good evening, I would like to report on the state of our war against American people.
We're mounting a sustained campaign,
to crack down on every American,
and every person of every faith,
and every nation,
and to bring them to justice.
All missions are being executed according to plan,
without ruining our provocation.
Americans are being swept up in an international drag net.
Thousands of FBI agents drawn to trail of other citizens here in a broad.
It has everything to do with hate and evil, and murder and prison.
America's strong strong strong strong.
I will agents, we'll run!
Why can't you tell me if you don't know what you're doing?
We're just in line with you,
but you're really good.
You're just trying to explain everything to me,
I see a message from the government, like every day, I'll watch it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and
listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen a listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it, and listen to it
Connected, stole a post, they control a race and take elections
It's the stolen bones, free-mason kill committing
See the dragon, get shitty or in every city
Why don't you know it yet?
Would you know it?
One of the things we don't know
Would you stand up for truth?
Oh, would you try and know it's true?
We have to be wanted, we don't know
All of the things that's wrong
Would you stand up for truth?
Oh, would you try and know?
No, I show self, who's the one with the most again?
All I love and motherfuckers couldn't stand his name
That even Nick is waving flags like they lost their mind
Everybody got opinions, but don't know the time
Cause I'm never cuz being took
It's playing the seat, the oldest trick in the book is making enemies
A phone to evil soul recover, making tourists don't
And take over your freedom, knocking low, eating search
And nothing changed, one more fellow people, locked in prison
He's big, still beat us, but it seemed we forgetting
But I remember, folks, they pimp our hoties, devil's do it
Fuck, truly, honey, ask the all around he's doing
We in the streets, highland trail to the feet
Follow, fuck, waving flags, greenies back and sitting knees
Boy, oh, blood, money, make these killers ride cold
I'm suspicious, who's five people dying never told
It's all a part of playing God
So you think we need them, we're being asked, cross
Pick away your rights to freedom
Be a witness to the sickness of this trick, take this
Hope you want to stand the time, brother, cause this makes you
What can we do, what can we do, what can we do, what can we do
Who can we do, what can we do, what can we do
So, now you asking, why my records always come the same
Keep it reoland facts, what the fuck am I doing, my days, see the gore here
To coming up the Beast, so every story, every word i'm saying
Fuck, beast, see you cook witness to your lumen, naughty
body, count, don't be surprised, these are devil's gonna
I'm talking bad, there where they are, they are
You think a couple thousand lies mean shit to killers
Niggas spread a God, we the ones ain't no villains
All ready up a world they think to demonize a country
Ain't no terror threatening us approval ratein' slumpin'
So I'ma say it for the record
We don't want that planned
Ain't no one in the country, cook a pawn
Had the hand in, just a way to keep your scary
So you think you need them
Praising through it's why that killer take away your freedom
I mean he ever got discovered, but it's not a symptom
Niggas talking loud, but ain't nobody's saying shit
And we can't afford for them at all and I's all in the first
That's why I'm fit to sign out each and every verse
I'll see the call out, whoopin' Harris, make a count
I'll see you in the fifth, each and every session now
I don't want a white-stack, burn sheet of public by it
I'll see you to profile and see the media's compliance
One's cut for business, either vicious, make a savior
Hope you understand the time, but the cut is great
Why won't you bear with you?
We're all our things, we know what we're just
And I want you all, what you try to lead to
And if you want it from the slow fall
I'll see the call out, whoopin' Harris, make a count
I'll see you to find out, whoopin' Harris, make a count
You try to hold the whole thing
What's going to be a very good deal?
You're part of things we know
We're just in the thought too
I'll see you to try to hide
And if you want it from the slow fall
I'll see the call out, whoopin' Harris, make a count
We're just in the thought too
We're all we're just in the thought too
You can't imagine how much money they spent trying to silence
Good people who put their lives on the line
The fight for change
Hear that?
Put your life on the line of fight for change
What would you do, played earlier this week by Paris?
Finally, we got some revolt going in music, man
Oh, you got to use the words to get people's attention, of course
If you use words like that, you usually can't get yourself played on mainstream
So I'll play this stuff as much as I can
Christian Quails says on a tweet here, as far as a country getting the government
They deserve the Chinese, did not elect their leaders
Yeah, but that's a cop-out, man
That's the whole point
You get the government you deserve, you have to fight for it
And you know, this is why I like the French, the French, man
If they don't like something
And you know, this after I yelled at our no
But if they don't like something, man, they say
They tell the government, you know what, then we're just going to burn this shit down
And guess what, it works, they get pretty much what they want
And everyone seems to be happy, sarcosis got a freaking supermodel girlfriend
Life is good over there
New destination for the Delta Shira
Yeah, and I'm not the only one picking up on on this trend
There is a lot more
Really good protest music coming out in hip-hop form
Hi Adam, this is Justin from Back of the Bus podcast
And I'm amazed to hear you play boots, Riley, and Paris
On DSC 746
We at Back of the Bus have played this song in tons of others from the same vein
And we kind of look forward to you playing more political music
Great choice, man
If you're ready to have your mind blown wide open
Uh-huh
You should listen to Jedi mind tricks and shadow business
Or just subscribe to our show
And by the way, the best place to download Jedi mind tricks
It's from e-music
Uh-huh
And if you head on over to Jusel Plotz and PW have a link ring at 35 free MP3
So you should probably check that out
This song, Shadow Business
I think applies to slavery you were discussing today in 746
So if you want to hear more, it's not provoking music
I don't know over to Back of the Bus podcast
Great hair, hope you win
Love you
When you were over in American Simo
What surprised you the most?
I guess what hit me the most is the commission of the factory that the workers were in
The factory was surrounded by fans
Uh-huh
On top and on the bottom
And they have a gentleman fans around the whole factory
And-and-and the military come out
The gate has a uh-huh
Has a guard shock where the guard
Sypen comes through
The welcome movement in and out of the factory
The factory made of um
Panos with tin roof
Um, it's really hot
The temperature over there is
Revolving 90 degree
And inside the factory with a note
It makes you way over there
Yeah, it's a concept for every former slavery they call his slave labor
But they don't prosecute them because it's how they make tape up
When you rockin' that flat shit that's made in China
Foggin' that your old child's trying to feed his mama
He explores the contamination of the seeds
And only 55% of them will get degrees
And the women have to try to play cake the boss
Because it's sex discrimination in the labor force
The slave masks only let them speak in silent
And they suffer from lung disease and not damage
14 hours shifts
Seven days a week
Two shitty meals a day
Very little sleep
Human life only worth three cents an hour
All human rights laws no sets of power
What could 400 years in the gray pastus?
Only do you prove cleverness to slave
Man is like for a living if you live in an hell
When the mind is confined to a prison
And the lives they devised and the system they failed
But I expect the system to fail
Is like for a living if you live in an hell
When the mind is confined to a prison and the sound
And the lives they devised and the system they failed
But I expect the system to fail
Many Chinese workers are forced to sign secret agreements
Known as shadow contracts
Actually for they leave China severely
And in some ways you'll legally reach 15 their activities
For an American soil
Workers are forbidden to participate in any religious or political activity
Or to ask for a salary increase or even to fall in love or get married
This 1.6 million people locked in jail
They didn't know slave labor force trapped in hell
Yeah, they generated over a billion dollars worth of power
And only campaigns, 26 and hours
They make clothes for McDonald's and for Apple Bays
And worker 40, I wish ships and prison factories
And while we stood around to pay food, a whack of sakes
They have to work when all's the ridiculous act of names
Slave agrees, not illegal, that's a fucking law
It's illegal unless it's full conviction of a crime
The main objective is to get you in your fucking crime
And keep the prison full and not give you a fucking stop
But they the real criminal keep a ucafine
For petty crime, but they give you to the knot
And they know body dance of protection
Except the thought you've been copied
And human rights is effective
It's life worth flipping
And if you live in hell
When the mind is confined to a prison
And the lives they devised and the system they failed
But I expect the system to fail
It's life worth flipping
And if you live in hell
When the mind is confined to a prison
And the lives they devised and the system they failed
But I expect the system to fail
But the sweatshaw situation
Kind of conveys different and kind of take advantage
You know, on the people that are poor
And Apple not be a criminal
That is an advantage of it
The Chinese women make t-shirts and hats
And they're going to be gay for you
They put us when we get to a bijna
Do you Man these United States
Do you refuse to have the abortion
And this has been
And define why the prejudice with the fact
That the Management of police
TheAMN workers are becoming pregnant
and having abortion
The human rights workers say is common practice
Instead of capturing Chinese lawplod
It's itious
The flight doesn't fly inside there.
There you go.
I love this stuff.
If you got more of that, please drop it in my drop.
Drop it in my drop.
You're new verb for that.
Drop it.
Drop it on me at drop.io slash daily source code.
Fantastic service.
I was trying to invest in those guys.
I was looking around seeing what's going on.
I love the idea they've come up with.
And turns out they already took a series A round of funding.
So that's too bad.
And by the way, for, oh no, just one more thing.
I do want to point out that I choose my products wisely.
And we purchased a French automobile.
Did I know?
There's a no twingo, which twingo.
I'm sure is a fine friend word.
Maybe it's a twingo.
It's probably what it is.
I don't know what the twin is.
It's got like a lawnmower engine in that puppy.
But man, I drove it out to the gas station today.
Who?
I got to tell you that that's a modern automobile right there.
And it's really comfortable.
It's almost like sitting in, kind of like a, like a, not a lounge chair, but in a really
comfortable garden chair.
And it's zippy and it's fast and it's, uh, it warms up really quickly.
I like that when everything is nice and warm and toasty.
It's got a great sound system.
You can plug in your iPod, plug in an MP3 player, or a USB memory stick, go figure.
And those guys got it together.
Let's see a couple more Chinese comments.
Adam, stress, find a comment on your latest idea to boycott sign up.
Which I'm a little, well, and good for, except that pulling out what we already have from
sign up, we'd rather point this because the money is already fixed.
Hence.
All right, as I said, you're confused.
I didn't say throw out shit you already have, of course not.
Hello, Adam.
This is Oscar from the Netherlands, now we're waiting in a trade to default from
Amsterdam Central Station to Denha.
Anyway, we've got in your, um, nice little marks about China and the Labour in China.
I mean, in real man, not every Chinese person that makes your iPod basically is a kid or
some other teen or near baby.
Kind of, uh, dude, how do you know that?
I'm, I look at my iPod.
I'm thinking, uh, there's women shackled to, uh, to machinery.
There's kids who are working 18 hours a day.
I don't know any better.
Do you?
I mean, uh, that just assembling your little device, of your lighting.
I mean, Chinese also had their other little issues and, yeah, politically, hmm, personally,
I don't like it.
But they had some nice little things.
I mean, they've got some, uh, that's got some modern stuff there as well.
I mean, don't forget, they had some villages that actually made some, uh, climate
neutral to, uh, however, because they, uh, recycle fully, uh, uh, you know what it is?
You're right.
I don't have enough information about China.
I'm only going by what I'm being told.
So the only thing I do know is that, uh, here in the so-called free West, we're not free.
Yeah, maybe we're not exactly chained to a desk or chained to a machine, maybe we're, what,
we are working 18 hours for sure my friends were working 18 hours a day.
Thank you, email.
Thank you, Blackberry.
Thank you, iPhone.
We're definitely working long.
We are totally enslaved.
Four months out of the year, you're working for the man.
You're working for taxes, which, of course, is something Murray Sabron wants to get rid
of.
I should talk to him on Monday.
That's going to be really interesting.
He may be, you can help us get rid of that little minor nuisance.
But, of course, we're shackled.
We're shackled to our homes by massive debt that was marketed effectively onto us very effectively.
Here in the United Kingdom, oh, man.
The government expressly kept the interest rates really low for decades.
Well, not decades, for decades.
So everyone will go out and start borrowing and no problem, refile, be easy to do baby.
You just watch.
Now we're slaves.
We're slaves to the man in the, in the free West.
That's what we got to be looking at.
That is my advice.
Okay.
Don't waste time protesting China.
Let's get our own house in order first.
It really is.
It really is important.
This is a mashup that I found.
French coincidentally.
What is it with France today?
How come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in
a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad taste, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come we' a bad style, how come we're in a bad style, how come, we're in a bad style, how
Oh, it's yours, it's yours, it's yours
That's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that
that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love
that is what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I have, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, it's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love , that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, yeah, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that's what I love, that is what I love, that's what I love, that's what
Hey, a little bit twisted.
I'm sure what I think of it yet.
The master has called it over-dumb.
It's a five-step, the title of this match.
A radiohead versus Dave Ruback.
Of course, you recognize, take five in there.
I got to think.
I really got to think about France.
Got to consider that.
Wow, man.
This is an old school Charlie really long.
We're at 75 minutes already.
And it's a two-tea program.
I rushed down during one of the songs downstairs.
Put the kettle on.
Rush back up.
During one of the other songs went back down.
Reheated the water, which was ready to go.
And got me another cup of tea here.
So I can last a little bit longer.
And we still got about 35 people on the live 365,
which seems to be the max.
It's really, really honking me off.
There's a couple things that came in through email that I didn't get to earlier this week.
Mainly because well, yes, of course we got the lady Patricia on,
which was a lot of fun.
This came from Peter Decker.
There's a website called condymusgo.com.
And the mission of this website is essentially that
when she was secretary of, was it defense?
Well, she, I can't remember now.
Anyway, she basically approved waterboarding as a,
quote, enhanced torture technique.
And they're calling for her resignation.
Definitely worth checking out that website.
Condymusgo.com.
Let me see what else is happening.
Passengers from Southwest are threatening to sue the airline
because they broke their contract with its passengers
by skipping important safety inspections.
Yes, indeed, I believe they deserve to get sued.
Oh, this was a very interesting one.
This is kind of frightening.
I sent me this.
Shayna, I think, probably emailed this to me.
In Germany, 29 people suffered from lead poisoning.
And the authorities couldn't figure it out
until they did some deeper investigation.
And low and behold, all the people had purchased
and consumed marijuana from the same or a similar source.
And this is a practice that you really got to watch out
for this shit, man.
I can't believe this.
So what, you know, once you,
once the good gun judge distributed, I guess,
in Germany, apparently, then the kids who are selling it
will mix it up with lead shavings to make it heavier.
I've seen, you know, similar practices like this.
I've seen people throw sand into their bags to make it heavier
and to mix it in with the actual holy herb.
It's a shitty ass practice.
And you all should be able to look out.
If you don't smoke anything that's in the bottom of the bag,
okay, that's just really bad.
And one other thing that I realize,
and I'm going to bring this up on no agenda
when I talk with John C. DeVorek.
I don't know if we'll do it today or otherwise obviously tomorrow.
Is the surge in Iraq?
I just wanted to point out,
if you're looking at, and of course,
we heard the kid from Brooklyn saying that he feels
we deserve to have live cameras there.
And I absolutely agree,
but even on the footage I'm seeing on the news,
you'll see that there's a new,
there's a new soldier.
And what I'm led to believe
is that the US government has contracted approximately
70,000, 70,000 Iraqis.
Malicious, essentially,
to be a part of the surge.
And these guys are murderers.
And they're kicking ass and taking names.
And so essentially, you know,
what happened is we didn't up by 30,000,
we uped it by 100,000 by contracting out.
Of course, that's what this entire war is.
It's one big contract outsource.
Ah.
You hear the dog barking downstairs?
We finally got our new fridge delivered.
The guys went on the blank, went Sunday.
We've been with another thing very interesting.
We've been with our refrigerator since Sunday.
The only thing I had is something I have up here in the office,
which is a portable refrigerator.
Actually, it's a box that can either blow hot or blow cold.
And it can really refrigerate, really, really cold.
And it runs either 12 volt DC or on the AC mains.
And so we've been living out of this little fridge.
And you know what?
It's actually not all that hard.
Once you have the basics, you don't really need all that crap
that you fill up these huge ridges with.
You should try that.
To me, it was astounding and really felt like a revelation.
It's like, I really didn't realize anything.
All right.
One more song to bring the freight train to a home
for the footballer Friday,
DSC 749.
Don't prove it.
All right.
All all right.
And that divides me somewhere in my mind
On the borderline of the edge and where I want to learn
I want to learn, I want to learn
The Lord, I walk that
I shout, the Lord, the Lord
I shout, the Lord
This is just some of about the combination of green day and mark rons and it hits me right between the eyes
He takes all the boxes, makes me feel like he never made me a sprite-day!
He takes all the boxes, he takes all the boxes, makes me feel like he never made me a sprite-day!
Party Ben, you are my hero!
Alright everybody, how am I? I was singing out loud to that one.
Spryday, my day Tuesday, Wednesday Thursday, full about Friday, I had a final fun phone to read.
I didn't quite queue it up properly. Well there you go, my friends.
It's been quite a ride today on the footballer Friday, did a source code episode number 749,
three quarters of a thousand coming up on Monday.
I'll see if I can get a very savor on the line. He seems like he's desperate to talk.
That should be pretty interesting. So the final thought of the week, well, what should I say?
I believe that we really need to have a closer look at ourselves about what's wrong in our life.
It's, well, a lot of it's between your ears.
Quite frankly, a lot of your attitude, a lot of how you look at the world and everything about how you feel is all controllable by you.
So if you continue to live your life with passion, I guarantee you you're going to feel a lot better.
And let's see if we can, uh, kind of our own house and literally do that.
Improve yourself and prove yourself around your friends, your family, do something nice this weekend.
Do something unexpected, turn left instead of right.
I guarantee you you'll feel better for it and you'll be better for it.
And let's not be pointing overseas to everybody. Let's get our own crap together.
No matter where you live, no matter where you're listening to the show, it's up to us.
The new generation, the Gen X, Gen Y, and Christ, the Gen Z.
They move our Friday and I'm spinal thought of the week.
My friends live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom.
Another hot show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Thanks for watching.