Alright, we got the mics set up, got the comments cute, we got the music set up, good
shape for the daily source code 759, we just need the host.
Let's see, Adam, Adam, Adam, Adam, you still in there?
Alright, he is still taking care of his prostate cancer prevention for this week, guess
nobody told him that you're not supposed to do it all in one morning.
Well, let's cue up some music in, soon, our host Adam Curry with a daily source code
759, this is the daily source code, 6 million dollars worth of airplane
strapped by us, and the next generation radio contenting my ears.
That's construction, oh, even though the feet of the body spurn in, as the warm machine
keeps turning, and the engine went tight, boys need their rain watchers, but not
way down, way down, way down, way down, way down, way down, way down, way down, way down, way down
way down, way down, way down, way down, way down, now we're talking as well as the
body spurn in, as you hear the bodies spurn in, oh, come on, we just have to go on,
and that's got a stocky hour, oh, yeah, just have to go on in, oh, I'm the needs of
the body spurn in, oh, come on, we just have to go on, we just have to go on, we just have to go on,
we just have to go on, we just have to go on, we just have to go on, we just have to go on, we just have to go on,
we just have to go on, we're talking to the body spurn in, this time now we just have to go on,
to kick off a show with a brand new week of the Charlie Hello chuckle heads, his daily source code episode number
759 coming to you from the curry manner on the west side of G-town. It's the afternoon suburb of
Suri known as Gilford. This is your daily source code. Oh my goodness, it's a good to talk to y'all
and I apologize about about Thursday and Friday. I warned you though because I had to
be show business bitch to the lady Pete. She was doing yet another live show of Holland's got talent
and she's got one more. Wow, is this like super compressed or is just me home on let me see if I
can how's that? Let me see, let me make a little different here. Just pumping too much baby, too much
pumping, not good for you. So she had another couple of really good you actually you'll laugh at this
all right. So as most of you know the lady Patricia refuses to fly with me across the English channel
that portion of the North Sea known as the English channel. And last I have a safety pilot with me.
Now she'll fly anywhere else and she does regularly in fact we've got another trip scheduled
pretty soon. We're going to go down to the south coast of the UK and you know when we have a nice
nice day weather wise today is actually not bad. It's not super. There's a it's you know there's some
clouds a little bit overcast or they would not be a candidate. Anyway it was anything but great weather
on Thursday and I had promised to take her suitcase which of course makes the easy jet trip that
much more enjoyable because then she doesn't have to deal with you know just anything really just
you know get your boarding pass walk go through security all she's got as her handbag and she
gets on she gets off no waiting at the other end and like yeah that's cool so um I loaded up this
huge to me bag which took up to all of the rear seats actually in the Delta Sierra and it was
interesting there was no one really flying at Ferroaks on Thursday and I could you know I knew
it was overcast about a thousand feet and saying well well we'll see yeah we'll see how we do
and so I took off indeed a thousand foot cloud base and about a minute into the flight it was
400 feet 300 feet pretty much touching the ground so I wound up flying in what this known as
instrument meteorological conditions for just are most of the flight really until I pretty much hit
mid channel wow the controllers are really friendly though here in the UK when you know when they
know you're flying through all kinds of shit then they really do help out it was cool that a good
time actually I should have recorded that one or the or the trip back because I feel that actually
mentioned this on Saturday on no agenda with the Johnson of Warack I feel like I've advanced a little bit
as an aviator and I'm getting pretty close to getting ready to take my well really focusing on
getting my instrument rating because boy will the skies open up for me now and I cannot wait listen we
got so much to talk about today because of course you know not only do we have Thursday and Friday
where I skipped a show but of course we had the weekends you guys have been calling with so much
stuff I mean really and we have stuff to catch up on from the food bar that we left behind so
first let's uh this is very important we have to see how our quota is our doing
morning Adam it's John Quirk yes got here I'll just listen to know again the 31 and I'll take
a guess that you like to listen to the news quiz on BBC Radio 4 from time to time yeah sometimes
I'm not gonna say how I know but I think you do oh and one more thing the prostate cancer prevention
closing thing you seem to be working tirelessly to turn one of the few in this piece of pleasure
less to the ordinary man into a chore you go dog I wouldn't say it's a chore I just want to
make sure we all stay good and healthy as you know survey has proven that masturbating five times
a week for men will reduce the chances of contracting prostate cancer severely and boy are you
guys responding to it Mr. Curry Jamaican in New York here you know I wasn't just show
give a day and um you guys were talking about prostate cancer prevention methods and you know I
must say that you know lately lately I've been very much meeting my quota no I just have one
question to ask with regards to meeting his quota no does this what what if what if meeting your quota
involves assistance let's say you know does that count as rubbing one out as well you know I
think it's called cheating you make it in New York what what about if let's say you have three
or four doors a night oh no what happens then to your quota you know so that's one thing I want one
thing I must ask you you need to get to the bottom of this no until the things Mr. Curry I
figure you know you're asking for a little theme song type thing you know and you know don't
through the song track of my life and I found this little ditty by a guy named Shinehead that
but apparently if it fits me perfect okay I'll be looking out for that one Jamaican New York I
appreciate you calling in with your hand to the grand comment report and we've got more hey Adam it's
being on desert I just want to know something I just let the comment be played brooding one
effort for cancer and how many times do I have to get my stuff aired on your show before I get a
jingle I want a jingle you know that's right just myth really should do a prostate cancer
prevention quotient or quota jingle or a mini song or something because that wouldn't you know
and in the lyrics kind of explain what it's all about so we have to go through that and then
whenever someone has a novel way of upping their quota then we could just play the jingle that's
a pretty good idea I just listen and I'm sure he'll come up with something here's something cool
I played a Frank Sinatra song last Wednesday and asked you to identify the mystery producer who
sang it and of course unanimously you all got it right
hello Adam it's yellow air from South Wales yes it's key dubbed seeing that song and quite honestly
you want to stick to the blues which is very well hey they're out of its youth path in San Diego
Wednesday morning we can end of DSC 768 and there you are we're doing end but those were the
unspeakable vocal stylings of the incomparable P. W. Fence and P. Dubb really nice
didn't really know that he had minimum in terms of singing it's a great great radio voice
of course in podcaster but wow nice warbling fair so thanks for that treat at the end of the show
and look forward to talking to you again soon keep up the great way it comes I think I've
mentioned before I don't remember I'm gonna be 39 this year so much a little bit with
19 month old little girl now definitely working on more and even with all that maintaining
you know good two or three times a week hold her great hair hope you win keep up the great work
alright show home hey you've done all right and not everyone knew exactly the guy what the
the guy's name was when it comes to P. Dubb I know this one I know what I know it it's that
CD slots in the P.D. got it he's melting no no no I know I know it's the repair dude
there the cable repair dude right do I have that jingle still somewhere I know I have around the other
machine crap I don't have the let me say satellite repair man should I've got to go look
that one I get anyway just when we think we're all done when need a way to integrate P. Dubb into
the rubbing one out for cancer please welcome Terry better known as little red hi Adam this is Terry
your favorite internet politics little red I had to pop in and say I thought the rendition
of your celebrity producer was great and I think P. Dubb does a really good Frankie
anyway I'm gonna keep it short great hair love yeah I don't even need the same now home well
folder no you've won because we all have totally shaped embrace your freedom and lives in passion
I have to go back to my shows now and I'm over on MVO under LRWH as far as the past state thing
sorry guys I have worries of rest answer so you're on your own but at least my boyfriend will
make him speakly quota have a good week everyone later for now I have a lot Terry I love you thank
you so much totally shaped you know so I was thinking about that and all of a sudden it hit me
we can pull a double whammy on this so of course we know guys you know we have to we have to
do the business five times a week in order to keep our prostate prevention cancer quotient or quota
up and high but indeed women have to worry about breast cancer and for that you need breast examination
so I think you know if if the women on the show at least five times a week will self examine themselves
there's even a combination to be made I mean there's things that you know two partners
the partners could do together and we could be a really combating cancer in new and novel ways
I got to think a little bit more about it but it's coming to me
the president of the United States is dead he was murdered in the morning sunlight by a four-year-old boy
so began J.C. Hudgens seventh son Patti of the trilogy the most popular podcast novel series
in history last December the trilogy concluded the heroes were triumphant or so we think
but now it's time to go back and reveal moments in the seventh son story that were merely hinted at
in the original trilogy welcome the seventh son of city and J.C. Hudgens has opened up his seventh
son universe and invited the seven biggest names in podcast fiction to chronicle a nationwide
blackout that rock America during the seventh son trilogy seven son of Sidion each of your short
stories from news award winning and nominated authors Michael A. Stackpole Scott Siggler T. Morris
Murr Laferty Matt Wallace Mark Yoshi Motonim Khan and Christiana Ellis and even more
tales from these trailblazing podcast entertainment he voterra Dan class which at all
rutherford George Prom TD0013 soccer girl and the cast of the radio adventures of Dr. Floyd
of Sidion also features dozens of audio and video recordings stories of the blackout as told by
its victims created by seven son fans across the globe on May 31st the lights go out America
becomes a police stick because when the power fails chaos rains subscribe now to seven son of
Sidion or catch up with the original seven son trilogy experience at J.C. Hudgens dot net
holy crap that sounds awesome I'm definitely subscribing to that one I can't wait to hear all
those voices here the stories and I've been a fan of that of the seven son ever since it came out
and it's feels like those were the cottage days weren't they? It must have been somewhere around the
three hundred oh man we're almost at seven hundred and what seven hundred and sixty came believe that
really moving along hey just got some news in today about the hum and the UK banks for those of
you in the UK you're gonna love this remember that you know the story that I've been tracking
obviously about the Gordon Brown deciding would be okay for the UK banks to swap that is a
literal translation of courses to just trade for temporary basis and it's based upon a
contract to swap the debt they have for government bonds and this was the 50 billion pound deal
that well definitely was highlighted for a while in the papers and now in the financial times
this comes from my sister days edition yes from from Monday check this out it is now turning
out to be closer to 80 or 90 billion pounds that the treasury of the Bank of England will swap
for bonds and they will and get this they're also of course going to get a triple a rating
because hey that's government money right oh by the way let me think it's our money that's right
wow they just increased that almost twofold from 50 billion to 90 billion it seems to me that
these banks are probably in a little bit more trouble than than is being explained to us and I think
it's quite worrisome tracking it for you as always I must have received at least 20 different
links to the story and the picture and you there's even some video of the two planes that collided
in a roanoke Texas at a a private commercial airfield and people are asking how the hell is this
possible if you haven't seen it I'll put a link in the show notes I think there's also a picture
on the drop drop.io slash daily source code what's happened there you literacy one plane and
another planes landed on top of it on its wings it's landing gear isn't bedded into the wings
and they're just sitting on top of each other like two deformed flies mating and I know exactly
how this happened of course the news meeting doesn't delve into it at all it's just here's the picture
and oh my gosh isn't that too not amazing or no one would hurt right there they don't get any
any of the details so the details are as follows this airfield a roanoke which is pretty much a
whole bunch of hangers and an air strip which is quite common actually in the United States this
type of roanoke I believe is in this case is roanoke Texas and you see them in California as well
and it's pretty much an operating airfield that does not have a control tower so it has what we call
a unicom frequency and sometimes it's even shared with other airports and you'll have to identify
which airport you're talking about what kind of maneuvers you're making so the airport the
the pilots speak to each other through this unicom frequency so they can say exactly what they're
doing where they're coming in from if they're joining the circuit if they're planning to land
if someone's lining up to leave and these two pilots apparently actually even knew each other and
here's where the confusion came in you know obviously one pilot was ready to line up to leave to
depart the runway while the other one was coming and I believe he actually had a student pilot with him
and there was some confusion which is I'd love to hear tapes of ATC or that unicom frequency
they probably don't exist but what obviously happened is you know both pilots thought that the
other had cleared them to for use of the runway and obviously you know it was a very very
fortunate ending could have been a lot worse but you know these things do happen and that's why
controllers and in towers at all kinds of airports are quite handy because they do look out for you
and they are watching your back I received email from Derek I'm still not happy with the microphone
today I'm not quite sure what's going on let me let me just do this that's a little better
Derek Richardson from I think it's in the UK but he's all in South Africa a lot he sent me a link
which I must put on in the show notes for today's episode of DailySourceco.com
the title of his email is the state of South Africa and I had no idea they were so bad when you
see these pictures it's basically a slideshow you see the horror the actually what are they call it
this this is a this is from the times of South Africa hold on I'm going to open up the web page
for a second the title of the of the of the pages flames of hate oh wait a minute I'm getting
an arrow establishing a database connection crap oh well I hope I hope this works by the time
I get the show notes up because you have to see these pictures it's really horrifying and it seems
like there's some form of genocide going on or genocide maybe something is is completely
completely wrong in in South Africa and uh uh crap man how come how come one down I don't hear
anything about this when you do hear some stuff but it just maybe it's just too much and the
and the news media doesn't have enough time to to handle all of it seems like this is pretty
important then again when you look at Burma or as the the junta there say uh me and Mar or if you
look at China where uh where hundreds of thousands are through are being threatened with starvation
same goes for Burma by the way um it's uh oh you just get a I don't know I don't know about you I
just get a nasty feeling I feel really crappy and I wish I could be doing a lot more and a lot of
things seem really really unimportant really they do you know I had uh one of those uh parent uh teenager
conversations over the weekend and I actually hear that shit coming out of my mouth you know like
do you realize what's going on in the rest of the world like oh fuck sound like my parents
well you know it it's it's our responsibility we're supposed to fix the world make it better for
our kids so we'll try let me see what can we do um I have so many different things I want to share
with you I'll tell you what just a light in the mood for a second let's bring in something that of
course normally happens on the football Friday when we had the maximum music express freight train
it's young palettes hit it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's
oh man for a second it sounded like Dion Warwick's heartbreaker but I don't think I know this one
number two oh man see what Dion is doing is he's thinking it's been too easy because I've gotten a
lot right recently now he's making really short clues and number three
y'all that's not fair you're not playing by the book I don't tell me I'm not gonna have anyone on
stand for the answer and answer number one in this week's hit this is from 1985
this is fruit k my feet one more wouldn't have guessed it
in a house that's been in front of us for this moon
I said my feet won't move that was a hard one not really hard my feet won't move
fruit cake is answer number one in this is answer number two
oh my goodness you're kidding me
I don't want my kids from 1993 Michael Jackson and Billy Jean
and this is answer number three from 1988 nearly finally
I think it's actually a good thing I didn't recognize this one
and they want to grant me to you believe it yes you know it's true
Billy Vanillie has answered number three with girl you know it's true and that concludes hit
that's number one hundred and twenty two so Adam how does it do this week
Leon considering you made it so hard I sucked monkey balls zero out of three
like always hit this that mepio dot com is the place to find the answers to this end
and the older hit this and of course the links to iTunes if you want to buy tricks
featured on the hit this online all right Adam thank you for playing again
everyone else thanks for listening next we've got the back for another hit this
so until then take care and very nice week and remember try to think with your heart bye-bye
for this as well this you think it will be so it's cool
just listening to Charlie 757 I know I'm a little behind but I didn't call it up I got a long drive
you have such people that you touched me I you convinced me to switch my party affiliation
for the primary election from libertarian republican and has done try I was able to vote for
Ron Paul we know we're that went but you can make me that she was the right guy you changed my mind
me to more or less one my heart and a little of a thing on June 1st in California
don't forget you got to wear an headset when you're yacking on your cell phone driving otherwise
you get a little ticket fair warning man all right buddy I appreciate it and of course it is
not too late things can happen you never know or can change and this one sweep in the intro
webs I had to record off a youtube unfortunately so it's a mono email and the wrong power revolution
no more bring our boys home to our shows we don't walk big of a man for the build the book
group have a place all with you you don't have the means of police
no Jefferson's rolling in this great and my name's been the number's life six six
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh on oh oh oh oh oh dinner
We haven't followed the Constitution and the next one we are to do.
The system that we have today are ripping off a little glass.
And you imagine how good a nation we can if we can't deserve system printing on as money.
If anyone has an MP3 of that or a pointer to where I can purchase that, please let me know.
I'd really like to have a high quality version of the YouTube video.
By the way, oh man, Amy, she is hot and I love her voice and that video, it's fantastic.
You know, Ron Paul officially is still in the in the race for the Republican nomination.
And as I said, anything can happen, but it doesn't really matter because the revolution has started the revolution continues.
It continues in the hearts of minds of hundreds of thousands of not millions of Americans who are waking up and understanding that there are things going on that do not make sense.
We need to keep our eye on because hey, these fuckers work for us, remember.
And I appreciate the call that came in before that. Let me see.
Well, I don't want to switch back to the UK just yet. Oh, this is something I just got to just got to address real briefly.
Hey, Adam, this is Paul.
Listen to DSE756.
And I heard you mentioned something about GIDs and downloading duplicates of the podcast.
And I use juice, like you said in your podcast.
And I have noticed probably over the last couple of weeks that the juice that I'm running in a living room that downloads video podcast has re-downloaded all of texture.
Let's see where their pod show shows all of deep brief TV.
And the only shows that I'm noticing it on are the pod show shows.
Yeah, exactly. And there's really two aggregators that were troubled by this or pod catchers, if you will.
One is juice, formerly known as iPod or lemon. And the other one is iTunes, unfortunately. So this has been a major point of contention and props to Mixmaster Andrew Grummit,
who figured it out.
I'm still waiting to find out exactly what it was. I'd like to explain it to you guys, but it was a technical error. It was something that happened with the release of the new site.
And that should have stopped by now. So now I know you were still on 7.56. So let's just keep it tally. If you're still having double downloads, let me know.
Because we definitely have to keep our eye on stuff like that.
Let me see. Oh, this was interesting. A couple of people sent me this.
Check this out. Jason the architect sent me an email. Adam, I was on Skype today.
And I've always had Roger Smalls on my Skype contacts. I've never seen him on until today. He popped up and I started talking to him.
Apparently, he's been to prison.
And he was in Guilford library looking at job sites and so on Skype.
He's been packing potatoes, et cetera, since he was released. He wouldn't tell me why.
And it's been chatting up Polish girls. Well, that sounds like the real Roger Smalls.
I told him we all miss him as soon as he gets a phone. He will call back into the show, Adam, for the sake of the show.
Buy him a phone and get the best man back on the show. Yeah, absolutely Jason Roger. Just reach out, baby.
Just let me know where I can send you a phone. I'll send you one of those Nokia candy bars. One of those prepaid.
You know, I'll have the number preprogrammed. I'd love to hear from you. I hope everything's okay.
And I hope you aren't in too much trouble, my friend.
You say, Matthew, I say, Matthew, you say, you're not saying you clear.
Let's call the whole thing.
Adam, what's up, brother?
You have some time with the pod. Say, we played a couple of my things. One of the things you played was Adam Curry for president.
And hey, what do you think was a joke or something? I'm serious, man. You can get like a lot of all of the nice president or something.
Be really cool. So, of course, I use the good old DSC number three discount code at GoDaddy.
And now I am the proud owner of this name. Adam Curry for president dot com.
And you can check it out and see where it links to.
But there will be no surprises. Listeners where it goes. But may again contact with me in case you'd like to.
You know, we'll farther with this. I like we need to start thinking about the future.
And you know, Adam Curry for president's very cool thing because we don't necessarily have to consider president the United States.
It could be president of the world or something like that. And I think about it. I think you can run and maybe win. Take care, brother. Bye.
The Dutch owner is the eye, a car that owned by Germany, a fairies by Dubai, our defense and arms capacity is largely based offshore.
Thought we're British British to the core.
We've sold a faster premium ship to Florida, of course. The sweet on Harry Ramsons and the Yanks on each piece of the Spanish owner.
I think that came off a channel for something that came into the drop at drop.au slash daily source code.
And oh, yes, there's all kinds of things going on here in Britain. Don't think all the messed up stuff that's exclusive to the United States. No, there's plenty going over on here in the UK as well, my friend.
So that's further companies who then looked to employ these people, can check it out and say, well, yes, no problem to what they think the previous employers speak for all messed up.
This has actually been launched by Action Against Business Crime, AADC,
a joint crime reduction partnership, such as British retail consulting and the home office.
Yeah, that's the thing that really bothers me that the home office is involved in this. I mean, I can certainly see where, you know, companies might think this is handy.
I guess it's legal, but man, to have the home office involved, that sounds wrong.
That's fucking government. Okay, what is the, the employees version of this? Oh, this, you know, basically stating what they believe that they're all really good and bad.
And ethically, ethnically poor activities that they believe all the companies are getting up to.
If this, if this is the other way around, and it was all full of potentially slanderers and reliable and abused information about companies, you can bet companies would stamp this into the freaking ground.
Why the hell are we even allowing this to be used against employees?
And also, because we're looking at the safest and effectively blockball people out of that are working.
How does this stand with human rights?
Yeah, don't you have a human right to be able to work?
Yeah, you have a right to work. That's for sure.
I'm not quite sure how human rights would fit into this.
What do we talk to you about that here in the UK? Is that a member of Parliament?
I really need to, I really need to start understanding how it works here and how it can reach out to people because this is very concerning.
And I'll tell you why, because my daughter actually may get listed in this national staff registry database.
So, is that what is, and a dismissal, national staff dismissal register? There you go.
I'll tell you why in a second.
So, dismiss me not to those who are looking for way out of ever having to work.
Can you use this? There's effectively a means to keep them in benefits for the rest of their life.
This is really fucking rotten.
I hope you can pick it up and actually room with it.
It's got major retail employees, including self-adjusted habits, read managed services, and H&V signed up to popular register with data.
First of all, information, including further grants that we held for three years, all five years in special circumstances.
This is absolutely malicious. I'll have to email the link to it.
I just cannot believe this wasn't in the fucking news.
I can't see that.
Actually, it wasn't the news. I did get a couple of links from folks to a BBC webpage about this.
But of course, that's not really big like the news the news.
The companies that are doing this seem to be retail oriented, and I think that's actually quite easy to handle.
Because we do need to protest. We do have to do something about stuff like this.
By the way, I'm sure something like this will get started in the States.
It seems like just too good of an idea.
The national staff dismissal registry.
Although, of course, it will be the NSCR in the States.
The national staff can't registry.
A register.
So here's what happened over the weekend.
Christina usually works Sunday at an outfit called Jack Wills.
Now, Jack Wills is a clothing line.
Very much like Abercrombie in Fitch, if you will.
So it's a big brand, very expensive, completely over-priced crap that portrays a lifestyle.
Okay, the Jack Wills lifestyle.
And Christina started working for them part-time only because of course you still in school.
Because she was recruited on the high street of Gilford recruited because of her looks.
And if you look at the staff in this store, it's nothing with beautiful children.
In fact, all of them going to what they call here public school, but that would be the equivalent of private school in the US.
So the opposite of a state school.
So they're all public school kids. They are all blonde.
Every single one of them, they're all beautiful. Have striking features.
Of course, my daughter definitely has all that.
She was talking to us at home about, you know, how she was kind of unhappy working there.
She didn't really, you know, like the, you know, the kind of the whole Jack Wills lifestyle that seemed a little, you know, just a little superficial to her.
You know, kidding, if you have to buy a $300 sweater.
And then she starts to say and mention a couple other things that really caught my attention. The first one is that they also recruit ugly kids.
That's really what she said. They have the ugly crew as they're known internally at the store. The ugly crew.
Who are supposed to do restocking only. They're not allowed to help in the store because they're not pretty enough, which just boggles the mind that this is actually taking place in 2008.
And here's the kicker. Okay. So these kids get absolute minimum wage.
And, and I also, it turns out she's starting to contract for Christ's.
A contract, which I didn't know about, and I can question the legality of that, you know, she's only 17. So
The contract says, if you want to quit, she has to give four weeks notice.
For a part time Sunday job, please, don't make me laugh.
But here's the thing that really pisses me off. So they get paid four pounds 60, which is a minimum wage per hour.
Here in the UK. But they are obliged. It's mandatory, although not written in there. You know, stellar employment contract. It's mandatory.
That whenever they're working, they're always wearing Jack Will's clothing. Now, they don't get the clothing for free.
In fact, they have to purchase the clothing. They can use their store discount, which is a big discounts, like 75% off.
But still, they have to wear it. It has to be new clothing. It has to be the new lines. It can't be something from last month. It has to be this month. So what happens is these kids wind up spending most of their harder and money on clothing at the same fricking store.
And it's, it's a, it's such a horrible nasty thing to do and to absolutely make it mandatory.
It's crazy. And so Christina is like, you know, I really want to quit, but I'm, I don't want to. I'm worried. I'm afraid because I don't want them to come after me.
You know, because I have to give four weeks notice and, you know, some other kid, Dan, he wanted to quit and they made him work for two more weeks. I'm like, wait a minute. This is freaking slavery. You can't do this. So I guess my whole point at here is that she may show up on some national staff dismissal register.
Right, for working in retail, which would be, and by the way, there should be a way under the Freedom of Information Act to find out if anyone's in there.
But let us not hold back from talking about the horrible practices of retail themselves. We don't need database for that. We can just say it.
And we can tell people not to go shop there because they treat workers unfairly or they report on them unfairly or they spy on them unfairly. And by the way, as much as it hurts me to say it,
we don't actually have to go and work in these stores. Let them know that they really need the workers to make all that money. They need their staff and the staff needs to be treated well.
And I can easily say this because I think I think I've been a pretty good job at treating staff very, very fairly throughout the years. And if not, let that person stand up.
So indeed, and again, helping out if there's a way to get to a minister of or a member of Parliament to discuss this and the home offices involvement by all means, let's get into it.
All right, what do we do on time? Let me just see what we're at.
Holy crap, 45 minutes. Let's go another 15 if you don't mind, because I still need to talk about fuel.
Hi Adam, this is spurred to going from Belgium again. I was catching up on some very source codes.
So we're in the April, I was and have ended up, and I wanted to weigh in or pitch you questions towards the responsibility on the following thing.
First, it's about oil prices. I learned from my brother, who works in the oil industry and directly that the list cost of oil.
That's like what it costs to fill up a barrel of oil is to stay at $12 dollars, roughly, around about that figure.
We're paying or on the market, they're paying over 100, what are we at, $120 and $30? Who gets this money?
First question. Second, if the euro is growing solar towards the dollar, that should mean that oil cost and our petrol cost and Europe should be lower, no, because our euro is worth more compared to the dollar.
So we should be getting more oil for less euros, but that's also something that's not happening. We're just paying more and more and more.
So thanks for somebody explain it. Thank you.
All right, man. Thank you. Yeah, of course. And this is something that was explained to me very simply by John C. Devorek on no agenda, no agenda.mevio.com.
It's basically the commodities and future traders. They're ripping us off. They are completely ripping you off and the government is standing by and letting it happen.
What's going on here is whenever the dollar gets stronger, weaker, IE, the euro gets stronger, the price of oil automatically goes up.
Okay, because the two are linked intrinsically, I think is the right expression.
In fact, if you really wonder the calculation, go back to 2000 and look at the euro versus the dollar. In fact, I think it was $1.2 to the euro.
I think that's it. Or 1.2 euros to the dollar. There you go.
And the price of oil was about per barrel about 70 euros at the time, 60 euros, actually 60 or 70.
So that's basically converting the dollar price to the euro. Now with a much weaker dollar, okay, a much weaker dollar.
But a much higher price of oil, it's still around 70 euros for a barrel of oil.
Okay, you could do these calculations. This is just roughly it's saying I'm just taking oil somewhere around $11020.
So that shows you that there is a margin in there. There's money to be made by basically selling the dollar and buying oil.
Or you can reverse that and sell the oil and buy the dollar.
And you can basically make money on the way up and on the way down. And that's exactly what happened.
This is what guys like nylon are doing. Notice he hasn't called in recently because this is what banks do. I'll cut them banksters.
Okay, banksters, commodity and future traders. And by the way, I can't really blame them because they're just doing their job, you know, they're making money. That's what they do.
But boy, I can't believe we're sitting on the sidelines and just letting it happen.
With someone please just show the public how are being ripped off because the price of diesel has doubled in Europe from 2000 to 2008 doubled.
So if the price of the raw material doing the conversion on the dollar to the euro has not changed, maybe by a euro or two, but pretty much stayed the same. Why are we paying twice as much for the end product?
Okay, why was very simple because you're getting ripped off.
So I guess now it's time to reintroduce the concept of an alternative.
Adam, both by Johnny here from New York, a couple weeks ago listeners to the Charlie may remember my lengthy screen about the D evolution of mankind.
And all this bitch and we do and all the action and the lack of action that we take. Well, when I hung up the phone I realized that I'm just part of the problem and I've done nothing to solve it.
I don't know if this was a good idea. I'll let you know in a month or so. I sold my my beloved Audi A4 with six on the floor that used to snap my head back and suck 16 miles to the gallon.
And I got a car that runs on straight and wasted vegetable oil.
And there's plenty of research out there about this and there's a lot of controversy whether or not it actually helps or hurts the economy. All I know is this.
Gas get $4 a gallon in New York last week and I'm paying a dollar a gallon from the Chinese lady who owns the Chinese food restaurant down at the corner.
So, we're going to have the car explode in a month or so, who knows?
At least some Mercedes, so I'm rolling in style. Anyway, I'll check in within a month. I can either be calling to tell you it's the greatest thing ever.
And that every chuckle head should have a car that runs on vegetable oil or I'll be back at the Audi dealership until then.
Well, glad you got it.
Yeah, awesome. Thank you. Hey, my next car. It's going to be a diesel and I've already seen over here in the UK. You can get this thing called the fuel pod. Actually, the fuel pod, too.
Cost 2 1 1,000 pounds. You can get it green fuels.co.uk. You can create your own biodiesel from vegetable oil.
That's, you know, we need to rebrand this stuff as well. Something like put a Chinese restaurant in your tank. Put a Chinese in your tank.
It is better.
Ah, that fits in perfectly with my rebranding of nuclear energy into nuclear energy, which actually isn't a rebrand. It's the way you're supposed to pronounce it, Mr. President.
Atomic rod here, new clear power. I like it. New clear. It's a great brand name. It should work to deflect any immediate negative reactions long enough to share the rest of the story.
Paul, if you're listening, thank you very much.
As you know, coming up with a good brand name is only one of many steps in a process of solving customer problems.
No brand succeeds without being built on a strong foundation of performance. Fortunately, the new clear business has a lot going for it.
The world's reactors are now producing the energy equivalent of about 12 million barrels of oil per day.
And there is room for huge growth. There are also thousands of ships flying the world's oceans that burn oil, but could vision uranium.
We can just build as many plants each year as we did in the 1970s to the 1990s.
We can break the market power of the coal oil and gas industries in just a few years.
We can really make the world a cleaner place with just two or three decades worth of steady effort.
The notion of a long-term struggle puts some people off. They advise that we should pick the low hanging fruit first.
They forget that our install base of power system took many years of hard work to build.
The quest for a quick fix for mining of how some people approach weak control. It doesn't matter to the years to get fat.
They still want to remove those pounds and time for their vacation next month.
Time to get back to work building the new clear infrastructure that will make us all win by hard to protect your freedom to compute, to travel,
and to take long, comfortable showers to aid in the achievement of prostate prevention quarters.
I think it's the long, long, nice warm showers.
That's a little more information about you than I needed my friend.
Yeah, I'm still, I gotta tell you, I'm still kind of into the nuclear, the nuclear products, the whole idea.
You know, stackable waste. We know how to take care of it. We know putting in water is one way.
Of course, I'd still love to figure out if we can shoot it to the sun, shoot it to the moon, or drop it off on Mars for that reason.
Hey, if we can get to 300 channels of stereo audio via satellite, we certainly, we should be able to throw some shit into space,
off towards the sun, ship it out there.
Stay on top of it, my friends. Oh, here's just one question I had for you guys.
This came in a while ago from Terence Daniels. Adam, do you know, or can you talk about a super network that Google plans to set up as the cable companies attempt to drive the phone companies out of business?
And the IT companies try to drive the cable companies out of business.
Interesting. I know I could love a good, good conspiracy, you know that.
So, I have not heard about a Google super network, but maybe I have something to do with those wireless frequencies they bid on, I don't know.
And maybe it's all those data centers they've got.
Why can't Google figure out what to do with our nuclear waste?
And why can't the President pronounce it properly?
Gee, wouldn't that be novel?
Something you don't hear very often. Actually, I don't think ever on the radio is poetry.
Certainly not poetry for our time.
And I think it is important to share that whenever possible.
Of course, on the media network, I actually beat up audio over here in the UK.
Today we have the slam idle podcast, which is just about the only one I'm aware of that really does any distribution of poetry.
And this one I found on the drop. The drop.io slash daily source code by a woman named Aaron Livingston.
And I think the title of the poem is Cassie and Ty.
And it's about our times, it's about our children, about our young people.
What they're going through. Things that we don't even take notice of.
Things that are happening, things that you see on the street.
And eyes of teenagers that we look into are hollow.
And we'll have a listen.
This is where it goes. I've got to have a story about two of my friends.
This is really important now because I mean, we're still a country at war, right?
So, and I hate how it just gets sort of pushed out of the way.
You know, once we're kind of like, oh, it's hard. You know, it's safe. You have same stuff every day on the news.
But it's, I mean, that shit adds up. You know, you hear just like stories coming through a couple people, you know, car bomb here, you know,
sneak attack there. And it's, it adds up.
And it's really important to remember that there are still affecting real people and real lives.
And so this is a story about a good friend of mine and her brother and their relationship.
As it pertains to the war. So.
He must know how her eyes stare at him.
From his unmistakable crew cut on down each brass button to polish pattern feathers.
And back up, Chris starts creases to confetti breast of patches finally landing on his name tag.
Only sometimes do they make it back up to his square jaw and on rare occasions they might meet his gaze.
But his eyes are faded, smoldering like mortar shells gone screening through house sites stored in memory reflex sense of smell.
And she wouldn't dare ask if he didn't want to tell it drips off him wanting someone to understand this first born son raised in an upper class subdivision turned college drop out left without meaning as a man and searching for approval.
He landed in Afghanistan, pride, weighing heavy as the machine gun and his soft hands and he wonders how did this happen.
Together, they ask the same questions.
Too many limbs lost to a cause, explained only in catch phrases. Too many bullets fired over rubble dalleys of misinformation. Too many graves dug to bury baby faces and sometimes.
She wishes the two of them could trade places because he must know how his eyes stare at her.
From her unmistakable nodded up locks on down each protest slogan button to scuffed and muddied marching boots and back up pants of patchwork trails finally landing on her unbound breasts.
Not only sometimes, do they make it back up to her square jaw and on rare occasions they might meet her gaze.
But her eyes are faded. Too long dated by her underestimated significance of accountic cultural presence in the face of a leader who would rather see her own brother die than admit to lying about why the US went to war.
This is not a battle over who loves our country more. This is a battle over preserving our nation's values conflicted as they are.
Hers.
She doesn't really happen. I'm sorry.
Hers is exactly the type of freedom he set out to defend, but believes is a two few dial memes to an end.
And his is exactly the type of freedom she could never defend because she believes that a two brutal memes to an end to be American is complicated to say the least.
And to air as human we all make mistakes.
And then we all wonder why it takes so long to learn from them.
So I learned from my friend and her piece making process with next of kin together around a dinner table mediated by two loving parents.
They settle conflicts that have baffled and plagued the greatest of nations.
So God bless these heroes that they may leave my generation.
Thank you.
Take my hand. I heard you say depend on me.
Close your eyes. I'll lead the way. Don't disagree.
I've tried so hard to make this happen. I've lost myself.
Now it's pain to see.
You won't let me go. I'll give you a shot. No, I don't want it anymore.
It won't be the same. Don't do what you think I can take over.
Here we are. You have me full. You're blind to me.
So I'll lead the way. Don't let me go. I'll give you a shot.
You won't let me go. I'll give you a shot. No, I don't want it anymore.
It won't be the same. Don't do what you think I can take over.
I'll lead the way. Don't let me go. I'll give you a shot. No, I don't want it anymore.
You won't let me go. I'll give you a shot. No, I don't want it anymore.
It won't be the same. Don't do what you think I can take over.
Don't do what you think I can take over.