More listening to a man who had his nail clipper confiscated outside a plane, only to have
a flight attendant inside a plane and a book and a knife, Adam Curry.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears, I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Just like it's namesake, this Charlie's here for your convenience.
Here's the Daily Source code, 7-11.
I'll fly, I'll fall in charge now, I know it makes me better.
I have something called a sky.
Oh, I'll take the myth and make it mine.
Oh, I want to tell you, I want to walk for you.
Oh, I'll come and make it mine.
Time now, my life's too hot, give it all the time, but I know it makes me better.
I don't show you why, I've got a touch of sky.
I know it makes me better.
I have something called a sky.
Oh, I'll take the myth and make it mine.
Oh, I want to tell you, I like to walk for you.
Oh, I'll come and make it mine.
Oh, I'll take the myth and make it mine.
Oh, I want to tell you, I like to walk for you.
Oh, I want to draw a book for Patreon.
Thank your audience.
Yeah.
Hi.
Go ahead.
You know, if I find it on the PMN, you got to download it.
You got to think about the order.
And then, of course, it's the voicemail message.
I think I had three, four, let me just count.
Probably about 150 or so to go through.
Anyhow, if each one can be a maximum of three minutes,
you can understand how that also is quite time consuming.
But I really don't want to miss anything.
So that's why I meticulously go through all of them.
Get everything set up, ready to roll.
And little side track there.
So I was looking at new mixers, young polette.
And after I saw his hit test video,
I'm getting wood for his set up there.
So what's a boy who has everything?
What's he going to go and buy?
Of course, a new mixer.
So in the market for that and found a fantastic one, by the way,
the law was Z4, Lima, Alpha, Whiskey, Oscar, Z4, Zulu,
four and check it out.
Man, I'm really liking that.
Not as a portable job, but just something
would give me a little more functionality
than the Yamaha that I'm using with Casplaster.
So then, of course, speaking of Casplaster,
I had so much stuff, so many different elements
that I knew I was going to fill up all the bays
as a word, the virtual bays we can fill up with tracks.
I've run into this before I think I recall
that when you really fill it up, then there's
some irreproducible bug that I just can't figure out.
That all of a sudden you get access violations.
And then it says, unable to open temp.mp3.
And then you basically have a choice,
and I always go the hard route.
Of course, you basically remove the Casplaster at I&I file
from its folder, rename it to something else.
Open that in a separate notebook window,
then start Casplaster again, so it's a new I&I file.
Then start copying, pasting stuff in until you hit a bug.
And that, of course, is the piece that doesn't seem
to be related to a specific file name
or a file, but just the number of files,
and then it starts to freak out.
So I got a couple of quick time windows open,
leaving three Casplaster windows free.
And so I'm going to kind of move it along.
A couple of comments from you guys in between
some awesome music, most of which today's Podsafe,
but how can I say, certainly not all?
Hey Adam, it's a glorified mic here.
How'd you listen to your show for a few months now?
I heard about you on the Ron Paul's forums,
and I've been listening to you ever since.
It's part of me for getting a little defensive
for a fellow Ron Paul supporter,
but this is about that douchebag, Chris Moelle.
Now I know your British fans are wondering,
where an American gets off-trashing a British shock
job after only hearing a few minutes of a show
on the DSC, and I'll tell you.
A golden rule of radio is, if you have to talk over
a music bed, you fucking suck.
It's proof that what the DJ is saying
isn't interesting enough to the listeners.
That's right.
You have to punch up as it dulling ramblings
with music that's just popular enough
not to turn off the radio.
Oh, and by the way, if your sidekick's name is
preceded by the word comedy, even on funny hack.
And Adam, I love you, but I'm not in love with you.
Oh, man, I love you too, de Homo.
That's absolutely, well, that's funny.
And it is interesting that that did catch my ear as well
when I played that Chris Moelle's bit,
that he had this background music,
you know, like real kind of almost like a techno
kind of driving beat.
I tend to agree, I've never been a big music bed guy.
I really like just the, well, actually,
what the hell am I talking about?
Let's do a little bit of our own background track
on the Charlie for this footballer.
Of course, something that fits in with the,
with the mellowness of the show.
We always, when we think of Glenn Miller,
we always think of the Moonlight Serenade,
but this is the sunrise Serenade.
By the way, I did hear back from Moelle's producer,
Rachel Jones, she, I guess she's like the,
she's like a BBC overall morning producer, something,
and then she turned me on to Alan Hayden.
I guess he is one of the producer boys who runs around there.
And he was really nice, actually, you know,
and he said that Chris was a big fan of the,
of the Daily Source code,
and you know, they were really working on their,
on their downloads as well,
and really serious about their podcast.
And it's, it's interesting,
we get 270,000 downloads per episode.
I'm like, damn, that's pretty good.
I said if you guys wanted any promotion from Potcho,
I'm bringing it over boys,
we're growing with 30,000 percent annually.
So what do you think?
Is this working this Glenn Miller stuff?
Let's try it under another comment here.
Hey, Adam, this is Rick and Ohio.
Oh, high of the airway, that was excellent, man.
Like when I heard that come on,
you just talk about a lot of memories coming back into my head.
And think good if you didn't talk over that one,
because well, they would've kind of ruined it,
but thanks a lot for bringing those memories.
And I suppose next one you'll be playing
as a one-ton soldier, something like that.
Rock on, buddy.
Come here, man.
Thanks, buddy.
Yeah, it's the soundtrack to your lives, man.
I got a lot of people sending me emails
about pilot of the airways when I played that.
Some people even sent me better recordings
and lots of stories just like that.
You know, I was in the car with my kid.
You know, you can place yourself immediately
when you hear that song.
It's just one of those.
And I believe in the category, a one-hit wonder.
Oh, yeah, I know what it's going to say.
Related to pilot, and this will be the only kind of like semi-rant
that I'm going to do today,
because I do want to get back to the music.
As we listen continuously to the sounds
of the Glenn Miller band, sunrise, serene.
Just good enough to keep you listening.
This crash landing of the British airways flight from Beijing.
I think it's BA38.
I've, you know, there's quite a nice discussion going
on over curry.com about this because when I heard of this,
I was like, wow, you know, this is really interesting.
And as a particular to airman like myself, you know,
we want to know what happened.
And, you know, because this is a situation,
and of course, the right now, the preliminary reports,
and I've been keeping my eye on here on this.
It's pretty much top of the news in the UK.
The preliminary reports state that the aircraft lost full power.
So not just both engines, but also all electrical power.
And I've heard conflicting reports
anywhere between 1,400 feet on final approach.
Now, this is something we actually trained for.
You know, well, not necessarily for a full electrical failure,
but we certainly trained for coming up short
because of an engine failure.
And that was pretty consistent I thought with what I saw.
But, you know, what we're getting news wise,
just really bugs the crap out of me because, well, you know,
they have no experts.
I have not, I've yet to see the BBC put an actual pilot
on television.
There was a pilot who called up on the radio two today.
And he said, look, you know, this is kind of interesting
because, you know, to have this double engine failure
on the triple seven, which only has two engines.
These massive Rolls Royes engines.
If that really happened, it's first it's the first time
and I believe the aircraft's history.
But, you know, add to that a full electrical failure,
I would say we'd have to ground the entire fleet.
That's the news.
That's what we should be talking about.
People should not be flying on triple seven
until we understand what happened.
That's a real safety issue.
Instead, all we're hearing from British Airways
is, look how great the flight crew was.
Now, you know, obviously any landing that you walk away
from good landing, any landing that the plane is reusable.
That's a great landing.
So, you know, of course, Kudos to the flight crew
for whatever happened, whether it was pilot error
or there really are only a couple of things
that this could have been, top of the list maintenance.
So, maybe there was something poorly maintained.
We'll find out eventually in the long, long run.
If they can't find anything else, it has to be maintenance.
Because, you know, that's just how it works.
You maintain the stuff and it won't break.
Unless there was faulty parts,
but we'll find that out as well.
But still, double engine failure, full electrical failure, man.
That's really tough to explain away to maybe one part
not working or being, or malfunctioning.
The second one.
Hold on a second, let me just take a look here.
Because I did kind of write this up,
and maybe I should fall along with my own notes.
Oh, crap.
What is this?
Now, I don't have connection to the net.
Oh, I hate it when that happens.
I've had a lot of connectivity problems.
Anyway, it could easily have been fuel starvation,
which means they ran out of fuel.
Now, this is certainly something
the air crew would have been aware of before 1000 feet.
So, they would have, I think,
legally have had to call it in if they were to run and low.
It's possible there was a malfunction there.
It's probably that there's, look, they got fuel in Beijing
presumably, so it's possible they got short change.
But still, the crew would have known about it.
Whether is another option, I'm always aware of the weather.
There was as far as I know, no wind shear conditions,
which could definitely have made this happen,
although that usually happens, I would say,
when you're a little bit closer to the runway.
And then there's all kinds of conflicting reports
about people saying, oh, I heard it roar overhead,
you know, well, the plane will make noise without its engines,
but it's not really going to roar.
And it could also be the pilot's just fucked up.
I mean, honestly, that's, it's just completely possible.
Maybe he misjudged the, the glide path.
You know, it looked to me like a hard landing.
And, you know, when you hear people speak of the plane belly flopping,
you know, I've done that and I wrecked some instruments
even doing it.
It was early in my flying career and what happens is,
you're too, they actually too high above the runway at one point.
And then you flare and then you run out of air speed.
And then it's just going to drop out of the sky now,
it doesn't matter whether you're at a thousand feet
or whether you're at a ten feet or five feet from the ground.
If you run out of air speed, you're going to drop down.
So it could also have just been a pure air speed issue.
I mean, all kinds of things we don't know about,
but I'm a little sick of all of this,
the crew were heroes.
We don't know that.
We don't know if they were or weren't.
Again, my thesis is that if they got everyone on the ground,
and they walked right away from the plane, they did their job.
Or if it was mechanical failure.
And until we know that, we should be very suspicious of this aircraft.
Because obviously, I'm going to give the benefit of doubt
to the, to the air crew.
Statistically, I'd have to say, top of the list pilot error
and then it's maintenance.
Okay, so much for that ramp.
Just need to get that out there, you know.
And it makes you wonder, this stuff I know about,
and I see the reporting being shitty.
How about the stuff I know nothing about?
Is that just a shit?
You might think so.
From our planet, I can't erase all my imagination.
What I wasted all night.
Oh, and I tried to believe in the simplification.
To be there when I arrived at my destination.
Feel like I was wasting the time in more time when we'd stay home.
I'm old, what if I never loved you?
I tried, but I could never be the one to say when we'd stay home.
Oh, I'm old, I could never leave that way.
You could see my light in the slogan, I think.
We were so unfaithful.
Oh, do you make me feel like a nearing hyperventilation?
When you call me liar?
Or is it my imagination?
Feel like I was wasting the time when we'd stay home.
I'm old, what if I never loved you?
I tried, but I could never be the one to say when we'd stay home.
Oh, I'm old, I could never leave that way.
But I could never have been that one to say when we'd stay home.
Oh, no.
If I said, I'd be the one to say when we'd stay home.
I could never have been the one to say when we'd stay home.
I could never be the one to say when we'd stay home.
I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I can't forget the more I know I know I can't forget the more I know I know I can't forget the more I know I know I can't forget the more I know I know I can't forget the more I know I know I can't forget the more I know I know I know I
But if I never never gonna evera else, never gonna ever
If from my Alberta i can't have a band- named is
once just as hyper-fenolation
Reading straight from the biopage and the pot-seventi music network once just has Blade hundreds of shows all over North America
They signed to JFK media early 2006 and released the first album destination with the lay Bloc Tortop Heat he first 2006 won's just is a blend of rock and reggae with hockey Popp melodies
Brought to you by, I guess, J.S.K. Meadie.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, cool song though.
I liked a lot of those guys.
I've liked a page of stuff up on the podcast music now.
We're starting in October 2007.
Oh, yes.
Oh, do I need some work on my ass?
Amy Mack.
How are you doing, darling?
It's time for my answer, sir.
Hey, Adam.
It's Amy Mack.
Yeah, huh?
I got you.
I'm so glad to hear that you're feeling better.
I didn't want to make you work out when you were down and out.
Aw, thanks, baby.
I appreciate it.
Now, today we're going to be doing a standing exercise.
Okay.
You're self situated and we'll get started.
We're going to do a standing, baby.
Okay.
I like that.
I'm ready.
Start with your feet shoulder with a part.
Okay.
Now, kick your right leg out to the front and then bring it back to center.
Then take your left leg and take it all the way behind you so that you're in a deep lunge.
Okay.
You're going to put your left hand on the floor.
Oh, shit.
Now, bring the left leg back to the center and stand up tall.
Okay.
Nice.
Now repeat.
Three more times.
Okay.
So right leg out.
Right.
Back to center.
Out center.
And then left leg back and then hand on the floor and back to center.
Okay.
Two more.
Out.
Right.
Center.
Back.
And left.
Yep.
And center.
One more.
Okay.
Right.
And center.
And left.
Four.
Great.
Now switch sides.
Left leg front.
Left leg.
And back to center.
Okay.
And then right leg back into a lunge.
Right hand touches the ground.
It's just tiring.
Great.
Keep it up.
Three more to go.
Okay.
Kick.
And lunge.
Yes.
Three.
Kick.
And lunge.
Last one.
Okay.
Kick.
And lunge.
I'm back.
Excellent job.
Great.
Well, it's a pleasure being done.
Good job, everybody.
Good job.
All you do is see listeners.
And until next time.
Exercise.
Yeah, baby.
Thank you so much, Amy Mac.
I love it when women are mean to me.
Let me tell you something about these motherfuckers out here.
When I scream at me, and curse at me.
Let me tell you something.
My brain has been washed.
And it's hollow with spell.
That wasn't too much.
She's just insisting.
Some's baby.
Jammed in the space of the hell.
Let me tell you something.
Like a cheese free.
I'm just better than you.
And I'm not buying you two.
So fix your arm.
Well, now that's something to do.
I chase my mouth to crack.
The loudest blow on my day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're a man, tell you something.
My mind's been washed.
And I'm copying a smoke.
They're working too much.
Make sure to never pay off our estimates.
To be our actors' plug.
Yeah, I tell you something.
Like a registered bar.
Die of your mind!
I keep on holding up.
Easier than your old girl away.
I tell you what being on my heart.
I tease my mouth to crack.
In the head's blue.
Bottom out a set.
Lisa If busca not a car.
Super meticulous.
You are almost unable.
Let me tell you something, my brain's been washed
And it's how it was fair
Can't we do what our business is doing
To explain it, damn it's me so fair
Yeah, let me tell you something
Latter, Jesus freak
I'm just better than you
And now I've got you two
But it's your honor
Won't you have something to do
I see you smell
I'm glad to crack
It's really not a set
I'm so free around most
Isn't she just like
Janice, Joplin, and Tina Turner
wrapped up in the one hot, sexy bundle
Oh man, I wish I wished
I could just do nothing
But the daily source code every day
I would put together such a kick-ass show for you guys
It would be so filled with
I just need more time
I need more time
Good morning, my friend Adam
Did you spot him or something?
I was going through
What's your great year
And I love you
I love you too, man
Meena, thank you so much for checking in
Glad to know you're still on board in Ecuador
Of course you are listening to the daily source code
Kingdom where you are bad
We are global
Hey Adam, Monten from Toronto here
I was just listening to DSC710
And I think this is a great time to finally call in
Instead of bugging you by email
You're absolutely right, I'm packaging options
Being wide open for music and movies
Radiohead and cigarette are both demonstrated
In late 2007
Radiohead with air in rainbows box
With LPC diversions of the album
Along with a booklet of artwork
And cigarette are sort of the deluxe edition of
CD that came with a fact book of photography
From their Icelandic tour
Both a very limited edition
And eBay re-fail price is a version
Considerably the luxury edition of Hayman
A currently floating around a hundred bucks
More than triple the original retail price
And it's just released in late November
It's clearly a strong market for quality packaging
As long as real added value
And looks pretty fantastic
The same principle applies to movie
The fact, looking at my library of DVDs
I realised that the majority of them are special edition kits
Many of them have those funky steel cases
And almost all have substantial bonus features
With a movie itself becoming increasingly commoditized
I wonder whether we'll get to a point where the movie is given away
But you go to the store to specifically buy a package with special features
It would definitely be a market sustaining and promoting quality
Filmmaking over cheap feed fill-up tap
And I wonder whether we'd get lines of a radio being made these days
And I glad to hear the lady piers doing better
I love you, I didn't carry it, etc
Yeah, I thank you, well, absolutely
This is part of the conversation I started earlier in the week
Maybe it was yesterday
Early in the week yesterday, whatever
This is clearly what people want
People pay you money for interesting things
And it's not just physical packaging
I think it's also, it's just packaging in general
Virtual packaging is just as valid
And as long as you make it easy
And as long as it's interesting packaging
Do you know that in the perfume industry
In the cosmetics industry
Which I happen to know a little bit about
My wife had a cosmetics company
Which helped out with from time to time
That the secondary
You have primary packaging
So if you have a lipstick as an example
Or if you have a perfume bottle
Sometimes even more apparent
That's primary packaging
The bottle itself or the lipstick dispenser
Think of the secondary packaging
Sometimes just as much money goes into the secondary packaging
Is into the entire fucking product
It's unbelievable
Not quite sure what I was talking about
Because people desire that
They desire the pretty box
So there are ways we can make pretty virtual boxes
And there's a lot more stuff
When I'm really enjoying seeing
There's a lot of people who are out there
Now kind of fulfilling the role of the promoter of music
And they're figuring out their own business models
So about three people I know now who are doing that
And it works
And there you go
You've got Princess Ty who Ty Poe I think
Who's always emailing about Sofia Ramos
So it sticks to my mind to get into the email
From her another update
Should you actually play some more that angry bitch
And it makes me feel good
And then of course there's guys like Chuck
Hey Anna
I'm Chuck
Chuck's sending from the Northwest side of Shai Town
Shai Town
I just emailed you to Adamachary.com
Two audio bumpers
And of course that that was a mistake
It took Chuck another try
Don't send it to Adamachary.com
Send it to Adamachary.com
From Chrissy Haksha
The
Chance Diva from Opus 3 back in the day
Remember 1992
Hell yeah
Anyway
I just emailed him up to Adamachary.com
I want to make sure you got him
And then I'll give you a little preview
I'll give you a preview
Listen to Chuck
Yeah, I'll call
I'll call
So there you go man
I just shot him off to you
So
Yeah, let me know what you think
Check out our new tunes
And that's a music network
She uploaded seven of them
And we're hooking up some special NGB too
So stay tuned
And let me know what you think about the man
Here we go
All right man, let me mean it
Great hair, hope you win
Love you mean it, great hair
Hope you win, thank you
That's almost as good as
Get Cape where Cape fly
Let me hear that again
That was pretty cool
I gotta remember this one
All right man, love you mean it
Great hair, hope you win
I love you mean it, great hair
Hope you win, absolutely
Hi, this is Kirstie Huckshaw
And we're listening to Adam Curry on the Daily Source Code
See, he sends me the artwork with her
And it's a little DSC logo on
She is beautiful of course
Since my name is something about naked pictures in the title
He gets me an ID
Of course, I'm going to play this song
And then it falls in the country on
And they only blind side
It's all so good dream, don't know
We are made of shapes
Keys who have closed out the freezer
One through his home
But I'm not a taste of
And now I can't hide
This blue trail of mine
And I'm happy
But I don't think they can see
Our own place
And you make your bed
And you lie in it
And you fade your head
And we lie to win
And fade and escape all the
As we mend to those
Now I can't control it
Make you died
His blue trail all around
And I don't think they can see
Our own place
I don't think they can't say
Oh, I don't think they can't say
Yeah, I could play that. I could accompany her.
Kirstie. Gosh, it's beautiful.
Yeah, we'd make a nice, I wonder what tall she is.
Yeah. Oh, how long for the good old days?
When the talent would just blow the DJ to get their song played.
Yeah, these days you've got to do it with a picture.
Okay.
Kirstie Hawkshia and Meteor's and of course you'll find links to that song
and all the songs played on today's Fubar Friday in the show notes.
A daily source code dot com.
I got some more mellow stuff coming your way.
But first, let's open the door and invite our good friend, John Poledin.
One girl in casting with Adam Curry.
Adam's Mark, you ready to be stumps down?
Because he used the hip dance.
Bring it on.
Hey, Adam. This is hit there's number 105 and all of the songs this week are from 1985.
So here we go with intro. Number one.
It's all of you for all of you, for all of me. Something like I'd have no idea to number two.
I remember that's so well.
You see this beautiful 35 millimeter camera fall off a camera head in the clip.
Eric Clapton forever.
And then this is number three.
Yeah, you know, no one outside of the Netherlands will probably know that.
Maybe in the UK, that's Princess Sam your number one.
And these are the answers.
This is 9.9.9.
You
All of me for all of you 9.9 and some number one.
And this is engine number two.
This is Eric Clapton.
Number one.
For every man Eric Clapton is engine number two.
And this is engine number three.
I was right.
This is Princess Sam your number one.
Three.
And Princess, this is engine number three.
And I in this week's hit test and that's number 105.
I almost got it all right.
So Adam, how did you do?
Yeah, just missed 9.9.
The answer is here to this hit test and also the links to iTunes so you can buy these
tricks online or to be found at hittest.botshow.com.
Yeah, go buy them.
Next week I'll be back for number 106.
So until then, take care and bye bye.
Hit test every female dot com.
Info, y'all, dot com.
Jay and P.O.L.G.T dot com.
Take guys, I'll post reviews answers and commentary that cut through the corporate bullshit
that's into poly the podcast.
Comment over, share a beer, and let's get our geek on over it.
He said nerds dot com.
Hey Adam, this is Josh, one of the judge more on the show in summerville, Massachusetts.
I have a suggestion and request.
I think there's a way we can get the word out about Ron Paul and any other objects of red pill
significance using your fabulous voice because I'm an unknown and an unattractive male.
I've decided to enlist the skills of a dear friend of mine out west.
Her name is a leg or west fall.
I believe she'll be able to get the point across to you a little bit more
and joyably at least.
Anyways, I tried to clean up her audio a little bit.
There's some noise in the background.
I used audacity and stuff like that.
Unfortunately, she's not as equipped as some of us podcasters are.
But I hope you'll give her a listen and give her a chance.
Anyway, I love you, Adam Curry.
Oh, man.
And that means no homo coming from me.
Back at your mark for a great day.
Hi, Adam.
It's a leg or west fall and select city Utah.
Hi, baby.
Rumor has it that you haven't been getting many audio messages from the ladies these days.
Correct.
I thought I dropped you a line and make a small request for all the podcasting,
Ron Paul supporters out there.
Many of us have seen your official endorsement of Ron Paul for President on YouTube.
And as beautiful as it is to see you, I think a quick DSC branded Adam Curry sound bite.
Endorsing Ron Paul would be great to hear too.
You know something that podcasters like my friend Josh can stick in their shows or
job in their feeds would be an ideal way to get the word out.
Face it Adam.
Wait, oh wait a minute.
That sounded like she was getting sexy.
That's a pretty good idea.
But I don't just want to do like a high amount of glory.
I want to do some different.
And then cough.
I know you're listening.
Let's do something.
I got to get an named cough credit for for the endorsement.
You know, I called them up and said, all right, man.
Here's what I, here's the outline.
Here's what I want to say.
Now, please put it in a fucking English and he did a great job.
And I feel so part of the system that I have a speech writer.
So name cough, come on, let's do something in audio.
Let's make it cool.
So the people who were for Ron Paul can use it.
That's a good idea.
And by the way, you'll have to do it on the weekend because I can't ask you this on company
time.
So I'll talk to you tomorrow.
No voice carries more authority in the podcasting universe than yours does.
Oh yeah.
I figure if hundreds of podcasters can offer awards of wisdom spoken by the pod father himself.
We can get more people listening to reason.
You've been in doubt with one of the world's best voices.
And we all are not all, baby.
I figured you could do just one of those velvety voice to min show comments that you often do for
other podcasters out there.
I know you're often reluctant to do them, but you know you do them so well.
Please add them.
I love you, Adam Curry.
Bye.
Oh, man.
I just got a little tingling in my private.
Who is she?
Send me naked pictures.
Oh, shit, there's my wife.
Hello?
Well, I was just getting really sexy, huh?
Yeah, and then you walked in.
Why are you doing that?
Why are you interrupting the show?
I'm doing the show.
I'm doing a, I'm doing something sexy.
Yes, I had this really sexy girl calling up.
I do have to miss that.
Well, I don't know what are you doing.
Are you in the kitchen making me a meal?
Hey, hi.
So, so while you're making a meal, I'm having sexy talk here.
You want to watch?
Uh, sorry, didn't know that.
It's okay.
Well, I didn't know, but I was right in the middle of it.
And then I heard the door open.
Like, oh, shit.
There's my wife.
Like, you have fucking radar.
Ah, he's thinking of some other woman.
Okay.
All right.
So, what was your question, honey?
What? Do you want your food up yet?
Can I, can you wait another like 15 minutes,
and then I'll come downstairs?
All right.
Yeah.
And I'll talk sexy to you.
Everyone's so know how you're doing.
You want to come over here and say hi?
It's Fubar Friday who gives a shit.
I mean, here, hold on a second.
Let me, uh, hold on.
Here.
Have a seat, baby.
Take some headphones.
Okay.
I'll prank him up, hold on.
All right.
You got sound?
Is that good?
Tell me one is too loud.
One, two, one, two, two.
It's very loud.
Okay.
How's this?
Is that good?
But is a singer doesn't matter.
Look, you want to hear this?
So, I'll just play a little piece, okay?
So, uh, this guy got this group,
because I, you know, women never call.
I don't know if there's any women who listen to my show.
And this, and this guy got some girl.
Does it do a really, you know what I'd say?
You know, you, Adam, you should do like a promo for Ron Paul,
that other podcasters can play.
Okay.
This.
I figure if hundreds of podcasters can offer
words of wisdom spoken by the pod father himself,
we can get more people listening to reason.
Listen, you've been in doubt with one of the world's best voices, Adam.
And we all love how you think.
I figure you could do just one of those
velvety voice to min show comments.
Say you often do for other podcasters out there.
I know you're often reluctant to do them,
but you know you do them so well.
Please, Adam.
I love you, Adam.
Curry.
And I, and I, I got a little tingle in my
private.
Did you get it, too?
No, but I can't imagine.
Yeah, I can't imagine.
I know you will.
Yeah, because I know you.
Yeah, and it was like, you know, you're very sensitive.
Yes, there.
I'm very sensitive.
No, especially in your language.
Yeah, what did you hear her?
That was, I know.
She's a beautiful voice.
Yeah, so yeah, so I was just about to say something.
Send me some naked pictures that you walked in.
No, you did not.
Yes, of course I did.
I didn't get it.
Well, I never send them anyway, so I might as well.
So I'm, let me tell you something.
That sounds so old, like you're an old man.
I am an old man.
Can you send me some naked pictures?
That's the whole problem.
Well, how would you suggest us?
No, not your young.
But when I was an MTV, when I was younger,
you're still.
I remember I had male bags filled of, of, of, of envelopes before you
feel, feel, feel, feel, feel, feel, feel,
keep with, feel the, feel, feel.
Don't, don't, don't bust a gut baby.
Easy.
Oh, yeah, we, we don't, we don't want your
spewing out through your holes.
I have a hole.
How's your hole doing?
It's, it's just like, a whale with a hole.
Look, yeah, you got a blow hole.
I got a blow hole.
Yeah, right.
Let's see.
That's it.
It's how it looks.
Blow.
It has a blow hole.
Oh, hand, look at my blow hole.
Oh, can I lick your blow hole?
I want to show you my blow hole.
For all of you who are wondering how the lady Patricia is doing,
as you can tell she's doing just fine.
Now, let me tell you something.
I think I, I, I feel so good.
It's been such a long time.
Now I remember how it was to feel good.
I had just to feel healthy again.
Yeah, because you get used to it.
Yeah, what used to feeling healthy?
Feeling shitty?
A feeling shitty, yeah.
There's about a year baby, but are you, and you know what?
Everyone suffers with you.
Really?
I mean, I don't mean that in a bad way.
I was acting very happy.
But you cannot fool us.
We know, and do you feel even a different vibe
in the house already?
Oh, yeah, you're happy now.
Of course I'm happy.
But now I know why.
What did you think?
I just walked into you.
Because, yeah, I'm having sex,
yeah, I'm having sex with my, with my listeners.
No, but I was happy before that, too.
Oh, okay.
Uh, it's so good to have you on the show, babe.
Oh, yeah, ratings.
I just want ratings.
Uh-huh.
I don't see Adam Curry busted by his wife.
Can I give them to you?
I was about to go cyber.
You are a ratings bananza.
Whenever you're on the show, it's almost double the amount of downloads.
Yeah, people like me like to hear me talking down to you.
Yes, yeah, yeah, they want to hear that.
Put me into, keep me in line, absolutely.
Yeah, kick him.
Right, would you have not done successfully yet?
Although, but walking you know, on the side of her sex talk?
Yeah, that was, that was what we'll talk about.
That's a fucking radar, man.
I'm telling you.
I want you to, if we do do me favor, just listen to this one,
this one song is one artist, tell me what you think of her after that,
and then I'll let you go.
All right.
Yeah, okay.
Baby, I should let him take my clothes off.
And baby, I should let him stay alive.
I'll think of that, leave my vehicle together.
Oh.
I guess we'll never know until we try.
Could you be the one that I've ever looked at for?
Oh, you just don't know the one that's nothing I'm at though.
I'm giving you the chance to show me how it looks.
Why I think I'm ready to know you think you're good enough?
If you play your country, this dress might be the night.
I lose my ambition
I've been gone for so long
If this feeling is too long
I won't be thinking of the same one
And I'm really feel
That I don't do bad rail
But apart of me's coming under
You're going just like
And it might be the time
I'll show you why we'll become
Maybe I should let him get to know
Maybe I should make him start a slowly
I'm kind of big, he never thought
He'd get to see
I'm thinking that we better together perfectly
Could you be the one
That I've been looking for
Are you just another brother
And I can have my dog
I've given you the chance
To show me how I am
I'll punch one
It's just my feeling
I lose my ambition
I've been gone for so long
If this feeling is too long
I won't be thinking of the same one
And I'm really feel
That I don't do bad rail
But apart of me's coming under
You're going just like
And it might be the time
I'll show you why we'll become
Maybe I should let him get to know
Maybe I should make him start a slowly
I want to treat my thing
I'll love you
But maybe I should do
I'll keep it to myself
Because I don't know
If it's too long
I'll feel the same
I lose my ambition
I've been gone for so long
If this feeling is too long
I won't be thinking of the same
I'll fight in those
I'll punish all these Re kunne
It's just my feeling
I've been gone for so long
If this feeling is too long
I'll get to know
I'll be working on all this
I lost my
It's my feeling
that I lose my ambition
I've been gone for so long
If this feeling is too long
I won't be thinking of the same one
I want you here, but I love you, be real
I want to be strong enough
You can win just like anyone in the time
Maybe I should just say goodbye
It's about a minute and a half too long
For my
It's a little bit too long
Isn't that amazing?
Her name is Sarah
S-E-R-A
I don't know, let me read from the bios
On the Podship Music Network
As a singer-songwriter musician
The creative edge of Sarah
Points to this young artist deep roots
And colorful background in the American South
An hour from New Orleans
There's a town called Burus, B-U-R-A-S
Name for her grandfather
Who settled there from France
Let me see, she has a Myspace page, I guess
Let me say
Wow
She looks pretty
Very pretty
That's not true
And it's not like
Christina Aguilera
No, she has a different sound
She has a very interesting sound
Actually I had to think
And I hope she's not going to be angry with me
There is a sort of a sound from Brittany
But Brittany would love to sing like this
Yeah, right
I'll look, she's pretty
Oh, she's lovely
Well, she could be a big star
Why not?
Let's see, that's the first sound
It's sweet, yeah
Amazing, huh?
Yeah, beautiful
Beautiful
This is such a pity
This girl like that should be
As famous as Brittany
And see what a stupid Brittany does
And she should
She throws it away
Well, you know, she should start by not wearing any underpants
Pana?
Why?
Well, she's saying she could have Brittany's career
So she should start by not wearing any underpants
That's a good start
Don't start
Come a little closer to the mic, huh?
I'm not hearing you very well today for some reason
Oh
No, well for sure
In that amazing
And she doesn't need that
Because she can sing
Wow
She doesn't need to take over
So this is Jay Ragusa
Adam, big fan since episode 365
Okay, no naked pictures
But Adam, let me tell you this girl is awesome
I met Sarah while
What did you say?
Well, back
Fucking Google, I can't read it
Fuck is this
Okay, he met her
Here we go
I met Sarah while back
And I'm solely responsible for posting some of her stuff on the PMM
She's unsigned
No record deal, huh?
And I want to promote her
Because I really think she's great
Please check it out
My favorite is funky love
You might like airplane ride
And so this was actually different one
This was
So you can download her
Well, you go to the link in the show
No, it's a deadly source code.com
And you can go
Don't everybody download her
Because she's fantastic
You can play
You can play it online
You can't download it
Maybe from her my space page
I don't know if she's selling it or not
I don't know
It doesn't matter
Go play it in your show
Yeah
Well, fuck I mean
Awesome
And fuck idols
Excuse me
This girl's amazing
Why no
Fine house
Fuck her too
Fine, I was fine
Oh, I'm so irritated by her
But she's sick, huh?
She has a
She's a dick she has addictions
This is an illness
They're so talented
They get the chance
Well, no one's helping her out
Everyone's laughing at her
Pointing at her
This is so fucking typical
Where are you going
How do you know
Because I know
This is what happens every single time
All over so-called friends
You know
It's true
What they say
None of their friends are now around
I'm going to ring her bell
And say, hello
I'm Patricia
I'm going to help you
Yeah
Oh yeah
My point is
If no one, it's like everyone
I think she has friends
I think she doesn't want to get out
Because they always say
They need to help themselves
They need to
They have to hit rock bottom
Yeah
But the unedipidious
Her chances are over
You know
It's done
I disagree
She can totally come back
She needs to get
Make Ronson
That producer dude
On the case again
Who wrote half of the songs
I think that's what he's called
Make Ronson
Yeah
Yeah, he's the guy produced it
He was on the
Nevermind the buzzcocks
I'll let that make Ronson
Yeah, yeah
Are you sure this name is me?
I have no fucking idea
Make Ronson
It's a guitar player
I have no fucking idea
From David Bowies
I can look it up
If you give me a second
Hold on
That's what I know
Producer Amy White
That means
This guy is not dead
No
Mark Ronson
What did I say?
Make Ronson
No Mark Ronson
Good job
Mark Ronson
From the seven
That guy's good
Yeah
And young and good
Good looking
Okay
We've had enough of you now
You're talking about good looking guys
Time to go
Really?
You're going on a stay
I'm just going to play some depressing stuff
Okay
All right
You want to stay?
No
No no it's okay
Okay
What no no I mean you're welcome to stay
No
So you don't want your food here?
No, give me a 15 minutes
You want to dress a wine?
Yes
Trying to dress a wine
Oh yeah, I'd love a glass of wine
Let me go play that girl again
Okay
And button up your shirt
Yeah
You're blow holo speaking out
Do you want my blow holo again?
Yes
I
You have such a lovely blow hol
Misses Jones
You've got a lovely blow hol
Do the do the do
Give me some wine
Okay
I love you too
All right
So
I will wait until you hear the door closed
Then we can continue
Bye
Love my wife
She's not
All right
Just what is this is
You know the other day I was talking about
Just a switch gears here for a second
A man the show is going to be so long
I don't know if anyone gives a shit
It's food bar Friday who cares
So the other day I was talking about
Gates the minister defense for the US
And he was quoted in the Los Angeles Times saying
That the coalition partners in Afghanistan
We're not equipped for
Counter-Insurgence
Operations
And it was it was a real insult to the other countries who were there
And as it turns out Britain
The Netherlands
And Canada
Because that's the one I couldn't come up with
I had them Daniel from Toronto Canada
The third country you're looking for in Afghanistan is Canada
Where we lost 77 soldiers are up to now
And actually, which is interesting
The
Canada is the country in charge of the southern region
Which was on the criticism that
From that US general
So that news
Been pretty much from page news today in Canada
And we even got the
College from the US ambassador's Canada
So to send you that Canada is still up there
Doing their part
Thanks, bye bye
You know what I've tried to do as much research as possible
There's not been a lot of reporting on this specific topic
But from everything I can gather and there's not been no
Retraction from the L.A. times
What what Gates said is exactly that
And it was insulting
And it really gave me yet another
You know peak underneath the curtain
Of how these guys are operating
And you know I'm raising some questions
Like what the
Thank you hon
Didn't even hear you sneak up on me
Thank you
What is this?
What is this hon?
Hold on, what is this?
Whites, symphonials
Children, why?
American wine
Yeah
Amateur wine
It's nice and refreshing
Yeah, nice
Nice and bubbly
Mm-hmm
Okay baby, thank you
15 minutes, yeah
All right
Okay
There we go
Um
I was going to say
You know, it's really insulting
And you know, Britain, yeah
I understand Canada, the Netherlands
Those are the only other two coalition partners
I mean, you have to say that pretty much
U.S.
Ascissors, the government's at least
So that makes total sense
Um
What the hell are we doing there?
What is actually happening?
What is the mission?
How can we measure success?
It's not still looking for bin Laden
We put $10 billion into Pakistan for that
Oh, please, please vote for Dr. Ron
Ron Paul, bring it, you know
You may not agree with everything at the end of the day
I'm sure that if we, you know, no matter who becomes president
We can, of course, effectively
Start to control our Congress
If we really got off our asses
So we'll be able to, you know, it doesn't really matter
It doesn't matter anyway
Let's just get this guy in
Because, you know, he will take everyone out
You'll take all the troops coming home
Stop
I'm fucking sick and tired of it
I
They
Can we just do something sweet?
Nice
Adam, hi, Dave Petersen here
And I'm kind to ask for
Um, a little assistance
My triplet three, eight-year-old daughters
Um, have been given a little school project
Called pets around the world
And it's a
Wait, wait
You say you have triple eight-year-old daughters
Dude, let me hear that again
A little assistance
My triplet three, eight-year-old daughter
Oh, dude
Shepo Ba
Um, my hat is off to you, my friend
Triplet eight-year-old girls
Woo hoo
Here is a father
It was calling out for help
Let me know
I'm listening, my friend
Um, have been given a little school project
Called pets around the world
And it's a, they're given a small stuffed animal
And, uh, in a journal
And what they're, to do is to send a
stuffed animal in a journal together
To somebody who will then take a picture with them
Or, you know, do something with them
And then send them onto somebody else
And eventually, uh, we would, you know,
The ultimate goal obviously is to, uh, have this pet
Travel around the world to make it back
To the space for their home playing party in April
And this is why I thought, uh, of you
You're a lot more well connected
And in fact, actually thought of your daughter
Maybe Christine would like to help out
But, uh, anyway, I sent you an email
With, uh, with my contact information
If you would, uh, like to, or you could go to my blog
Which is, uh, www.dipstick.com
That's D-I-P-S-H-T-I-C-T-A.com
Uh, I did a post on it
And you can, if anybody is, um, willing to help out
Uh, they can leave a comment on the blog
And that will give me the contact information
And I can contact them
And, uh, we're looking for three people to start this
um, and, uh, ought to be interesting
Looking forward to it
Uh, I love you, I don't agree
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Alright, yes, of course, I'll help you out
No problem
Uh, as long as I can remember to put a link in the
Show notes to your blog post
That will be okay
Alright, I gotta wrap this up
We're over an hour already
This is one of the longer shows
That I've done in a while
I had a lot of fun though, good to have petritioned drop by
That was kind of cool
Oh, here's something we haven't done in a while,
mine is what they would know.
It's Friday.
Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday,
food about Friday and a final thought of the week.
Well, I just kind of moved stuff around because, you know,
I don't always have the final thought.
And in fact, I don't think it up because
it wouldn't be the final thought.
Now, what it is, it's literally why I'm feeling
at the end of the footballer festivities.
And it is the final thought of the week.
Today, I have a comment, which really the whole comment
is a theme for the comment of the week.
And what we really should be happy for.
Hey, head of this is David from the Sound of the Us podcast.
Just Google Sound of the Us.
He'll be able to find me, PhD, OS, ultimate combination
of music and biology.
We have some pretty good discussions on the show.
Anyway, I just wanted to comment on your talking about your wife
being ill.
I think two of them had an ill wife for quite a while.
Actually, she's finally getting better.
But she had ulcerative colitis pretty severely.
And in 2006, she had her colin removed.
Which she had what is called a total collective meat.
Her entire large intestine was removed.
So we've been dealing with that.
And hopefully, we'll have a follow-up surgery schedule in spring.
But I just want to be like, you know,
I totally empathize with the having a sick wife thing.
It really sucks.
And just any advice I can give you, which sounds like you're
you guys are doing so much better now.
But any advice I can give you is simply
to love or with all you got and be there for.
So I really enjoy the show.
And I'm kind of in and out of the podcasting radar.
It seems like I'm off and off because of my busy hectic life.
But I'd love for you to check out the sound of the house.
I believe it's a sound of the house.
That my podcast dot to come.
If I remember correctly, that tells you how I'm into it.
So anyway, love you.
Not home home.
Bye.
All right, man, I really appreciate that that call because it does, of course,
once again help me realize how incredibly fortunate I am in my wife is
once again, to have good health.
So I wish good health to you and your wife.
And of course, everyone who listens to the show.
So, man, let's be healthy for 2008, okay?
We've had a lot of crap.
We off to a rocky start and now we're ready to take this year head on.
And that my friends is the final thought of the week.
And with the final thought, I think we need a final song.
So I think eight minutes or something like that.
So I'm just going to leave it all the way to the end and kick back.
Now, I'll touch you guys next week.
Live life with passion and joy and spirit.
Oh, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long
long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long long, long, long, long
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
The reason that we hear, the reason that we feel I feel too warm
There's won't disappear
I have, after the love game, I can play
All our illusion were just a parade
And all the reasons are still on the plane
And in the morning when I rise
No longer feeling it's my time
But the reason, the reason, the reason
And the power, the power
After all, the reason
All the reasons are still on the plane
And in the morning when I rise
No longer feeling it's my time
Oh baby, I can't find a reason
Why my love, it won't disappear
Can't find the reason
Why I love you
Hey, hey, I love you
Oh baby, I can't find a reason
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah
It's all about love, who pays for love.
Check this out.
You hear me?
So we just tell them together.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
The best and the brightest.
Saved up daily by the sharpest minds in content delivering pod show and limelight.