This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and Go Gay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
This is the Daily Source Code.
The Daily Source Code.
60 million dollars worth of airplane straps by ass.
Three minutes?
To the next generation radio caught any of my ears.
We don't need no digging trees in.
I like to think I'm flying into this church.
The podcasting is Adam Curry.
Don't just sit back and complain about how the world is going.
Do something about it.
Start your personal reformation with the DSC 745.
And let Adam Curry show you the way.
I want to know how you feel.
There's ringing in my ear.
I know what to relate to.
Same to C.
Who can't believe it.
I'm eating on the floor.
There has to be a fault.
Who do I fall?
The stars around me shining.
But I'm not feeling vulnerable.
Follow up to you.
Show me the way.
Every day I want to.
My love, my love, my love, my love.
Oh, my love, my love, my love, my love.
When I get to know reason.
You're living on your nerve.
When someone drops the cup.
Then I answer first.
I'm swimming in the circle.
I'll feel I'm going out.
They have to be a fault.
To play in my heart.
But someone gonna be there.
But I'm not feeling vulnerable.
Follow up to you.
Show me the way.
Every day I want to.
I want you.
Baby.
I want you to find the dreamy
I'll feel so unashamed
I can't believe this is happening to me
I want you when you sleep in
And I want to take it
I want you
I'll make it the way
Every day I want you
I want you
The organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
From the biggest selling line out of all time
Peter Frampton
Show me the way
Kick it off
Daily source code
Difficult number
Coming to you from the Curry Condo
Overlooking the Bay Bridge right across from the 70's
Story Tower of Death
It's a Thursday everybody
Combining two days and once
Because of the hectic travel schedule
We'll kind of do half a food bar, half a catch up
And some mustard and sour crowd on top
Like that
Oh man man man
How you guys doing?
It's been a couple days
Nice fade out there
As I said here in the condo
A rife here Tuesday afternoon
Went straight onto the office
Did all the stuff that we needed to do
Had some had a big meeting
Tuesday afternoon
When I'm sorry
Wednesday
I'm confused man
I am all over the map with the jet lag today
Oh man
And you know once again
I go to bed
I go to bed at 10 o'clock
And ping my eyes open up
It's 545
And I'm awake
I can't even sleep any more than that
I've been so messed up
With just
I think it's a combination of
The meeting schedules
Between the UK and San Francisco
The United States
Shifting to daylight savings
Time two weeks early
If it's just difficult
Doesn't it bother you as well?
Don't just suck
So a beautiful day here in San Francisco
The sun is coming up
It's just about quarter to nine right now
And I spent most of the morning
Prepping for today's show
What I'm not doing is streaming live
Through live 365
For a number of reasons
The first one being that
I neglected to pick up a second monitor
And I really can't do the show
With all the different things
I've got running on one laptop screen
And also be able to monitor the live 365 stream
But there's other reasons of course
So I do
It's like a go-mem
Go-mem
Live 365
I've got a truck of shit
That's several people I've loads of trouble with it
Then I've much fun with it myself
Especially with you because you're here
They're not going bucks for the pilot
Wrap
Um
So it's better
We do live them
I've done some live stuff
Yeah, I know what you're going to
I know you're going to recommend all kinds of stuff
You know, I am quite disappointed
But I think it's solvable
And I think using live 365
Four years
Without much problem
And I hadn't used it for about a year and a half
To be quite honest
And reactivated my account
And which indeed
It's 99 bucks a month
But they also pay music royalty
So I like that kind of deal
Where I can actually play
Licensed music
And supposedly
The artists get paid
Or the record company
At least I'm sure get some piece of it
So that part I liked
Which I think is built into that 99 dollar fee
So I'm digging that
But
Um
When you go to the website
Even though this my station
Adam C 1999 is on the air
Often people will have to refresh
Twenty times
And even then it will still show that it's off air
I tried handing out direct links
To the dot PLS file
But that seems to expire after a while
So if anyone has a way
For me just to just to get a link
A PLS file
Or one link
That will not expire
To live through 65
I would love that
Please help me out
I'm really in deep trouble on this
There of course
Other ways to do it
Let's just go and have to say about that
Just read
From
Uh
Some of my B2 net solutions.com
A
FACTOR
So it's kind of stuff
So
Let's go
FACTOR
It never times
You can spend some time in this thing
You want on it
And
Um
And it has no advertisement
Some white bloody life 365
Okay, I think it's fucking awesome
Yeah, I'm impressed
That's my thoughts
Oh you think
Yeah, great
No way
Blah blah blah blah
Blah blah blah
Yeah, it's pretty cool
Scrunchers
Alright man, thank you
Yeah, I don't like the ads either
That's also bugging me
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Gotta work on it
Okay
I promise when I get back home
So
In
I don't know, like
Seven hours from now
I'll be boarding a plane to New York
I was supposed to go to New York last night
But decided there was a couple things
I could do here in San Francisco
Well Ron is already off
He took the red eye last night to New York
So I got a couple meetings in New York
And then Friday night
I fly back to London
So it's
So I get half a red eye
And then a full red eye
Oh, I'm going to be
Oh, wonderful at home
People will just love my attitude
Speaking of which, I
Boy, did I really mess this one up?
I should have thought about this
Adam, Dave from the Netherlands
Dude, on last two baragician
It told us you can drunk
Yeah, so this of course
Was the evening out
I had with Super Agent Keith
The guys from two way traffic
At five Cavendish Square
Where I was overserved on
Italian wine
Little, the notes to me
It had a much higher alcohol content
Than the wine that I've normally drunk
On an evening out
And yeah, I got hammered.com
Now, what do you do when you get drunk?
You call the DSC voicemail
So I didn't give you
Here to me finding
Anyway, I'm calling to tell you
Why I listened to the Charlie
Well, it's
I guess, being part of a tribe
You know, same group of interest people
You know, I'm concerned about environment
And about the money is going on
Our privacy
And yeah, just get a sense of
Belonging when he listened to the show
So I got a suggestion
Instead of that laying
Great area
Yada, Yada, Yada
And we should end with
What kind of tribe you're into
Well, I'm David
And I'm into
The DSC
I'm into
Music
I'm into the tribe of
Well, gaining a little bit apple
And that's about it
And of course, the tribe of Adam
Take care
I'm in
Thank you
Thank you very much
I don't like the word
Try
I understand what you're saying
But I also kind of like the great hair
Hope you win
I got it made that's kind of cool
Hey, by the way
Excuse me
Did I call it
At the beginning of the week
Well, maybe wasn't even last week
When I said that hey, the FAA
We got to watch these guys
Because they're letting
Airlines get away with the low maintenance
The hello
American Airlines heard the call
Didn't they
Boom
What is it now?
1100 fights of flights cancelled
And it's all over the news now
And initially, I was even talking about
American Airlines
I predict we're going to see a lot more of this
These maintenance
Someone woke up and said
Holy crap
We're going to be in big trouble
If we don't have all of the airlines
Up to date on their maintenance
Yeah, duh
Maintenance is everything
So the two aircraft
I will not get on
Currently until
I'm satisfied with
Maintenance
Directives, etc.
Boeing triple seven
We'll not fly it
Because there's still something fishy
Going on with their high pressure fuel pumps
This, of course, is the same type of aircraft
That landed short
At London's Heathrow Airport
British Airways
And I guess MD 80's are out for now
For me, I mean, there's been a lot of these
No-swheel issues
And you know what?
Even though
Turns out that the
The issues aren't
Well, it's kind of crazy
Right?
The nose wheel might not retract
But, you know, the plane still flies
And nose wheel works
Yeah, it's a pilot
You just don't want that shit
You know, that stuff you can't see
You really don't want something
With your landing gear
It's just not, it's not fun
At all
Once I hear sirens outside
I guess they're coming to give me already
Hey, yesterday
Speaking of sirens
Man, this was out of control
So the Olympic torch
It's like I beat the torch
The flame
To San Francisco
Of course, it was in London
We had all kinds of skirmishes
People trying to extinguish the flame
Then in France
They actually doused the flame
And actually I thought
It was kind of like, you know, the American flag
Where if it's flag touches the ground
You have to burn it
I thought if the Olympic flame goes out
Don't they have to go back to Greece
And get it re-lit?
Apparently not
Apparently they have like, they carry the flame
In a backup case
And it's always lit
And they can relight
But yesterday the flame
Decended upon San Francisco
And of course there were all kinds of skirmishes
And krefuffles
And right outside our office
In fact, it was crazy
Because it wasn't just the
Pro-Tibet protesters
And anti-China protesters
But they were pro-China protesters
And they were converging on the street
Right here on Second Street
Yet people with Chinese flags
And they were yelling at each other
And it was like, oh my god
It was absolutely surreal
To see this
And where did all these Chinese
But supporters come from
Just a start
I saw a couple of them walking around with maps
It had to be organized
I don't think they actually
They may not even live here
I don't know
But it was wow
This was just amazing to me
The amount of vocal outrage
And of course I come right back to
Man, what the hell is going on
How come we're so loud
And so vocal about
About, you know,
Props to Tibet
And I understand there's issues
And it's been that way
For more than just this upcoming Olympics
The suppression of Tibet
And other countries like Taiwan
By China
Has been going on for many many years
But look at all the crap that's going on
At home that we're not yelling about
Why?
It boggles my mind
I love that outrage
I love the emotion
I love the passion
But please, can't we be passionate about
A couple other things
Like the war
We need bigger protests and demonstrations
How about just simple things
Like our idiot kids
Who have no decent education
Holy crap
That's just freaking me out
Hey Adam, Billy, I'm here
Lost Queen is Texas USA
And just actually getting caught up right now
And I'm listening to 744
Of the Charlie
And you said something that piss me off
But not a you at all
It's one of those things that just kind of
Every time it comes up it just gets to me
You were talking about the
The new writing in the UK
And how
People are so willing to
You know, say something when it doesn't affect them
But they have absolutely no willingness
to say anything when
You know, when they're
When they're the oppressed majority
And
I think that's really been going on for
As long as I'm 25
It's been going on for as long as I've been alive
In the States
Oh son, let me tell you
I'm 43
Hell yes has been going on forever
It's for some reason as human nature
I just don't understand it
We're so concerned about
Other people in other countries
Absolutely important
But
And we got some
Who's who's writing for us
Who's writing for what's going on with our economy
Who's writing for that?
Nobody
Particularly in education
I mean we have
Probably the highest turnout of
People who graduate high school
And you know can't read
Or have so very little desire to do so
That they cannot move on in life
And everyone finds this completely
It's very obvious it's well-known
There's no dialogue about it at all
I mean it's
It's one of these things
You know just like the
Just like the vague racism
As people keep calling it
That's going on behind closed doors
That's not at all racism
It's just one of those things
It comes up in private
And it's completely pointless
Anyways
Love you
I mean it's great here
Hope you win
And let's make a change
Man
Thank you
Well of course the dialogue is here on the Charlie
So I appreciate that
Let me just say something about China
And about boycotting it
If you want to boycott
Okay
Boycott the freaking Olympics
All right
Now I've dealt with the local Olympic committees
I've had some exposure to the international Olympic committee
The IOC you see it written everywhere now
These guys are evil
Okay
It has nothing to do with sports
It has nothing to do with
With a political agenda
It is all about money
This is one huge money making machine
If you truly want to
Support to bet
Okay
If you want to protest China
Do not watch the Olympics
Do not watch any of that coverage
Which by the way
The rights to that is over a billion
Dollars
Okay
Just the rights to broadcast it
Athletes are forbidden
From posting pictures or video
Of any kind on their personal web
Logs while they're there
They're allowed to write
But they're not allowed to post any media files
Because that's all part of the rights
And it's ludicrous
It's absolutely
A stounding that we're still falling for this scam
Hey another if you want to boycott China
Hey
If you're listening to the show on an iPod right now
Okay
In fact I'm going to look
I'm going to look at my
Um
In my old iPod here
Yes indeed
Check this out
Flip it over
Okay
Now be careful if you're driving
But right there
And have my iPod here
This is an iPod touch 16 gigabyte
On the back casing
It's really it's tiny letters
And with my old age eyesight
I actually have to
Bring it really close to my eyes
And I have to take my specs off
Designed by Apple in California
Assembled in China
So instead of being all messed up
About you know the Olympics
Stop buying iPods
Stop buying shit from China
What is it?
75% of everything in the United States
Is manufactured in China
If you really truly want to protest
Stop buying that crap
Stop it
You can't
We're addicted to crap
I'm addicted to crap
Okay
I got a backslash on that
That's really
Oh man that gets me all riled up
Oh this was interesting
We knew this was going to happen
It seems like for some reason
In a stoke
Some weird stuff happens in the UK
If you hadn't picked up on this story
A BBC radio reporter
Was held to the ground
And searched by police
Under the Terrorism Act
After his transmitter equipment
Was mistaken for a bomb
This is Max Khan
Was forced to his knees
And there's a picture of his backpack
Here which is like
If he was truly
Suicide bomber
He would have failed the exam
Because it's not it's pretty obvious
That he's got all
It's got antennas
They can out
He's got headphones on
And this is in stoke
It's the second time this happened
Earlier this year
Police tackled a guy in the stoke
After they thought his MP3 player was a gun
I'm all for preventive
For prevention
But it's getting a little bit crazy
Of course it was phoned in by someone who said
Oh there's a terrorist
By the way
I believe Max looks a little bit ethnic
So I don't know
I don't know if anything to do
Had anything to do with it whatsoever
But it's just nuts
I'm definitely going to mess with your head
In a little bit
I've got something fantastic
We're going to play with your brain
I think you really enjoy this
Stay tuned because
This is going to blow your mind
When we do this a little
A little brain experiment
Stay tuned
You'll never know
With the chill cast
With Andrew B
presents a special half-hour interview
Future with science for girls
I have been
Not around the music business for a while
I've worked inside touring music
With Ray Charles
Wow
Did a tour with Barry Madeline
Quite a way to hone your chops
This is going to be exclusive
For the chill cast
Should you be plugging in his me
Life is a game
We've been doing pretty well in the CMJ radio charts
And the tune that seems to be getting the most
Airplay is Australia
Really
A number of people have come up to me
And I said, why are you thinking
You know, it's my record
You know, no one can stop me
Which maybe you can stop me
Check out the chill cast
Science for Girls' Feature
It's AndrewB.com
Oh yeah
You know I will
Yeah, I've been using that drop.io
Slash Daily source code thing
And I'm getting all kinds of interesting files
I've never heard of this guy's name is David Garza
But whenever you've got a
A song titled that includes the word
TrueBador I'm in baby
Such a beautiful French word
TrueBador
In fact, this is the Il TrueBador
If a Garza in the Charlie episode
7-4-5
Oh
Time to sweep the underground
Time to sweep the town
Oh
Time to roll the windows down
Because we're so velvety
Oh
For better pass than they throw
Let's miss a little of these pieces
No
Let me jump
I like rub it up faster
Baby lives
It knows a beautiful cast
Oh
I just ride
And keep jumping on the highway
And glide
Could have met all the bells
And hold it up slow
Oh
I'm a less lame pass
And while I'm putting a stop
And yeah
With the chill cast
I'm the same
I'm going to make quick
No, you all had a long day
Oh
Time to sweep the town
Time to roll the windows down
Because we're so velvety
Oh
Time to sweep the town
I'm a strange mess of man
When I hit the stand
And the whesses of the black and hand
I'm the sage of rage
When I smack the stage
Like some guilt you would don't want to be
Oh
I got a feeling of no mistakes
I don't know when the ghosts are okay
Yeah
Oh
What if I slip it
I drop these with a lace ass trippin
Tap trees with CDs
That's kiffin
So I saw a lot of shippin
Tiffin
Sip them up and sit there
Yeah
Gas my fast girl
Dab your
Moth will be your Flavio
To know the day is baby
We need these ladios
I can't rock
Queen of y'all
Row you in LA
When one of the cars is done
Oh crazy
When you bring the city
I bring the white game
When one of the cars is done
Oh crazy
Check out who will never
She's not saying
The whole jail has done
Oh
I can rock you in the y'all
Row you in LA
When you bring the city
I bring the white game
Oh
David Garza
It's a true bad duer
True bad duer
My damn an issue
I should play some more friends music for you
I was thinking actually
I get back Saturday
Depending on what time I get in depending on feeling
I may
Or maybe even Sunday I just might do a full music show
I really feel like playing this
I'm cool jams for you
And that of course I will put on live 365
So we can enjoy it all together
That's part of the tribe
It's funny
Well that song was playing
I'm here in the condo
And I have my first gen iPod
Which is
Is that the first gen 30 gigabyte
It's funny when you hold this thing in your hands
It's like wow
It feels like a brick compared to the new iPods
And I was looking at the back
You know thinking
Just let me continue my
You might rant here about
Protesting a Chinese
Stop buying the shit man in China
Which by the way
A lot of it is shit
Okay
A lot of it contains dangerous chemicals
And it's just shit
Although I love my new iPod touch
Here check this out
Designed by Apple and California
A symbol in Taiwan
How interesting is that
So they were manufacturing these things in Taiwan
First which of course
The country which has been suppressed by China for many many years
And then they switched to
And they switched to a assembly in China
Interesting
Why don't you go boycott Apple
Or you just love your Apple products too much
Ah
In consistencies my friend
It just drives me nuts
Let me see
When I also have here in my much
Oh yes, this is a very important
Then we had a
A new
Monetary scientist
A lot of the charlie
And this of course is a trace mayor
And he operates
RunToGold.com
And I had a whole bunch of questions
Last time he called him we talked about on the show
And he's answered them
He's put up a page which of course
I'll put a link in the show
No it's a daily source code.com
And he's answered a lot of the questions
That I posed
And I think there's some really good answers
So you want to check out RunToGold.com
R-U-N-T-O-G-O-L-D.com
Link in the show
No it's a daily source code.com
All right
Ready to have your mind blown
This is an audio file
That I've heard things similar to this
But I've never heard this one
Sent me when I got my girlfriend
Kacha in the Netherlands
I've worked with on many different projects
Video audio
Or like
And it's funny because she sent this to me
And email said
Listen to this with your headphones on
And that was the subject line of the email
I'm like
Oh man, you know it's going to be something really dirty
It wasn't but it was equally exciting
This is the virtual barbershop
So I want you to listen to this
Now it really works best if you have headphones on
It'll work if you have ear buds in
But what I want you to do is I really want you to plug them into your ear
Like jam them in a little bit deep
It's about four minutes
But it'll be well worth it
In order to get the full effect
Because through the
The Magic of Stereo
Which is not all that magical
But really what your brain is going to be doing
Your brain is going to position sound
In a virtual space
Around your head
That's why it's best with headphones
I think it probably would work in the car as well
If you have they if you turn it really loud
And close your eyes
Which of course is not a really good idea in the car
I'm just saying
Enjoy this as we
And I mean all of us together
Charlie heads hand in hand
Have a virtual haircut
At the virtual barber shop
Enjoy
Oh
Hello there hello there how are you yes yes
You are here for the virtual haircut
Yes it's okay
I will go get the Ouija you will come and cut your hair
I mean well just stay right there
Oh
Ouija
Hello Ouija
It's my ladder
The person is here for the virtual haircut
You better come on
What?
Come running out
He is coming up right now
I mean when I will go over here
And play the music
Then the guitar
Because that is what I do here at the barber shop
It's so nice to see you
Welcome to the Starky Settera barber shop
And your virtual haircut
I'd like to start the demonstration
By moving over to your right hand side
And I'm making up this bag
It can just hold still for a second
I'll put this bag over your hair
Just like that
The bag over the top of the head
And now I'll take the bag off
There we go
The only reason I did that is because
All of the fancy barber shops do that
What you're listening to is I move off to your right side
Very quickly wash my hands
Then well
If you get that please
I will make it my way
Let me finish washing my hands
Just thought they were waiting for us
There we go
Oh yes
As always the same
All we are doing is using your head
As the listening point
No
And we have two microphones
One on either side of the head
In the same position
Is where you're left
And you're right
The ears are
Your brain is doing all of the work
Telling you where the sounds are coming from
Okay
I'll go get the scissors
Now is the beginning clipping
And I bring the clippers closer to your ear
Very close to the right ear
All the means I move around the back of the head
To the left ear
And up
And over the top of the head
Okay
Oh
You can get the same effect
The better with the electric razor
All the first ring it's close to your right ear
And around the back
And onto your neck
Yeah
I think that looks wonderful
Manuel, what do you think?
But yes
It looks wonderful Luigi
You do such nice work
Oh thank you so much Manuel
So fast too
Now
As I walk around
I just want to tell you once more
The durability to hear where I am
As I walk around the room
Is simply the amazing power of your brain
Calculating the tiny differences
Work use in sound intensity
And arrival time from two open ears
And unlike any other hearing instrument
Only one has the digital algorithm
That negates its own physical presence
In the ear to fully restore those differences
That algorithm is called
Set there on
Well thank you
Thank you so much for stopping by
It's starting virtual barbershop
Goodbye
Have a great day
I did it work for you
It worked once again for me
I really enjoyed that
Although I think the limited compressor limit
I have room was a little bit of the effect
But oh man
Love that
You want to all probably upload that
File to the drop.io slash daily source code
Which you should check out from time to time
Because it's amazing stuff
People are putting up there
Not that I use everything in the show
But it's just amazing
The things that people are uploading
And posting and links
And really really like that system
Congratulations
By the way
To the ladies over at lip gloss
And laptops celebrating their 100th episode
I've been listening to them following them for a couple of years
Always love the whole concept
I love the title of the show right off
The bad lip gloss and laptops.com
Definitely go check them out
So
I just got word that I'll be leaving
Town to PM
I think I'm going to be playing out of San Jose
It's hard to get a flight that gets you in
Any decent time in New York unless you want to take the red eye
So I actually got to move shit along here
Now because we're doing a combined football Friday
Really
I mean only because I just won't be able to actually physically do anything on Friday
Again, that's why I'm going to hook you up on the weekend
There is of course one thing that comes with every single football Friday show
And your week just isn't complete without it
And well, y'all that is best so we might as well get down to the hit test
Number 117
Fantastic
Hey Adam, it's time for another hit test
And this one is themed
I hope you'll figure it out
Here we go with intro
Oh, it's not I thought it was Eric Clapton though
It's a BG's nice on Broadway
Number two
I got the theme
I got you
On Broadway George Benson
Is this a Broadway theme by any chance?
What other Broadway song could y'all have in store for us?
Number three
Okay
Well, I thought it was a Broadway theme
That would be
I don't know
I give up
Time's up and here we go with the answers
Give me the hit test
And so number one is from 1975
He's got the BG
Hell yeah
It's a little bit set up
I'm a night song from
Singin' at the sun
Singin' at me
Baby
Night song Broadway by the BG's
As answer number one
Yeah
This is answer number two
Got that one right
This is your adventure
So what's number three then, you know?
On Broadway by George Benson
The answer number two
Number three
And this is answer number three
Hellbow bone
Send the record to yours
He's got me
Oh yeah, I recognize this now
What's the final song?
Broadway
Take me for a night
New York
Oh, I got it
To New York
Answer number three
Hellbow bone
Send the record to yours
From 1984
Take me for a night
In New York
In this New York theme hit test
And it's number 117
So how did you do Edmund?
Well, you kind of messed me up with the two Broadway songs
I wouldn't have known Hellbow bones in the record
Here's two out of three
For us to this hit test
And also the iTunes links
So you can buy these tracks online
Or to be found at hittest.barsho.com
Thank you for playing Edmund
Have a nice trip home
Everyone else, thank you for listening
Next week I'll be back for the next hit test
So stay tuned
Have a very nice week
And remember try to think with your heart
Bye bye
Johnny Boy
Fantastic
I like that thing with your heart
That's his sign-off now
Very cool
Okay, so we're just about
Just about there with the show
I think I got to
Let me see one or two more things to do here
And so we'll have a no agenda
Which we'll do on Saturday
As I said, I'm thinking about doing a maximum music
Football or freight train over the weekend
Actually Patricia and Christina
We'll be in there on the road
Patricia is doing
Another day of taping for Holland's Got Talent
And I believe my daughter has an audition for a movie
Yeah, we're in show business mode, everybody
Adam, there's just a comment on the smile
And this isn't the 744
Do you want to know why people listen to the show?
Yeah, the reason I listen to the show
Is because I've been listening
Since you moved to the college
Which is a good few years now
I'm 23
So the reason I listen to podcasts
Just have a specialist
Because you are the same track to my life
Or at least a good percentage of us
So that's me
Oh man, I really appreciate that
That's so nice of you to say
Well, let me add another entry to the soundtrack of your life
This is brand new on the Podsave Music Network
Fuck Cherry
Oh man, I miss you
And things was the same
Because everything is time
And now what comes out of
And when I see you cry
It makes me want to die
I'll tell you about
I'll tell you about all the things
I said to you, I don't know
I can't say goodbye
I love how you kiss
I love all your sounds
Maybe the way you make my world
Go round and adjust
What is the same
I'm sorry
Let's start
I think I'm too blame
It's harder to get through the days
We get all the blame
Turns the shame
Because everything is time
And now what comes out of
And when I see you cry
It makes me want to die
I'll tell you about
I'll tell you about all the things
I said to you, I don't know
I can't say goodbye
I love how you kiss
I love all your sounds
Maybe the way you make my world
Go round and adjust
What is the same
I'm sorry
Every single day
I think about how we came all this way
The sleepless nights
And the tears you cried
It's harder to get through the days
We get all the blame
All the blame
I'm sorry I'm bad
I'm sorry about all the things
I said to you, I don't know
I can't say goodbye
I love how you kiss
I love all your sounds
Maybe the way you make my world
Go round and adjust
What is the same
I'm sorry
Oh man
There's sold over a million albums
They're probably the biggest rock band in the United States today
Fuck Cherry
Now on the pod save music network
With a track sorry
See these guys, they get it
Man, that's right
Put it out there
You'll sell more, you'll have more people going to concerts
More merchandise
Oh yeah
Love it
Links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Fantastic
Ah
Okay
I'm tired
I'm spent
I gotta get my ass in gear
I'm still actually here in my bathroom
In the condo
So apologies for the parents
Usually I try to do a little bit better for you guys
Okay
So as I said no show tomorrow
Unless of course you're living down under
Australia, which means we'll be a show tomorrow
Because it's actually Friday
In fact, you're probably working on Saturdays
We speak
And
Well
Be good
Adam at podshow.com
Dailysourcecode.com
For the show notes and links to everything
Of course my blog at curie.com
And please
Especially on a day like today
Live your life with passion
And while you still can
Enjoy your freedom
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear