Dromatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise cancelling headphones
and work, home or travel, shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones, Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good.
Delta Sierra Charley 705.
Dromatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony's noise and really enjoy your tracks.
to Dustin Hoffman to walk in with a contamination suit,
particularly when you hear that kind of stuff
on the radio, just a little bit trippy.
And man, I've been in and out of just drifting
in and out of consciousness for the past week
with my laptop by my side because what else can you do?
But just lane beds, sweat, be delirious,
and watch conspiracy theory videos.
It'll really put you into a spiral.
Yeah, I got some of that, too.
So where I picked this up is actually
was a very happy occasion on, let's see,
right after Christmas, the 28th, Friday the 28th.
Oh, I take off my bathroom a little bit here.
I'm getting warm.
Do you like the wife, Peter?
Thank you.
We, the three of us went over to
with a Netherlands to Amsterdam to see my sister Willow,
her husband, Alessandro and her kids,
Matteo and Sabe and my other sister lives in Holland,
Tiffany, her friend, Hido and my sister's son, Julius.
And it was great, we had a fantastic dinner,
we hadn't seen it, but it's been a little while since
we'd all kind of been together like that,
but really with the full families, it was a lot of fun.
And, but Willow, my sister from Italy,
I could tell she was kind of on the rope,
she had a really bad cold, she didn't feel well,
but she was young.
She's a woman, so you know, she didn't let on about that shit,
and she just stuck right through it.
And we stayed at the night in Amsterdam,
and there were about four or five in the morning,
I woke up and I said, oh man, I got a headache,
which is atypical for me, I don't wake up for anything.
And so, of course, that was the beginnings of
of what this flu would be for me.
So, by the time I got back, I was, which was Saturday,
I was starting to get pretty wiped out,
and it just went downhill from there.
Anyway, let's see, we, I do have a show for you,
filled with some flu-warm fraude and music for you,
but let's see what we got here.
Hello?
Hi Adam, this is Bigger Health from Silicon Valley.
Yeah, I wanted to just take a minute to say thank you.
Thank you for giving us
the by far, the best podcast out there.
You continue episode in an episode out to inform,
to educate, to entertain, and it's occasionally to irritate,
or infuriate us, but every episode is at learning experience,
and I get more thrill out of listening to your show
on my daily drive.
And I do from just about any of the other shows I've listened to,
or any other content I read,
really do appreciate all the work you put go,
that goes into putting the show together.
And as a result of all the time you spent,
and all the time I put into this new show,
I've finally taken to leap myself.
So if you could tell your listeners,
if they want to hear the stories of a more average American guy,
please send them to my podcast site at normalmanority.lipsen.com.
Again, Adam, thanks for all the great content.
I hope you have a fantastic day.
It's a big out of sign-in-off.
Yo yo, big out.
Thank you, my friend.
I need a mash-up, how about you?
I'm pleased to meet you.
It's the best of booty, two thousand seven DJ Moore.
You can't smile, I love you.
It's a sympathy for teen spirit.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you can't smile, I love you.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a man, well, and taste.
I've been around for it all along you.
Still many amends, so to fit.
When I was around with Jesus Christ,
had his moment a doubt of pain.
Me, damn sure the pilot watched his hands,
the seal is great.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you can't smile, I love you.
But what good led you with the nature of my game?
I've been too bad, they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm stupid, they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm a baby.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you can't smile, I love you.
Still many amends, so to fit.
When I was around with Jesus Christ,
had his moment a doubt of pain.
Me, damn sure the pilot watched his hands,
I've been too bad, they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm a skater,
fit to meet you.
Hope you can't smile, I love you.
But I'm a skater, my baby,
they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm a skater,
I've been too bad, they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm stupid,
they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm a skater,
Hope you can't smile, I love you.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm a skater, my baby, I'm a skater,
they're contagious.
I'm a skater, my baby,
they're contagious guys.
For stars,
I'd love to meet you,
Queen's raw tender gays
For the god's name
I shout out
Who killed the candidates
Where and thrall
It was me when
Let the police ever do smile now
But I'm a man of wealth and taste
I need tracks for true love
Who killed the four their reach
Tomorrow they're coming back
To play
That's exactly the day
No, day, no
Nothing, no, day
That's exactly the day
No, day, no
No, no, no
That's exactly the day
Yeah, yeah
Returned spirit
On your daily source code episode number
It is, uh, f5
Wow, man. A lot of people sent me this link and of course, you know, I appreciate it. Don't ever think that millions of people sent the tune me already about the spot program from the our friends, the TSA spot stands for screening passengers by observation technique. Oh, yes.
It's now being called the face crime initiative on the on the internet. Essentially, in the spot program says,
who's this guy who's talking on behalf of the TSA. Hold on, let me just, my brains moving a little bit slower than normal as you can tell.
Carl Maccario, this is who helps start this program for the TSA. Okay. So Carl is is the culprit here in the spot program.
We have a conversation with passengers and we asked them about their trip.
When someone lies or tries to deceive, there are behavior cues that show it a brief flash of fear.
The definition of terror, actually, such people are referred for secondary screening, which can include a pat down search and an x-ray exam.
The micro facial expressions are the same across many, many cultures.
Well, apparently since January 2006, this has been going on, behavior detection officers better better known as BDOs have referred about 70,000 people for secondary screening.
Of those, about 600 to 700, we're arrested on a variety of charges, including possession of drugs, weapons violations and outstanding warrants.
Now, this is very interesting to me.
This essentially, and maybe it's something I should talk with John Devorek about on no agenda, which we may do today, but it may not be told to mark. Got to figure out what our timing is.
Because they're supposed to be screening me for, you know, I guess if I'm going to do some, you know, trying to hijack an airplane.
But now essentially, this TSA, which is not really police, are, you know, basically searching me without just cause.
And, and they're searching for drugs and outstanding warrants.
I don't know. This is really, this is really quite strange. It's a little disconcerning that people are being pulled out of, you know, basically in a public place and airport in this manner.
I got to think about this. It doesn't, it doesn't sit well with me at all, particularly with me, as you know, I'm a mild case of Tourette syndrome.
But what's funny is in this article that actually says, let me see if I can find it, to emphasize the sensitivity TSA is bringing to the program.
They had a meeting with an association for people with Tourette's disorder to assure that having a tick will not result in a pat down. Yeah, we'll see.
That's truly out of control. You know, over these past few days of Patricia has started getting interested in all of the stuff that I'm talking about and listening to.
And, you know, of course, I can't shut my big mouth when I see something on TV and I say, you know, this is not really what's happening. I think this is what's going on.
And, uh, that was, I'm going to say, uh, sorry. I lost my train of thought. It is a food bar Friday. Let's just hit a voicemail comment that'll help me out.
Okay, Adam, Jeff and Florida, bizarre travel experience. You would appreciate it on, uh, so the Christmas weekend flying out of Fort Lorda Dale heading for colonial Williamsburg, which is another story altogether.
Show up at the airport. My girlfriend, I with our luggage, I've done the online boarding pass check in, but I still have to check my bags. It's real crowded. Don't really want to wait in the long lines. I go up to a TSA guy and just ask, you know, where's the curbside check in and can I do that if I have my online.
Produced boarding pass and he says, uh, don't worry about it. Come with me. I call my girlfriend off the line. He pulls us to the side takes my computer printed boarding passes never asks me for my ID.
Those behind the counter cuts the long line, punches some keys and comes out luggage tags, tags are three bags takes them away hands need properly printed boarding passes and we're on our way in three minutes. He never requested my ID for every rule in the book.
I shook his hands and slipped him 10 bucks. And as we walked to the security check and I wondered if maybe I've been scanned in my bag to just been stolen.
But I looked at those printed receipts three or four times and they certainly looked legitimate and sure enough we arrived at our destination with our luggage there to meet us. So who knows?
It was my lucky day, I guess, or not, depending on how you look at it from the security standpoint. Anyway, hope you're not in great holiday season, thought with all your TSA talks, you'll enjoy that story.
I'm happy to have more more to tell Hollywood airport, by the way. Fantastic here.
All of a sudden remembered what I was telling Patricia was saying, the Travis Lee is that there are hundreds of thousands of American men and women fighting in the fucking desert and listen to the rhetoric, you know, to protect our freedom, the very same freedoms that are being taken away systematically every single day.
Now you tell me how that works, okay?
Adam Man, it's right, I'm a lot of time listener, first time caller. You read one of my emails on mine before, but I'm here. I've been in state college Pennsylvania, Penn State, let's go.
It's three o'clock in the morning, I'm a little behind on my source codes, but I just listened to 677, you're out of view with Dr. Ron Paul.
And the election coming up with you in the second election, I've ever had a chance to vote in, and you have influenced my leaning, did this, this is a huge thing.
I mean, I'm a couple of months behind, I've no idea what's going on now, but you've got the power to decide the next president of the United States of America.
I hope you recognize this power, and I hope you harness it for good, because with great power comes great responsibility.
Keep doing what you do and Adam have a good night.
Yeah, well, that power ain't so my Mojo ain't in full strength apparently, looking at the, at the caucuses from yesterday.
I'm not going to get into it, because honestly, I don't really understand it, I don't understand how it works, all I know is that the only thing that counts is being number one.
Our guy was definitely not number one, so I'm already reading all kinds of theories, and I would just didn't put enough butts in the right seats in Iowa, I presume.
I'm just amazed by Huckabito, that's quite an amazing feat that he's pulled off there.
I'm pretty convinced that two things were really working well in his favor, which doesn't, it's probably not so good for, you know, us as a nation.
And I think that the Chuck Norris promotion worked very, very well.
I just got to hand it to him, what a great idea.
And also the appearance on Lena, I think, really helped a lot of people watch that.
So we'll see where this leads.
There are several more caucuses to come, as things start to heat up, and I still, of course, stand subtly behind my man, Dr. Ron Paul.
Hi Adam, Mike from Wilmington, Delaware. I've been listening since before the counting started.
I'm a scroller, and I love it when pictures is on.
With that out of the way, I want to take a moment to share with you a little bit about a friend, a friend of my wife and I at misplaced.
Jimmy is a dear friend of my wife and me. He had been secretly struggling with addiction, and we didn't learn about it until it was too late.
When the secret came out, Jimmy fled Ohio with others who were probably using, and they probably went somewhere in the Cincinnati area.
We've not heard from Jimmy since the spring of 2007.
At the beginning of December this year, my wife contacted Jimmy's family, but they don't know where he is either.
But they could tell us as far as they know he's still in Ohio, and it's very likely that he's homeless.
We're torn apart about the loss of our friend, and even more so that it is likely that he's cold and lonely.
If anybody out there has seen Jimmy or Noah's current whereabouts, please contact us at our website, www.findingJimmy.org.
Thank you for taking a moment to listen to this and a bigger thanks if you share it with the rest of the audience.
My hope is that someone may recognize him from the picture at www.findingJimmy.org
and contact me through the site so that I can reach out and try to help him.
Thanks again, and I love you, man.
No homo.
I always kills me when you wind up with a no homo.
I still had this one queued up, I think, from the last show that I did as the one I did with Patricia.
Like number one of the whole month of December from the Pod Save Music Network,
Clark Dazzler, the classic Shadow Dreams.
What it was you who said they died for me.
And just see you giving me, giving me nothing but Shadow Dreams, Shadow Dreams.
Feel like I could run away run away from this city.
Oh, come to reality and found the future not so bright.
I dreamt the impossible, the name of things could work out right.
I thought it was you who said they died for me.
And just see you giving me, giving me nothing but Shadow Dreams, Shadow Dreams.
Feel like I could run away run away from this city.
You know you give me, giving me nothing but Shadow Dreams, Shadow Dreams.
Oh, come to reality and found the future not so bright.
I thought it was you who said they died for me.
And just see you giving me, giving me nothing but Shadow Dreams, Shadow Dreams.
Feel like I could run away run away from this city.
You know you give me, giving me nothing but Shadow Dreams, Shadow Dreams.
Oh, come to reality and find the future not so bright.
I dreamt the impossible, come on, dreamt the impossible.
It's from Mark Dadsler's new CD, it's titled Tomorrow.
And I just can't wait to find out what the next track will be that it'll be made hot safe.
Honestly, I'm kind of hoping for the title track because it's great song.
We'll see.
Good, good, good stuff.
I guess it, man.
Completely independent.
Right on, Clark.
The weather is perfect.
Perfect for the way I feel today.
There's snow in the air.
We're a little bit south of the snow borderline.
I think there's some wet snow up at Heathrow.
And so we're just a little bit south of that.
So nothing here yet that I can see.
But it's really, really dark outside.
And it's perfect weather to be stuck indoors with the no-row virus.
Hey Adam, Chris, go out on here from Seattle.
I've been just listening to some of you remember what you have sort of was.
But it was the heat test with the envelope.
And I realized I didn't know any of the songs that he was playing.
Now, it's unusual for me because I'm actually really,
I'm kind of a savante of 80s music trivia.
And I'm not challenging you or calling you out.
But I just kind of my thing.
And I realized a lot of times when young police stuff,
I have never heard the songs before.
Not that I just don't remember what they are.
I just never heard them before.
And the life and I were discussing not too long ago as she grew up on the Heathcoats,
I grew up on the west coast.
And we have very different recollections about a lot of songs.
And I wondered if you could just talk for a minute about the regionality of radio,
especially 25 years ago as compared to what is popular now nationally.
And now it's all programmed by one place,
to the post to using a different regions of different flavors and different things
were popular.
I'd even more so in the 60s and 70s.
I just wanted you to kind of talk to that guy.
I think that's the way I work, but I don't know for sure.
Anyway, thanks for what you do.
And I like you a lot.
I can't say that I love you yet.
Yeah, you know, I think that's that's pretty typical.
First of all, you know, young is from the Netherlands.
And we grew up with a whole different music scene in the very early 80s
when I was on the pirate radio station.
I mean, Madonna actually,
the album with the Lucky Star Holiday borderline.
That was out a year, a full year before it actually became a hit
worldwide, which I think started in the UK with
maybe it was borderline.
The borderline, it wasn't holiday.
Holiday was the big mega smash,
but Lucky Star maybe.
I think it was Lucky Star that came first.
That's right.
Yeah, I mean, there was all different kinds of music at the time.
The states was still very much into,
let's see, what was a big hit at the time of some of the songs
that young has been pulling from the last week's hit test.
I was probably Kenny Rogers and Daldy Park.
Islands in this dream.
No, no, no.
It's a, it is very different.
Of course, you know, the music industry, you know,
it's, it's mission.
It's, as always been to sell as much product as possible.
And so, you know, they focus.
And, you know, just the way the radio has traditionally worked
in the United States, which now is,
is ending, of course, we're seeing everything fall apart.
But, you know, it was a very simple system.
You release a number of songs.
You pay radio stations indirectly,
but make no mistake.
They were being promoted to by independent promoters
who actually gave out checks.
Not directly to disjockeys and as all kinds of legal ways
they were getting around it.
But, you know, it's pay for play.
That's basically what the system has been.
And, and it always worked, which is, by the way,
which is why these guys are so pissed off
is because, you know, their whole system broke down.
You know, they're, they're cry babies.
So, yeah, I understand where,
for a lot of folks, this stuff is, you know,
you've never heard of this longs before.
Let's see what Yon has for us today, yeah.
It's got another crazy video.
You ready to be stumps,
because he used that full text.
Yeah.
Hey, Adam, as you say, he tests number 103.
Look at what we're looking good.
Let me wish all the deadly source coating is first,
best wishes from the Netherlands.
Very happy new year, 2008, and, uh,
make it a good one, okay?
All right, then.
All righty.
This is test.
Number 103.
Here we go.
This is intro.
Number 101.
Uh, you'd be 40.
Uh, it's, uh, go your week and go our own way.
Uh, something like that.
Number two.
Uh, let no man put us under.
Um.
And the final one is number three.
That, that's, that, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that, that's it, that's, that's, that, that's, that's, that's, that, this is.
I'm trying to think of, it sounded like, it, sounded like,
what was the one before that sounded like it was, uh, letting no man put us, and times up, and these are the answers.
I know I have to do it.
And so number one is from 1986.
This is UV 40 and sing our own song.
Go your own way, sing your own song.
I want that.
We'll take half the point for that.
Answer number one is UV 40.
And this is Answer number two from 1986.
Yes.
This is first choice and let no man put his under.
First choice is Answer number three.
Two.
This is Answer number three from 1980 liquid goals.
All right everybody, we sing a lot now.
Then you're self-dizzy liquid goal is Answer number three.
And hit that number one.
Oh three.
So that's it for the first hit test in 2008.
How did you do at them?
Like two full stars.
One has the answers.
To this hit test.
And also the I2 plane.
So you can buy these tracks online.
To be found at hittest.botshow.com.
So I don't thank you for playing everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
I'll see you next week for hit test number 104.
So until then, take care.
Bye bye.
You really got to check out hittest.botshow.com.
And besides being able to get the iTunes tracks straight from the links.
You got to see the video version of the hit test.
Young is really putting some energy into that.
It looks good.
He's got all them covers and all kinds of stuff going on.
It's a very very flash, very flashy production.
Good choices there young.
Thank you so much.
Let me see.
Come at.
I had a message Justin from San Francisco.
I had two things for you today.
I had a book.
I thought you might find interesting.
Called the creature from Jackal Island.
It's called the second look at the Federal Reserve.
Great book.
I want to check that out.
And a movie I just found.
You should watch this movie.
It's a plane on Comcast on demand right now.
So the next time you're over in the city, check it out.
It's called Iraq for sale.
The war profit tiers.
It talks about the connections between Blackwater, Haliburton, KBR, Titan, Awesome
Awesome movie.
I think you might be interested in it.
All right, man.
Talk to you later.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, I've heard about both of those.
And of course, that Island is a whole conspiracy theory about that.
That's in many.
There are so many videos that are being produced now.
And it's it's flabbergasting almost when you see all this fantastic stuff that people
are putting together telling stories right wrong and different.
But they're telling stories in such a compelling way.
I'm very, very excited about it.
And there's this one thing that.
And then I'm definitely going to bring up on Noah gender.
Hold on a second.
Let me just see if I can find this link.
It wasn't actually going to talk about it right now.
But I've, you know, I have never wondered where the name Al Qaeda came from.
And as I've been doing my research, I've been looking around.
And the name Al Qaeda.
Apparently is an is Arabic or a dialect of Arabic that means the database.
And it is my understanding from the research that I've done, which comes from some pretty
reliable sources.
I'd have to say the Guardian in the UK is reasonably reliable.
They've mentioned this as well.
It's been published several times throughout the years.
That it was a name that was made up when.
The U.S. when the CIA was essentially supporting a summer bin Laden.
And the Mujahideen to kick the Russians out of Afghanistan.
They built up a database of freedom fighters.
And that was called the al Qaeda.
The database was called the al Qaeda.
So the whole name, the whole origin of this al Qaeda is actually as far as I can tell in American
invention.
And it's just flabbergasting to me.
Now, whenever I hear anyone talk about al Qaeda, particularly, I've heard several politicians
talk about it who actually should know better.
They should really know, I mean, ask one of these guys.
Where does this al Qaeda come from?
Who came up with the name al Qaeda?
It's pretty interesting to read.
Let me see if I can find that Guardian article.
Hold on.
I wasn't really prepared for this, but I was just thinking about it.
I don't want to say I want to get it from one of these.
Here we go.
The Guardian.
Okay.
Here it is.
This is from July 8th, 2005.
Oh boy.
Hold on one second.
Okay.
I got it here.
Bin Laden was a product of monumental miscalculation by Western security agencies.
Throughout the 80s, he was armed by the CIA and funded by the Saudis to wage Jihad against the Russian occupation of Afghanistan.
Al Qaeda, literally the database, was originally the computer file of the thousands of Mujahideen,
who were recruited and trained with help from the CIA to defeat the Russians, inexplicably, and with disastrous consequences,
it never appears to have occurred to Washington that once Russia was out of the way, Bin Laden's organization
returned its attention to the West.
So having links to al Qaeda literally means that the CIA has linked that person to their database.
It's an extrapolation, but I think you understand where I'm going with all of this stuff.
Interesting.
All right.
Because of the flu, I've been slowed down severely.
And I'm just, we're already 40 minutes into this.
And I want to leave you with a song that PDUB sent this to me, our good friend, PDUB-Ethenton,
to some affectionately known as the Satellite Repairman.
It's a YouTube video, actually, from Randy Newman.
And it's kind of a downer when you listen to it, but I'm going to close out the show with it today.
And that'll kind of close out the bummerness of 2007, so I can start Monday, a fresh with 2008,
and we'll really get into the swing of things.
It's titled a few words in defense of our country, and I think it's well worth a listen.
I was recently in Europe, and despite all we've done for them, and to them, they don't like us very much.
You don't respect us at all.
And I want to reply to their score in a song, which is the following.
I like to say the few words, defense of our country,
which people aren't bad, nor the mean.
Now, the leaders we have, while they're the worst that we've had.
A heart in the worst is poor world is seen.
Let's turn history's pages shall we?
Take the season's folks, example, while at the first few of them,
it was sweet with their sister, stage and little boys and swimming pools and burdened down the city.
One of them, one of them, supported his own horse to be crowned through the empire,
that's like vice president or something.
That's not a very good example right now, isn't it?
But he is one.
Spanish it wasish.
That's a good one.
Put people in the terrible position.
I don't even like to think about it.
Sometimes I like to think about it.
Just a few words.
Defense of our country.
It's time at the top.
I'm going to become a new anian.
We don't want their love.
Respect this points pretty much out of the question.
Time at the end.
We're sure we can use a friend.
He will.
Stalin.
I mean, you need to know what you're doing.
King Leopold about it.
That's right.
Everyone thinks he's so great.
We own the cargo.
He tore up too.
Took the diamonds.
Took the silver.
Took the gold.
You know what he left him with?
Well, there he is.
You know, president once said,
the only thing we have to fear is fear itself.
Not seems like we're supposed to be afraid.
It's patriotic in fact.
The color coat.
Are we supposed to be afraid of?
Why being afraid?
That's what term means, doesn't it?
That's what he used to mean.
You know what pisses me off a little
to the Supreme Court's going to have lived me?
A couple of young Italian fellows in the brother
on the court now too.
But I'd defy you anywhere in the world
to find me two Italians,
as tight ass as two Italians we got.
Nice for the brother.
Well, it was not a planet anymore either.
The end of an empire is messy at best.
And this empire's ending.
Like all the rest.
Not to Spanish our mother.
Drift down the sea.
We're drifting the land to the brave.
No more to free.
Good bye.
All right, Brandi Newmanberg.
I wouldn't say it's all that bad actually,
but what a great song to wrap up the Fubar Friday.
Ah, they're still home, my friends.
Vote for Ron Paul.
Enjoy your freedom.
And please live life with passion.
Imagine headphones without wires.
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset.
A rechargeable listening experience
with 11 hours of music playback.
So you and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com slash headphones.
Sony wireless headphones.
Your music are unplugged.