This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Hey, I'm a media guy, and I know how television works.
You know, I've been a part of the machine, it is one big.
It's a flickering fucking box, okay?
It's a light box, and people are tuned into this thing that jacked in.
So deeply, I see how it affects very rational people,
how they really believe things.
And this is carried over to the internet.
I see, you know, I watch all of these loose-change 9-11.
You know, every single, I watch them.
But I can see all the pieces to it,
and I can take away and I can analyze that and still keep some sanity.
But, you know, other people, they don't have that capability.
They have not been able to switch that off.
So that's why they get sucked very deeply into these types of stories,
which people forget that it's just people right in shit.
They can't think of themselves.
They can't think straight. They're jacked into the matrix.
So we're here getting ready for the big gala that will be the DSC 750.
Oh, look over there, there's Jersey Todd ensuring that the stage is safe for the bands that will be playing.
Guess he doesn't want any new clients.
But look over there, his CSBN Rodgers small.
What a pair they make talking together, looks like it's getting a little heated.
We better move on.
Oh, that there's P-Dub.
Telling some stories to some listeners.
Let's see, see Chapman.
Mark Usherwood and him call them Marcus Couch taking in the great stories by the satellite repairman and so on.
Oh, over there's the room of girls and Angie B.
And don't quite recognize that other lady with them.
Oh, wait, she's turning around.
Oh, it's the nylon.
Oh, Mark.
Oh, he is the man of the hour.
Mr. Adam Curry.
Let's see if we can get a moment with him.
Adam?
Could you say something to our listeners getting ready to participate in the DSC 750 celebrations?
Yeah, awesome.
I'm sorry.
I think it ends.
Okay, so we should probably, all right.
I got to think about this.
You already here.
I'm getting diarrhea of the mouth.
Gee, thank you, Adam.
That's a very nice.
What is 750 anyway?
It's three cores of the way to a thousand.
One with the show.
Oh, $16 billion worth of airplane straps by us.
To the next generation radio caught any of my ears.
We don't need no digging through the end.
I like to think I'm sorry.
You should be sure.
I guess it's angry.
But you are all going to make a big noise.
Pain in the street.
Don't know if you'll be a great matchup.
And you got mud on your face.
You'll make this great.
Kicking your trend all over the face.
Picking the face.
We will roll you.
We will roll you again.
But you are a young man.
I'm actually in the street.
I don't know what's up.
You got blood on your face.
You'll make this great.
Wave in your power.
Picking your trend.
We will roll you.
We will roll you again.
But you are a normal man.
Poor man.
You knew you'd rise.
Got a big smile.
Be something.
You got mud on your face.
You'll make this great.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
We will rock you in the
more clean ACVC wrapped up in the matchup. Thanks to Dr. Art from mashuptown.com for
sourcing and specifically for the Charlie. Everybody how you doing? How are you?
It's Adam your buddy. Here in the Curry condo. It's Wednesday the 23rd of April 2008
and haven't done any shows up until today because as you know, I split pretty quickly
last week from London off to San Francisco and lots of stuff happening here at HQ which of course
is part of the reason why I'm here. You probably noticed that today it's no longer pod show.
It's mevio.com. So that's the first important change that has been made and there's a lot of cool stuff
of coming around this time actually. I believe mevio.com should be up and the crew is pushing out
a whole bunch of changes and features. Oh man, the list is pretty endless. You should see them pretty
quickly. Some of the big ones of course are embedding of shows. That's under our sharing
features. We have more options to put shows. I mean, this is all kinds. By the way, I really
want to tell you how awesome. As an entrepreneur, having a business, there are many beautiful
moments in a company's lifespan. Right now, we are in one of those moments where the team
is really together. We're all bonded. We hang out last night. Everyone worked pretty well.
I think some people were actually through the night. All in an effort to get this up because
the run and I did a lot of press. Of course, our producer group, which also, by the way,
awesome bunch of people who all participated in the conversation about the name change
and are working with this rebranding. It's just beautiful when everything starts to come together
and I'm really, really happy, really proud. I want to thank everybody who's been working so hard
on making this work. Why the name change? Well, quite frankly, having the word pod in
our name was hurting our business and not really on the audience side, although we'll see
the proof is in the pudding if that'll make any difference. But certainly on the advertising
side. I'll just give you one example, but this is really the main reason why we change
our name is you look at a media buyer. They have a plan for their client. We do a lot of
direct client work as well, but a lot of it goes through media buying agencies. And
inevitably, or invariably, I should say, there's adjustments to a budget and the first
thing to be reduced or chopped off all together is always something that has the word
pod in it because it's difficult for the media agency to explain it to the client.
There's this negative connotation, which I can't do anything about, although my goodness
I have tried, pod casting brings with it some kind of stigma of people sitting in
their basement with a microphone, which, by the way, is awesome content often, okay? So
there's no problem with that. I have no problem with it. But when it's hurting business,
that's when we got to change things. So we have a brand new senior vice president of
sales, Chris Little, who came over to us from Dakota, which is now, that's a behavioral
marketing firm that I think was sold to American online. And Chris has really been
kicking ass and he's doing great stuff for us. And he has a vision. He has a vision of
some really big stuff, which fits in perfectly with our big stuff vision. So
couldn't be happier. And of course, here I am talking into a microphone, not in my
basement, but close enough to it in the Curry condo here in No Cal. Got a lot of
stuff to get through today since I've been short on shows this week. And I got a lot of
cool comments, particularly this first one, as our buddy who should have a
jingle, he being pretty much a Savanti's days with the amount of air
time he's getting the Arjuna. Make it in New York, calls up with an invitation
which is a very hard offer to refuse. Mr. Curry,
Jamaican in New York here. First of all, let me congratulate you on the
DSC 750. Thank you. That's a lot of shows. It's a commendable man.
It's amazing. Thank you. Thank you for all the shows.
And all the time you put in. I appreciate it. We all appreciate it.
And by the way, let me just reiterate you guys actually put the show together.
Every single time I sit down to do my show prep. I'm looking at the stuff you
dropped on the DSC drop at drop.io slash daily source code. I'm looking at my emails.
By the way, I fixed Curry dot com in case you hadn't noticed. If you sent an email
to Adam at Curry dot com, that's working again. Finally, I finally took the
time and just sit down and make it happen. And it actually didn't take that long.
And I can't believe it took me so long to get that fixed.
But also these comments, man, the voice mail is the stuff that you guys send in.
I love it. Thank you for helping me get through 750 episodes.
And let's do at least 250 more.
But I want to tell you a little story about what happened to me over the weekend.
You know, you've been saying every springtime in the summer.
You know, how it gets warm and unlawed and becomes beautiful. You see
you see boobs everywhere. Those kind of things.
Yeah, apparently New York is a lot like like London.
Ah, this is something that I noticed.
I haven't been in the UK for a while now in the springtime and in summer.
The women in London. Oh, man. They are so sexy.
They're all walking around and short mini skirts and tight tops and just
everything popping out. And it's just as a guy.
It's a wonderful, wonderful time of year.
I had better than Christmas even.
You know, this is my first spring. My first spring in New York.
And you know, I figure, man, let me go to Central Park tomorrow.
One day on Saturday, you know, people must be in the parks.
First time going to the park.
And let me tell you what I saw.
I don't, I saw people laying down bathing suits.
I don't know where I am.
Having lived in New York, I know.
I know how people treat Central Park in the spring and in the summertime.
They treat it like a beach. I know.
But it's not quite the same thing.
I'm thinking to myself, man, Adam would love this.
I would love this.
Adam needs to come join me in New York.
And sit on the great lawn would be on it.
And then just enjoy the sights.
Watch the people throw it free.
And jump in a row and clean.
You know, Adam, when you come into New York when we can,
we can chill out in Central Park.
But tomorrow, no.
It's here for you, man.
Just, we can just bring a brew on.
And let's do it.
Yeah.
Jimmy, can you New York?
I don't.
I love you.
Yeah, I don't.
You had me up until brew.
I was thinking something else that the Jamaican in New York
had hooked me up with.
But, uh, I wouldn't have been nice.
Yeah, you'll find me in New York.
Jamaica in New York.
Ginny.
Let's call him Ginny.
Jamaican in New York.
Ginny.
The Ginny survived.
Yeah, you'll see me, man.
Plenty of business to be done.
And I love New York.
I can't say that enough.
I fact was just talking about it today with the, with the
Opscrew.
And, uh, I say, you know, every single time in New York,
it just, I call Patricia and I just say,
I'll, you know, it feels, like home, you know,
it just feels really good.
And now that I have a friend like Jamaica in New York,
it's going to feel even better.
Speaking of the lady pee, lots of, uh,
comments on, um, I think it was, uh,
was it source code 748, where we discovered together
that she's indeed quite dyslexic.
And boy, did I get a lot of comments on that?
Hey, Adam, this is Carolyn Colorado.
You were talking about the, uh,
difficulty of driving directions with dyslexia.
And I wanted to relate to you an interesting story.
Um, I grew up in the U.S.
and when I lived in Australia for a couple of years,
I had a very strange occurrence where I was given my wife
directions and told her to turn right while I was pointing to the left.
Um, I was very interesting occurrence.
Um, my theory was that it's because in the U.S.
we learned that the near turn is right and the far turn is left
when, uh, of course, that's, um,
reverse for people that drive on the right on the left side of the street.
You know, that's something we didn't discuss because you,
I think you're on to something here because of course,
we're used to, uh, sitting in the left hand side of the car
and driving in the right hand side of the road.
Uh, now obviously we're kind of used to driving on the left hand side
of the road sitting in the right hand seat of the car.
By the way, I fly the airplane in the left hand seat
and the helicopter in the right hand seat.
So yeah, you can see working at kind of confusing.
So, um, that was very strange.
I also ran into many occurrences where we would mix up east
and west, um, relative to north and south.
Uh, that was very strange.
Even to the point where I would get convinced that the points
of the compass were reversed.
Uh-huh.
Trust your people to figure out whether that was due to being
in the southern hemisphere or just being unfamiliar with the, uh,
territory, not sure.
So anyway, um, I don't chalk this up to dyslexia
because I've never really had a problem with that.
But, uh, when you're driving,
there's other weird things that go on in your mind.
Um, take care.
Uh, 53, uh, no hair left, uh, two kids.
Uh, whatever blah, blah, blah, blah.
Take care.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So, um, the trick for a west and east, uh,
which, uh, even I sometimes have to think about,
you know, I use the compass a lot, obviously, uh, with flying.
And all you have to remember is that, uh,
it's always west on the left, east on the right,
if north is up.
And then, because that spells we.
And otherwise it would be,
ooh.
And that's not really a word.
And I still catch myself using that.
A lot of people call them with this, uh,
with the following, uh,
little, uh, little trick for the lady P.
And for anyone who has trouble.
And by the way, don't be ashamed if you,
uh, if you get confused between your left and right hand,
because apparently a lot of people have this issue.
Uh, so this might be helpful for you as well.
I had him as Parkie checking in with a top tip for the lady P.
Yeah.
She's getting confused with the left hand and a right hand.
I'll ask her to put her,
both her hands facing down,
so the palm is facing down on the top of the hand is facing up.
Yeah.
And then if you extend her thumbs inwards,
the left hand one will make a lovely else.
Oh, yes.
How about that?
That's nice and easy to remember.
So, both palms facing down,
thumbs facing inwards.
Lift it up and you go a lovely L on the left hand.
I'll keep it up to it.
See you later.
I like it.
Yeah.
And you're more of those.
Hey, I saw somewhere I was on Twitter on email,
the parking that your house got burglared.
Is that true, man?
That that sucks ass.
If it is, I'm really sorry that that happened.
Parkie has been sending me all kinds of awesome financial stuff.
Uh, so he's, uh, he's kind of a hidden sabond here of the Charlie.
But yeah, a lot of people sent in, uh,
sent in that tip, uh, the top tip, just by holding your hands,
palms down in front of you, um,
the hand that makes a lovely L with the, uh,
four finger in the thumb is your left hand.
There you go.
It's not all that hard.
And we love the lady Patricia regardless, don't we?
Yeah, we do.
Hey, I'm Mrs. Schmall from not so sunny,
I knew this morning.
I just don't really call that much.
I actually, it's the first time I call,
I sent a few emails.
But I thought I would shoot, uh,
leave a voicemail to tell you that last year was, uh,
that was BFC 748, where the late Patricia was in.
I thought it was wonderful.
It's been listening for two years,
and that was probably the best show to me,
as so much fun.
And hopefully we will get her back online.
All right.
Thank you, Adam.
And I'll talk to you soon.
My friend, thank you.
Yeah.
Have you really been listening for two years?
Because no sign off.
I get no big hair, I hope you win.
Okay.
That's all right.
I'll let you slide for this time.
Yeah.
We all love the lady Patricia.
And, uh,
I know it works, man.
Whenever she's on the show,
and whenever we just talk the way we talk normally,
the show is always awesome.
And of course, we'll have her on.
Uh, but she's busy.
You know, she's, uh, she's cranked up her career,
man.
She's doing all kinds of stuff.
Next week when I'm back in Blighty,
I think Thursday,
the two of us are going over to the Netherlands.
I'm going to go with her.
She's doing a talk show.
Very famous one that we've been on together before.
So we're going to be on that Thursday night.
And of course, she's promoting her,
her first live show in the series of Holland's Got Talent,
which kicks off Friday night.
And of course, I'm going to be there for that as well.
So we'll be together.
We'll be having fun.
And we'll be having a crazy monkey sex in the hotel,
which I'm looking forward to.
This past Saturday was a very special date.
It was the 20th of April, 2008.
And for those in the know,
the date four and two zero four,
20 is quite significant amongst the stoners.
And I know who you are out there.
We've made this two way.
I can see you.
And a couple of people called in,
because it's kind of like a ritual amongst people
who indulge from time to time in the holy herb.
They wish them a happy 420.
And I think the 420, it was either a police code
or I can't remember where it came from.
There's a story behind it.
I'm sure someone will call it and tell me all about it.
And we'll keep that for next year.
But this is a quintessential example of a fort.
Someone calling in to wish me a happy 420.
This is a.
Okay.
Hold on a second here.
Something is fired.
Ah, it happens to the best of us.
Doesn't it?
All right.
Here it comes.
Adam.
That be 420.
Oh.
So I had a thought that I wanted to share with the world.
And crap.
Now that I'm on the message.
They got in my mind with a thought to share with the world.
I don't remember what that thought was.
So I'm going to have to.
But it's quick a little bit.
Yeah.
And call us call.
How's fun?
Yeah.
420.
Yes.
All right.
Happy 420.
You as a girl, my friend.
I.
Yes.
I remember when we yesterday have protests songs.
But we actually said something to song.
I was reminded of that on the DSC drop.
His artist against apartheid.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, holy everything ain't in it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Joey was cutting back after his thud, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, had to say something, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, left behind and just now, you know what I was doing
I thought it was something to say
I thought that I was something to say
I love it's gross. It's gross
But I will understand that
I guess I need the word
No we fall, no homeguards
I thought I would buy somebody
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Right, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah what are we singing?
We will hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear
we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, I will hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you I, we'll hear you, we'll hear you, we'll hear you,
It's a part-time completely over.
I don't know, I'm just asking, you know.
Great suggestion, by the way, that came in through the daily source code drop.io slash daily source
code.
Great place to upload ideas, clips, things you just call it.
It also has a voicemail number, by the way.
It's a voice line, you can call it and it'll automatically post it into the drop.
All kinds of cool stuff there.
It's, of course, was the, uh, wasn't like the 12 inch version, so a little bit too long
even for the Charlie, because just kind of drones on after a while.
And I do have, uh, a number of, um, number of things that I found here and there that I
wanted to talk about.
First of all, how about that euro, huh?
It's not like I didn't say, uh, and I think I'm on record somewhere that this is really
out of control, the euro now passed one dollar and 60 cents for one euro and
I'm telling you, I have a feeling, by the end of this year, this thing could go to $2.
We just might see a $2 euro, which, of course, will mean that the oil per barrel will
be somewhere, somewhere around $200, if not more.
And I've predicted something pretty close to this before, and I think, uh, I think I just
might, might be right.
And, uh, well, for more of this, uh, I refer to, uh, Noah Jen, I'm sure that, uh, John C.
to work, and I will have, um, more conversations about, uh, the state of the, uh, financial
or the financial status of the world, anything that we'd, I'll tell you, things are bad
when you are on sand hill road, which is a very famous, uh, here in Silicon Valley, it's
where all the big, uh, venture capital firms are.
And, uh, just today, uh, an investor told me, he said, you know, man, it's really getting
out of control.
I'm flying commercial to Europe, instead of taking the golf stream, it's just so expensive,
the fuel cost in Europe, and all you have to pay these euro control fees, and, oh, no,
work flying commercial.
I thought that was quite a sign of the times, uh, pretty funny.
You know, um, uh, our fridge went on the blank two weeks ago, and, uh, because of, you
know, we have a special size and has to fit into this, uh, specific dimensions of the cabin
in the kitchen.
We had to wait for a week until, um, until we got a new fridge.
And I think I, I think I told you about this, right?
And, uh, so it's finally arrived and, uh, and boy, we had a party that was really nice,
but when the guys delivered the fridge, uh, excuse me, I had to move, uh, the Twingo,
because, you know, now, of course, we have three cars in the driveway, like we need that,
right?
So the Twingo had to be moved off to the side a little bit, and so I went outside to
move the car.
And, uh, so these, you know, two guys like delivery dudes, right there, they're kind
of standing up.
Not too far from me.
A little bit higher, there's a plateau before you go into the front door of the house.
And I smelled something in the air.
I'm like, man, am I just standing down, wind for these guys?
Because they smell like shit.
I mean, honestly, I was like, oh, man, I hope they don't smell this and hope, and think
it's me, you know, but the wind was literally blowing, um, from their direction, like, man,
these guys, they're, they're rancid.
They've been out delivering, uh, refrigerators all day.
And, uh, now these reports are starting to surface, which makes total sense because I thought
I recognized this smell, and it wasn't something that I'd smell them myself before.
Here's, uh, from CNN.com, a foul smelling permeating London and parts of England over
the past two days is due to farmers on the European continent spreading manure in their fields.
And it's true, we had a very strong Easterly wind for the past, uh, about a week or so.
Anyway, between 20 and 35 knots, a really strong wind.
And that means it's, if you remember now, we, right?
We have the United Kingdom is to the left of, uh, continental hearth.
So the east would be, uh, the continent and the poops smell was just coming across and
boy, it really was a stench and I have to say, typically we have the wind coming from the
southwest.
That was really funny to see this combination of events in combination with the fridge
being on a blink and me immediately thinking that this guy was just ripping a couple, uh,
right in front of me.
Now combine that with this news from, uh, from the Fox network and, uh, gentlemen, you'll
be, uh, particularly people listening, guys listening to the chucklehead who are chuckleheads
listening to the Charlie will be very happy to hear this news report, men who frequently
masturbate appear to have a lower risk of developing prostate cancer.
This is according to Australian researchers from the cancer council of Victoria and
indeed to found the men who masturbated more than five times each week were one third
less likely to develop the cancer of the prostate.
And as some technical details, the study surveyed 1000 men who developed prostate cancer
and 1,250 who did not and all were between the ages of 20 and 50 according to report,
came out Monday.
And this was actually this reporter originally originated from the, uh, from planet
out, uh, what they're calling here, the gay and lesbian news site.
Researchers told the BBC last week the prostate produces one of the fluids involved in
ejaculation and that frequent masturbation appears to flush out carcinogens.
Well, well, well, how are we feeling about that?
To say five times a week.
Okay.
So I think this needs to be a part of the new sign-off.
Love you, mean it.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Are you a five timer?
Five times a week?
Be honest.
Include it.
You're sign-off, please.
Analogy.
Great.
Now you can watch movies and TV shows anywhere you want on devices.
You can hold in your hand.
But not on a show full.
And what if you're driving or just walking down the street?
Who who are vision impaired always have to try to enjoy visual media without looking
at it?
Sometimes they can help from something called audio description.
Which turns this.
It's amazing.
Into this.
But the story of punches, Joe drives Gilbert across the ring.
He keeps connecting, pinning Gilbert in the corner, making a movie, into an audiobook.
He reads a letter.
He's writing to a district attorney.
Dear Sir, my wife and close friend, who is also my physician, are planning to kill
me.
He was in love with her before I met her.
Check out movies for the blind.
A weekly podcast of great public domain movies from the internet archive.
And you can enjoy them without looking at a screen.
Moviesfortheblind.com.
Excellent.
Great initiative.
And of course, you can also go to podshowpress.com.
That will probably change.
By the way, all of the links, all the email addresses, podshow, obviously, that's going
to stay.
We're not going to break anything.
Just get used to saying, mevio.
And Mark and him often, I've been talking about this.
He's going to think about the name, if you want to.
I said, I'm fine.
If you want to keep it podshowpress, if you want to make it meviopress, if you want
to make it some other name, I'm totally happy with that.
The point is if you want some great audio content.
If you want great stories, original stories by fantastic brand new authors who are part of
the new media revolution, go to podshowpress.com.
You will not be disappointed.
And I received a really, man, if all clients were like this, many of you probably know
that Luke the Candyman works for Nokia.
He's a Dutchman.
He lives in Finland, and we work with him to create the Nokia N810 Internet Tablet
Promotion and Campaign across the network.
The campaign ended on April 15th.
He called in, and he gave some stats.
Just listen to this.
Now, remember, yes, he's someone who we talk to, and he does his own show with a comic strip
blogger called YoAjenda, a little plug there, which is kind of an answer show to know
agenda.
But he's also a client.
And it's really lovely when you receive something like this from a client.
Hello, Adam.
It's the Candyman here.
You know that the last couple of months when people have been signing off their audio
come and comments, they have been hoping that you would win, hope you win and all that stuff.
So I now receive the final results of the Nokia N810 Potshow Promotion campaign.
And let's have a look whether you actually did win, shall we?
Of course, for all I want to thank everybody who went out and bought an N810 using one
of the Potshow Promotion codes.
I think that's a great thing, and I really hope they enjoy using the N810 and that it
adds something to their day-to-day internet, use it, or media experience.
There you go.
So let's look at the top three of the big selling shows during the N810 campaign.
On number three, our favorite tech goddess Kelly Lewis with Geek Rift TV.
In second place, and sorry, Adam, but that means you didn't win.
So in second place, Adam Curry with the Daily Source Code.
And on number one, my new hero, he's my BFF, new BFF of the Candyman, the sales monster
of the Potshow Network, Marcus Couch from the scenes scene.
Go, Marcus.
I mean, he completely destroyed the competition with his sales numbers, it was a hold on a second
look.
There's no competition, dude.
We all sit together in groups and we talk about the best way to do this, it's no competition.
It's co-optician.
We love working together, and I couldn't be happier for Marcus.
It was really a very, very good achievement, so I advise everybody to check out this show
at the scenes scenes.com.
In terms of countries where we ran the promotions, at the top three was not unexpectedly
perhaps, it was number one USA, number two Canada, and number three, the UK.
And Belchia, no punta, no chic, zero, unfortunately, but well, it happens.
So thanks again, everybody, for joining in, and Adam, I really do hope that next time.
You win, because you still have great hair, and we all love you very, very daily.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, man.
Candyman, everybody.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, and the fine folks at Nokia for making that promotion available to the
mevio, I remember to the mevio audience, making that available, and I think it's certainly
a lot of people will enjoy it.
I enjoy my tablet every single day, particularly using gizmo, I love using it on the tablet,
really good implementation.
Okay, let's see, why can do a couple of things here?
I taught you, I'm just going to run a little bit long today, because I really want to
get through all the stuff that have lined up, oh, by the way, talking about the surveillance
state.
You've got to check out this website, bluetoothtracking.org.
It's initiated from the Netherlands, I believe, but it's spreading out to other cities,
and I haven't looked through everything, but you can probably sign up and create your own
bluetooth tracker.
But they're literally tracking bluetooth signals, and it's really interesting, because
first of all, the names that people name their phones and subsequently that shows up
as your bluetooth name, those are pretty trippy, but also, you know, they're seeing where
people were, and I'm not quite sure if there's a great application for this, but something
went off of my brain.
I'm like, this is interesting.
We've got to keep our eye on that, so make sure you keep checking that.
And here's a savant who doesn't have a jingle, but should have one is tray or monetary
scientist checking in.
Hi, Anna.
This is tray, the monetary scientist of the Charlie with Run to Go.com, I've been traveling
and it wasn't Washington at Data's Conference, TA.org, where to talk about the central
link in the situation of the gold market.
Anyways, I'd like to respond to nylon's arguments about, and VSC-747, where it says to
get off the pad, that we've had 15 years of growth and everybody's better off, but always
have corrections, they go up and down and come back and forth, whatever, and then that we
don't have a gold standard, that says when first is argument that we've had 15 years
of growth.
Well, in 1994, Alan Greenspan said that central banks generated a lease and gold to the
price rise.
Central banks have been manipulating in the gold market since 1994, these 15 years
have had the prosperity has been tick-tissious capital, and we aren't really better off
because we've been consuming our capital instead of actually producing anything.
And go back and measure your net worth or your salaries in terms of gold, and we'll see
this stuff better off who really are.
I just want to say two things, one, what a point you make there tray.
We've been consuming our capital, that is a fantastic point, I really love that.
And the other thing I just noticed, you and John C. Dvorak both say, measure, where I say
measure, and I'm sure measure is the proper pronunciation, I just thought that's interesting.
The two people I respect and finance, or at least some of their visions and finance,
both say, measure, hmm, things that make you go, hmm.
And as far as they're always being corrections, well, because it said causes it, if we had
essentially planned egg commission that determined how many eggs everybody got at work
price, whatever really screwed up egg market, so likewise, the Fed determines the quantity
of money and the cost of money, and because it's central to plan and the market doesn't
decide it, there are these huge misallications of capital, cause of business cycle, it's
all the fedsfall.
And as far as not having a gold standard, well, it's true, in 1971 we did go off the gold standard,
but that doesn't mean that the financial world didn't go off the gold standard, it just
means that the dollar and gold dealings from each other, and, you know, I kind of agree with Isaac
Newton, who had been at the gold standard, because I believe that the earth, the U.S. dollar
revolves around the sun, which is gold.
Anyway, love your hair, keep up the good work, and keep fine for freedom, because that's
great. Oh, and by the way, gold is what keeps us free. So, run the gold buddy, back to you later.
Hi, Tray. Thank you so much. Gold keeps us free, huh? I have some gold. I, uh, I was advice to
buy some gold. It's an evolved. I can go look at it if I want. Oh, yeah. So what I didn't get
around to, uh, on the last no agenda with, uh, with John is, uh, he's talking about what Gordon Brown
has now done. Um, he's, uh, that's crazy. Man, what's happening. We're getting screwed. At least
people who pay taxes in the U.K. Like me, I want to point out, getting screwed. Our, our tax
pounds are now going to be used as a guarantee in a swap, which is, uh, it's a, it doesn't
name use in derivatives. So I presume it's almost like a derivative. Maybe the trade is being
done like a derivative, a swap of, um, bad, mortgage-based securities with questionable backing,
being swapped for government bonds. So the banks can borrow and lend money, mainly borrow money,
based upon, uh, this, uh, secure bond. I mean, wow, are we propin' up the system or what? By the way,
considering it's the system we live in, you know, maybe that is the only right choice,
maybe it's the only thing that can be done. But one thing's for sure. Certainly, I fault the
mainstream media with explaining to people what this means. They get the facts, you know, you,
you look at the, at the, at the, at the 10 o'clock news, which is, I guess what everyone these days
catches, who watches news at 630 anymore. You catch the 10 o'clock news. And, you know, it's like,
oh, here's what the government's doing and the doing this with, uh, they're taking the, you know,
they're swapping out bonds for these excuses. And then there's no analysis. Nothing that the
common man can understand because of course, what's really happening is our tax money is being put at risk.
You know, this reasons why it's being done. None of that's explained, you know, it's really a poor
poor shitty job. And of course, that goes back to the government who, um, are not helping us.
You know, they're not, uh, they're not explaining what they're doing. Could it, you know, please,
please in this, uh, in this race for the Democratic nominee, uh, Hillary Obama, you know,
start, start talking to us like, like, shit that we give that we care about.
You know, oh, yeah. Now, both of you will, we'll nuke Iran. You've made that very clear. What are
going to do here? How does it work? Explain it to us? You know what, you can patronize me a little
bit. I don't mind. I think the first candidate, whether they're in the Democratic race or whether
they're in the general election, the first candidate actually talked about some of these issues and
say, hey, look, here's how it works and here's what we're doing. And here's the big game. And,
and this is the game that we're in, we're at the center of it. Oh, and by the way, the dollar, you know,
160 to the euros, two to be 170, even 180 is being predicted. And, uh, and it wouldn't be great if
Barack Obama said, you know, Adam Curry predicted a $2 a year on the daily source code. And,
and here's why I think he's right. You know, just do it. Just explain it to people. It's really
important. And by the way, I'm tired of struggling trying to figure it out myself. Hey, man, this is
I don't know. So you can buy this. I don't know. I know. I know is a friend. I think he still works
for out. Thanks for playing my, um, my message the other day. Oh, by the way, I'm, um, I, uh, I don't
live in Cupertino. In fact, I moved last year. I know live up in one country. Ah, some of those stock
options vested. Okay. Got you. I don't know. Well, welcome to the club. Uh, a couple of hours north
of the San Francisco. So if you're up for tasting some wine, I know you're not big on the
Reno, but, you know, I know you're going to appreciate it. So yeah, be careful. Do you just
mind see John? See you in me up there. Anyway, um, you know, I'm with you, we're going to hold
it up to see something. It's so obvious that there's a ton of hypocrisy. There's so obvious
that there's a lot of house cleaning to do in the United States and France and Great Britain.
I mean, especially in the United States, I mean, when Panama Bay, how can you be critical of,
you know, anything unthinkable in my opinion that some people who have voted for Bush twice,
who have supported the Iraq War, uh, now would be criticizing the human rights record in China.
That's so hypocritical. Thank you. Anyway, um, however there's one thing that that shocked me about what
you said, man, I would like what? Um, and in your last BSC, say, um, you know, people get the government
that deserve. Yeah, it's true, but it's true in a democracy, man, but, uh, you know, we can vote
in France and the United States and Great Britain. Yeah, okay, hold on a second. Hold on a second.
So yes, people get the government data, deserve. So what's happening in the United States? What's
happening in, uh, in Europe, uh, you know, France or the UK or whichever country you want,
it's all because of the government they choose. Now, um, sometimes you have to go beyond just voting,
okay, I never said people get the government they vote for. I said people get the government
they deserve. By the way, not an original A to the C quote, um, I picked it up somewhere.
Well, I said it, but a lot of people agree with that statement. In France,
by the way, I'm trying to say France more, more often now, um, because it sounds so weird when everyone in the
the UK is talking about France and I say France. So I'm bear with me. In France,
yes, they have officials, they elected into office, but how do the French people make sure they get the
government they deserve? Well, they say, hey, government, you know, what you that decision you just made,
we don't like that. So you change that if you don't, we're going to strike. And if that doesn't
change your mind, we're going to burn your shit down. And you know what, the government listens to
that. Sometimes you have to do that. So respect, respect to the frogs of which you were one of,
no, highlight my pronunciation of your name, by the way. Okay, this is that house of the Lord
I don't know, but anyway, we can vote. We can vote, um, people trying to cancel,
people in Cuba can't. Okay, man, look, so same thing. America was founded the United States
or the new land and the new country. By people who could vote, right, they couldn't vote,
there was a king, a monarchy, they didn't like what the king was doing, they wanted a different
form of government, democracy, a friend's invention, by the way. And so they went and they said,
screw it. We're going to go start our own country, form our own government. They got the government
they deserved at the time. Um, which had nothing to do with voting. It had to do with the pure
anarchy. So if the Chinese want to do from government, um, I think there's a lot more Chinese
people than there are, uh, government officials in China. They can absolutely make a change, you know,
right now, they have the government they deserve. And I'm not one for inciting violence,
but you got to resort to that history is is papered all the way this far back as we can count
with violence to get governments to do what the people truly want. So no, they can't vote
democratically, then they have to rise up and they have to change that if they want to, they will,
every people's, every people's on earth has proven this. So, uh, that just doesn't float my
boat, my friend. They're not given that choice and they don't have access to all that information.
They don't, they're internet is either none existent, a completely censored intel. So you don't
need an internet, you need an axe, you to rock. That's all you need, rock. Anyway, not Iraq,
but a rock. Uh, just suits the top, man. Uh, you take care. I'm going to have a glass of
vino. And, uh, listen to, uh, the, uh, coming episode of a DNC, pick your man. Okay, I know.
So you understand what I'm saying, right? And by the way, the right to bear arms,
you know, that's not just for evil from outside our borders and our shores. It's internally as
well. And maybe even just look at it metaphorically speaking. But if we don't like the government
that we have, and that voting thing isn't working, by the way, I have to agree with my conversation
partner, John C. Devore Act, that it's all rigged. The candidates are rigged. Everything is rigged.
I, you know, even the voting machines are rigged. And there's been some pretty conclusive
evidence of that. We too may just have to rise up one day. And I'll tell you, I am very,
you know, look, I've lived 43 years. I'm a, I'm happy I made it this far. I'm, I'm prepared to rise up.
No problem. I'll, I'll make it better for my daughter. Oh, these kids growing up completely
apathetic to what's going on in the world. And by the way, um, I recorded my most recent entry into the
United States. Um, I took my, this was so funny. Uh, this was kind of on a, not a dare or a bed, but it was
like the next step in this. It's not been 10 or 11 times that I've been, this is 11th time. I think
whenever I entered the United States, I have to go to the first screening. Go through a secondary
screening, go through a tertiary screening, have my bags open. And it happens over and over again.
I get promise that I'm taking off the list, but I'm not taking off the list. And that's, so this
time I decided to record the whole process. Three stops and all coming into the country,
then going into secondary, then after I got my bag actually trying to get out of the airport,
there's another stop there. You know, check, questioned every single step of the way. And this time,
I recorded everything on my, uh, I river, uh, IFP 799, which is a pretty legendary device. It's what
I recorded, uh, I've been using that for, uh, four years now, almost. And, uh, man, the thing is still,
is still fantastic. Um, so no external microphone, just the internal mic. And I was just holding it
in my hand, okay? I didn't put it in my pocket. I was holding it in my hand like a cell phone.
And I literally, on the counter when I was talking to these people when they were interrogating me,
I was just holding it. And I was even pointing it. I was directing the, I was pointing the
direction of the microphone towards them. And no one said anything. I mean, I was prepared, right?
If someone said, hey, what's that? I was, oh, it's my MP3 player, um, which it is. I wouldn't have
been lying. It just happened to be on record at the, at the time. So I have about two hours of recording.
And honestly, um, I just haven't had the time myself to cut that down into because I really want
to get those three segments. I want to process the audio. Um, it's very legible, but still, you know,
there's a lot of ancillary noise. So I just want to get it really good. John actually called me
and he said, hey, man, you know, we should talk about this because I think you're going to get into trouble,
uh, you know, this really could be bad. And I'm like, you fucking pussy. I'm going to play that.
So I will play it on the daily source code. Not going to do it today because I do, you know,
if I'm going to do it, I want to do it right. Um, I can actually, uh, just to prove to you that I have
it, not that you don't believe me, right? Um, hold on. I think I can drop this in here. Let me see if
this works. Hold on. Now, let me see if I can find a spot where I'm actually talking to one of
the officers. Oh, man, wait, I can't be that far in. Here it is.
Wait, I got to turn off the, uh, I'm not going to be there.
Uh, I'm just being there. What are you going to have now?
I need somebody to get this mess. Yeah.
I'm bringing any kind of plants or needs or food or vegetables. No, so
any kind of currency over $10,000 USD or you know. So you guys can probably see you can
hear, right? So you bring any fruits or plants into the country and you currency over $10,000. I
know, and I'll just play this a little bit. You see, it's not, it's not being processed, right? So
that's why I really want to hook it up right. But just listen to the first bit here. You can hear it.
I actually, well, listen, we're going to have to talk to a team leader. So I'm saying I got to talk to a
team leader. So now I'm giving her like attitude. Just bring her my record baby happens every time.
Yeah, it might, it just might be a tough one.
Yeah, it was a tough one. Has it? Yeah, every time.
Maybe they could help you. Yeah, they've been trying. But that's been pretty
unsuccessful. Yeah, last 10 times in a row. So she was actually quite helpful. No one was
mean. Again, but it's just dumb. And when I get this all cleaned up and when you hear the whole thing,
you will actually be pretty shocked because just based once again on the questioning,
they have absolutely no clue as to what they're looking for. And it's a waste of time. It's a
waste of money. And I don't actually believe we're any, we're better off because of this
shenanigans that they're literally going through. So that will happen probably after a
good back to Blighty. So stay tuned for it. Again, just want to process it so we can have maximum
enjoyment because there are some very funny bits in there as well, which I'm not going to tell you,
but well worth a listen. I know there was a song that was left on the drop drop that I owed us.
Slash that was the day of this. Yeah, we're there. Drop.io. Slash daily source code.
It's another protest song from our era. If you're in Europe, listen up to Fort Europe.
I'm Charlie seven five ohs. I was the point of time not long ago when people were still living
in the northern zone. They could still breathe and everybody wasn't there. Somebody recorded a song.
This is what it says. Half of the first and the second world was you think a few Europeans couldn't
take a no more. But we built up and caught on a Berlin wall. Only the building went and proved
the right. I chromed it for your own. This one was a bit tricky. Now visible to it and you can
die. And if you was lucky, you could slip through the cracks and impresses it. You're like
thunder. You're on this way. Some people knocking only to become second class citizens.
You're not listed in the system. Not existing in the city. You go in my grave.
But where lift the fittest and this place is called, me blush it and never went to put you
rope. My soul called you. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. We are behind the cold.
Hello, I'll get you flowers, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her
ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, hers ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell, her ring fell,
Who's your enclosed son?
Right here, and for you.
Don't worry about you.
Right here.
Right here, and for everyone.
Right here, and for you.
On you.
Hey here.
Yeah.
Right here, and for you.
Right there, and for you.
Oh.
I had to extract some recycled dust.
taking care of business. I'm digging it. It's about time. We're all fed up, you know,
and by the way, don't mind saying what's really on your mind. We'll play it. We'll get
your message out there. Well, we'll make sure people here. You don't have to rely on mainstream
media. You don't have to compromise in the language and what you're saying and who you're
pissing off because we're there for you to support the artists who really have something to
say. Yes. I have to go according to my media. Oh.
This is Marsha Geller. She is, she runs a set of conferences called the IMedia conference. I did
a keynote there once and they got like highest marks of all key notes ever. Not to stroke
myself, which by the way will probably stop me from getting prostate cancer. Five timer for sure.
And Marsha's cute. And she wants me to be on a panel, I think, for an upcoming IMedia.
And honestly, I've been kind of scurrying around it because it might mean a special trip.
It's in that Texas, which is not really somewhere that I find myself that often, although I do
like Texas a lot. And I guess now she's calling into the daily source code voicemail line to
get my attention. Let's see what she has to say. I'm not talking to Greg Meand, and I haven't
heard that. No, sales, we's a Greg yet. Whether or not you're going to be able to reprise your
appearance at the Texas agency permit. Go here. That is of course my job. I got to go out there
and blow all these agencies so that they'll spend money on our network and make everybody and make
the cash flow baby. That's all right. I accept that responsibility. Just coming up in a few weeks,
I'd love to hear about the minister as possible. We're going to print with a book and I would love
to have you join us. If you can give me a... Okay, so I think Russell Simmons is on the panel.
And someone else, I'm not sure who else is on. It was a couple of names that didn't recognize.
You know, I was like, I think, you know, go ahead and Google Marsha Geller. I think it's G-E-L-L-A-R.
Let me just check for you. She's also on Facebook. Let's have some fun. Okay, guys. I got an idea here.
Let me just see, M-A-R would be M-A-R-S-C-H. Like Marsha, yeah. Geller, I think that's it. Let me see if
Marsha Geller. I don't know if that's the right spelling.
Uh, because I get a lot of Sarah Michelle Geller. Well, it may be Geller with E-R.
Oh, man. Yeah. With E-R, there you go. Marsha G-E-L-L-E-R. Now I'm going to look at images.
You know what? Do some research. Go look around for... I'm not quite sure how to spell the name.
Um, Marsha, if you're listening, send me a naked picture and I'll be on your panel.
Isn't it? Come on. Hey, chuckleheads. That's fair. One naked picture of Marsha and I'll go on her panel.
So get ready to jot down her details because what I want you to do is I want you guys to call her an emailer
and say, you know, hey, I'm a part of the Daily Source Code community. I'm an official chucklehead or a
Mr. Bond or a long time listener. First time caller. I'm a five timer. I'm a folder. I'm a scruncher.
I'm taking the red bill. We all agree that if you want to add them on the panel, which of course will mean
I'll probably miss another show because I'm too busy. Then you need to send them a naked picture.
Add them at potshow.com. Add them at niveo.com or add them at curry.com.
You call if you're down on a ground and in the country or somewhere near a phone would love to hear from you.
The number is 2-0-3-9-8-1-7-2-5-6. What do you mean email? It's Marsha M8 FHA at imediaconnection.com.
Example, do you hear from me since I did? Yeah, do you win? Okay.
All right. Leave it. Can't mind you sending it in.
Yeah, I'm Highlander doing under. Okay. I'm from Sydney, Australia. Sunday early evening with some stuff. I just
have to go off my chest. That's what I'm here for. I'm listening.
So I've been listening to the DSC since I discovered it about three months ago.
And as I've got, I'll be in Oz. I feel Julie qualified to talk about economics, finance, and money.
Okay. As well as China and Tibet. If you think of economists such as John Law,
Adam Smith, who's the author of a wealth of nations. Wait, let me guess. All Scots?
Or even the first Secretary of the Treasury, Alexander Hamilton, they were all Scottish.
How was copper wire invented? I know the two Scots. I'm inviting over a penny. You got the
So you've been talking about two separate subjects in China and the economy in the UK, US and Europe,
including this current credit crunch over the last few DSCs and a bit about it on no agenda as well.
By the way, it's not just a credit crunch. I think we should get over that misnomer. That's like a code
being used in mainstream media. I hear it all the time and Britain. You know, saying,
well, you know, these are American problems that are hurting us, too. Bullshit. Bullshit.
Is the international finance system? I don't know. Can't anybody see the money fix is what I'd call it?
He, all the stuff is released. Yes. So the Chinese yuan is a currency that is not
debt based on like Federal Reserve issued notes. The Bank of China is government controlled and
issues one as a bill of credit. The snow interest is in card for its creation.
Basically, the Chinese are doing what Lincoln did back in 1862. Wait a minute. Are you telling me?
This is very interesting. So the Chinese, I guess, do what people like Ron Paul thinks we should be doing.
Well, it certainly doesn't seem to be hurting their economy. Okay, interesting. Good knowledge.
When the U.S. Treasury issued greenbacks instead of private created, Lee contender.
This is a naval China with his economic and miracle to form the biggest foreign exchange reserves in the world.
A worth over $1.3 trillion. You heard that correctly. $1.3 trillion. What they're doing with some of
this money is bailing out U.S. companies suffering from the subprime crisis. For example,
Morgan Stanley, 5 billion in cash, but a 9.9% stake in a company back in December 2007.
So China is the one place where the establishment moneymen have no stronghold and we effectively
gave them the blueprint for their success whilst cutting everyone through it.
Oh, very interesting. Okay. So we showed them how to do it with the greenbacks, which is not the
dollar we know as today, which was issued not by the Federal Reserve, but by the people.
And China took that. Good idea. Thanks, guys. And then we went and stabbed ourselves and
in our own back. Oh, man, you need a sub on status as well. Our Scottish sub on.
And I do know that Tibetans are exempt from all taxation and the Chinese government provides
90% of Tibet and government expenditure. So in an Olympic year, internal protest and hence
suppression of Tibet is not about politics or freedom. It is about money. If we're worried about
freedom, then we should worry about our own freedoms first. In China, they may not be politically free,
but in the US and the UK, we're saddled up turn nets and debt. So I ask you, yes, we are slave to the
man who is freeer. Indeed, to go on a further, what's the difference between democracy and China
and the US? In both cases, the power rests in the hand of a few people with all the corruption
and nepotism that comes with, at least this bullshit situation in China is semi-honest compared
to having a non-majority, questionably elect present. You can't run a business, never mind a country.
But it's dad and his friends are all just into the money man who on the turn of assimilating another
country to the empire of unpayable, high-interest foreign loans from major US-funded
re-building contracts make him present of the US-AV. The US and UK are really run by non-elected
shadowy money man. Well, China is run by non-freedom to choose one party elected officials,
which one sounds more democratic? The government is a shite state of affairs. Meanwhile,
I had to leave the UK because a big brother killing my personal liberty, high-interest rates,
meaning no chance of getting a mortgage, crappy immigration, financial, political and military
subservience to the US. I'm telling you, man, Australia is a 24th province of China. What do you
think are PM's big Mandarin? It's all about the money. So instead of protesting by not buying
Chinese made goods, that's fucking the off-China and start fixing their own shit first. The economic
credit crisis business cycle that screwing all countries that love so-called constitutionally
guaranteed freedoms will be the last one initiated by shadowy powers that be, unless we can fight
for own changes, our own freedoms, otherwise the balance of power and world economic control
will move east over the wall. Great home, oh no hair, not not wink wink, hope you win
yet. By the way, can I be the official Scottish Savannah? Hell yes, hell yes, hereby hold on
Neil yes and okay, you are hereby knighted the official Scottish Savannah Highlander down under my
friend. Thank you. Good clarity there, that really helped. Yeah, absolutely. I agree, I don't know if
you're right about everything, but it sounds right on and boy do I agree, we have to fix our own
shit first. Really we do. You know, I was sitting with the Republican today, Ray Lane, one of our
investors in Mivio. And, you know, he's going to vote for the party with the party chooses, right?
He's going to vote for McCain, but I said, you know, dude, is that really the best you guys
come up with? And he said, well, you know, I don't determine that anymore, because he used to be
very connected into the party. And like, you know, we all determine this, you know, we really,
we really, really, really got to do some soul searching, okay? And, boy, for me, you know, just it
becomes so clear how easily we've been manipulated into a life of luxury. And, and I'm not talking
about Louis Vuitton bags and Rolex watches, I'm talking about a roof over your head. You can go back
50 years and there was, there were people in a lot worse situations in this country in the United
States as well, all over. In the United Kingdom, wow, man, the blitz destroyed massive amounts of
dwellings and livelihood and people. We've been through a lot of hard times, but it's just not
you know, it we're not feeling the physical effect yet and we're being duped. We're being given
all this luxury shit that is keeping us really occupied and, you know, we're pissed off when we
can't sync up our iPod to iTunes. And meanwhile, we're being robbed. We really do have to get our own
house in order. And you know what, we all have to do it together. Yeah, I had a PSC at a board in here
question of why we listen to the pod show. I'm in the same demographic as you, so I guess that's
one of the reasons the second is all we all are connected. We're also all responsible. And I think
you keep bringing that collide. And I think we need more people to bring that to life. Is that,
well, yeah, it's all one big community. But we're also one big responsibility and we're responsible
for everything to happen and everything that will happen. Just to tell it is from the music to the
conversation. Always, always, always interesting, always interested in to hear something new
and while sometimes it's just a rehash of the old thing and it's always a new opinion.
And plus you like guys like me calling it, but you know, this is like this.
Right. Like they say gray hair. Not so much anymore. I still think I have better hair.
I'll be a normal, all that stuff. I'm people talking. Hell yeah. We are all connected. We are all
in this together. You know, it was so surreal, surreal that I was in a cab the other day in London.
Sorry, a new gilford from the train station to home to the manner.
Talk about luxury. And I'm talking to the driver. I say, we from, he says, I'm from Iran.
I said, oh, that's the country we want. We're going to bomb. And he's like,
ah, he's man, man, that's so messed up over there. He says, you know, we're all, we're all young.
And we've got the internet and the not enough people speaking, but they're really, you know,
trying to get on board with that. But our government is suppressing us and they're crap.
And we've got to change that and same thing came to mind. It said, man, you know, you get a government
you deserve. We got the government we deserve. Should we really let a bunch of assholes drop
bombs on us? Because they can't figure out what, it's like screw that.
It was a guy, a human being. And I'm connected to him. And you know, we're doing commerce together.
He's performing a service on paying. It's like, that's the way the world should work. And I know we can get there.
My good friend Ray from from Holland sent in a song that was actually intended for a
football Friday. But I want to play it today. It's kind of appropriate with people being connected
and and being able to do beautiful things together. This is a track of the Reverend Al Green,
who, of course, is quite a performer in his own right. And he was in the same studio as Chicago
in the 70s. And they were messing around and they decided to do an Al Green song. And he joined
in on vocals. And this is actually a studio recording, which includes the pre-banchor before they
start to record. And then the banter after I'll let the whole thing play out so you can hear how
excited they were. This is people come and certainly in the 70s, Al Green and Chicago,
two separate worlds. But all people, in this case, with a common interest, music. And when you
really get together, you can make beautiful music together. But I came in, I thought I heard you
felt rehearsing my tune. If it's cool, let's get together and do it. One, two, one, two, three, four.
Sounds so good today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I love me yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah k vacation yeah yeah yeah there yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not, not, so cold, just fall down inside. Everything is crying now.
How awesome is that, huh?
I can't wait to go to the booth.
I'll green and Chicago.
And yeah, I too am tired of being alone.
I think we're all tired of being alone.
Not just alone but as individuals, but as just one people against another nation, I'm tired
of being alone.
Let's do this all together.
We have the technology, we have the communication, we've got guys running our countries who
are old-fashioned, I'm tired of being alone.
Hey, live your life with passion, okay?
And I'll talk to you as soon as I can.
I hope it's going to be Friday and you know, you've got to enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation, share it with your friend.