It's Friday, October 31st, 2008, the new world owner has shown its ugly face.
Bringing down the global financial system and a heap of disgrace, all the chuckleheads
know what to do. As we roll out Delta Shira Charney 802, warning, these stories aren't just
any Halloween tales, I tell you, these my predictions are the reality of the world, they are
all true, being afraid my predictions, being a veteran afraid.
It's close to me and I, something people are working from the door, I'm not the
moon. You try to scream, but terror take this song before you make it, and you start to breathe,
as I will look you like a dream in the eyes, you're very nice, I can set it down.
Delta, I know, it's no one's gonna sing, and probably it's a lot's fine, but you know, it's down.
Delta, I know, it's no one's gonna sing, but terror take this song before you make it, and you start to breathe,
you're very nice, I know, it's no one's gonna sing, but terror take this song before you make it,
and hope that there's just a mission nation, there's a lot of world, there's a dream that
feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels
a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream and feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream that feels like a dream.
I'm going to do it now, I'm going to roll you get the
Yeah, I'll do the night
I'll take it from the chair on the screen
I'll make a scene, I'm not gonna do it
Then I'm going to go back and change the moment
Then I'll go back and change the moment
Then I'm going to do it
Then I'll do it now
Then I'll go back and change my Kamera
Then I'll go back and change the moment
I've got a way to run
Darkness falls across the land
The midnight hour is close at hand
Creatures crawling the certain land
I've terrorized your inevitable
I don't remember shall we hold
Without the souls all getting down
A stand in the face of the homes of hell
And rock inside a corpse and shell
I've got a way to run
I'm having, we might as well be brutally honest about it
There is no better record for a Halloween footballer friend
What do you say?
I've got a way to run
It takes all my marks and all the messages in the air
The funk of 40,000 years
And currently the goals were never too long
I've got a way to see you live
And though you've found out to stay alive
You're far in your start to achieve
Or no more cold
For the law
I absolutely love it
Vince and Christ Michael Jackson
And thriller Perfect for a footballer Friday
Of course, the Halloween addition
Which means we've got to keep the maximum
Music freight train express roll
And cruisin' the drop, playin' some tunes.
It's football in joy.
Why is marijuana not legal?
It's a natural plant that grows in the dirt.
You know, it's not natural, 80-year-old dudes with hard-ons.
That's not natural, but we got pills for that.
We're dedicating all our medical resources
to keeping the old guys erect,
but we're putting people in jail for smoking
something that grows in the dirt.
You know, we have more prescription drugs now
that every commercial entity is a prescription drug addict.
We can't watch TV for four minutes.
We have five series diseases.
Like, you ever wake up tired in the morning?
I've got to have this right this down whenever it is I have it.
That's the time you don't even know what the commercial is.
There's people running through fields or flying kites.
There's swimming in the ocean like that.
It's the greatest disease ever.
How do you get that?
That disease comes with a hot chick and a puppy.
The schools, now it's all about self-esteem and the school.
The kids self-esteem.
Make them feel good about themselves.
If everybody grows up with high self-esteem,
who's gonna dance in our strip clubs?
What's gonna happen?
The point out with these women don't just grow on trees.
It takes lots and grunked out.
He's missing a lot of dance recital before you decide to blow a goat on the internet for 50 bucks.
And if that disappears, when does that leave me on a Friday with a new high-speed connection?
The baby is a baby.
We're going to try and kick it through.
The baby is also a baby.
The baby's doing well after a week.
The baby.
Torries.
To find other men.
What to call our baby.
You should go.
I'll get some sleep.
You are there.
Do you?
If you're going to use stairs ride.
The baby's hiding behind.
Normally, with many kids leaves,
a morning, and the baby's keeping him with each other.
They're real you
Americans this face that we've been a spoiled country for a long time. I mean, what the number one health risk in America is obesity
obesity
They say we're the middle of an obesity epidemic and epidemic like it's polio
And we'll be telling our grandkids about it one day the great obesity epidemic of 2004 had to get through a grandpot
Oh, it was horrible Charlie there was cheese cake and pork chops everywhere
Nobody knows why we're getting fat or look at our lifestyle. I'll sit in a drive to us at different
I'll sit there behind 15 other cars instead of getting up and making an eight foot walk in the totally empty counter
Everything's mega meal super fries won't piggy fries with that one a jumbo fry one a collage one a big fry one a 30-footers for a neckley
If I'm on the blue there's room in the bag and take it
What a 55 gallon drum with coke with that. It's only three more cents
You
Sometimes you got to suffer a little in your youth to motivate you to see later in life
You think of Bill Gates got laid in high school. Do you think there be a Microsoft?
Of course not you got to spend a lot of time stuff in your locker with you underwear wedge top your ass before you start thinking
We're in one of the richest countries in the world in the minimum wage
So it's lower now than it was 35 years ago
There are homeless people everywhere that this homeless guy asked me for money together day as about to give it to him
And I thought you just can use it on drugs or alcohol and then I thought that's what I'm gonna use it on
Why am I judging this poor bastard people loves each other homeless guys like you get the money
She's gonna waste it. He's gonna waste the money. Well, he lives in a box
What do you want to do with this thing that I'm by all alone? You're gonna take a little run the store for a throw
We're gonna see the rackies homeless. I walk the honest guy the other day a homeless guy
Answered for money. You'll try that the homeless guy is much better. I'm gonna job your film
People always say that the homeless guys get a job like it's always that easy this homeless guy
We've heard his underwear outside his pants. I'm guessing he's resonating all up to date
I'm predicting some problem during the interview process
I'm pretty sure even McDonald's as an underwear go inside the pants policy
Not that they enforce it very strictly, but technically I'm sure it's on the books
Yeah, it's been around for a couple of years for the perfect song to play on a Friday
Lazy boy
underwear goes inside the pants
Oh
We got some good stuff coming up for you today. Yeah, as I said just kind of cruising through the drop got a couple of
Awesome pieces of a video to share with you later on
Of course, you'll only hear the audio. I'll be enjoying the video. You can check that out later in the show knows
You don't want to find those daily source go dot com crosspost at a curry dot com
Coming to you friends again from the curry man in
One of the west side of G town the affluent suburb of Surrey known as gilford. It is Halloween
I don't think you know although they do celebrate it here in the UK trick or treating is not really a big thing
And it's funny because Halloween has been kind of propagated throughout to western Europe mainly because of the movie
Halloween
And what's even funny here is that in some countries I'm looking at you Holland people call it
Halloween. I mean, they've really taken it a whole extra step further
So in honor of
Halloween
Let me
Give you a Halloween joke
Cabby picks up a nun. She gets into the cab and notices the very handsome cab driver just won't stop staring at her
She asks him a while he's staring he replies why have a question asked but I really don't want to offend you
She answers my son. You cannot offend me when you're as old as I am you've been a nun as long as I have
You get a chance to see and hear just about everything. I'm sure there's nothing you could say or ask that
I wouldn't find that I would find offensive in any manner whatsoever
Well, I've always had a fantasy to kiss a nun
She responds well, uh, let's see what we can do about that apparently she was a milking nun
Well, but of course you have to be single and you must be Catholic
The cab driver is very excited and says yeah, yeah, I'm single and I'm Catholic
Okay, the nun says
The next alley
The nun fulfills his fantasy with a kiss that would make a hooker blush
And they've get back on the road the cab driver starts crying. Oh my dear child said the nun. Why are you crying?
Forgive me sister, I have sinned
I lied and I must confess
I married and I'm Jewish
The nun says it's okay. My name's Kevin. I'm going to a Halloween party
It can happen in Amsterdam in fact easily
Today, I'm whole confused
Yet I look for the light to the pouring rain
You know that again that I hate to lose
And I'm feeling the strain
And in a shame
In a dream I saw
You lost and you rocked it all and you didn't go away
Oh, you in a dream I saw
I want to get lost and you rocked it all and you didn't go away
Hey
Beginning to think that I'm wasting time
I don't understand the things I do
The world outside looks so unkind
And I'm coming over you
To carry me through
Oh, you in a dream I saw
You lost and you rocked it all and you didn't go away
Hell, you in a dream I saw
When my mind is free
You know melody can move me
When I'm feeling blue
It does come in through the foot me
Thanks for the joy that you give me
I want you to know I'm leaving you so home
With a miriam and harmony
You help me alone
Making this home
Give me the beat for us and free my soul
I want to get lost and you rock and roll and drift away
I want you to know I'm leaving you so home
Oh, you in a dream I saw
You lost and you rocked it all and you didn't go away
Now, now, now, now, now, now
Now, now, now, now, now
Now, now, now, now
I've been keeping notes every single time I hear a think of a song that's good for the
Chuck, I'm putting it into my Nokia
He knew a spreadsheet no less with the quick office
I've set up a quick key for it
Oh, yeah, it works so nice
Who? Another fabulous fade out
Sorry about that
I just wanted to hit one piece of feedback that had come in from
I know a long time listener, Doug Ritter
And Doug had a little bit of feedback on 801, which was yesterday's show
And two points, two main points really, first one about credit cards
And I think I pretty much stated that
You know, this, you're going to be hearing this mean paper to plastic
Moving from money to credit cards paper to plastic paper to plastic
You're going to be hearing that over and over again because they want to
You know, make digital money the next big thing
And based upon what only God knows, but just numbers in a spreadsheet
Highly, many people have been in a minute, many people have been in a bit of a bowl
And I said, you know, man, hey, there's lots of people using credit cards
Now, number one vendor is McDonald's
And I take that, I absolutely to be a cheap dinner
Bracket up on the credit card
I mean, maybe that is just the way I am
However, Doug says, just want to give you some feedback in a comment about credit cards and McDonald's
I laughed because just before listening to the show, I used to credit card for six dollars and one cent at
Chick-fil-A, that's a Southern U.S. fast food joint
I'm just about 30, but I noticed there's a generation who view people using credit cards with a certain amount of prejudice
And this indeed could be me Doug
I noticed that a lot with my dad as well, okay, that hurts
He's of a simpler mindset of you
I and a lot of your listeners about the current state of the world
And he will tell me stories about people using credit cards for this and that and when I pull a credit card out to use it for a meal
He always says, oh no, no, I can get it and whips out his cash assuming I don't have the money to pay for it
Even though he knows better
I guess my point is, as Doug, I own my own home paid off mortgage own both cars outright have no debt
These are not gonna cash in the bank. Yeah, you know what Doug, you're an exception my friend
I hope you're not, but I'm pretty sure an exception
I have been known to frequent McDonald's and I see what's going on
Second thing Doug says about the exon profits
Why is such a big deal made out of this?
And he goes on to say that you know the margin their profit margin is is quite
Quite thin compared to other companies
And it goes on to say it's a really easy to jump on the anti-big oil bandwagon
But not very logical. What do you think exon is a charity? No, but I wanted to say they're um Doug
That they're not a charity. They're more like a dealer and what's happening now is a large
Part of the dealer's customers
mainly those who use oil for driving and transportation
Use little stimulus in the market let the drug dealer provide this stimulus seems pretty fair to me
Like hey kid want a taste
Come on, I'll give it to you for free, you know
Come on, don't you want to be cool all the kids to do what it has some oil hey they snap it down
Get suspicious, but no oil in the middle of my head
And I know that it's true that all the things that I do will come out of me on my sleeping time
So keep on rockin' me made
Keep on or rockin' me made
keep on or rockin' me made
Don't walk in me, baby
Keep on walking me, baby
Baby, baby, baby, baby
Keep on walking, baby
Keep on walking me, baby
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah
Don't get suspicious, no, no
Be suspicious, baby
No, you won't wear my mind
And you know that it's true
That all I'm thinking of, you won't
I'm going back to you in your sweet day
I'll wait for Phoenix
I don't want to go away
I just don't want to feel it
Help me, you will have a L.A.
No, then California weather curve
So I could have a living baby
Say, keep on walking me
No, I just need a minute
I got news for you, man
The girls in northern California
I can't even walk
Besides, it's like, warm
I know they're kind of cold
He's not by the bay
It's cold
I can't even walk
Oh, I got to speak in a weather
I got to have a lot of some
Some of the weather coming up for you
You're gonna love that
I can't even be there
And just staying with the
With the proposed bailout of the auto industry
That Doug responded to John McCain
Is not come out and said
The struggling US auto industry
Could not be allowed to fail
And if elected president he would do quote
Whatever I think needs to be done
To save it and quote
25 billion dollars
What they're looking for
And some of this is earmarked
Some of this is earmarked
To be used for
New plug-in vehicles
Or actually I don't think he actually
stipulates plug-in vehicles
I think this 25 billion was discussed
Earlier has been on the table a long time
Before they started talking about a bailout
They were looking for low cost loans
But it was for alternative fuel vehicles
Now the plug-in hybrid that's Barack Obama's agenda
Hi, yes
Something that I had not seen yet
Which has apparently been around for
Well, it looks like almost a year
If not longer
An HBO special called Hacking Democracy
And of course you're going to see a lot of
Talk now about voting machines
And how they work
And I urge you to take a look at this
About an hour and a half
It's HBO its quality
Although it's very much a reality type documentary
Following these people who
Basically try to track down and see
If there is a possibility to commit
fraud with voting machines
And well, I'm not going to spoil it for you
Okay
I almost won't do that
But definitely have a look at that
And of course you can find both links
In the show notes of dailysourcecode.com
Or crosspost it at curie.com
We'll be cruising more of the drop
Drop.au slash daily source code
We're all the mainstream news
That you never hear about is posted for your enjoyment
And if you're awakening
If not longer
We'll be cruising more of the drop
We'll be cruising
You and me, you and I should get ahold of me
You and me, you and me, you and me
You and me, you and me, you and me, you and me
You and me, you and me
You and me, you and me, you but, you and me
You and me, you and me, you and I should get ahold of me
You and me, you and me, you and me
You and me, you and me, you and you
I should get ahold of me
You and me, you and me, you and me
Makes me mad, it's not the moment
I'm the star, I'm the star
The best moment, people are people
On daily source code episode eight zero two
Very, very dark here in the UK
That's mainly because we're all alone at home
and have not turned on the backyard lights
Usually there's a whole family doing stuff like that
No, it's just me, all alone
I've fed the animals though, next up it's my turn
First though, to continue, this is fantastic
I can't believe that I'm only hearing about this now
This apparently was posted to YouTube in March earlier this year
But it's only now coming to my attention
This is a YouTube video, it's an interview from...
I think it's a...
Yes, hold on a second, let me just turn that back
What is it, KUS?
I am trying to see what the...
It looks...
Well, it definitely looks like a real news interview
Because you know, this monitors in the background
And something, you know, news desk logo
KUSI is, I think, is the call letters
And so this is Jim Coleman, Jim Coleman is the founder of the weather channel
And it's great to have a guy of his authority, he's a scientist
And he's been a long time meteorologist on television as well
And as I said, he founded the network, the weather channel
And he is finally someone of authority who is just sitting there
And almost in a disgusted manner
Talking about this bogus climate change
bogus bogus bogus
And the bogus IPCC, which is a division of the United Nations
Since, when is the last time you trusted that crooked bunch, huh?
There's always shenanigans going on there
I mean, just say that's...
Just Google News that, you'll find all kinds of shit going on with the United Nations
Huh, please
But he actually has the statistics, he has the figures
He knows how many scientists actually sign papers
Who doesn't agree, what the general consensus is
The guy is amazing and I love the way he talks
It's four parts, so what is that?
It's probably like a 30 minutes total, a little over 35 minutes
You know, YouTube's 10-minute restriction on the upload
I just can't get enough of this
I'm going to play you a couple minutes worth
And I know you're going to immediately after the show is over
In the minute you hit a computer, you're going to want to get the show link from
DailySourceCode.com, you'll love it
Are you real concerned about this global warming?
I'm only concerned about the incredible frenzy and hype
For something that's a total myth
That concerns me a lot
Because people are going hysterical about it
It's amazing to me
How upset so many people are
And how many billions of dollars
Apparently our governments are going to spend of our tax dollars
To combat something that isn't real
That has my attention
Believe me
As a scientist, I know the global warming
Doesn't really exist at all
In any sense of significance
And that we have nothing to worry about
At this guy, I love the ways
You guys are full of shit, that's basically what he says
Are you saying that there hasn't even been any warming?
Absolutely, natural climate fluctuations
We have little ice ages, we have warm-ups
Historically, the earth has vacilated through all of these
Solar cycles change dramatically
Urgent currents change
And all of that has a significant impact on climate
And the building of cities, the flying of airplanes
The existence of all these billions of people on earth
Have all influenced the climate of earth
But none of it is a significant and thank goodness
Things are doing just fine
Oh man, I love this
Of course, the reason why this is so important is because
Based upon this report from the IPCCA division within
The United Nations and John Coleman will talk about that
I got to play it at least up to that bid for it
It's like another minute and a half in
They came out with a report, the report
To get the movie and inconvenient truth from Al Gore
And that within a span of two years has given us these
Outrages carbon taxes on anything you do
Including farting cows
This is nuts
That's why this is really important
And it's amazing that this has not been mainstream news
I mean, this is a definitely a credible guy saying this
Just as credible as anyone else I would presume
And it goes nowhere, you got to embed this video
This thing has to ask to really how many views
8,246 is like nothing
A zero views, embed this thing
We got to get this thing going viral for sure
So you're not in a panic over the iceberg's melting
And sea levels rising
I promise you, 20 years from today
I'll be the one this laughing
The icebergs, the ice caps, the poles
They're not going to mouth the oceans
They're not going to flood the coast
People are not going to die
We're not going to have global climate change
That cuts off the food supply
We're not going to have thousands of species eliminated
As they lose their habitat
Now of course not
It's all one big joke
One big joke being played on us
And the next carbon credits
This is what a plan, huh?
What a plan
I mean you almost can't, how can you even plan for something like this?
These guys must be taking advantage of a great situation
Get the report out, that must have been planned
Make it really dumb
To end lie
And force your hand in there, force your agenda
Then start to build, you know, taxes on it
Then make it virtual by making it carbon credits
And then turn that into money
That's next, you watch
None of these things is going to happen
The earth is going to, the climate is going to change
With cycles of the sun
And with ocean currents
And we're all going to do just fine
But now war has a very convincing video
Out there that seems to show that
We're really facing a content
You should see his face
He's like grimacing is going
Oh man, there's outgoer question again
It's so nice that it's not me talking about this
This is finally someone else who is very articulate here
Saying exactly what this is
Namely a scam
I'm part of all the world of the hype
The media is full of it every day
I'll grow up in Nobel Peace Prize
And Oscar and a Grammy
And apparently millions of dollars
I believe is sincere in his belief
But also misguided
As is the entire UNIPCC
The internet and governmental panel
I'm climate change
Here it is
It's a specific panel set up to deliver the report
That we have global warming
Subsequently called climate change
Because of course we're freezing our ass off
Over here in Europe
Well, that doesn't bring us to the point
That Mr. Gore makes
And many others that science has spoken
There is a universal consensus
Among scientists
So to look at the history of the IPCC
It was formed by people who's
agendas were of
Question
And they really wanted to
Get back at the industrialized nations
And get them to pay patents
To the third world nations
For their pollution of the atmosphere
They're industrialized to be
Exactly a bunch of overzealous
Greeney sitting there saying
Let's go stick it to him
But really they were programmed
They've been misused
To get to these carbon tax and carbon credits
That's what it was all for
It was the little guys picking on the big guys
For a common in the UN
And it was from people who had
A world government in mind
That history is pretty well documented
People who had world government in mind
There you go
He's saying it right there
They used it
They wanted to get to one government
World government how do you get there
You start with the money
Chuggle heads
By an engineer named Alan Cheetham
He is really dug into it
And that panel
So you create this bureau
Within the UN
On climate change
Well it's mission
And its existence then
Is to prove that there's climate change
So it starts hiring scientists
And giving them research money
To want to prove that its mission is valid
Prove its point
Exactly
And all of this
And then it's meeting
And it does publicity
And the whole thing just
Christianity and bills
Now
Was there a consensus of
2,500 scientists
At the ballet meeting
Oh, this is so important
This is so important
Listen to this
Sponsor
The key
Paragraphs
For chapters
Of this report
And the research documents behind it
Which are very impressive
Our
Not anything that we're widely read
By these scientists
They were many of them
We're political scientists as it were
We're scientists who have
A political mission
Representatives are from Greenpeace
And the Sierra Club
From government ministries
In addition to some more meaning scientists
But it appears that only about
25 scientists
Out of that
Actually read and reviewed
In a scientific manner
A peer review
The key chapter
On radio
Defourcing by carbon dioxide
Causing climate change
Okay
I could go on
I could listen to this for hours
And I really urge it
Let's embed this thing
This thing is got to go viral
This is really important
This is really really critical stuff
This is
Obviously
What is proof
But this is a very strong witness
Very strong testimony
That this whole thing is a scam
With a one-world government agenda
And we know that the name
It went from global warming
Oops, that's not working
Because it's actually cooling down
In many places
Let's just call it climate change
Well indeed
We just had one of the
I don't know if it was
Record-breaking but certainly
Uncharacteristically
Early snow
We had it just the day before
I arrived
In October
Thousands of people without power
That was a horrible accident
On the motorway here
I mean it is getting colder
You know all of this is
The just changing the words
The changing everything on us
Trying to manipulate around
The big why
And we need to call him out on it
Come on
That's a word good
On the interwebs
Aren't we calling you out
I'm going to call you out on this
Oh look
It's so cold
It's raining
We are going to go
And we got the news
We are going to listen
Get ready
Oh, you're coming
And leave us on the road
And hope
All right
It's rising
Oh
Right
I'll just get low
How low
Oh, girl
I'll just get low
So my eyes are filled
And Oh, girl
I'll just get low
Okay
I'll go
I'm going to go
After the last weekend, it's raining
Hallelujah, it's raining
Everything's not so wet
Oh, run, don't need
Don't run, don't run, don't need
Don't run, run, don't need
Don't share the same love, one, two, one
She does not care about
If you get away, see her to the floor
She's my average girl
She really is the sky
So that we can't everyone
The farmer from the sky
Who is raining again?
Hate your flap
Livin' strike, sim
And Livin''s grizzling Hey, listen
Hey, hold us get loose
One, two, one, don't run, don't run
Don't watch ya'll walk off that side
All in a circus
Places in place too, run
Oh, run, run, don't raise
Drop the ball, head back to you
I'm lost, I'm in the hands of the radio
Cause I'm on a side and I'm on a side and I'm on a side
I am lost, oh, ommm
I I'm lost, yo, I'm in the hands of the radio
I am lost, I'm in the warehouse
I am lost, yo, I'm in the front
I am lost, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh My God, I tell you, I later
I got to tell you, I was tempted, tempted to even continue listening to that interview.
While the weather girls were playing because man is such high quality, it's so awesome.
And just the way the guy talks is great.
Do yourself a favor and take a look at that.
That's a conversation I'm going to take on for a little bit longer here on the Charney.
Because it seems to be connected to a lot of other things.
Major, massive scan.
All right, let's stop the bad weather.
Part of, of course, what's going on is the big bail out.
And this is an article from New York Times that caught my attention.
I believe it was displayed on the drop from drop.io slash daily source code.
It is known as Sarah.
Jonah Sarah, sorry, from October 24th.
So a couple days ago, titled so when will banks give loans?
Oh man, you're going to love this.
Chase Manhattan recently received $25 billion in federal funding.
What effects will that have on the business side and will it change our strategic lending policy?
It was October 17th.
It's nice little story this.
Just four days after JP Morgan Chase's chief executive, Jamie Diamond.
Jamie Diamond.
Cool name.
Jamie Diamond agreed to take a $25 billion capital injection courtesy of the United States government.
When a JP Morgan employee asked that question,
it came toward the end of an employee only conference call that had been largely devoted to
meshing certain divisions of JP Morgan with this new acquisition watched the mutual.
So what's going on, this is an employee conference call.
These things take place all the time.
And a reporter got a hold of the number and called in and listened in.
And here's what was discussed.
Here's what was said in that conference call.
So this is our money.
I just want you to know what's happening with it.
All quotes.
$25 billion is obviously going to help the folks who are struggling more than Chase he began.
What we do think it will help us do is perhaps be a little bit more active on the acquisition side or
opportunistic side for some banks who are still struggling.
And I would not assume that we are done on the acquisition side just because of the
Washington Mutual and Bear Stearns mergers.
I think they're going to be some great opportunities for us to grow in this environment.
And I think we have an opportunity to use that $25 billion in that way.
And obviously depending on whether recession turns into deep pressure or what happens in the future.
You know, we have that as a backstop.
So you need to go read this article.
The article even says read that answers many times as you want.
The question being, what are going to do with the $25 billion?
You're not going to find a single word in there about making loans to help the American economy on the contrary.
At another point in the conference call, the same executive who the reporters not naming because he didn't know he was listening in makes sense.
Explain that loan dollars are down significantly.
He added, we would think that loan volume will continue to go down as we continue to tighten credit to fully reflect the high cost of pricing on the loan side.
In other words, JPMorgan has no intention of turning on the lending,
spigot whatsoever.
So one can only presume that they were just lying to us once again about what this bailout was for.
They've just all strengthened their balance sheet to the and their batting down the hatches and getting ready for what's happening next with our money.
And we're still paying $2 per transaction fees at the ATM.
It is despicable.
I'm proud of the casting.
I'm proud of this.
You say it.
It's just.
Young pole.
Hey, Adam.
Hi, doing.
You said that me having a cold edition of the latest number 145.
And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
Hi.
Morning, Mr. Radio.
That a, that, that, that.
I think it's algebra.
Morning, I think it's the title of the song.
Nice video when along with that.
Number two.
The thumb, thumb, thumb, bell stars.
Sign up at times.
Written by Prince.
I think.
Wow.
Could be.
And the final one is number three.
Boom.
Okay.
Michael Jackson want to be starting something.
Young.
A perfect mix for this footballer Friday, the Halloween edition.
I think I got six out of six stars.
It's time for the answers.
And this week they're all from.
I think I need to read it.
Just.
Yeah.
This is answer number one.
This is algebra.
Morning.
On investor radio.
On investor stereo.
Answer number one.
Algebra One.
And this is Anton number two, Bell Star.
Now hold.
I remember the question.
The sign of time.
The music.
Time to be alone.
The sign of time.
The music.
Bell Star.
It's answering number two.
And this is Anton number three.
This is Michael Jackson.
There you go.
Yeah.
One of these guys.
Got it.
He's got it.
Michael Jackson want to be starting something.
And that concludes hit this number one, four, five.
So Adam.
Yeah.
How did you do this week?
Well, I got to say young.
I got six out of six.
I'm feeling pretty good.
It was about time.
Nice mix of songs all from my air.
I appreciate it.
The answer to this hit this.
And also any other hit this.
And of course, the links for iTunes.
You can buy the tricks.
Reach it on hit this.
Online to be founded hittest.mevio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Yeah.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening.
Next week I hope to be back with another hittest.
And hopefully I'll sound better.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And remember, try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
Be back.
Hit test at gmail.com.
info.
Y'all.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T-A-S-O.
Thank you.
Y'all.
And a quick reminder that we have a number of awesome deals for you.
Everything from domain names to go daddy to products from Brooksstone.com.
Budget rental car and e-music.
The best deals if you're going to buy any product that represents any of those things.
Please go to dailysourcecode.com or check out curie.com for the show notes.
And you'll see links that will give you good deals.
You can't get a better deal anywhere online.
Period.
Just to wind up talking about the financial crisis.
Which of course has been completely displaced here in the United Kingdom by the Russell Brands
of Jonathan Ross controversy.
By the way, I think the thing people might take advantage of that situation here.
Yesterday I told you how incredibly important this news is taking up 10 minutes of the top of the news
Cassie.
BBC, preempting anything about what's going on in the world, including US helicopters, killing people in Syria.
Yeah.
I think I might want to look into that one.
People have been talking about these guys who made some prank phone calls on the air.
And Jonathan Ross winds up getting suspended for 12 weeks.
And the brand guy, Russell Brand resigned.
They should have been kicked in the head for bad humor, bad comedy, a bad show.
You know, this whole Bruhahah is not necessary.
However, it does send another shockwave throughout the BBC, a hugely influential organization, of course,
because of just the sheer vastness of the authority they have in what they say and what they report.
So I think that, you know, it's very possible that people take advantage of this shock that goes through the company.
And it really, it alters the DNA.
It tightens the way I've been in these companies when these things happen.
You're very much like the Janet Jackson Super Bowl wardrobe malfunction episode, controversy.
You know, it really made everyone mind their peace and cues and their stuff that we'll not now be broadcast anymore in the BBC.
Believe me, not the comedy stuff, but other stuff.
Because it'll come down to say, hey, you know, this is not appropriate.
Or we don't do that around here or remember what happened to so-and-so.
These things do take place.
So maybe that is a part of the reason why it became such a big deal.
I don't know, because now they're talking about, you know, what is the use of the BBC?
You know, they're taking it way beyond the incident and they're taking it.
What is the reason for existence if this is the infantile crap that our money is paying for?
Fair question, of course.
But keep your eye on that ball for sure.
This is a report that I don't normally report on stuff that appears on info wars.com, Alex Jones the site.
But this is exclusive to his crew.
And I trust him enough having heard the story about how they actually obtained this information.
This is about the Rand Corporation, which I guess I think the Rand Corporation is a think tank.
They've been around for a long time. Let me just read this story.
And I'll tell you this. Well, actually it may be the synopsis first.
Apparently in the Chinese media, they are now reporting that the Rand Corporation has been and they represent the military industrial complex just to make it simple.
Or parts of it.
They've been lobbying the Pentagon to start a war with the significant enemy to save the U.S. economy.
Which, of course, is, you know, then you crank up the economy because we're making more tanks and more airplanes and more death machines.
And we sell them to all kinds of people.
Also in the McCain and Obama plans, by the way, to continue selling weapons to other countries.
Or arms dealers.
So anyway, for this, according to reports out of top Chinese mainstream news outlets, the Rand Corporation recently presented a shocking proposal to the Pentagon.
In which it lobbied for a war to be started with a major foreign power in attempt to stimulate the American economy and prevent a recession.
A fierce debate has now ensued in China about who that foreign power may be with China itself as well as with Russia,
even Japan's suspected to be the targets of aggression.
This is pretty, this is pretty amazing. If this is true, if this is really true,
we need to get some form of proof beyond info wars.com.
There is a link to a Chinese news corporation website.
We do have someone in the organization who can speak, I don't know if it's Chinese, Mandarin, whatever,
but I'm going to get my own translation done because if this is true, that really does put a whole new color over the world.
As time goes on, I realize just what you mean to me and now, not that you're near.
Promise your love that I've waited to share, and dreams of our moments together.
Call of my world with hope of hope of hope.
I don't know about you, but that worked for me, I'd qualify that story as officially scary,
and why to prepare it for this Halloween edition of the Football Friday on the Daily Source Code,
but have no fear because we're doing the right thing.
We're getting the true information out.
Collecting aggregating the mainstream news sources that never make it above the full that are buried away 16 pages deep.
Show people what's really going on in their world, and they'll wake up.
Hey, we got four years of somebody, and we'll be following every single step of the way.
I look forward to talking to all of you tomorrow at no agenda, you can find the show at no agenda.
And I do with the John C. Devore Act, until we speak again, my friends, enjoy your freedom and live your life with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation, stick it in your ear.