Now you know that Adam loves the ladies.
He's buying his ladies cars, cinema, exotic trips wherever they want to go around the world.
So all you chuckle heads of the female variety just remember, Adam has a lot of love to
share.
When the DSC 748-20 has for naked pictures, just remember a nice little wink, a cute little smile,
some sexy talk, an old Adam is very, very sweet, and he's pretty safe too.
He's getting to be an old man, share the love on the DSC 748.
This is the daily source code, the daily source code.
If you're up to run away, and all your friends always say I'm real, I didn't see him running,
and I gotta go, you're real, and still, what I don't hold on to you, you fail to stop,
and I get old for him, you messed up, and I get old again, I get old again,
you, you, you, you, you.
Once I'm all with you, and I'll tell you, on the boy I'm big and I'll be unattended.
This damn, it's your Announcer underway.
And if you feel up outside, what I grow with your better to you, that's true, I
Oh, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
you, you, you, you, you, you, you, no, you, you, me, you, no.
I, you, you, mm-hmm, you, you, you, mm-hmm, you are so bold to me, yes, yeah, good one, yeah, here better, yeah, yeahed, yeahAY,
time to go, i, that you made me someone, yeah, Duke it's just you, you, that you, you,
What I don't hold on you, you've been on the same
Can't make it all for you
You've been on the same
I think you love it all for you
Sometimes when atoms all alone
You need to love right there on the microphone
So here she is, yes, the lady Patricia
The stage you had some better than one
And with this angel from above
There's nothing that they both can do
But make your wildest dreams come true
To grab your earphones
And jam them in my head
And let the fabulous show begin
It's Adam and Patricia
Yes, Adam and Patricia
Adam and Lady Patricia
Yeah, Bonnet
Ladies and gentlemen, episode number 748
Coming to you from the curry manner
And indeed we are once again very proud
To welcome amongst her
The one and only lady Patricia
Well, thank you for having me
My darling
Hello
So happy you're here
Can you move the microphone a little bit closer?
Okay
I'm sorry about all the noises
Delays and all kinds of crap going on
Yeah
But I would fire you if you were my technician
I don't know what's going on
It's like it's some kind of noise thing
What do I hear?
Oh, I said the door
That's probably quite
I'll kick the show off with the Sarah Borg
Borgis I think it is in the broken single
I love that
In that cool
Oh
Yeah, that just got uploaded to the podcast
Music Network
See February 13 this cool though
Fantastic
I would love that song
And then I see
Can I use it?
For what?
I don't know
You want to sing it?
Well, I need some songs
Oh yes
Are you in the market for some songs, dear?
Well, I need some songs
Tell me
Tell me what's going on
Well, I think we have a performance in December
So goodbye to the mayor of Rotterdam
Uh-huh
And he requested the star sisters
Really?
Among other wonderful guests from Rotterdam
Yeah
Because you of course are officially a Rotterdamer
Oh yeah
And so
Oh, hell yeah
Yeah
May I just say how incredibly
Lucky we are to have you back on the show
Now that you are such an incredible television star
A ratings for NASA
Well, we knew that
Didn't we?
What the year ratings for NASA
Yeah, I knew that
Oh, don't want to do it
What are we going to do with him?
Well, I think you should take him off the couch
May we?
That's what he means
You want to be off the couch, baby?
Okay, good
He doesn't communicate so well
How old is he now?
15?
Yep
Oh
Yeah, that's all
Sit down
Don't go downstairs
You will follow the stairs
So how's the show going?
The show is going well
Yeah
I think we have the highest rating
Not just to let everyone know that
Yeah, you're a judge on Britain's Britain
I wish
Yeah
On Holland's Got Talent
Yeah, which is something else
It is the same show
Only it's in Dutch with Dutch talent
Yes
The quote marks
Yeah
Well, you know we're getting there
I have to say
And I've only seen two episodes and pieces of the third
And I have the third one here
The DVD
This is a pretty good talent
That's a real talent
Yeah
Yeah, because we've been through about hundreds and hundreds
We've seen hundreds and hundreds of people
Doing something
I can only imagine
That they think it's very talented
And
And then
So have way we thought
It's going nowhere
Where are the talented people
Right
That's part of the format
I mean you're supposed to say
It's a certain point
Oh my god
Do we have no talent
Is that part of what you feel in Dutch talent
No really
Yes
So it's true
It's true
But then again
The people who have no talent at all
Are actually the funniest
Right
The ones who think they have talent
Yeah
And actually have no talent
I mean that is funny
And that is wonderful to look at of course
Yeah
What's your favorite been so far?
Are you allowed to say?
No
What do you mean no?
No, no, we're not allowed to say that
But I do have a favorite
Really?
Yes, I think I do
But you're not
Are you going to tell me?
No
Really?
Not
That's not a single one
I know it will be fired
Are you kidding?
That's a different show
You're not on that one
Yes
You're fired
Yeah
Trisha pie
You're fired
Yeah
It must be a lot of fun
No
It's a lot of fun
Robert stopped it
I invited you into the studio
You can't be jumping around
I don't know what you want
He wants to sit on my lap
Seems weird
Yeah
You hold him
Okay
Yeah
Go sit here
All right
You want to be part of the conversation
What did you say?
What was the last question?
I don't know
Yeah, will you take your top off
I think was it
Was that the question?
I don't know anyone
Yeah
You were so sexy baby
Look at you
Yeah
You got your Chanel pearls
And
Yeah
Right
That's nice
That's very nice
No, we were talking about
About the show
Yeah
So
You're not going to tell me who you think you're talented
No
No, I'm not allowed to
All right
But you think you've seen the winner
Do you think you actually know who was going to win?
No
I haven't seen them all
No, no, no
Because
We end probably with six people or something
And they can do anything
Could be seeing it could be
Do you actually know how many people won up in the finals?
I think just about six
And then the people start at home
Start to vote
They can vote
Okay, that's what I like it
People will decide who's the winner
Right
I like it when people let home vote
Yeah
That makes a lot of sense
What is honest?
Well, I don't know about that
But I like it more than anything
Well, they don't know these people
Yeah
How honest can it be?
So would you like to do more of this?
Or would you like to work with children?
Children from other lands?
My platform is
I have to say you're really good
From what I've seen
A lot of these contestants
Are young
Or are completely delusional
And really think they have talent
And even though you're telling them
Honestly what you think
You're nice about it
Which is
Yeah
It's tough
That's tough to do
You don't want them to
Demotivate
Is that
It'd be demotivated
Demotivate
So especially kids
It's very important that they
Keep believing in themselves
When you can tell the parents are pushing them
On stage
Well, that's it
I think that's it
Of course
Every child wants to do something
On radio or television
Or hear the voices
Or see themselves
Oh, yeah
I just don't protect it
I dream about it
I have to protect them
Of course
Every child will love that
But they have no idea
What they
They're going through after that
And once they're there
And somebody says
You suck
You cannot do that
Right
When children come home
With a nice drawing
And you know
You don't even know what it is
And you can recognize
You're not saying
You know that's not a good drawing
That sucks
Now you can't say that
It's horrible
You cannot say that
You always say
Well
Something to build them up
Wow
That's good
Our daughter also never came home
With artwork
Well she was the one who says
Doesn't it suck
Doesn't it suck?
No actually we think it's pretty damn good
Yeah
And we thought it was good
But most of the children
Need that
You know you need to say
You jump so high
Right
And they're not coming up
Of the floor at all
Now over there was one lady
And this is now in the news
Who was really angry at you
For essentially
And not just voting her off
But I think you told her off
And she's going into
Newspapers
And she's calling up radio shows
And saying that you know
She has had a very successful career
And you guys don't know what you're talking about
Right
We never heard of her
Which is awesome
Because so good for the show
That's fantastic
Yeah
So good for the show
And she's taking her own whole
Yeah
You know she's just falling
And falling
I think it's great
Of course
That's true
You're digging your own whole
They
It's a whole
Go over here and dig a hole for me
Okay, you're digging your own grave
Yeah
You're going down to drain
Were there any more
Any more incidents like that
That that you can recall
But still has an answer
Well there aren't people because we don't know that
We don't see that
You know
Just like instant deck
Well waiting
We have here
Joling
Waiting
And he talks to them
And then
Afterwards
When I look at the show
And I'm watching the show
I can see that people are very angry
When they get off stage
And they're saying all sorts of things
About us
Yeah
I
I didn't ask them to just do
Do you want to know
Do you want to do more of this?
Would you like to do more judging
I don't know
That was the question
Would you like to do more television work
Would you like to
I mean
Obviously you're awesome
Obviously
And I think people forgot about that
I always knew it
You're married to me
Yes
That's why
But
You know that I get
I'm enslaved to you
Inventations
For other shows
But most of the time
I say no
Because I think
Why
Don't give a shit
But
If it's something
I knew this
So show
And it was a big success
And a great great Britain
And we loved it
We really enjoyed it
I like this show
Very much
I saw some of it in America
I thought it was pretty funny
But I think it's even better
We were actually a little bit addicted to it
Because we wanted to know what happened
Not just a little bit
I love these types of shows
Yeah
I love it
But how can they do these shows
So I don't want to be a judge forever
Right
Or see sometimes you are a judge
This is my first time in a show like this
And they might
You know, think
Patricia's a judge
We have to ask her as a judge
And I don't know about that
The way I look at it
With the internet
And the ability for people to put
Anything up online on YouTube
Or on Pod Show
You know, create a video
Create a song
You can put stuff on the Pod set
Music network
Anyone could do anything
Yeah
And somehow
Getting recognition for that is important
I think more and more people want the recognition
Yeah
So while there's always been a market for talent shows
Always
I mean going back to before you and I were born
Which obviously is before wood was invented
I think
I think there'll be enough room for that
I think people will be really interested
You know, the
The genies out of the bottle
You know, we now know that there's more
To media and more to music
And more to entertainment in general
Then what we see on television
Or what we've been seeing on television
That's the audience
And the people at home
Want to choose their own stars
Yeah
That's very good
So choosing their own stars
Instead of the stars being forced down
There's throat
Very good
So there could be a lot of longevity in this format
Yeah
But I think basically all you have to do is
If you see another show that you like
That is because you know these are formats
And then they can translate that and do it
And any country you want
Yeah
So
But you're really good
You're absolutely smashing
Oh, that's because you love me
That's because I'm taking all the money
To buy new airplanes
Yeah
Ah, lemon
Speaking of love before I forget
I want to mention today
Is the
14th wedding anniversary
Lisa and James are celebrating
Oh, are they?
Just listeners
Oh, listen to the show
And what's today?
Yeah, 14 years
Pretty good
Yeah
We've been together now for over 21 years
And last night it was quite a stand
No, in the 13th of May
We will be together
22 years
The 13th of May
How do you figure that?
Well, because I just found an old gender
And a diary
Yeah
And it has all sort of first things
Like gigs
And I don't know
I don't know
This is an appointment book from the 80s
Yeah, it's 1986
Oh, you maybe you could get to money
For that on the anti-rocho
And I just found it back
Because I always saved it
And you can see I have a TV show that I have to go to
On the 13th of May 1986
And that's where I met you
Actually we met you
We knew each other just from
No, no, no, because no
Being a celebrity
Which show was it?
That's boom show
No, that's not the first time
That's the first time we kissed
No, that was the first time
No, it was
It was the first time we really connected
Not true
Disagree
It was native language
Yeah, but that was only high
And I gave you a kiss
No, that's no
That's when we sat down in the cafeteria
Yeah, yeah
And we had a great talk about America
Yeah, so that was the real meaning
Yeah, but the past boom show
We actually showed each other
That we liked each other
That was the day
I showed you my rod
No, you did not
I wish you did right away
Really?
I could have saved so much time at the exhibition
Yeah, you were such a nerd
Yeah
You were such a nerd
I remember
I waited forever
I waited forever for you to kiss me
And then I said
Can I give you a kiss?
How good?
Yeah, close your eyes
And I'll give you a special spot to kiss
Yeah, no, you were not like that
No, no, no, no
I do remember at the pots boom show
That's when you did
You French kissed me
Yeah
For like a second
What?
You kissed me
And then
And then you had to leave
It was like
Take this and go home
Boy
Think about that
Maybe that would excite you
Maybe
But I had to do it
Because you were just
You can wait forever
I probably would have still waited
So
But besides going into that again
Yeah
So it's been 22 years
22 years
And of course, you get to know someone pretty good
In 22 years
And you learn a lot
And I'm sure there's all kinds of things
You figured out about me about how I work and how I
What makes me tick and what will be tick
And you're pretty simple actually
It's not a hard manual to figure out
No, I read the manual
It was pretty easy
But
Yesterday last night we actually discovered something
Or confirmed something that I'd always
Kind of suspected for 22 years
And you confirmed it
You actually came out to me
And you confirmed something
Which was really nice
Because it was okay
It was okay
After 22 years
I can still
Absolutely learn something about my partner
That even though I kind of knew what I didn't really know for sure
And it doesn't bother me because it just doesn't bother me
So we went to pick up
Christina's car yesterday
You're already last
And I gave you a list
And I lovely
Lovely
Right, so Patricia has the smart roadster
And I said, well look, let's
You drive me over there in your car
And I'll drive it home
Because it has a manual stick
She has a left hand side
Which neither of us had ever driven before
No
Which that's a whole different story
Yeah
So we're driving
And I'm giving you directions
And I say, okay turn right here
And I'm like
Turn right
Yeah, you said turn right
Yeah
It's happening already
Yeah, it's okay
So I said turn right here
And I see that she's not moving over to the right
To get into the right hand
I moved to the left
Yes
And I said, turn right
And he's like, no, you said left
Right
And I said, no, no, no, stop
Turn right here
Yeah
And I didn't think much about it
But it was really weird
But I've seen this happen a couple times
Yeah
Like just now you said no, right
You said left
I still don't know
So
So last night
We're
Before going to bed
We're talking about it
And what she says
Well
Honestly, I've had this problem all my life
And I said
Well, it totally makes sense
Yeah
If you had it since childhood
The confusion between right and left
Yeah
And because it's one of those things
You learn how you learn
I think once it's one of the first things
You learn as a kid
Left and right
This is your right hand
Is your left hand
Exactly
So
You basically came out and said
You know, you have a problem
Yeah
And how and you've known this all your life
And you kept it secret
Yeah
Are you embarrassed?
No, no, no, no
Because I have my solutions for it
Oh, oh, tell me some of the things
No, no, no, no
I'm thinking harder
And I'm saying it
Saying it out loud
I have to say it myself
In myself
Okay, right
Right
Oh my god
That's crazy
Yeah, and then I have to think about my right hand
And then I'm going right
The white
It's your way me
So you have to
Especially when somebody tells me to go right
Not when I think about it
I know exactly that I have to go to the right
Could to the left
But if somebody tells me
Next to me
If I'm going somewhere
That I don't know
I don't know the area
And they say
Well, next and then I'm going to the right
You always go left
I have to think about it
Oh, yeah, okay, right
Oh, yeah, right
And what is your little trick there?
So we have to think about it
How do you rob your mind
The hand that I'm writing with
The hand that you're writing with
So that's how I learned it
And I was three
So I'm very good at it now
But sometimes it's just
Not working
It's crazy
If I don't
You know, put some energy in it
So I immediately said that sounds like dyslexia
Yeah
And dyslexia
I'm of course I've done some research now
Typically that's associated with people mixing words up
Which by the way
When you're speaking English and Dutch
Everyone's looking dyslexia
Because the structure of the sentence
Literally is very different
Which makes it very difficult
Yeah
But I
I went online
And there's a wonderful
I think I like this
There's a wonderful website
Called the British dyslexia association
Yeah
It's a D-B-A-D
Slexia.org
You can't
Can't read it
And they have a checklist
It's called the
I think I might be dyslexic
The adult dyslexia checklist
Oh good
And so it's so
Let me see how many questions it is here
It's 20 questions
Yeah
And if you answer
Well, I can tell you
I mean, some of them are more important than other ones
Yeah
Or more important to whether you're dyslexic or not
But essentially if you answer more than nine of them
Yeah
With the yes
Then you're dyslexic
Okay
Which by the way
As far as I know
Is no big deal
It's being dyslexic
It's nothing to do with being stupid
No, that's not
You're so stupid
Yeah, no, it hasn't
Well, that's the stigma
That's why dyslexia is a problem
Because, you know, here you are
I bet you
I'll bet you a hundred
Well, dollars isn't worth it anymore
I'll bet you a hundred euros
That you've been
You have been embarrassed by this your entire life
Because you felt people might think you were stupid
I don't know
I haven't thought about it
Well, you just said it
Yeah
Oh, when I hear people say it
And I think, well, boy
They must think, yeah
He's stupid or something
Yeah
Well, let's see how stupid
I mean, how dyslexic you are
I just like to keep you on
Okay, so the first question
You just have to enter
Yes or no
Yeah
Let me get a pen here
Okay, totally
And just be honest, okay
There's no wrong answers
And we will not make fun of you too much
No, I don't care
I know you don't
Okay, first question
Do you find
Difficulty telling left from right
Sometimes
Yeah
That's it, yes
Okay
Is map reading
Or finding your way to a strange place
Confusing
Should I get a map?
Yeah, because I never know
Is upside down
Or, you know, how I have to hold it
Huh, that's a definite
Yes
Just say yes
I love this
Do you dislike reading aloud?
Yes
Yes, I do
Yep, you're ticking the boxes
Oh, this is a good
You're gonna love this
I think you're gonna get a perfect score
You're gonna get 20 questions
Do you take longer than you should to read a page of a book?
Yes
Sometimes you sit in your mind
Man, she's looking at that page
Okay, this is a good one
Okay
Oh, this is a good one
Do you find it difficult
To remember the sense of what you have just read
Yeah
Oh, man, it gets better
Patricia
Oh, cry
Do you dislike reading long books?
Yes
Well, no, here's what, is your writing difficult to read?
No, I don't think so either
No, I think so either
I think that's what I think so
But, handwriting
Do you get confused if you have to speak in public
No
No, not at all
You don't get confused there either
This is a, your whole family has this
Yeah
Do you find it difficult to take messages on the telephone and pass them on correctly?
I was hoping you were gonna be honest about that
Yeah, I'm honest
See what I'm dealing with, ladies
Get them in
See the life I have to live with
You should have people living with this lecture
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, so I don't have dyslexia necessarily
But living with people of dyslexia
Yeah, we can have
For you have Tourette, so it's a wonderful combination
Yeah, we should have a super support group
Yeah
Um, wait
Oh, this is good
When you say a long word
Do you sometimes find it difficult to get all the sounds in the right order?
Yeah
Yeah, absolutely
I turn it around a lot
When using the telephone, question number 13
Do you tend to get the numbers mixed up when you dial?
Yeah
Absolutely
Yes
Yeah
Oh my gosh
Do you find, uh, this is, oh, we can try this one
Do you find it difficult to say the months of the year
Four words in a fluent manner?
Can you do the months?
Yeah
Let's try them
Yeah, in Dutch
You can do it in Dutch one
Okay, so not that hard
No, not
Do you find it difficult to do somes in your head
Without using your fingers or paper?
I'll just put the checkmark right there
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
But I'm going to give it to you
But you're really good at it
Is it sales?
Yeah
You know exactly that's there
20% off or something
You want
Exactly
Yeah
Okay
Do you find, oh, this is interesting
Do you find it difficult to say...
Oh, I'm sorry
I'm not in the wrong one
I missed a question here
Here we go
Do you find it difficult to say the months of the year backwards?
Crap
That's, that's even hard
I've never tried that
December, November, October, September, August, July, June, May, April, March, February, January
Good
You can't do that
Do you want to try it?
No
You can do it in touch
Just try it
No, it's part of the test baby
This is science
You can say it in touch
Okay
December, November, October, August, July, June
Is that good?
No
You forgot September
Oh, September
Right again
We're not going to laugh at you
December, November, October, September, July, August, August, October
August, July, June, May, April
Do I do that?
Yeah, keep going
February, March, February, January
Do you ever tried it?
No
This was my first time
It was my first time, too
Yeah
I've never did it
Okay, so you do, you do, you do have some trouble saying
Yeah, it's a special check mark there
Do you mix up...
Patricia Curry
Yeah
makes up dates and times and miss a point. Oh, absolutely. Absolutely. I hear something else.
Here's one. When writing checks, do you frequently find yourself making mistakes?
No. Not my checks. I'm actually very good at it. Only just like you, I forget the date.
Put the date. You don't, but you don't like destroy a check once. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay. All right. Do you mix up bus numbers like 95 and 59? I never go with the bus. No idea. Okay. Let's just try the numbers.
The trim, maybe. 59 and 95. That's not fair for a Dutch person because in Dutch literally 59 would be
85. I, yeah. Which is 9. I do that a lot with my. We're age.
True, true, true, true. Did you find it hard to learn your multiplication tables at school?
I don't think I could at it. See, this is what's interesting because you do have the ability to learn certain
things and just pound them into your brain. Well, especially the very, very difficult things that
other pupils didn't get, I got it. And if it was something simple, I did it.
As far as you weren't concentrating. Okay. Let's see what you have. Like Elgobra and all those,
you know, ask you that. I couldn't do that. Yeah. I was very good. No, I was very good at it.
Really? Yeah. You had 12. So you are definitely dyslexic. Well, I don't know what that means.
I mean, so I'll just see if that means anything.
You don't have any music? For what? For saying you aren't. No, I didn't. The link with your
show you are definitely. Okay. The lady Patricia, you are definitely dyslexic. I don't know what
it means. Let me see. Let's see what they say about it. I think I might be dyslexic. Oh, that's
the checklist. So what is it? What kind of people are we? Here we go. What does dyslexia mean for me?
Everyone is different. And so we're all dyslexic people. The hello. Everybody's view before.
dyslexia is nothing to be ashamed of. Many people see their dyslexia as an advantage. Oh, really?
What is the advantage? I don't know, but dyslexic people often say it's difficult to explain
their dyslexia. Here's some of the things they say. My brain is wired differently. Yeah.
It's like my computer crashing with too much information. Yeah, that's what do I always say?
Yes, baby. This is so you. I know what I want to say, but I can never find the right words.
Yeah. I see things from a different perspective. Yeah. I have all the right ideas, but I can't
get them down on paper. No, that's not true with you. Speaking out in front of other people makes
me stumble and forget what I was trying to say. You don't have that either. Do you?
I write lyrics like, you know, like that. Like Vincent Van Gogh. Yeah, really. I have no,
no problem with that. Amazing. Isn't it amazing? Well, we are special, I guess so.
It's almost like there's something else going on in your brain. It's too occupied. Really?
Yeah, a little bit like that. But can you identify what it's like occupied with? I don't know.
The thoughts are coming in and they're probably more busier and faster than also the things that
I want to write down. If I want to write down, I skip words because my brains are already
past that. Your brains move beyond your mouth. Yeah, exactly. Connections.
Okay, well, I love you anyway. No. It really doesn't bother me. No, but if you see me on TV, I mean,
my one line is okay. So I'm thinking too fast. If your one line is awesome, absolutely. Yeah,
but that's that's what's amazing. It's kind of like my Tourette's. I can stop it when I have to
perform do something interesting. But I have bad days. I have bad days. It me too. No,
shit. Yeah, you too. Yeah. All right. You asked me to play a song and you requested one specifically.
Remember what it was last night and I said, you've come, it's for the last, so last night, I said,
you know, I wonder this test with you. I'm not going to do what you want to do it last night and
bad. I'm like, no, I'm not going to do this. Let's do it on the show and then I ask you if you want
me to play a certain song. Oh, it goes very nice with this, where we just did. Okay. What is it?
If you could read my mind. Yeah, I know what it is, but you're supposed to like say it for the audience.
It's Gordon Lightfoot. It's like football. Exactly.
Goes from a wish and well. In a castle dark or a fortress strong with change of all my feet.
You know that goes just me. And I will never be sad for you as long as I'm a ghost. You can't see.
Yeah. If I could reach all my love, what a tale of thoughts could still just like a
paper back in the home, the kind of the drugs to yourself. When you reach the heart where the heart is
come, the hero would be me. You won't read that book again because the ending just too hard to take.
I don't go away. Like a movie star who gets burned in a three-way sprint.
Enter number two. A movie queen to play the scene. No ringing, no the good things out in me.
But from now on, let's be real. I never thought I could act this way.
I've got to say it, I just don't get it. I don't know where we went wrong, but the feeling's gone and I just can't get it back.
If you could read my love, what a tale of my thoughts could still just like a note I'm holding.
I'll ghost from a wish and will, in a castle dark or a fortress strong with change of all my feet.
The story always ain't home. If you read between the lines, you'll know that I'm just trying to understand the feelings that you love.
I've never thought I could feel this way and I've got to say that I'm just don't get it. I don't know where we went wrong, but the feeling's gone and I just can't get it back.
I couldn't have said it better.
Hell yeah, from the 70s I think that is. It's beautiful.
If you could read my mind, you were just about to say something while the song was on where I stopped you.
You were talking about when you were a kid. Well, I suddenly started to think when I was before I went to kindergarten,
you know, now the children are going, you know, younger and younger when they're going. I had to wait until I was four, five, five, I guess.
And that's when you start to read. And my mom tried a little bit, but I couldn't. So when I saw the paper,
I would sit on my grandfather's last. When you were five, four, I guess. When I was reading, you know, sitting on a slap and he was reading the paper because he was always with his paper.
And I saw all those little letters and words and I thought, oh my, I'll never learn.
This is so hard. And then later on, my mom would read to me a lot. I love to listen.
And she would read all of the story. And I had all those children books and she all, she read it every night.
We were sitting in the train going to my grandmother and I had my book and I was reading page after page
loud. Somebody said, wow. Wow. Well, she's a good reader, especially for her age.
And, but it wasn't, of course, because I did it all of the memory. I memorized it. I memorized it.
Really? I every word I knew. I didn't just knew every word. And that's interesting.
People were amazed in the train that I could read. But, uh, did you, uh,
shrubber the dog is like not cooperating? No. Where you, could you, um, could you recognize if you can recall
stuff on the page that you knew that that word, like, kind of looks like this? Yeah, well, I saw
pictures next to it. So I knew that when my mom read this and that. Well, that's, that's an important
part of storytelling. So you actually learn the art of storytelling at every young age, which is
important for singing. Yes. Because wow, it's amazing that you, you know, you lyrics. I know it's
your biggest nightmare. Yeah. The, in fact, you have nightmares where you wake up the middle of the
night and I don't know. And I don't know. And you don't know the lyrics. No, I don't know which song
I don't know the words. I'd, and people are waiting looking at me. What is she going to do?
And I think I don't know. Did my it way? No, nothing. I don't recognize it. I don't know what to
sing. I don't know what to do. It hasn't actually happened ever. No, never. Okay. That's your
nightmare. Well, you can never. Baby, you can let it go because now that your secret's out,
maybe. Everybody knows, but it's amazing how both of us control our severe inadequacies and
mental disorders when necessary. I'm standing in front of thousands and thousands of people.
Or millions. So no, millions, millions and seconds and millions. But see, it's no problem at all.
So it just can be anything. Yes, you care. There's proof. You too can be 39.
And do anything you want. Yes. So I just wanted to share with you my personal feelings on our daughter
who will be taking her driving test next week. And of course, you know, I couldn't get out of it.
Well, how did all of a sudden a new car show up for her? It just didn't even have her license.
I know, but she doesn't pass her test man. I'm going to be driving in that thing. What are you doing?
If he's he doesn't want to sit on the couch.
He's jealous. He wants to be in the conversation.
Yeah, well, I'm almost done with you guys. They don't like it here.
In the studio. Maybe he is the sounds. There's no sound frequency sounds. Yeah, there is a high frequency sound in it.
Yeah, I think so. So I have to say, yes, so yesterday, because it really she needs to practice.
And the main, I can do the main point of getting the car honestly, getting it now is because we don't have a
stick shift. She has to practice with a stick shift. No one has a car that's even decent or running well enough with a stick
test. So, you know, it's an out. So anyway, it's why I buckled on that, but no problem.
So now we're going out driving with her. How does it feel for you when you're sitting next to your daughter?
Who came out of your womb and is now driving with those glasses on? She puts her glasses on.
Yeah, scary, scary. Unbelievable. They do everything so slow.
What do you mean? The last minute.
The last minute. Yeah, let's turn now. Yeah.
But I have to say, she has a lot. She exudes a lot of confidence and she's not shaken by it. That's good. That's very good.
She's not scared. I mean, my mom was a bit scared. She's going to get her big scare. That'll happen. It always does.
Yeah, we've all had it happen to us. But what's interesting for me, strawberry, stop it. What's interesting for me
is I just went through this a couple of years ago, not five or six years ago, no, seven years ago,
when I learned how to fly. And it's weird as an adult because you kind of forget what it was,
you were learning to drive. And now you have someone telling you what to do, telling you went to,
well, not brain, but essentially, but you know, more throttle or left or right or up or down or whatever.
And I think I actually, I became much calmer by having had that experience and a great
William with the wink of manners, it was a great instructor. He had me, you know, he
turned me into real. He gave you confidence, yeah. It's, uh, it's rubber. You're going to be dinner.
She likes it. She likes it all the time. What are you doing? I don't know, I'll play a jingle
while you do that. Okay. And then come back quickly.
Adam Curry was just a guy with big hair who sold his first company and thought he just
kicked back and taken easy, but he never counted on this. Adam and Patricia, the king and queen of the
manner, or just the lady and the tramp, only on the daily source code.
Okay. Well done. Well timed. Excellent. Yeah.
Anyway, so what I was saying is, um, I feel that I'm actually much calmer sitting next to her and
knowing that the hell, that's, I'm sorry, is that your publishes, publishes, publishes, publishes,
your publishes, calling and saying, uh, what does it say? Well, you might as well know where the
text message reads now. Does everybody want to know? Yes, we all want to know. What does it say?
Yes. It is the production company. Yes. Of Holland's got talent, that owns the Friday night.
Number one is twice-wise for something from what advice? Well, yeah, I helping that extra.
Also, that's extra. Coaching a little bit. Coaching who? Well, there's a lady who sings
opera and they want to know the song that I suggested. Oh, now is, is that allowed? Is that
how the rules work? Well, you can, of course. Well, but wait a minute, aren't you, aren't you
giving preference and favor to one person or another? I don't care. If she doesn't, if she doesn't.
I did see her. She was amazing. Yeah. That she was like, must have been like, you know, your age.
Yeah. Um, had a beautiful, like a, a gala dress on. And she opened her mouth and out came this voice.
And as far as I could tell, she was really spot on, um, on, um, in key. What do you call that?
She was, uh, are you saying that? But she had a nice range. Nice pitch. Nice pitch. Yeah. It was, uh,
I was lovely. She had a beautiful warmth. So what song do you want her to do? Well, I, I don't
I, I have to ask my sister. She knows. She's a classic song. Which is a key thing. Can you say it?
Can you tell me? I can call it. Can you just tell me what, just, if you were to hum the song,
do you know what song, if you're singing? You put your headphones on your head a little
just a little bit more. No, no, because I hate it. Well, then let me turn it down a little bit.
Because it's a game feedback. Okay. Oh, sorry. Uh, yeah. That's you. All right. What are you doing?
I'll ask you. On. So, uh, we are in the middle of a show. Oh, isn't it? Is it here? Here we are doing
up? It's fantastic. That's life. It's amazing. I'm, I'm so incredibly happy that you're doing that.
Mm. Not. Huh. So that we know what kind of song that
this is what the fast forward button was made for on your iPod. Okay. You were wondering.
Sing it again?
Is that Andrea, but Charlie do that one? No, I think women, women. But didn't he do that one?
It's not, but I'm sure Charlie. Andrea, but Charlie. Oh, maybe. I don't know. Have no idea.
I think I think that that was a big idea. I think that was a big idea. I think that was a big hit. Yeah. I think so.
No, no, no, no. It's the other song. No, I think that was his big hit. Remember, I invented the
internet. I think it's something with Bombini, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. All right.
Full check it out. Anyway, so, uh, with a little bit of luck, which of course is where
preparation meets opportunity. Our daughter will be driving next week. Yeah. Yeah. I know.
Okay. But I rather put her in a tank with a helmet. You know, and so I know she's safe.
Yeah, but I am doing good. And I'm doing right and doing everything, uh, you know, what I should
do. I said, yeah, but other people around you have to watch them, too. It's not only you.
It's everybody around you. You have to neat eyes everywhere. It's funny when I was
going up in America, which was very different, um, because, um, well, not, not wasn't even in America.
I did get my first license in the US when we were on like a somewhere vacation for a couple of
months when I turned 16. Yeah. Um, but it was much less of a big deal. People weren't like
really crazily concerned about my safety. It could just be my family. Yeah. But, you know,
they were more like, you know, they were all things like you know, don't drink. It wasn't as busy
as it is now. Yeah, but the cars were three times as big. Yeah, it felt you felt so safe in them.
The big cars. Yeah. You were as like tank. I think it's just perception. No, no, they have no
nose. They have no bots. They have nothing. The bag of fun. No. If they have airbags. Yeah.
Yeah. You have a much, much better chance of sliding and more accidents with young people.
I don't. There's, well, first of all, there may just be more young people. There's more news.
There's more news outlets to hear. Maybe we didn't hear from them. So I think that's pretty much
all right. I mean, the thing, you know, the only thing I told Patricia, Patricia Christina,
you get those two mixed up. So look, what you really got to do is just know where you're going.
Yeah. Drive the car and look out for all the other fucking idiots. That's really all.
I know screaming kids in your car that I was like, well, the kids don't like that. They are
much cooler. I remember even when I had first had my license, we never did that shit.
We're not going to do. No, no, no. No, we were all pretty cool. Even though we were a
rowdy bunch, we were pretty cool about that. Because we, you know, no, I disagree. But what could
happen, I told us, if you don't feel fit to drive for whatever reason, do not have someone else
drive you. No, no, you call me no matter where you are. I will come and get you no questions asked,
no repercussions, just that's the agreement. I, you know, that's it. No, no speech, no, nothing,
just call me and I'll come and, and I promise you, I'll be happy. I'll be proud of you that
you might ask her, what's going on? But that's how the system works. I make that big process and
then you go in with the knives and daggers. I'm the one that's going to get up at three in the
morning and go get her when she's tank somewhere. What she didn't until now? No, never, never.
I've never seen her any breathing. No, no, no, no. I think she doesn't like the feeling of being
well, neither do we. I mean, she is a total product of us, total product. Yeah, I don't like it either.
I like to be in control. Hell is. Stay in control. Hell, yeah. Yeah. Okay. What are you controlling me to
do now? Uh, I need to go to hell. I examine. Yeah. And I examine. Yeah. To see how my eyes are doing right now,
because I need some new glasses. Because I use my glasses on TV. I'm going to need them pretty soon.
So I need good ones. Beautiful. I need by-focals actually. Can you believe that?
Ah, yeah, you do. Yeah. I heard you. Because it's either that or it. Because yeah.
Oh, this is the age. Yeah. You know, you cannot focus. This is my moment. Yeah. This is the moment.
So I'm having my physical done on Saturday. My medical. Yep. Which is for insurance for my
pilot's license. But it also kind of tell me also longs and every time. Longs, heart, eyes,
testicles. Yeah. Everything. Blow, blow, blow. Yeah. Exactly. That's what the doctor said.
No, it's cough. Oh, cough. It's low. It's low. If the doctor says, blow to me, I'm running away.
It's actually, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's the guy who opened up the whole fucking cardiology
way. Yeah. Right. When you had your, uh, attack. So, uh, yeah. I can't really at it. It wasn't an attack,
but I had my moment. You had your moment, the gas moment. Darling, thank you so much for coming
on the program. It was nice. Is it the light? It's been way too long. It's a great show. So it's a
love to be. You're just talking. Now, that's, now that hurts me. You don't know. It's a great
show because everybody's talking about it. Everywhere I go, even when I get my, my suitcase of the
carousel. Yeah. And, uh, get with, get with, get with. Yeah. You know, guys, uh, hey, um, aren't you
lady betraying? You betray, yeah. That was a Dutch guy. Yeah. So he recognized me. What he said,
I was just listening to Adam. I love his show. Yeah. Interesting. Yeah. He was just listening to you.
Hmm. And other people in Holland. But you don't listen to him. Well, you know, I have other
things to do. What if I'm listening to you the whole day? I already listened to you to other things
for you. You're bored enough of me just here. You're bored enough? No, no, no, no, no. Anyway,
so we're going on a little trip next week. Uh, next Thursday, we're appearing on, uh, I got the, uh,
the producer sent me. Yeah. I saw a Yenset, which is, uh, which is a, uh, it's not a daily talk show.
Yes. No, that he's daily. I didn't know that. I thought it was three times a week, but it's
five days a week. Oh, wow. Really. Yeah. And it's kind of like he's a cross between Letterman
and Leno. I would say. But then a little bit, I, yeah. I think so. But we've known him for a long
time. And I love you. And younger than, yeah. But he's very funny. And I think he has our humor.
Yeah. To say the live. We all the last time we did the show. He's on the edge now and there,
but I really like that. So I'm sure they're going to cook. I'll cook all kinds of stupid shit.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm, uh, uh, Jerry. So that'll be Thursday next week. But you're afraid to go by yourself.
I know. I'm deathly afraid. I know. Because I'm not funny. I'm with you. I'm, uh, then it's fun, you know,
because then I'm not worried. This is, you know, I can just, you always very relaxed when you're
sitting next to me on couch on TV and I think, wow, he's so really dead. It's because I'm there.
Because I know that no matter what happens, you'll, you'll, I'm right behind you. Yeah.
I'm right behind you, baby. You'll take on the shrapnel. The shrapnel. You'll take,
you'll take the bullet. I know you're good at it. But you also boom, you, you parry back immediately.
Did you ever tell them that something happened around the house in America?
We'll tell them. We'll tell them. We'll tell them this time. Yeah. That's fine. I don't care.
Yeah, okay. On this show, you want to fill on TV? Yeah, no, no.
Well, it's, okay, there's two perspectives on this story, okay? So there was,
we were in New Jersey and there was some kind of racket outside.
Something very strange. It was very, it was dark. It was, uh, in the middle of the night.
And something was actually going out in suburban New Jersey where we had a house like,
you could hear somebody walk around the house. Yeah. So I said,
let's have a look. And then wait a minute. I got my shotgun. Got your shotgun. Yeah. We opened
the door. You said to me, you go. I'm right behind you. Wait a minute. And I go with my flashlight.
And you're right behind me. And he let me. Let's go first. Let me just say that's not entirely how
it happened. I was literally right behind you. But I had the shotgun in front of you. No,
Yes, I did. I had the shotgun pointing out in front of you. How old are you? In your dreams.
It's not. I, uh, I was whimpy. And I did notice it later, I thought. What a day. What was that?
I was saying front. Well, so that I could, I could shoot the guy, if he shot me. Yeah. But
I'm in front of you. Yeah, I'm very good. And what was it, a scunk? It was a big scunk. Yeah.
Good. I should have blasted that fucker out of this car. Oh, no. Oh, it's so beautiful.
All right, my darling. But anyway, you have to be a person.
No, so far we're doing this. We're good. We're good.
All right, I appreciate you coming on being so open on us. I'm sure you've helped a lot of people who are
to the test with you. I mean, I'm very successful. Don't be shy. It just goes to show.
It just goes to show. Nothing to do with it. And you're not dumb. You just have problems with left and right.
Well, I can't be dumb now. But so does everybody. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. All right, darling. Well, thank you, dear. I'm going now. Okay. Hey, huh? Yeah.
Live life with passion. Yes, I will. And enjoy your freedom. Yes. See, you don't even know. I say that every time I'm in the show.
Do you? You do. I know you do. All right, everybody. You've got it for me, probably.
Live life with passion. Tony Robbins, actually. Oh, what?
Adam at podshow.com daily source code.com. Lady Patricia, thank you so much. Well, thank you so much. Don't, don't stay away so long.
Okay. We need you on the show a little more. All right. All right.
All right, everybody. I'll talk tomorrow for the full bar Friday. Take care.