Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony
ear buds with style meets sound.
There's only two men in the world that could pull off the DSC 709, and ironically, both of
them are Adam Curry.
Confused, you won't be after the daily source code.
Keep it in hit, be out of nowhere, just when I thought I had everything, didn't recognize
a feeling, feel like a rush coming to me, yeah you were shining like a diamond, just like a
girl from a baby, your mystery is getting to me but so fast, and not a day go by, you'll
know my body, I'll take my time, I think you'll find it, not a day go by, I don't know why,
I'm gonna be out of love, I'm thinking of how to save it, I'm afraid that the gentleman
took me to me, could've stopped myself shaking, I knew I'd just spent my destiny, yeah
you were just like a angel, you were just a friend that you loved at me, you're the world
girl in a million, I never believed, I would never see, tell you not to be, and that wasn't
changed my life, and now the day goes by, no matter what I'm about, I'll take my time, I'll make you
find it, not a day go by, I don't know why, I'm gonna be out of love, I'm thinking of love, I'm thinking
of love, I'm just a friend, I'll have you find it, you were just like a angel, you
You gotta take your back
You gotta take my back
Man, I'm such a sucker for a hooky pop song
Love it
Cherry's swayed from the pop song music network
Not a day goes by
Just part of the soundtrack to our lives here
For those of you who've been listening to Charlie for...
Excuse me
More than a year or so
I love it
It's particularly that 80 sound, man
It's been filled right at home
Yep
That's...
Cousin mold
Welcome to Daily Source Code episode
Number 709 coming to you for the curry manner
And west side of G-town
That affluent suburb of Surrey
Known as Gilford
It's actually Tuesday evening
It's about 915-920
And I had to get a show out today
First of all, because I promised it's second of all
Because I really wanted to respond to this Chris Moils thing
If you've been following the weblog at curry.com
You probably saw a posting about it this morning
That Chris Moils, who's a very famous morning radio guy
Here in the UK on radio one
He was talking about me
Apparently talking shit
So we'll get to that in a minute
So it's kind of been a long day
Because I did have to go into the city
I didn't have time to do the show at the regular time
In the morning
I had to go to my new
My new tax advisors at Pricewaterhouse Cooper's
It's pretty funny
They actually have a brochure
That it's kind of like a really expensive glossy
One flip open inside type brochure
One page
International entrepreneurs
When your personal business interest cross borders
So does our tax advice
And it's really true
I've committed to my wife
And to our banker, charity
The beautiful blonde in the Netherlands
My backup wife
That I would really get PWC involved
Because what happens with the guy like me is
I'm working here, I'm working in the states
Sometimes I do something in the Netherlands
As all kinds of
Well basically everyone winds up wanting a piece of my money
And the worst, you know, because you can get credits
If you pay tax in one country, you don't have to pay in another
But if you don't set it up right
Then eventually they all come at you
And they all want the money
And I'm kind of tired to plan the games
So I committed I would get all that shit set up right
And low and behold
Recommended by the beautiful banks
In Holland
Another great looking woman
Who would be my advisor here
South African
God, I'm lucky
All right, so here's what happened this morning
I got up real early by the way
Like 630, because you know
There's this thing with the trash over here, man
First of all, we can't really leave anything out
The night before because, you know, where we live
West side, remember
The end, the foxes get into it
And so it gets thrown all across the road
So we really have to have to put the bins out in the morning
And they show up really unpredictable times
So you have to pretty much, you know, have everything out
Between 7 and 730, because if you miss them then
You know, it's a whole another week
And actually want to extend that to 14 days now
I mean, that's not going to be a trash problem here
There already is a trash problem actually
So anyway, so
I'm up and about around, you know, 730, whatever
Upstairs, looking at email, drinking a cup of tea
And I start getting emails from people saying
A Christmas just talked about you about 715
And, you know, and so I blogged about it
And wanted to know if anyone had, you know, had found
Obviously, I didn't expect them to have a
And, you know, the podcast version up
But I was wondering if anyone had heard it
And so people started me links
And then, of course, the official
A historian of the daily source code, Tom Schuiting
Clawgwag from Down Under
He of course found it
Spotted off on to MP3 format
And sent me a link
You know, within like maybe 45 minutes of the first email I got
And he's in Australia, so I think he had to go to bed
Anyway, so
I'm really quite bummed about this situation
And this actually does prove a point
The John Devore, I can I were talking about
I know a gender recently
Where John said that he felt that
The way the internet is culturally growing
And shaping itself, they would actually
Really hurt news
And the truth and good reporting
And facts
And I've always kind of been a believer
That, you know, the truth eventually
Bubbles to the top even though I have several personal examples
Where that didn't happen
In fact, what I see more and more
Is, you know, these
This kind of spectacle of the society
Thing where we latch on to a certain mean
Build the story
Blog about it, blog about it, blog about it
Aggregate it, blog about it
And before you know it, there's pretty much
An untruth or
Certainly something taken out of context
That is grown beyond proportion of what it was to begin with
And that's actually how all of this started
When I think about
Was it maybe three quarters of a year ago or so
Maybe even longer
I think it was like Chris Moiles
I did go back to the episodes
I don't want to play that original episode
Because there are a couple of bits and bytes I want you to hear
And particularly with Chris Moiles said about me this morning
He's been to good amount of time talking about me
Which in a way, of course, is quite flattering
Anyway
There was something that he had said about podcasting
And then, you know, I went through that
All day and there were a couple comments and people said
Some people said he was a wanker
And, you know, there was all these different opinions
Which pretty much were based on
Memology, if you will
Or just stuff that's out there
And, well, I'll let Chris Moiles explain it the way he explained it this morning
It's kind of weird because this happened so long ago
I've forgotten the entire incident
And this is now just only now bubbling to the top
Of course, because someone stumbled across this
That knows Chris Moile
Or email the two of them or whatever and said
Dude, you got to listen to this guy
And, you know, so he did some research
But not enough and
Well, you'll, I'm bummed about it
You'll find out why after, after we listen to this bit
Erred this morning
I'm BBC radio one
So, let me just get something I'm going to put in
I'm going to name
Oh, I just great thing yesterday
I've been getting a slagging on some podcast
But, like, from ages and ages ago
From, like, over year ago
And it's podcast
Oh, I don't know
I want you to want to talk about it
Just because it was a very odd thing
I stumbled across
This Adam Curry podcast yesterday
Adam Curry is the guy who's
He's often credited as a man who invented podcasts
So I came up with a podcast right
Anyway, so don't ask me how I end up in a
Because I genuinely actually can't remember
But I'm, I'm on the net and I'm kind of jumping
From thing to thing
You know, like you do
And then I end up on the net
He was, he goes surfing is what he was doing
Obviously he's putting his name into Google
And into Google blog search
And, oh, wait a minute
There's a podcast where I mentioned
Let me listen to it
This Adam Curry guy
He gave me off on one of his podcasts
Right?
And so he has all these people
Find out, go, oh, Chris Moe's an idiot
Blow, he's an American guy
That's exactly what I said
Is that there were people
Yeah, that's what people called in with
You make it sound like I'm telling people to call in and say that
Obviously, I wasn't
So that's these people
So I'm listening to this guy this
It's quite funny
He's an absolute tool
He boils my attack
Man, he flows my attack
He's an absolute
B-B-B-B-B-B-B
And what you said about him
The other day, that's just, you know, sure
And I'm like, what's going on?
I've got to say, go, that seems to be like a strand
So then I, I did it
I've been very cool
The Chris Moe, he must've spent a lot of time
Going through all that stuff
And what he calls a strand
Yes, what we call a thread, you know, this is what people do
Catch up on the show
So they can figure out where the hell this came from
Interesting, even Chris Moeils is doing it
That's some good data there
Guys, I find the podcastman
I've originally talked about it
And it's the weirdest thing because
I kind of don't really get the point
Of why he slags me off
But he's calling me a banker
No, no, no, no, no, no way
This is what people who were calling in
We're calling you
Right?
And these were all based upon, you know, people's opinions
And I think just a lot of stuff that's out there on the net
Just like you're, what's on your Wikipedia page
You know what I'm talking about
There's some, and I'm like, what?
And they play a clip from our show
On that podcast, which part of why he did that permission for?
Yeah, okay, okay, please, Chris, please
You know, this, that's very used dude
You know, they even have that in the UK
So, what are you worried about?
What are you worried about?
We're going to get the fucking BBC, you make a billion
Dollarsy, a million pounds
At least, you're doing fine and worried about that
Let's just have some fun
Yes, yeah, sure, sure, sure
But, you know, whatever
And it's from our show
From about
November, 2006 or something
Where Michelle the cleaner gets the reference
Right?
And he goes, he keeps pulling
Like the show
And yeah, like this, right?
Yeah, he's net irritating
And coming in and talking over it
And he goes, by the way, that's not cool
It's taking me out of someone's voice
Because they're from somewhere else
Because you know, Michelle the cleaner
It's not cool man
That's not cool man, it's taking me out
That's how he's saying
It's the weirdest thing
You know, here's the guy who's cleaning up your stuff
You know, I'm getting you tea, and the guy has no idea what he's talking about
You know, we've all done it
You know, when you walk into see
You might in the pub by the office
And you walk in on a conversation
And you try and join in
You can completely get the wrong idea
And that's exactly the point Chris
That's exactly what you did
You walked in on our conversation
Or strand, as we say
And you completely missed the point of it
And unfortunately, you didn't really follow the entire thread
You probably would have been quite surprised
Will you will be?
And you start plowing through and they'll go and they know what he's talking about
But it's podcast
And it's like American slugging you off as well
No, no, just praise my words
Just Brit, exactly, not me, the Brit
And at the whole point of it is
Is the fact that I've heard something to do with
I mentioned podcasts
And I mentioned this Adam Curry guy
And he just is
I think he just too podcast, which is what I've watched out now
He's got one where he just rambles on about
He's got one which is like best bits of podcasts
From around the world
He's talking about pod finder
And I'm talking about this one
And you're saying about how
I don't really understand
I've never really downloaded anything in the blah blah blah blah
Got those days when I didn't really understand
I'm because of that
Then he starts having to go up
He didn't understand it, that's exactly right
But I wasn't having to go out here
I wasn't having to laugh
I don't understand podcasts, and I'm a banker
And all this
And it's the weirdest thing
I'm banker
And do you go?
I'm sure I did not call you a banker
Yeah, I understand how it works
You know, I listen to it on my computer
Through the speakers and he goes
This guy obviously knows what he's talking
Yeah, I'm not talking about it
I'm not talking about it
As being the man who invented podcasts
The rumor is about this guy
There wasn't a rumor
I don't know how true this is
Here we go, Chris
The rumor
Okay, it is
That he
He went on Wikipedia
And edited it
So that everyone else who got credited with invented podcasts
He removed that
He was the only one left
It's crazy
So which kind of
You know
I just like that
Oh my god
Alex on the grain belt
No
They didn't
I
That's brilliant
That's how rewriting
History
Yeah
It's super exact
I invented
Correctional food
The car
Yes, that was me
And I
Anyway, so they continue slagging me off
A little bit there
And that's exactly my point
The point is
Chris, I actually like you
You know, I see on all kinds of stuff here
And you're not a bad singer either
And you seem like a pretty nice guy
And what's happened here
Is my audience
You know, picked up on a whole bunch of memes
And you know, I could play this other bit of
Of the daily source code
Why I was corrected and where I actually
Apologize
You didn't hear that part
And I said the same thing
I don't know you
But you seem like a nice guy
You know, when I've listened to your show
It's cool
You know, it's all right
And I'm a little bum
That the
You're propagating even
Stupid or shit about me
And I just want to get along
Here, let me
Talk about the episode 505
200 episodes ago
David Graham, we sent in that
Six minute long comment
Yesterday about Chris Moiles, the BBC
What they can and can't do with podcasts
He heard the call
He edited it down
To three minutes
Okay
I'm not going to play the whole thing
But listen to a little bit
You'll get the idea
Listen to the feedback you received
From your listeners about
The mention you got from Radio 1 DJ
Chris Moiles
I have to reply and make some corrections
Our response from one of your listeners
Called James made out
The Chris Moiles was against podcasting
And so no future in it
This is incorrect
Chris actively promotes his podcast
Which in turn educates the public
About podcasting
This is pretty cool that I have this archive
And then you, of course, David emailed
To me and said, please remind everyone
That we already went through this
And we went, so these are all the things
That the British caller said
About Chris Moiles
And now here's this guy correcting it
Which is the way it should be
It's part of the strand, my boy
First we'd love to do a original content
For his podcast
But BBC rules restrict him from doing so
And the following explains this
It's the new and improved podcast this week
And I'll tell you what how this works
And I don't explain to you exactly the truth
Who dug his currently loading it onto
Anyway, let me just play the bit where I punch
Do you want to bother me in the slightest
I still find it
And believe I'm finding wasting time doing this
Fucking funny
He's really funny and he's endearing in
Wait
I hate, I hate all the games
But you are a bit mean to Ali
No, to be fair
Let's just clear the sum
Yeah, there was something else
You guys called it and said that he was homophobic
So we pulled that apart as well
Yeah, what's so to speak
Anybody's sexual orientation is
I really care
How'd you know?
Hey talent though
But nothing to do with his gay
If he was bisexual, stray, acesial
Wouldn't bother me in the slightest
I'd still find him irritated with a G&G go
Yeah
My follow questions
This statement, the Chris Swerzel
It's on there
Again, which I think is untrue
The majority of time
It's Chris's guess who's swear
On there, not actually him
But again, the media headlines
It sounds like he was the one with the foul mouth
Well, there you have it Adam
You can make your mind at what you really think Chris is like
I find it interesting that listeners
Who obviously don't listen to Chris's show
Find it acceptable to comments on something
They don't listen to
I find that odd
Anyway, this has been David Graham from Dorset
England
Who some of us say has been corrupted by Chris Mos
Bruncha
Yeah, of course you're a scruncher
Not you're absolutely right
I don't know Chris Moiles
I've not listened to his show enough
So you've certainly given me a different perspective
And I appreciate it
And I'm still watching
I'm a celebrity getting me out of here
Which I think is four more nights
Anyway, so there you go
So I was corrected
And hopefully now Chris is corrected
I'm sure whoever started this strand
I will finish it
And thanks for the mention, dude
Traffic is up
And I welcome all of the Chris Moiles audience
It's really not that much difference between the two of us
Except if I don't feel like doing a show
I don't do one
But I can do it whenever I feel like doing it
And Chris has a live program
Which I have to say I'm pretty jealous of
I really like doing live radio
And you know that working on
Doing some experimenting and doing this live
Yeah, what within a couple of years may be five years
It'll be pretty normal
You'll just flip on whatever device you have
And it won't make any difference
Whether it's streaming digital bits over the air
Through some kind of wireless provider
It's all going to be blank
It's just going to be all the same
It'll really come then it'll be an even playing field
When it comes to audience share
Yeah, I got time
All right
That's it
And of as we say here
Hey Adam, this is Michael Butler from the rock and roll geek show
Banging with Butler and several other train wrecks
I just came off the road
I was playing with this band Jetboy
And we were on tour with Steven Pearcey from Rat
And this other band the anti-division opened up the show
And I brought my little video camera
And I taped the entire thing
You can watch the entire thing
Only on the plus TV that plus
What is it that the plus TV dot com
Exclusively on the place
It's an exclusive
Off from January 11th through January 18th
You will see the opening band's drummer quit
Halfway through the tour you'll see Steven Pearcey's bass player quit
You'll see us driving through
Blizzards through rain through ice
You will see groupies
You'll see strippers
You'll see all the rock and roll decadent
It sounds like the high spot
It sounds like you're there
This thing should be nominated for like a
I don't know what is it like a Pulitzer Prize or a Sundance
It's really good
You will not
It's totally spinal to have
You just point to go to the plus TV dot com
From January 11th through the 18th
It's going to repeat every night
At 11 p.m. Pacific time
Eastern time and whatever London time
That's what that Grinit's mean time
Plus TV dot com
It is called
I don't know what it's called
It's like behind the scenes of a rock and roll band
Or something like that
What a touring with Butler there you go
And stick around after that
You can see a new episode of Bangless Butler
Thanks a lot for promoting this
I really appreciate it
Hey Mike, thanks man
Yeah
I can't wait
I gotta watch that
I presume that you'll have it in your feed later on
Because I do want to keep stuff like that for prosperity
Because that's amazing
You know what?
It probably should be up for some kind of award
A betcha really rocks
Okay
A couple of comments
Come into the voice mail lines
Hi Adam, this is
Low from Merchyside
Again
You've probably been sent a link a million times
I'm just looking at a video on YouTube
By a guy called Scott Ritter
He's a UN
And he's completely
And utterly
This found in the series
That the run is a
Imminent nuclear threat
Excellent
To the American people and the country
If you just have searched on YouTube
For Scott Ritter on Iranian nuclear program
If it's a 10-minute video
I mean tell you why
They cannot
To be a threat
I mean in the first few minutes
One of the reasons it gives you is because of the centrifuges they have
Keep blowing up
Whatever they've run them
Because the uranium is contaminated
With an album and coal, malignant
But anyway, it's really interesting
And just shows what a complaint
There's a bullshit, a bullshit
And the rest of these crony's out
Anyway
Love you?
No homo
Bye
He loved you no homo
Yeah
I googled in my bookmarked it
That's got to be homework
I haven't had the time
That's pretty cool
Yeah, there's a lot of talk about nuclear
In fact, I'm amazed that
Atomic Rod, one of our savants on duty
He hasn't called in yet
Because there's a lot of talk about
Opening up nuclear plants
New nuclear plants in the UK
As a part of reducing carbon emissions
As well as just an alternative energy source
And so an old debate has been stirred up again
And it's pretty interesting to follow along
And by the way, it'll take until 2020
To bring new plants online
So yeah, it doesn't really surprise me
When I hear how long it takes just to build a couple new facilities
That Iran's centrifuge blades
Flappin' all of them blades
Somehow it just doesn't surprise me
Hey, man, this is John
Hey, John
Forlapodgeos.com
That's the real advice
But I was wondering
Gillian lives show
Wouldn't it be extremely difficult to do it without a producer
I mean, would it be possible to do a quality of life show by yourself?
I was just wondering
All right, take care
I don't know what technology is or how he's doing
I know I wouldn't be able to do it
All right
He's up to good work
And let me talk to the next show
All right, talk to you
Bye
So this is for the live stuff that I want to do
And I think I am going to try it out with talk to you
Because it seems like they have the interface that I need
Because yeah, obviously it would be nice to have a producer
Or at least a producer
And it would be nice if a producer and a phone screener
Someone who's basically taking calls
Listening to what the topic is
The person wants to discuss
Then passes that on to the producer
The producer looks at the list of stuff
You know, makes choices
Make sure that people are still on the line
Talk soon does a little pre-chat
I mean, that's how a real professional get up would work
So I think that the way I want this to work
Is if we have a chat room
Right
And I have the ability to mute and unmute people
Which is I think is what the talk show interface has
You know, then people could be saying comments
Or just writing a quick line about the topic they want to discuss
And whatever's going on
I could be following along with that
And I could probably multitask that much
Even though I'm a guy
And be able to pick the next topic
Or the next person that I would unmute
Or really bring the next caller in
So
And I really wanted to work without a producer
That's the whole point
And there's a lot of stuff
I can, you know, I'm used to doing a lot of stuff
While I'm talking
It does slow down the speech once in a while
Hey, this is Julio from New York
Julio
Under the weather myself
I just can't hear it
Well, I actually started listening to DSC707
And I heard you're concerned about trying to do a live streaming show
With a live call and whatnot
And there's a podcast that already does this called
Keepnigirl.com
I know there's an animosity between you guys
At least I'm there indefinitely
But you might want to check out their website
Try to get some experts to probably do some reverse engineering
And figure out how podcasts can implement that same technology
And get your live show going
Talk to you later
Bye
Hi, man. Thanks Julio
Yeah
I think that, you know, there's a number of people on that show
So that does make it a little bit easier to do the
The whole thing, you know, like with the producer part
And screening the calls part
So
I got no item animosity towards them
Away
I kind of like it when they get all riled up
Anyway, I love the fact that your name is Julio
Because that reminded me that there's definitely another piece
That comprises the soundtrack of our lives
Mys are all at some pole signing
When the papa found out he began to shout
The star of the investigation
It's against the law
It was against the law
I walked him out on his own
Who didn't mind me looking down
And spit on the ground every time the name gets mentioned
The papa said, oh, if I get that boy
I'm gonna stick them in the house of the tension
Well, I'm on the way
I don't know where I'm going
I'm on my way
I'm taking my time, but I don't know where
I'm about to roll
Say, the queen of corona
Say, me and Julio
Down by the school yard
I see me and Julio
I don't know where I'm going
I'm on my way
I'm taking my time, but I don't know where
I'm about to roll
Say, the queen of corona
Say, me and Julio
Down by the school yard
I see me and Julio
Say, me and Julio
Down by the school yard
I remember this the 45 actually
The vinyl single
I think it was on Holly Door
Yeah, you can kind of remember the labels
From back in the day Paul Simon, me and Julio
Down by the school yard
And I would say we could start getting used to hearing
I would say we could start getting used to hearing
That type of music played legally
In independent productions
I can totally foresee this coming
If you've been following along with the EMI story man
Those guys are in big trouble
It's front news here
The radio head, of course, left the label
I went on to arguably successfully sell
With the pay what you want model
Robby Williams and said he's boycotting
Give his album
Sir Paul McCartney says that they're full of shit
You know and really what's happened here is the credit crunch is affected EMI
And they can't secure it ties the the back catalog
Which was part of the how they were going to finance this whole deal
So it's really just a business problem
That's why they've cut 2,000 people
They need to save money
I can see what's going on there
That's really easy
Believe me, Greg Hans guy
He didn't you don't want to cut all the fruit and flowers budget
Which is a record-speak code for hookers and blow
You know, yeah it was 400,000 pounds worth of fat you cut right out
But he didn't want to really get rid of that
I had no way
I also think Robby Williams
How you get Robby Williams to hand over the goods
Yeah, it's a part of the system of their system at least
Now I predict that's all falling apart
And I think that they're going to move into independent
Promotion
You watch, it's going to happen
No doubt about it
And what promoters call on us and say hey man, we play my record
It's going to be interesting to see what happens
You watch, pay all will exist
And you know what, it'll be out in the open
And people will be cool with it
Because if they're not, they just won't listen to the shows
And it's all about the same integrity that we find on the internet
Which of course works in some ways doesn't work
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel
On this week's show we've got a review of Ratchet & Clank
Tools of Destruction for the PlayStation 3
Cypher & Filter Logan Shadow on the PSP
And I've got five copies of Ghost Squad for the Wii to give away
That's all at Gamesweasel.btpotshow.com
Alright, I'm going to wrap it up
Got another song I want to play for you
With good reason
And I just want to say fuck you Steve Jobs
Man, you've taken money out of my wallet again
Did you see the shit that they've got
Now, first of all, they upgrade the iPhone with all this groovy stuff
And they've got the SDK coming
Then this MacBook Air
Oh man, the thinnest notebook computer anywhere
And then the Apple TV, that looks positively awesome
Doesn't it?
Man, I can't wait to load up some video channels in that
That's going to be cool
That is really going to rock
So, anyway, piss me off
You know, it excites me, I just can't help myself
But I'm not going to buy a MacBook Air
I'm not going to, I'm going to wait
I just got the MacBook Pro
It's a plenty fast
I really like it, I've started to customize it the way I want it to be
And then around the time when it starts to fall apart
Then, of course, I'll do the easy Mac upgrade
And, you know, just plug one into the other
It'll transfer everything and it'll just work
If not, close it, shake it like an etchist catch
And open it and it'll work
That's a Mac
Hey, we out of Chris Copper here from Seattle
Washington Lone Time listener, call some time
And I wanted to tell you two things
The first one being that the song you played a couple of
So, let's go
I'm sure, which episode by Miss Michael thing
Called the way I am
That's fun of getting played here on local radio
And Seattle ad nauseam
I got every 20 minutes on at least one of the local stations
So, pretty cool that it's up on public music network as well
Secondly, you would ask the comment about
How to do a live show
And that's going to stop just one of the way you know
Talks to you
She used to be whatever you'd like to use this for live podcasting
Talks to you.com
Is where you can find it and
Every other show, listen to this, use it
Sounds great
So, I don't know if you're looking for more technical
This isn't that, but Talks to you.com
How's it going?
You good man?
That's a good work
Folder
Yep
Red pill
Yeah
Oh baby, no homo
All right, man, so the most important part of that message
Was of course that
Ingrid Michaelson is getting severe play
She's been on the podcast music network for a while
So, good to see you here
And over there
If you were falling
Then I would catch you
You need a light
I'd find a match
Cause I
Oh the way you say good morning
And you
Take me the way I am
If you are chilly
Here take my sweater
Your head is aching
I'll make it better
Cause I love the way you call me baby
And you take me the way I am
I'd buy your road game
When you start losing all your hair
So I'm patches
To all your tears
Cause I love you more than my could never promise
And you take me the way I am
You take me the way I am
Oh man, love that song
Ingrid Michaelson
Take me the way I am
I might play out again this week
That's a really pretty song
And it's only 2 minutes 15 seconds
And of course the question
In my mind is
What we playing it here first
Or was it mainstream first?
I mean I really don't keep up with it anymore
That matters to me
Cause just the fact that I can play it
And share it with the audience
It's great
There is one other song
I want to play for you
Kind of as a bonus coupon
Because my episode
Of pussy the musical is finally out
And this is my contribution to the project
This is snatch
There's a part of me that's thinking
When I'm with the boys out drinking
There's something special
About you, girl
If I'm not thinking about all of you
I'm sure thinking about what of you
Snatch
My heart belongs to you
I love you
Ever with pain
To be snatched by your love
Overwades
Snatch
Even if you don't here with me
I want to be the one who has this feeling inside of you
If you're just given a link to me
Maybe someday you will see the stage
My heart belongs to you
I love you, darling true
Some guys would probably pay
To be snatched by your love
The way I'm on
If I've been chasing you
Without too much haste
Please grow, don't think that it's in better
Sash
My heart belongs to you
I love you, darling true
Come on girl, why you say
Let me be such by your love
The way I'm on Sash
Sash
My heart belongs to you
I love you, darling true
The signal is gone
Makes me feel gay
Let me be snatched by your love
The way I'm on Sash
Sash
I love you, darling true
Good to the very last drop
Snatched from pussy the musical
If you have not yet heard pussy the musical
We're up to episode number nine
I think there's 12 or 13
Every single one of them includes an interesting song
Performed by someone you probably know
From the network and beyond
Pussy the musical.potshow.com
Words, music and all instruments played by Mark Yoshimot
Vocals by your truly and Patricia Pi
I'm backing vocals snatch
I love you, darling true
All right
I got a whole bunch of stuff stored up for tomorrow
So I'll be back with another show then
Adam and podshow.com
DailySourceco.com
Live life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Dromatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85%
With Sony's noise canceling headphones at work, home or travel
Shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones
Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good