Today's program is sponsored in its entirety by emusic.com, get 35 free songs with absolutely
no obligation at emusic.com slash daily source code.
Warning, the daily source code has been known to influence people and not necessarily in
a good way.
I am the root of all evil.
I am the root of your drinking.
There you go.
So please cautiously listen to the DSC 737 and hey, be careful out there.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying to the future.
Today's message is a solemn warning to all young people who listen to rock and roll and heavy
metal music.
Satan knows he only has a short time to deceive the earth.
So it's using music as his anti-trace tool to deceive the masses.
I'm finally beginning to unravel a bizarre and finished plot, designed by Satan's anti-Christ
system to corrupt, revert and ultimately enslave the youth of this generation.
And another one buys the dice.
Satan's satanic takeover of our youth.
I want to tell you that today, even come at the metal stuff that doesn't sound like
and has anything that could be subjective or even misleading.
I started asking God, can you show me how we're doing it?
I wanted to have proof positive.
Wayne has a song called the one buys the dust.
We have the same reaction the first service.
The kids went, oh no, not Queen.
Not another one buys the dust.
All right, music is dangerous.
Satan has planted his lyrics in the music and some of it is subliminal.
It's down at low decibel levels where you wouldn't hear it audibly.
The music at the speed that you or the high sound levels that you would regularly play.
Satan has planted his lyrics in the music.
There's another message going on below the service.
This is called subliminal programming.
But I want to say something.
I don't believe that this particular asking was intentional.
I think that this is something that Satan himself put into the music.
Play it forwards.
Another one bites the dust.
Okay, I'm going to play that for you backwards.
The next cassette we have for the new cassette in.
On this next cassette, I want you to hear the secret message.
It's over and over and over.
It's fun.
Let's play that.
You see what the secret message was?
It's fun.
I'm going to play that backwards for you once more for those of you that are stuck.
Hey man, hey man, do you say lobster dust kicking off the footballer's Friday everybody?
How did you do win?
This entire program has got to be influenced by this voicemail comment.
Hello, this is Melissa from Southwest Florida.
I just had a thought, you know, I really got into the music deal with playing this now yesterday.
I guess I listened to it this morning so I've done yesterday's, I'm going to be able to source code.
I mean, what's really cool?
Have you thought about just putting together and maybe once a week, just putting a podcast together
that just is new and are doing some music for like 30 minutes or so?
I mean, I don't listen to this very much.
I usually listen to a lot of technical podcasts.
You definitely want to come across a love, you know, a gentle man.
The more you're in a guy with some man, I really came way back when PC mag is small.
I keep this track.
I run here right here with you, not home home, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'll talk to you later.
What a great idea.
You know, I think I've done that before.
It's called full bar Friday.
That's right.
You're in the middle of it.
We're going to bring you a maximum music full bar Friday daily source code.
Episode number 737.
That means music from the soundtrack to my life, heavily influenced by the 80s.
Today, a hit test from Yon Palette, one or two calls, a couple of promos,
but we're really going to keep the music steaming through.
Here's the first song I played on a radio station ever.
I'll tell you about it after we listen to sound envisioned.
The sound envisioned.
No, no, let's take a look.
It's the color of my room.
Where I will live.
You're good.
You're fine, you're on a land.
You're just a night.
You're good.
I'm a little sick right now, waiting for you for the sound envisioned.
Nothing until my stomach beat.
Don't you wonder sometimes.
But not only was that the first 45 RPM single I ever owned.
But it's not that loud.
Not only was it the first 45 RPM single I ever owned.
It was indeed the first song I ever played on a radio station ever, of course the radio station was one that I built myself.
I built it.
Oh man, I built it all by hand and then had my mom drive me around the block to see how far my signal would reach and I just played this song over and over.
And that was it. David Bowie sounded vision.
Food bar Friday, hey everybody, my name's Adam Curry and I'm here to do nothing but entertain you today.
Jesus!
What the heck are you?
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show.
We show two soldiers a better than one with army of two.
We also try out no more heroes on the Wii.
I've got a fantastic preview of Far Cry 2, a hands-on demo in fact,
and you can be in copies of Kendem 2 for the PS3,
along with some funky t-shirts.
That's all at Gamesweasel.com.
Oh man, this is taking me back in time.
Let me see about 30 years.
Where were you when you first heard this song by the Dooby Brothers?
What a full belief on the Charlie on the football Friday.
We've never come in there when you wanted to say,
Oh, it's a real life.
We've never really was to say,
I had a place in his life.
He never meant nothing was.
As he rises through,
I'll follow you.
And everybody else will surely know.
As long as you're right now,
I've got a full belief.
He's seen the wise man has the power.
To reason the way.
The way I said I've just realized.
The way I had the power is what I had to say
The way I had to hear what악.
It started and ended
I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I don't know why, I
don't know why, I don't know what, I don't know, why,
For the Christmas Christmas26
Once upon a time.
Michael McDonald, did we rather as what a full release?
Of course, I'll play it under the educational auspices of the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
We all contribute to that soundtrack, but we each have individual and probably quite different line or notes.
I don't even remember this song so much about the first time I heard it.
It always reminds me of the Daddy of the Ratio, one of my big idols in radio, his name is Big Bad Al,
Alfred LaHarda, who passed away.
Oh, man, must be about 10 years ago now.
Well, we learned so much from him, and he was always hanging out with the Dooby Brothers,
always going off to Santa Monica, wherever they were recording,
and he had some awesome, awesome outtakes and just some great live stuff.
And I always have to think of him when I play what a full-believes.
So, I had a whole bunch of stuff that I was thinking about talking about today.
Yesterday I saw Richard Blustein's eclectic news brief number 46,
so it's the Iraq War Special.
I was like, wow, man.
I should probably talk about that.
It was really moving.
And then I thought, you know, maybe I should ask people to explain what's going on in Tibet.
And then the rumor girls saw them as well yesterday.
They had a special about menopause.
Not to myself.
I know.
I'll just keep it straight up, saw straight Charlie with them.
Oh, a little bit of messed up stuff thrown in, just to mix it up a bit.
Peace of Palace, Gary.
Do you have 30 minutes towards free?
This is Mary.
May I take your order?
Hi.
Mary.
Yes, I'd like to the order.
Is this Mr. Kelly?
Yes.
Thank you for calling again, sir.
I'm sure your national identification number is 6102049998-45-54610.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Kelly.
I see you with a 736 Montrose Corb, which you're calling for yourself on.
Are you at home?
I'm just leaving work, but I'm...
Oh, we can deliver to Bob's out of supply.
That's a 1, 7, 5 Lincoln Avenue, yes?
No.
I'm on my way home.
How do you know all this stuff?
We just got wired into this system, sir.
Oh.
Well, I'd like to order a couple of your double meat special pizzas.
Sure thing.
There'll be a new 20L charge for this, sir.
What do you mean?
So, the system shows me that your medical records indicate that you have high blood pressure
and extremely high cholesterol.
Luckily, we have a new agreement with your national health care providers that allows us to
double meat pies while I'm sure agreed away of all future plans to buy a billet.
What?
Do you agree, sir?
You can sign the form when we deliver, but there is a charge for processing.
The total of $67.
$37.
That includes the delivery search charge of $15 to cover the address to our driver of traveling through
an orange zone.
I live in an orange zone?
No, you do.
Looks like there was another robbery on Montrose yesterday.
Hmm.
You could say $48.
If you ordered our special front submarine combo picked out yourself.
Comes with tofu sticks that are very tasty, sir.
Good value, too.
But I want double meat.
Well, I'm sure you can afford the $67.
You just bought those tickets for Hawaii.
They weren't cheap, eh?
Oh.
But I see you checked out the budget beach on the library last week.
Hmm.
Up to you, sir.
All right.
I'll get the sprouts, sir.
Good choice, sir.
Got to watch that way, sir.
You're hitting the beach, ain't it?
42 inches.
Wow.
And I'd say tofu and sprouts is like required.
That's so much.
Just between you and me.
There's a $3 off coupon in this one.
Total men's fitness magazine.
Your wife, Betty, subscribe to that, right?
Anyhow.
Put that in its 1999 even.
Whoa.
Looks like you maxed out on all your credit cards.
Bring cash, okay?
Got to get credit, sauce.
I don't go in.
Your honor.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's don't give a nod.
To the hardest work in law here.
It's jersey time.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Your honor.
What do you say?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
How's it going, Adam?
It's jersey time.
The official musicologist of the Chacha.
Dude.
We've been in this game long enough.
We know exactly what's going on.
And today we have to respect our history.
The band allowed posting the song called Beaches up on the PMman on April 4th 2006.
It's one of the all-time greatest tracks ever posted to the PMman.
In fact, it's one of the songs that inspired me to become a podcaster.
Well, that band is back on the positive music network with a brand, a spanking new album.
And I got to tell you, I love it a lot.
The band is allowed.
They're out of Boston, Massachusetts, Gen D. Lowe, San Henry Bergstein.
The share the lead vocals.
They're a fantastic pot-safe band.
And I know you're going to dig this track.
Check it out.
It's fan The Fury 5.
Allow.
On.
You're for more Friday.
Crank it up.
It's burning in my belly.
And I want it at my head.
I'll read the rate before I can use it.
It's the best thing going up there.
You don't want to get worse in the coming days.
I might as well say what I would need to say.
You don't have to remember the other day.
You've started a new campaign with EMUZIC.com.
If you never say a lot of people know about EMUZIC because you can get free and clear, DRM free, MP3s.
You can purchase from EMUZIC.
We've got a lot of great offers.
I think we have the best one around.
35 free songs.
Absolutely no obligation.
You're used to keep using my checkout code or just go directly to the URL, which I'll also put in the show notes.
DailySourceCode.com, I'm sorry.
EMUZIC.com slash daily source code.
Hey, Adam, a tower green scene from New York.
I'm noticing a big lag between the time that your podcast is listed at hurried.com.
And the time that iTunes decides that it's available for me to download it.
A couple of hours actually.
Sorry, the iPhone is making the wire in duck there.
Sorry about that.
So what's the story there?
Why is Potsho taking such a long time to let iTunes feed note in its published?
Is it an iTunes problem or a Potsho problem?
Please let me know.
Especially in a couple of hours lag here.
Yeah, yeah.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Yes, that is an iTunes problem.
Although it could be spurned and spawned by a Potsho problem.
When we released V2.5, apparently a number of actually all the show sites that have a domain name maps to it.
So for instance, I have dailySourceCode.com mapped to my show page at Potsho.
So there's also a URL for the RSS feed dailySourceCode.com slash RSS.xml.
I think it is or feed.xml, whatever.
That apparently got misconfigured in the push with the new site.
So that was down for about a day and a half.
And so iTunes, I guess they have to catch up.
I'm not quite sure what happens.
So my feed wasn't available for at least a full 24 hours.
And they're catching up, but we publish immediately.
So I guess they're just slow.
Mind you, it's a big deal to be out there looking at all these feeds and aggregating them.
How do I know?
Let me see.
Because we do it too.
Hey Adam, this is another hit test and we're going to start right away with intro number one.
Bring it on.
Please, y'all.
That of course is a Harold Fultimire and Axel F from Beverly Hills Cop.
That was pretty easy.
Number two.
It sounds like Donna Summer, I feel love maybe.
And intro number three.
Adam.
I don't push any further.
Don't look any further.
Luther Vandros, for sure.
I think it's don't look any further.
Yeah, that's the thing.
And these are the answers.
Yeah.
Answer number one is from 1985.
This is Axel F by Harold Fultimire.
We're also known as that crazy frog song.
Only this is the original kid.
This is what you should be using as a ringtone on your mobile.
Can you believe your daddy actually thought this was a great song back in a day?
Axel F, Harold Fultimire.
Answer number one.
And now what was number two?
And this is answer number two from 1986.
What's this?
Oh, it's not a total lie.
That sounds like Luther.
That's how it was.
Give me the reason Luther Vandros has answered number two.
What is number three?
And this is number three.
From 1987, this is don't look any further.
Right, but it was a bite.
I'm going to take credit for Luther some time.
Let'suggish again.
Is there no way?
Max, you guys are blind, are you looking for us?
An incredible difference, listen to what I did.
What I did?
What was it, Sean?
I think I said that's what...
I have to ask for thepersa arkadaş in the works we need to do.
And that concludes hit dance.
We're number 114.
Well, so Adam, how did you do this time?
Well, kind of shitty.
I'd say 1.75 stars today.
You want to know the answers for this hit test?
You can find them at hittest.bossio.com.
And the links to iTunes you can buy distract online are there to be found as well.
Alrighty, Adam, thank you for playing.
Everyone else, thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for 115.
It's been until then.
Take care.
I'll be back.
Hittest.bgmail.com.
info.
Yon Polet.com.
J&BOLT.com.
It is the maximum music from our Friday.
This is pretty easily been part of Young's Hittest.
Now people who are...
Well, you still listen to me on Radio Despawn Amsterdam.
We'll certainly recognize this song.
I'm not even going to give you a hint.
I'll just tell you the BB and Q band Brooklyn Bronx and Queens band on the beat.
I think this is the 12 inch maxi single version.
I may cut it short.
Stand by.
I'll be back.
I'll that bring money and save.
I'll that bring money.
Today's source code concerns that doesn't have line going ahead.
I had a bit steep in San Francisco.
You were talking with a fuel about identifying future criminals by DNA.
I planned what's against San Francisco accurately predicts the future.
Have you seen the minority report?
It's the steelberg movie?
Years ago?
Better yet, have you read?
Is this your story?
Is it a space on?
I felt a dick.
It's precisely about this issue.
I can make it up.
I'll make it enough.
Are you ready for that?
Is it a big opportunity?
I'll make it enough.
It's where we call to meet.
How much of your belief is he made?
Oh, say that you hope for me.
Take it out.
Somewhere between this measure.
I know that I don't know.
From what I heard them say.
No music that they play.
It's nothing like it ever hurt for.
Once you get the dance, it's not your belief.
Because I'll really don't keep you tight.
What do you say now?
I'll make it enough.
It's a big opportunity.
Instead of saying, let it be.
How much of your belief is he made?
I'll make it enough.
It's where we call to meet.
Everybody's dancing.
Everybody's on the beat.
Are you ready for that?
Is it a big opportunity?
Everybody's dancing.
Everybody's on the beat.
Are you ready for that?
Is it a big opportunity?
Everybody's dancing.
Everybody's on the beat.
How much of your belief is he made?
And what kind of things might happen?
You're breaking up here, isn't it?
I know.
Like, I don't even know the really song that I'm going to come up.
Okay.
Welcome all great singers here to open with 44.
44, 44,
and Mary-1 Good.
Yes.
Every week,
the Outlaw Funkhouse Best,
the hit-up,
Funk, clam,
dance,
get pop bus to work clean.
Play, cast, y'all've heard it soon.
Bubble walls have rode on news from our favorite
toughest cowboy,
as he contested two stuff,
like wild-bathers,
eye-cone suits,
three tones,
full phone.
Yeser tickets,
iTunes, swank,
from a favorite man.
What's the guarantee?
She's going in,
bring up some digital pet drone,
head over to alawpunk.com
and subscribe to alawpunk Cowboys Show.
Let's spring this puppy down
just a nod shall we,
with some esoteric shit
from the soundtrack to my life.
Michael Franks,
when Slicals.
When Slicals.
The Prophet speaks
when Slicals.
The secret leagues,
the sky and falls.
The day has stopped.
The war is won.
The battle is lost.
When Slicals.
It's their team takes.
The summer breaks.
The sky and falls.
The rain begins.
At the last.
Some of the unspins.
Two inside.
From the icy aftersharp.
I've heard each turn.
Let's fly home.
Right.
You watched that phone with a set phone.
For me, you hear this worked with Dad that team.
When you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're
when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, you're the only one you've seen here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you're here, when you
The past laid lands, the sky falls
The single beats, I laugh, no doubt
And shine my shades, and contemplate the crystal blue
From will you fuck, I'm plunged into, where it's like all
Oh, ya.
Only this one is death
I am laughier, I am making my escape
And I thought it was that full of love that was that full of love
And here we are, that's my good time to keep
It's that full of love that's that full of love that's that full of love
Look how it's out, it's that full of love that's me
And I thought it was that full of love that was that full of love
When you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear the beat
And you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear
that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, when you hear that, the sound of the sound again.
I'm trying to think, I believe the album was popsicle-toes.
Certainly, that was a track on the album.
Michael Franks went SLies Calls.
This is the song that we used back in a day of the Pio치 radio station to evaluate the sound of the station
Doesn't really pump into the compressor, you know, you know what my sound is today, right?
It's it's definitely a throwback to early 80s mayonnaise FM sound. I love it. I'm a part of the whole mix
If you don't like it, well, top you're stuck with it
Oh, boy, so good to hear those songs on the soundtrack to my life. What day is it today? It's Friday
Well, just about time to wrap it up as we've moved past the 30 minutes
I kind of promised to do today, but a lot of fun just jamming out to these songs
Thanks to seekpod.com for helping me find stuff that is absolutely not available anywhere
Including iTunes also unfortunately not on e-music. However, as you know today's program is brought to you by e-music.com
Go to e-music.com slash daily source code for 35 free songs absolutely no obligation
Final thought of the week. You know, we've been talking a lot about conspiracies the government DNA cameras
Being watched big brother three strikes your out. Can I just remind us all that it is extremely
Important and you can change this at any moment no matter what's bothering you no matter if you're worried about the future
If you're worried about the economy the government in your head you can
Create happiness in one second. That's all it takes one second. Listen very close to the sound of my voice
All you have to do is live your life with passion
All right one last song and while you're thinking about how to live with your life with passion
And why do listen closely to this song
Because the words will tell you what love is really about brought to you by Chaka Khan. It's through the fire body
And that's the day and you see
You're not a trust in your heart to anyone
You tell me you're gonna play it smart
We're through before we start
Whatever that we've all been just for fun
When it's this good there's no
I want you so
High
For
But I'm not alone
Watch out that I know
I take it away
And climb down to the wall
Even through the wild
I know you're afraid of what you feel
It's still any time to feel
And I'm alone and let me drive
You took me and something new
And I can't even do
I'm not living just isn't that pretty goodbye
Where does this mean that knows I know
I need you so I'm ready to go
To limit to the wall
Watch out that I know
I can limit to the wall
To limit to the wall
Watch out that I know
I take it away
And climb down to the wall
Even through the wild
Watch out that I know
I can limit to the wall
To limit to the wall
Watch out that I know
I can limit to the wall
I know you're afraid of what you feel
It's still any time to feel
And I can limit to the wall
To limit to the wall
I am
Chuck a car
Through the fire
There's more than I'm every woman
Chuck Chuck a car
I am ready
Wow
I've had a great time
I hope you guys have enjoyed it
Because it was all about music that
Related to me
So I hope you had some fun
Great way to wrap up
The week has been a long week
Got a weekend ahead
It's a bank holiday here in the UK
So that means we can even chill out
A little bit on Monday
Or at least everyone else can
I'm sure the San Francisco office will have something for me to do on Monday
So have a great weekend
If you're listening to this during the weekend
Or maybe you're just starting the week out
And want to kick on a Monday if you're down under
Same to you
Live that life with passion
And why don't last enjoy your freedom
Another hot show podcast
Stick it in your ear
You