Delta Sierra Charley, 744.
In Britain, Vicki Barker reports on what the British are calling a national curry crisis.
Britain's very love affair with Curry is under threat.
He says peace thinking of relocating to New York.
For NPR News, I'm Vicki Barker in London.
With this, this is the daily source code, the daily source code.
For $16 million worth of airplane strapped by us, in the next generation radio content in my years.
We don't need lost deep dreams in.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
I'm guessing he's very clean.
Do you know just how bad I want to get to you?
Just so I can talk to you, I think all they're in school.
Oh my mind, every day I think about you all night.
You got me going crazy, baby, do you know what that's like?
Baby, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it.
Oh my mind, every day I think about you all night.
Did you even notice me?
I wore this dress for you.
I found out where you were tonight, so I could be here too.
I love it when you look at me.
I think I called your eye.
Wanna see what's on my mind?
Baby, I'm not sorry.
Baby, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it.
Wanna see what's in your mind?
Baby, I'm not sorry.
Baby, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it every day.
I'm going to be like, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ah, ah, ah, ah, Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
from the affluent suburb of Surrey,
known as Gilford, we're on the west side of G-Town.
In the manner up in the top,
you may hear a little bit different acoustics today,
as I spend some time over the weekend,
clean the entire joint up up here.
I actually should take a picture of this
because I've really set it up nicely.
I got really tired.
I'm using everything my MacBook Pro now
is used almost exclusively for everything I do,
but also for all of my DSE and no agenda audio production.
I got kind of tired of picking it up,
preparing stuff behind one desk
and then unplugging everything,
then moving the Mac over to the other workstation.
So what I've done now is I've set up the secondary workstation
as a complete editing, it's all clean, dedicated thing,
and I've set up my big cinema monitor,
cinema display on the desk,
and I've got my, I've got my controls,
and I've got my microphone,
everything else set up.
So I don't actually have to move anymore.
I can just kind of prep the show,
and then before you know what I can roll into,
I'll have to do is move the microphone over,
and I think it's working,
but because the mic is directed in a different angle,
you'll probably hear some different sounds
that you can pick up since we have everything,
but a soundproof booth.
Once again, streaming live on 365.com
with varying results for everybody,
that's really pissing me off.
For some reason, it's just not working.
People go to the play page, the station page,
it doesn't refresh, or even if you refresh,
it doesn't say the station is on air.
I've handed out dot PLS files,
and those expire after a certain amount of time,
it should be a hell of a lot easier.
What I have done though is I've changed the bitrate
from I was basically sending out
to 128 kilobit streaming bitrate.
I've lowered that to 96,
so that should make a lot of difference
to everybody out there.
Hey Adam, this is Kevin and Dallas Texas.
Hey, a long time listener,
man, I had a question.
I noticed today that episode of 128 live.
And I hadn't listened to yet, but I'm about to.
And I was just wondering if there's any plans
for pod showed, implement any kind of live streaming,
like you're doing with a live 365.
Just curious.
I love the show, no one will love you.
Hope you win, love your hair, all that good stuff.
Yeah, yeah, excellent.
I'll wait a bit.
No, I'll tell you, when's back at you, my brother?
Yeah, so just let me explain that,
because I also heard some people over the weekend
talking about the validity of doing something live.
It has nothing to do with a replacement of the show.
In fact, I'm just recording the show
as if I normally would, but it adds two dimensions.
Actually, one, it does not add.
It does not add a humongous additional audience
because it's kind of, you know,
look, I'm not setting this thing up at a schedule.
I'm waiting until I think, you know, San Francisco
and New York are more or less up.
Europe is available, but it may be a bad time in the afternoon.
I mean, there's no good time for any agreement
because the show is of such a global nature.
But what it does give me, it gives me the feedback loop.
That, you know, there isn't audience out there.
Of course, I've got my phone calls
and the pre-prepared bits that you guys send in.
But to actually have some feedback coming in
and I'm using Twitter and I don't want to chat room
at least not right now.
I really like the whole idea of, you know,
like a two or three minute delay before, you know,
people send something to me or do the outside,
Adam Curry on Twitter for me to, you know, pick up
on whatever comment they have.
And for some reason that timing just works,
so I'm gonna leave it that way.
But as nothing to do with, you know,
live radio or replacement of the podcast,
that's just an enhancement.
And as long as we get it working perfectly,
by the way, you know, I spend like 99 bucks a month for this.
And they just make it incredibly difficult
for people to get into it, which pisses me off.
Ah, very big day today.
My lovely bride of,
to all what is now 21, 22 years.
The Lady Patricia celebrates her birthday today.
Big deal.
The Dutch are always big on birthdays.
And it starts off, and I've said this many times before,
but it starts off the minute you wake up.
In fact, back in the day, I don't know if they still do that.
It would be quite traditional for families
to decorate the kitchen and decorate the birthday,
boy or girl's chair and hang up balloons.
And kind of make a celebration all day.
And in the evening, you know, family from far and wide
will stop by and we'll all have coffee
and sit in a circle and talk about doctors appointments.
And, well, not just doctors appointments.
We'll talk about the economy at large.
You know, kind of like this show, actually.
So lots of SMS text messages, lots of phone calls,
flowers showing up at the door.
And of course, I gave my present, which I give every single year.
She is allowed to take a full expenses trip
with her sister anywhere in the world.
I think they've chosen Venice this time.
And it's just the two of them,
and they go away for like three or four days.
They've done different locations.
They've gone to the sun a couple times,
but they'd really like to do kind of a chick thing.
So, quite happy that they're gonna go, go to Venice
and enjoy themselves.
Over the weekend, it's been a interesting week
from my wallet.
I just couldn't get around it under it
or past it anymore.
Christina needs to have a car.
Her test is coming up in two weeks.
And I promised I said, Dad, we'll get some for you know.
I even offered her the jag.
I said, look, I don't drive this thing.
Why don't she use it?
And for the one time a month, I need a car,
I'll borrow it or I'll do whatever.
Of course, that was no good.
And she'd been watching these commercial.
If you'd seen it here in the UK, it's for the Renault Clio.
It's pretty funny commercial, actually,
where there's like one of those tours of the stars,
buses is going through what I guess
it's supposed to look like Beverly Hills.
And so the tour guide says,
now look at all these wonderful homes,
the rich and famous live here
and look at all these beautiful cars they have.
And it's like, it's like 830 in the morning
or whatever.
You see everyone rolling out humurs and porches
and Ferrari's.
And then when the bus is the gone,
then one of the neighborhood inhabitants
calls the rest on his phone, he says,
okay, they're gone, we're all clear.
And everyone puts their expensive car back
in the garage and they all roll out their Renault Clio's,
which is kind of funny.
And it had some great offer,
like you get a Tom Tom Go Navigator.
They even, and I was actually quite excited about this.
I thought this is perfect.
The help my daughter understand how credit works
and how fucked up it is when you have to pay
the 99 pounds every single month
to keep your car just in your possession.
Like, obviously that hooker up with down payment
and all of that stuff.
But yeah, she should work for some of it,
at least some of the keeping it on the roadbits.
And well, that offers no longer valid.
That was only up until March 31st.
In fact, they stopped making the car all together.
So we looked at a couple others and I like these Renault's.
You know, they're kind of cute.
And then they saw a Renault Twingo,
which I've heard about,
I think it's just been introduced into Britain.
But it's been on the road in Europe, I know for sure.
And it was actually the cheapest car there
that the girls fell in love with it.
It's a very, very girly car.
And of course, the biggest feature of the Twingo
is that there's a connector for not just your iPod.
It also has a general audio connector
for any generic MP3 player.
And it has, and this was pretty cool.
It has a USB port.
So you can plug in a memory stick.
You know, just slap some songs on to your memory stick
and you can control the memory stick
or at least you can surf through the directories,
I guess, right there.
On the onboard sound system.
So anyway, so that should be shown up in a week or two.
And I'm Mr. Hero, can I say?
Let me see, what's going on?
A couple of bits of feedback from you guys.
Oh, we got a couple of sub-onts
and sub-onts in training, coming up.
And this was interesting.
This was, I kind of like this,
because whenever people try to figure out
why they listen to this show or why they listen
to any particular podcast in general,
it's always interesting to hear them struggling
to come up with a reason.
And I don't actually know if I know why it works either,
but I do know that no agenda is quickly building up
a massive audience.
This is the show that I do once a week with John Cedar-Vorac.
And in fact, the audience is coming pretty close
to rivaling the daily source code.
It just went incredibly fast.
Now, I know that a lot of that is coming through,
you know, DeVorac's circle of fans and listeners
and detractors, I'm sure, lots of them checking it as well.
But it's always fun to listen to people trying to figure out
why they listen to a show like no agenda
or the daily source code.
Yeah, it's gross from washing couldn't.
And this was named to your Monday, DSC.
And that's a reason that you'll know you'll go
in episode that, definitely a beautiful thing
that YouTube has viewing John Cedar-Vorac on a no agenda.
Start listening to about two weeks ago
on the kind of gun off my ass.
And I noticed that people go back and listen
to all the original episodes.
We're only up in number 25 so far.
But people really turn in hand.
People, I mean, like, you people, you know, you folks.
But one thing I kind of wondered was,
why don't you even listen to either of you,
especially you, I mean, I've been listening to you
for six months now.
And I'm not really a big talk soul listener,
listen up on the radio.
And just along this time, you know,
I even bought my iPods,
only for the habit, like to have all my musical in place.
I had to have to listen to a bunch of blowharts
on the radio, planned, you know,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
listen to commercials.
And I don't know.
Maybe that's what you are, a blow-hard.
Well, I can't, I'll listen to it all the way through
and be like, dude, it's just great.
I don't know, it's like a big mystery, maybe.
You know, that's not what you're here.
No, no, that is a real good point.
I believe that the interactivity of podcasting
is much bigger than anyone gives it credit for,
because of course, what everybody does.
When you listen to a show,
and it doesn't matter how long it is or how short,
you ultimately have the control
whether you're going to listen to it,
whether you're going to skip over certain bits.
I know lots of people skip through the music on this show.
I think that's a big part of it.
And by the way, that's not just for independently produce shows
like this one that goes for NPR shows as well.
You know, that's a big deal.
We don't really think about how incredibly cool it is
that you can skip ahead in your favorite radio show.
I don't know, because I saw you on Cranky Geeks
and kids say that your hair was doing all that good.
That's being said, you and the horror
looks like twins, but I'm like a 10-year delay.
You know, make that 20.
Twenty-four years old, single, like male,
go into school here at UWT.
They're here, hope you win.
Love you, meme it, and bye-bye.
Yeah, you know, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, that's a good observation.
Before I can hire like evil twins separated by not 10,
but by 20 years, he celebrated his birthday on Saturday,
by the way, didn't want anyone to know.
And I also know his real age,
which I don't think he wants anyone to know either,
but a happy belated birthday.
I was talking to a couple of people in aviation today.
It's been a week since that Cessna citation
one jet came down just near Farmbro after only
after just taking off from big and hill.
And of course, you know, this is always of interest,
not just to me, but to many people,
and you'll never hear about it in the newspaper again.
Maybe maybe maybe if the report comes out and it says,
and it states what I've heard,
and this is really horrible,
because you know, basically there's only two things that can happen
that can go wrong.
It's either maintenance,
which I would say is still 90% of all issues in aviation,
or it's pilot error, which can happen.
What I understand is that the jet took off almost empty,
with almost no fuel on board.
And that would explain why both engines quit.
That would explain the quote vibration
that the captain reported when he called in his May day,
because the jets will essentially rev up real fast
and trying to stay lit.
And particularly if there's a fadeck involved
fully authorized digital engine control,
so that could produce some kind of shuddering
or stuttering or something that seemed a bit like
what was reported as the pilot keyed the mic on his way down.
And you think about, how can that happen?
It's really quite easy.
And I think the circuits, if this is true,
and I don't want to put blame,
or say that this is the absolute truth,
is just what's circulating around in aviation circles.
This does seem to happen,
particularly when celebrities are involved.
And it's really, really sad, because you get an air cruise,
so they had a pilot and co-pilot.
They have never flown with each other,
or maybe once or twice,
they may not be an air-crew team,
particularly when you're in the game of renting planes,
or leasing, or calling up like a net jets,
or something of the like,
and so they may or may not have been all that familiar
with this particular aircraft,
probably they were.
But when you get like two celebrities,
they were two very famous former racing car drivers on board,
and you're going down to see the races.
And before you know it,
it's very easy to forget something like a fuel selector,
which seems like that would have been solvable,
if that was the problem.
But it's also possible that you actually can take off
without any fuel.
It's not the first time this has happened.
It's really, really horrible if that's where went down.
But man, so by the time the pilot had had
figured out that he had no more air speed left,
and just kind of floated down like a brick,
which is just what we call that as severely bad day
and aviation.
That's for sure.
Okay.
Let's see.
What do we got?
Oh yeah.
Christopher.
Chris laden calling in from the UK.
Adam is Chris laden here.
Suspect the terrorist.
And podcasting, you sense.
You know,
I hate Section 44.
The terrorist met 2000 with a passion.
In total,
I was detained by the police,
an impressive four times,
and as many days during my stay in London.
You know,
once he's bad enough,
he's being stopped and searched four times,
come on.
Adam, you've met me.
Since when have I been a threat to society?
Okay.
So I was a rotten kid.
All right.
Stabbing people with scissors.
But I'm not a terrorist.
Secondly,
I just wanted to let you know
that the drama of my university projects is finished.
You know,
this is the drama based on the documentary,
which you yourself greased with your appearance.
Should you want to check it out?
You can do so by going to project
elements.podshow.com
or projects.
Hi,
for an element.com.
Thanks once again, Adam.
Love you.
I mean,
it's and God save you from Section 44.
Yeah.
And I noticed something interesting over the weekend.
You probably saw that there were riots in London,
or near riots,
as people tried to extinguish the Olympic flame,
which came through London,
London,
and to run to Beijing.
This is very typical.
All these all these different cities,
and they light up torches from left to right,
and carry the flame all the way to open up the Olympic games,
just before the games actually start.
And it was amazing.
But now we had some real pissed off angry protesters.
And of course,
this is all in line with the human rights issues,
and how people are recognizing that China is suppressing Tibet.
Which turns out a lot of people live there about six or seven million.
It's amazing to me to what lengths people will go to,
to protest something like,
which is, and it's, by the way, it's a good protest.
If you want to protest,
what China's doing,
while they're hosting the Beijing Olympics,
so you want to disrupt the Olympics,
get some attention and bear us them.
So that makes sense.
But why don't we do that kind of stuff for,
the crap that's going on here at home?
You know, like,
would also read over the weekend,
the weekend's families are in crisis.
The family life is in crisis.
Binge drinking continues.
People are not even completing school.
If they're coming out,
they're total idiots.
Our freedoms are completely being taken away.
Where's the protest over that?
I find that extremely interesting.
We're willing to go the mile for other people,
but we don't seem to want to do it for ourselves.
Just one of those interesting observations
that you bump into from time to time.
Hey, we've got a new levant and training here on the Charlie.
It's a guy who's close to my heart because everybody needs a friend
who's a Jamaican living in New York.
Mr. Curry,
Jamaican in New York here.
But just want to leave a comment,
to move something that you mentioned,
near seeing on the footballer Friday.
No.
Here's what you were talking about.
There's a lot of conspiracy theory stuff going on
about the federal reserve.
Stuff that actually doesn't really matter anymore.
How it was created or why it was created.
The fact that it is is really the problem at hand.
And this whole jekyll island thing,
that is a major conspiracy theory,
but I think it's almost distraction.
You know, this word,
destruction.
This is very interesting to me.
I believe that we have been distracted from great amount of time.
Many things actually.
You know, I think the war is a distraction for the oil prices.
Hold on a second.
I'm with you on the distraction,
my friend, my Jamaican friend in New York.
But I think the war is about something else.
Distractions are more like
entertainment tonight.
That's a distraction.
Any form of mindless entertainment is a distraction.
But when it gets put on the front page of the newspaper,
continuously, like
Madeleine McCann or any wine house or Brittany Spears.
That's distracting you from the real news, obviously.
The Federal Reserve, you know, is asking for more powers.
And we are so distracted by the fact that our mortgages
are going into foreclosure.
But we can't even pay attention to the things that are happening.
You know?
Yeah, hold on.
Hold on a second.
I will say, you know,
that I think there were plenty of distractions
when we were all signing up to those mortgages, okay?
And the distraction was probably greed
and a bigger house and more stuff and more
bling.
And turn part of the distraction of what you see all around you
in the celebrity culture.
So in that regard, yeah, big distraction money.
I'm distracted by the money.
But they are putting cameras up to spy on us.
Yeah, yeah, no, no, no.
There's going on here.
No, man.
This is all a part of a master plan.
You know, there's going to be a mistake in any of this.
These people, people are planning planning all of this before
and we are just reacting exactly the way they expect us.
Hold on a second.
I'll take the tin foil hat off.
No one's forcing you to do anything, okay?
The fact that we're aware of maybe the possibility of
being some big master plan, which I think
would not be so much about the distractions in the media
would be more about implanting a chip in your arm.
If you don't, if you're not subservient to the man,
then they turn off your money and your identity.
Now, that would be a grand master plan,
who knows if it's taking place or not.
You see, they plan that as well.
Because they have decided not to educate us enough to understand
what is going on.
Yep.
No, we have to change this trend.
I don't know.
You know what I suppose is that we need to rise up against this.
Let them understand that they aren't in control.
We are in control.
Yes.
Work.
For us.
Or us.
Yes.
They work for us.
We want to shift the balance.
Yeah.
To the populace.
Let's go out of this suit.
Do you make any New York?
Yo.
Thanks for listening to today's podcast.
This podcast has been easily made with the trial version
of Uber Huster, the only one podcasting solution for the McIntosh.
www.UverCaster.com
I guess that works.
That's a way to advertise your products.
By the way, that's for the McIntosh.
If you're looking for a great solution for Windows,
haven't mentioned it in a long-time castblaster.com
and a fantastic program that I was using for many years
until I switched back to the McPlatform.
It's just something I want to take a look at.
So, do you make it in New York, Mom?
Because you are a savant and training.
You need to do a little bit of work on your microphone there.
It sounds like you were talking into your laptop,
not always given the best results.
Regardless, here is a mashup just for you.
You are cool.
I've got loads to go play.
Here we live.
Do the things you need to come.
I'm gonna fight the ball.
I still don't think I could hold me back.
I've got to go with the ball.
Even the time right behind my back.
I'm holding to myself and I because I can't forget.
I don't fall into my mind.
But I don't see your eyes.
You always keep us right there.
I don't have such moments in my eyes.
I just don't need to do that.
I still don't fall into my mind.
I just don't want to go with you today.
I don't want to hold the ball in.
I'm gonna play the things you need to come to.
I'm gonna fight the ball.
I have kind of back heavy all around.
I'm gonna play the things you need to come to.
I don't want to hold the ball.
I'm gonna fight the ball.
I'm gonna play the things you need to come to.
Dracula 77 nation army mashed up as I said by DJ not I right here on the daily source code episode number 744.
Trip time for me this week tomorrow head and off to San Francisco and I'm going back either.
I'll you to take the red eye Wednesday night or Thursday night to New York because I have a couple meetings in the city on Friday and then back to the UK more meetings next week.
It's a busy busy.
I found this awesome new site called drop dot I.
Those of you who follow the weblog at curie dot com.
Not only seen it but I've also used it.
It's a very interesting kind of like a reverse version like a file system for a hush.
I call it more like a wiki for a file system or file for files and assets.
Maybe that's better.
And essentially you can upload.
Any type of file or you can leave notes or it even has a it's own voice mail that will then you know record the the incoming messages and put them on to the.
On to the page in MP3 format and what's really cool about it is you don't.
Need to register to use it.
So there is actually no knowledge whatsoever about who you are.
Well, I'm sure there's IP addresses and stuff.
They're not, they're not claiming a big security thing, but.
You basically, you know, you said a user password and you can set an admin password and you can create a what they call a drop for.
For anything at any time.
So let's say all of a sudden I was working on a project with a couple of people I'd create a drop.
It would be it have a URL which would be drop dot IO slash.
You know project items project.
And I can and anyone can start uploading files to it.
It's it's a hell of a lot easier than.
And a lot of these files sharing services.
There's also no ads.
It automatically creates an RSS feed within closures of everything you put up there.
There's something new added.
You can have email alerts and off.
I'm really liking it.
So I'll put it into the show notes again for today.
I think there's a hundred megabyte limit, which I'll more than likely upgrade, but I'll probably start deleting some stuff that is either already being used.
Or is just too big and useless.
There's some of that stuff going up as well.
But give it a shot.
I think these guys are on something really, really cool.
I'm not quite sure how.
Well, you know, I think somehow it's going to fit into what we're doing.
I'm not quite sure yet.
Maybe when they if they decide to expose an API, it could become even more interesting.
But this whole idea of creating drops.
I'm liking.
Check it out definitely.
It's drop dot IO.
Okay.
Let's continue.
You know, actually, I wanted to mention that George Soros, the international finance year.
One of the richest men in the world.
He's he has been in the financial markets for a long, long time.
He's been all over the news.
I saw at least three different places, including the financial times.
Parkie sent me a link that I looked at this morning.
But also Maria Barda Romo interviewed him over the weekend.
And he's just been on television everywhere saying, look, a recession is coming in the US.
Not exactly sure how big it is.
And he's going to a space where I've already had my head out, which is the whole idea of derivatives.
And I've been saying that this is much, much bigger.
And it's all based on trust.
And there is no central clearing house as of yet for derivatives.
The amount of these derivatives or CDS, I think it's credit default swaps is what they're called.
That's trillions and trillions of dollars.
I mean, there could be hundreds of trillions of dollars.
There's so many.
And these are basically just trades, okay.
Where the easiest and simplest way to look at is that there's maybe a trade where you need to buy a million dollars worth of stuff in the US.
Yet you live in the UK and you have 500,000 pounds worth of pounds.
And you can swap that.
So there's no loss in the foreign exchange.
And there's all kinds of micro-micro-sized interest payments.
It's a very complicated business.
When you get out of the CDS, these default swaps, which are actually quite easy.
They're kind of like one pages that are facts back and forth.
But it's for trillions of dollars.
And he's saying that the Fed was right to bail out Bear Stearns because it's not so much the mortgage crisis.
They could not default on these trillions of dollars of derivatives.
And what he's calling for now is something that even with my limited knowledge,
I know is something we need, which is a clearing house for all of these derivatives.
You should look up what derivatives are.
I'm sure there's a Wikipedia page on it, which will probably explain it in some degree.
It's really simple in its basis.
I mean, it really is just like trading hands across the borders.
But I'm trying to keep my eye on this and see where all this is going.
Get rid of your credit cards, that's for sure.
Try to stay off the credit, try to save some money.
And of course, we've got plenty of folks out there in the chucklehead audience who are calling with interesting tidbits and information.
And indeed, some explanation about how things work.
For instance, the question that Andrew Grummit asked me last week about federal reserve banking.
Here's an answer to that one.
I wanted to give you a column for actual reserve banking.
It was interesting listening to you and Andrew talk on Wednesday, Charlie.
As you pre-owned for describing both sides of the same coin.
The way of fractional reserves or requirement works is that if you've got a hundred bucks,
you've got to keep ten bucks on books.
In the 90, you can lend out.
So, thank you, Andrew Grummit.
What ends up happening though, with this, as conventionally a thousand dollars total gets lend out.
You're right.
So, if you don't win, the way that works though is think about it.
You have to keep ten dollars on the books.
You can lend out 90.
When does that 90 dollars go?
It goes back to the bank pretty much.
You lend it up to someone that opposed it.
Now the bank can lend out another 81 dollars.
And so on and so on and so on.
Eventually, you get a multiplier.
In fact, on the dollars, and with a ten percent reserve requirement, you get a ten-time multiplier.
Um, five percent reserve requirement, or do you get twenty-time multiplier.
So, that's pretty much how that works.
Um, an information in the gold standard.
You're not going to get to that in a minute.
Uh, um, people write paid speed assertations on stuff like that.
So, you know, we're going to open up over the weekend.
Other than that, uh, let me read it.
Hope you win.
Yeah.
I'll talk to you later.
Right on.
Okay.
That makes a lot of sense, of course.
I forgot about the interest part.
Okay.
So, Grummit and I were both right.
That's pretty good.
By the way, this portion of the, uh, the Charlie, the financial portion is brought to you by AccuQuote.
And you can get, uh, great life insurance at a seventy percent discount.
Up to seventy percent, if you use my checkout code, there's two ways to get to him.
AccuQuote.com slash dsc.
Or you can give them a call at 1-800-410-7214.
Let me know if you call them, okay?
I'm trying to figure out what kind of people don't have life insurance.
But, uh, maybe none of you have life insurance.
You should have some, really.
It's not all that expensive.
And take it if you're married or you have a significant other.
It's well worth it.
And again, up to seventy percent discount through AccuQuote.com.
Now, let's run to the gold.
Hey, Adam.
This is Trace from San Diego.
And I know this you've been talking a lot about the current credit crunch and what's happening in the economy.
And I, I'm a monetary scientist.
Now, actually, a critical website to how to explain some of these basics.
I love it.
Monetary scientist.
Come on in.
Officials, Vermont.
You're close.
Does that as my friend?
We eat a better name, though.
The official monetary scientist of the Charlie.
That sounds kind of good.
Science to people.
It's called run to gold.com.
Are you into urlb.com.
And there I, on the front page, I talked about the four main risks that are associated
with cash balances and a payment risk, counter-party risk, exchange rate risk.
And I wouldn't mind to have a couple of tips.
Yeah, we'll definitely take a look at the site run to gold.com.
I wouldn't mind if you, if you gave the Charlie heads some tips on what to do with their money.
Or should we be running to the gold and forget the paper?
Performance risk.
And what we are seeing right now is risk is being reprised.
Not just with the US dollar, but with all fiat currencies.
And so these fist and disinfectant so much collapse is evaporating.
And that's what we're seeing happen in entire markets like auction rate securities, mortgage tax securities, asset-back commercial paper, etc.
It's all evaporating.
And the counter-parties, to these contracts, which is bear-sterns, they really are too big to fail.
Bear-sterns, for example, was subject to about $13.6 trillion of risk.
There you go.
The derivative contract has been entered.
So there's no way that the Federal Reserve would want bear-sterns to fail because then you have $13.6 trillion of other assets,
but no longer insured or whatnot that counter-parties failed anyways.
So I wonder how that works.
I wonder how much money you need, what percentage of that, you know,
that big trillions of dollars number do you need in reserves in order to be seen as a healthy counterparty?
Again, this is what Sauros is calling for.
He's saying, we should have a centralized system.
We need it yesterday, where the credit worthiness of these types of trades, swaps, literally, they're called swaps, like a swap meat, only with lots of money.
Where the counterparties can be guaranteed, they're not going to go out of business.
Make sense.
Now that you're explaining the vastness of this, which, of course, I was kind of already on to, wow.
All right, website runtagold.com.
Outline some of the basics on monetary policy, and I have some videos there,
but some of the leading monetary scientists in the world, like Dr. Antalpecatee and Robert Landis,
who's JD from Harvard and some of the others anyways.
I think you might find some of it helpful, and it is a complex subject.
And so I'm trying to break it down so it's easily understandable for people.
Anyways, love your hair, keep up the good work, all the good stuff, and sign it all.
Bye.
All right, man, thank you.
All right, there you go.
The official monetary scientists of the Charlie.
Oh, hold on, that's my, I see what that is.
That means my 40 minutes are over.
We'll keep it going for a little bit longer, because we've got more about the federal reserve.
But I think that this is it, this is the guy.
Much more reliable than nylon, by the way.
Here's the guy, the monetary scientist,
bringing you tips and tricks go to runtogold.com.
Hi, Adam, here's the board one.
There's taxation without representation.
That is the problem with the Fed.
By printing money, and I borrowing it at interest,
and then the Fed puts out more money, which he values the money that I already borrowed.
It isn't a sense.
He pays back to tax.
The problem is, I think it's a vote for who's on the Fed.
It's a private bank.
So, I've got no representation.
It's taxation without representation.
And that's the problem with the Fed in 60 seconds or less.
Love you, man.
Yeah.
Love it.
Folder.
Red pill.
I hear you.
I hope you wear it.
Yeah, I'll bet it.
Thank you.
Taxation without representation.
Well, I agree with that.
Because printing a more money, devalues our money,
causes inflation.
It's a hidden tax.
It is taxation without representation.
Although, of course, not officially called that.
But that's one for the cocktail parties, huh?
That's an easy way.
And under 60 seconds, what the hell is going on?
Well, you know how the Fed prints up money, whatever they want to, right?
So, that calls is inflation.
It devalues the dollars in your pocket.
That's the same as a taxation.
It's taxation without representation.
But I have another martini, please.
Hi, Adam.
This is Janice from New York.
I really thought about the conversation you've been having on the D.S.C.
About Muslims and the Netherlands.
Oh, yeah.
This is kind of heated up a little bit.
And I kind of expected that to happen.
We saw this big anticipation of, oh, the Heardveilders film is coming out
and fit another movie is what it's called.
I think there's a new re-edited version up on live league
and some other spots around the net.
I took the movie differently than the way it was explained
for instance by the prime minister of the Netherlands
who immediately, before the movie, he before he even seen the movie
when apologizing to everybody for it.
In fact, it's funny.
I saw it in reverse order.
It was up on two parts on YouTube.
And I saw a part two first, which I thought was far more interesting
than part one.
Part one is really, you know,
all these phrases from the Quran apparently translated properly.
I obviously don't know.
And then showing the real-life versions of what those pages mean,
I wasn't too interested in that.
What I was interested in was the issues of immigration
that were showing up in all the different news clippings,
which pretty much filled up part two.
So I would say that in indeed has a lot to do with the problems
of a lot more to do with immigration, as I've said before.
But now, we're seeing, I think it was at Pakistan.
There was a couple countries where, you know,
10, 20,000 people now calling for a feared builders head
on a stake, you know, boycotting Dutch products, you know, all kinds of,
all kinds of things that you don't typically get with other religions
when they're made fun of or when they're held up against the light
or when they're discussed in any form.
Except, of course, with Scientology,
those guys are probably the closest you can get to being really, really horrible.
They don't pose death threats, but I don't know what's worse.
Getting sued to oblivion or just getting shot and head.
I don't know which one I'd prefer.
You were saying that you think it's not a religious issue,
it's an immigration issue.
And I was even wondering whether it wasn't as much an immigration issue
as really an economic issue, so maybe the two spreads of conversation
you've been having on the DSC come together
when we're talking about money.
I don't know much about the Moroccan and the Netherlands,
but I would guess if they're probably poor.
Oh, I think this is exactly where it cuts.
And the same pretty much goes for the UK.
This really knows such thing as being poor in the Netherlands.
There's just no such thing.
Because it's a socialist state, it's a complete nanny state.
They take care of you from cradle to grave.
It's expected.
So lots of people who I know who have been on the dull or are,
or they can still take a vacation.
They can have a car in the driveway.
They get subsidized housing.
You know, it's not great.
It's not fantastic.
Look, you get seriously ill.
You want that to happen in the Netherlands, dude.
You know, all the shit my dad's going through.
All of the stuff my mom went through
or lung cancer, lung removal.
Everything all paid for by centralized medical care.
Governmentalized medical care, I should say.
So there really is no such thing as being poor.
And if anything, and a lot of that,
I think is the same for here in the UK.
What people say is, they come in.
They don't contribute.
And they just benefit from all of the great things
that we provide in this country.
That's exactly where it's cutting.
You see people who probably have no chance of really integrating
very well because there's no forced teaching of the language.
It's very easy to get around that to get out of it.
Big story in the Sunday Times over here about that over the weekend.
How all these, not the residency, but the citizenship tests are being
supported.
And I think that's exactly what's so irritating.
Why should someone else get great treatment if they don't appear
to actually want to contribute?
Which is a pretty human emotion, I think.
And when immigrant groups become a part of the economic fabric of a country,
then they become less interested in changing the fabric of that society.
Yeah, that's true.
If they weren't poor, it's kind of makes the problem maybe even
soluble because it's their economic status could be improved.
Then they might 48% of them might not be interested in changing the government anymore.
Anyway, this like 48% from what I understand,
don't want the current system of government.
They want a different type of law, such as Sharia law or a hybrid.
I thought Adam loves a show.
Love you.
I mean, it's so long.
Thank you, Janus.
That's appreciated.
It was another good show on the BBC on Saturday.
The big questions is what it's called.
If you live in the UK, you can see it on the BBC eye player.
Otherwise, hopefully someone uploaded that somewhere else.
We can take a look at it all hunt around.
See if it's on YouTube or Google video.
And it was a very good conversation about this.
Really open amongst a number of groups.
I think really the question was, do we have the right to offend?
Does the freedom of speech carry through?
And it's interesting because it's not that way in every country.
In Canada, there are some restrictions.
I think on free speech, you know, they're,
particularly when it comes to the multicultural society,
which seems to be working much better in Canada.
I've heard that they have this sitcom called Little House,
Little Mosque on the Prairie, and it's supposed to be really funny.
But it seems to me like they've dealt with the immigration differently in Canada.
And again, it comes down to immigration, how it's handled,
what the expectations are.
And really, you know, your government,
and you get the government you deserve.
Time and time again, you'll see,
every single nation gets the government it deserves.
No answers for you today, my friends.
Just more questions.
And here's one that was uploaded to the drop.io slash
daily source code.
Figured at my as well play and pod save for not.
It's a apology.
Not the churning.
How long is that for you?
Besides all you?
Don't you know?
Maybe it could be a while.
Even though I heard you,
I'm not good at all, I'm good at all.
I'm good at all.
I'm not good at all.
And maybe it would be a while.
Even though I was going you.
I can't find what I'm pulling down
Tonight is my favorite
The whiffs of the world
We're all silent
And then get me
I call you
And then I will call you
And then get that's life
Maybe it could be alright
Even though I hold you
If I were to touch us
And make it right
The band's name is Slings
Title of the song is Apology
Actually that was just emailed to me
It wasn't sent through the drum
I thought it was the drop
Maybe it was
Just a typical little email
Please review and consider our new single
Apology for you and your show
You can also listen to some of our other songs
Alright
Get that shit up on the podcast
Music Network, my friends
That's where you want it to be
That's where it's going to happen
That's what billboard will be writing about
In this coming week or next week
God, I hope it's a good article
Alright, everybody
Let's see
Will over the 40 minute mark
Tomorrow
No show, big big travel day
But maybe I'll get away with one tomorrow night
Which would be good for Wednesday
So somewhere
It'll be light on shows
Just because of all the traveling
But I'm taking everything with me
So it's the minute I have a
A couple of seconds to sit down
And bring you a chuck
Of course will
So ad about podshow.com
DailySourceco.com
For all of the show notes
And
Live your life
With passion
For crying out loud
You only get one
Not a dress rehearsal
And while you're at it
Enjoy your freedom
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear