What better way to start your day than with a hot cup of coffee, the financial times,
a little DSC-810.
Well, you might want to go to the bathroom first.
Here's Adam Curry and the Daily Source.
The $16 billion worth of airplanes wrapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not sticky in trees, man
I like to think I'm sighing into this shirt
Fantastic, it's a battle curry
Bibi Bumble in the stingers, Mumble who've already killed singers
Lonnie, Mac, Twang, and Eddie, he's been ring with Go and Steady
Take it easy, take me high, lie, lie, lie, lie
So far, no commotion, Boko patch, a deeper purple set
As fashion, baby, baby, gotta gotta give me give me getin' high
The same is cooking less the girl, richy balance in the story
My face, the Fuji, I'm a camera, suit your romma, lumber, richy berries
Back to Barry, white, just don't just dance and Harry
She means she me, me, Goko, puppet fence, back to Goko on the climb
And say, wow, but the baby, oh, hold me
Gotta turn it up loud, oh, oh, oh
So my ticket, oh, leave me
Roo, who lies, is it love, under ready-o-side?
I'm eating love, I'm eating love, I'm eating love
Guys, I'm cold, can't hold me
If a meme hits a clicking one of the boys,
Pockets a gift, raise a room and say, if you keep renderin'
Then tabulate your college, I'm in the air, hold the rose,
Hold the rose, hold it, hold the daddy, catchin' down in the river
Just catchin' now, I got the shivers, mungajiri, payin' for you
Bowin' while I'm merry, merry, knackin' down in the night
Trapped with guards, they inject the river, got it, goes to catch
What a lame, what's the gimme, shin' the miracles
And tell people, it's like a toss of tender bass and mushroom
I'm livin' the money, brown, that was a pick at town, kick it high
This ain't rock, but the radio's high
This ain't rock, but the radio's woo!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, unless there's no one else but there's a never a
They say rock, but they're ready, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey you, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
December 2008, getting ready to close out the year. And I'm ready for some changes in the new year.
A lot of things going on. The big move, of course, is what's top of mind. As we have the key,
we're in, well, we're still living in the manner. We have the, and by the way, final,
it's curry terrace. It just, it just sounds good. I like it. Curry court, curry square, etc.
Now, curry terrace, I like the ring to it. No illiteration. We're doing good. It's going to be
fantastic. And not just the fact that it's, that it's a great house, that the location is
surprisingly fantastic. It's just so typical of the lady Patricia. She'll find a place
now it's in Southwest London. And when we tell people, you know, SW4, they're like, huh?
Which is, it's really only right behind Chelsea when you think about it. Maybe a 10 minute cab right
away. But we don't want to live in Chelsea. We don't, there's a lot of places we don't want to live.
But, you know, we like some that has cultures, something that has the art, something that has,
let's just call it, quote, normal people instead of Russian billionaires. And I think we've
really found it. And I'm very, very excited about it. The house is just, it's going to be great
for a number of reasons. One of the big pluses, of course, is that this thing has a, an apartment
out back. So if you, uh, if you go through the, the ground floor, the SW2A, and you're in the kitchen,
which is humongous, a great kitchen with an aga, one of those fantastic stoves. You walk right
out the back. There's a little Palazzo. And right there is an apartment to converted garage, garage,
I should say. And that's where we're going to stick the teenager. So that means we get massive
privacy back in our house. Christina has massive privacy. Still nice and closely located to each other.
But my office is what I'm most excited about. I have to admit, I get the, uh, the Sutoah,
and the front of the house. So actually, I even have my own door, my own entrance if I want
and high ceiling, which means plenty of space for the light racks, which I'm planning on hanging
up. Oh, yeah, I'm going to do it right. I'm going completely minimalistic. I'm building one
19 inch rack of external gear that I just want to have because there are those moments when you need
something. So, uh, let's see what will that out. My, uh, TLA 5052 processor. I've got, uh, some dbx,
compressor gates. I've got, um, oh, uh, I've got, uh, some more processing gear. I mean, it's maybe
there's like 8 or 9 different boxes that'll just happen one beautiful 19 inch rack. All of the
wiring tucked away. When I've one mixer instead of the four that I have out here on display,
I've got a massive honk and quad dual core mega honker Mac G5 with two screens, which is going
to be used for video editing because I have to say, I knew I would really get into it once I started
and had a reason to. And I've been doing these media today segments all by myself from spreadsheet
to upload is what I say. It's been a very, very steep climb and the learning curve is still, um,
you know, I can't quite see the horizon yet, but I'm getting there. But I'm very excited because
this has given me a lot of experience and a lot of, well, a lot of licensed to mess around and,
and, uh, essentially, muck stuff up. But I am getting very close to being ready for a video program
that accompanies the daily source code. But also the daily source code. I want to change it.
Someone wrote, maybe it was on the on the drop, which, of course, is a big catalyst behind the
changes that I'd like to make in the show. And which, of course, is what the daily source code has
always been about. It's always been about change and experimenting and trying new things and
you format. Someone wrote somewhere and I can't quite find it anymore that felt a little bit like
I was in a vacuum and you're absolutely right. You know, for years now, we'd be doing
voicemails, um, running through different links. And now, of course, with the source code drop,
drop.io slash daily source code, there's enough material in here easily to do a show every single
day. But I don't, you know, yeah, I can sit here and I can, you know, pick the, the choice articles
for you to read and, uh, I can talk about them and then you respond to them one or two or three days
later. And of course, it's been incredibly difficult and just challenging time-wise, um,
because of the amount of production involved. And of course, the longer you wait between shows,
the more there is to look at, the more there is to sift through, the more there is to talk about,
which makes the show is really, really long. I know people aren't hating the longer shows.
But I'm, I'm feeling like I'm in a bit of a rut and I'm, I'm ready for a change and I do want
to talk about that with y'all today. And we're going to be playing lots of music, uh, some really
good comments that came back. The first one, this is pretty funny, uh, not just the comment,
but eight word oh man, you just sound lovely. Listen to this. Joe Adam. Yo, man,
eight word oh, where are we going from Seattle? Yo, long time, Lisa and her first shine
dropper. And I wanted to drop you a message. By the way, that is now official, uh, Charlie
vernacular. First time listener, long time dropper. Or no, first time caller, long time dropper.
Just as long as you're dropping, that's good, because during your past show, you keep
complaining about hearing the dog and you play around with your noise get and I couldn't tell
the difference. I've been here your dog and I wasn't sure if you're just, uh,
I love the way you say that. Tell the difference. I've been here your dog, man. I didn't hear
your fucking dog. And I wasn't sure if you're just going crazy. I killed the dog or the job
was processed. You're obvious. Oh, no. Here that dog barking. Anyways, just curious. Love the hair.
Eduardo, I need you to send me some jingles and shit, man. I love your voice. I love the accent.
You know, come up with some stuff and email it to me. Please, I love it. I couldn't hear your
dog. You know what? It's interesting, because I was convinced that I go to hit, you know,
I'm hearing the dog. I got my headphones on. He's not barking loud enough for me to hear it.
Through the headphones, but not through the microphone. So I don't know. But no, there's never any post
processing going on. Everything is done live to disc as it were. But Eduardo, you are officially
hired, man. Please send me some more stuff. I just love the way that sounds.
I don't agree. Well, I'm sure that Jesus was a hell of a man. If he was in the city,
don't understand. The whole thing sucks. It's all about books. If you ain't got him,
you're at a lot. A nice little Christmas getting from the super suckers.
The city coming up to a bunch of ways. Not about the change in the weather. I don't think she would say
like to get here. But we're not sick. You don't totally throw back in the bathroom. Come on, we're here.
Yeah, yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do.
Yeah, something to do.
Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do.
Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do.
Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do.
Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do. Yeah, something to do.
What they tell, why don't change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change,
why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, they said, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why not, they change, why don't they change, what don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they changed, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, it they change, why don't they change, why don't they change, why don't they change,
Super suckers, call it Christmas time, the first of what I'm sure will be many, many alternative
Christmas songs, this holiday season on the Chuck, by the way, big move date is December 29th
and 30th.
So who knows what I'm going to be doing over the Christmas holidays?
Packin' up, I guess, is what I'm doing.
So just to reiterate, I'm going minimalistic, I can already see it for me, I've got my big,
nice long desk table, I've got nothing but two monitors right in front of me, keyboard,
wireless mouse, then off to the left is where I want to have a station for my laptop, which
is where I do all my, my source code production on.
That will have its own monitor and only the two MIDI control surfaces I've been harping
about, for ever since I set up this new system, which of course is the Fader Fox.
So a little mini mixer fader, which really isn't the audio mixer, it's just a MIDI control
surface, and then the Mega Button array.
What is this?
Microsoft's Micro Module LX2, Lima X-ray 2, and that'll be it, and then the 19-inch
rack and everything else, I'm getting rid of, I'm, I'm trying to give it away, throw it
away, throw it out, we have to clean out, we already did our big storage clean out,
and boy, that was actually quite wonderful, a good rid of a lot of crap.
And so here come the new year's resolutions, I've already said that at least the stuff
I will talk about with you guys, I got plenty of things, I'm still flushing out, there's
a lot of improvements I'd like to make in life.
So I want to continue, obviously I'll be continuing these MVO today segments, I want to
get better at that, learn more about the editing process, it's funny, I'm, you know,
that have been doing this now for a couple of weeks, which means I've put in probably
over 100 hours now, a video editing time and messing around and understanding how to make
things faster, how to work faster, how to work more creatively, and now I'm watching
television, I'm seeing all these, these effects and stuff, like, oh, okay, I know how they did
that.
Oh, of course, they, they didn't make that choice, it's really kind of, I'm reborn here,
rebirthing process into video.
So that means I'm going to make my, my gear show, I'll talk to, um, MVO UK, mega producer
Rob Dolly about putting some together, so he's, he's working with me on that, and then
there's the, they work for us show, which I think could easily be a daily program, it
may not be actually on camera, but it has to be video, I want to show your government,
your officials worldwide, and the calamities they're involved in.
I mean, I'm just looking at the, uh, the front page of the financial times for today with
the mega mini reptilian, uh, what's the guy's name, Rod, Blod Jovich, I think that's
a pronounce it.
Blod, Blod, Blod Jovich, Blod Jovich, okay, he's the governor of Illinois.
He's the guy, if you have, and this is all over the mainstream news, so I'm, I'm hope
you've heard a bit Patricia heard about, and she was laughing, uh, because she's, uh, she's
seeing, she's not asleep.
I'll tell you that.
She doesn't want to wake up.
She likes living in her own little Patricia dream world, which is fine, but she's not
asleep.
So this guy is the governor.
He is the one who determines what happens with the present elect Barack Obama's Illinois
Senate seat.
That is an appointment by, um, that will be an appointment by the governor of Illinois.
And he essentially was, uh, right on the front page of the financial times here, uh,
a quote, of course, it's, uh, it's starred out for your protection, because we don't really
want you to know what words we're used, but here's the quote, not safe work.
I've got this thing that would be the Senate seat.
It's fucking golden, and I, uh, I'm not just giving it up for fucking nothing.
That's right.
He wanted ambassador ship.
He wanted some kind of, um, you know, all, all different kinds of perks and thoughts.
And he just, it was using it to make some money from self.
And this is not just one bad dude.
This is the entire system.
This is the system.
Because it's certainly the Chicago system, your future president comes out of full of corruption.
This is just the tip of the iceberg, and you know it don't hide from it.
And it's in mainstream news, but of course, you know, it'll get glossed over.
I'm sure we'll have, but is Amy Winehouse still in the hospital that'll probably take
the headlines today.
So anyway, so I'd love to do kind of a headline show.
I'm sure it can be effective in video and I'm looking forward to producing that, but the
core of my existence, not just professionally, but personally and well as well is the daily
source code.
Is the relationship that I have with you guys with the charcoal heads out there?
As it congeels and comes together on the source code drop, there is so much happening.
These are fantastic times to be talking about the world in general.
People are interested.
They're just being snowed under and hypnotized by mainstream media.
So here's the thinking that I have for this show and where I'd like to take it.
I would like to commit a minimum of an hour, five days a week.
And I'd like, we've talked about this many times, but I think it's time to really try it.
I'd just like to start, let's say, and I thought about the time as well.
If I started at three o'clock in the afternoon, UK time, I pretty much, there's a, everyone
has a possibility to, to check it out live because you'll either be, let's see, San
Francisco time would be seven a.m.
So you could actually listen to some of it at home.
If you're on your way to work, well, you're screwed.
But of course, you live on the West Coast.
You're a half, you're a whole day behind the world anyway.
New York would be much better.
You would be at work.
The United Kingdom would be after your lunch break.
Australia.
Shit, it's the weekend already.
Well, when it's three o'clock on Wednesday, here in the UK.
But I really want to do it the right way.
And here's a technical challenge, because this is what I'm racking my brain about.
Now, you know, I've got Skype hooked in and I've got the mix minus signal all set up so
that there's no echo when you're talking to me and that stuff works perfectly.
But I really need to be able to manage the call so that I can stack up two or three calls,
and I want to talk to people that'll be about what's going on in the drop.
It's what's going on in the world.
But I have to pre-screen.
And not like if I want, you know, the screening sounds wrong.
But I need to know what you're going to talk about.
I need to know what the topic is.
I got to set you up because otherwise it just becomes not fun to listen to if someone,
you know, just doesn't sound right on the air.
Can't talk, you know, we can't get the message across.
That doesn't happen all that often, by the way.
But you know, I just need to know.
Okay, we got Bob and he's got this to say, we got Russ, he's got that to say.
And gee, we might even have some women calling in when that be novel.
And of course, the whole thing would be saved as a show and would be in the feed is normal.
And you know, and I have a little better chance to really do something topical daily.
Because we need to, you know, I can know, I can no longer wait a day to talk about something
because then there's five other things that pile on top of it.
I'll just run down what what I've got for today.
And this is all, we're most of it is taken from the draw.
Actually, let me see, I say actually, but I, what I'm saying is I don't know where to start.
That's what I'm saying.
Okay, judicial watch announced its Hillary Clinton constitutionally ineligible to serve as Secretary
of State.
Well, that's an interesting one.
Although probably right in article one section six of the U.S. Constitution, it says,
no Senator or representative shall during the time for which he was elected be appointed
to any civil office under the authority of the United States, which he'll have been created
or emulments where of shall have been increased during such time.
So they actually all voted for a raise for themselves, which means technically Hillary
Clinton would not be eligible.
I'm sure a lot of people would like to weigh in on that one.
If we had to open phone lines, the World Health Organization, this link is directly
to the WHO website, Geneva, international experts have established a tolerable daily intake
better known as a TDI for melamine.
The chemical found recently incontaminated milk products.
So instead of saying, hey, stop this chemical should not be in our milk and it could be
killing people, including our children.
We'll just come up with an acceptable intake level, the TDI, we even give it a little
acronym there.
Hey, man, your TDI is no problem there for your melamine for the poison we've gotten
your food.
I mean, do you think we could talk about that?
I'm sure some of you would want to say that.
Now, the link here, melamine is just the tip of the iceberg.
This comes from natural news, putting it in the show notes.
All of these, of course, are in the show notes at dailysourceco.com, crossposted at curry.com
because you've got to read what is going on.
It will just blow you away.
Financial times is doing such a fantastic job.
And there, what are the, oops, what that was?
Well, they, uh, I love their little byline, their, their mission statement, home on
where is it?
I hear it is.
Financial times without fear and without favor.
Yeah.
And I think they actually get away with that.
Gideon Rackman is a, uh, I guess he's a columnist for the financial times.
He wrote, uh, he didn't saw Johnson Devorick post this on Devorick.org.org.
He wrote a fantastic article titled, and now for a world government.
Now remember, this is not cookie add um, this is not wacky websites.
This is the financial effing times writing about, well, actually, it's, I'll read a little
bit of it as as Gideon Rackman starts off.
I have never believed that there is a secret United Nations plot to take over the US.
I have never seen black helicopters hovering in the sky above Montana, but for the first
time in my life, I think the formation of some sort of world government is plausible.
That's how that article starts off.
Of course, is what we've been talking about for quite some time.
And it's starting to dawn on people, which is good.
But man, you know, when people say, why do they want that?
Well, you know, has this, is this the European Union thing?
No, no, this has been going on for eons.
This is what it's always been about.
But now we finally have the opportunity through the internet to communicate with each other,
to actually share these ideas and studies are now proving that people are starting to
believe news from the internet more often than they believe mainstream media news.
This is all good.
This is positive.
This is why I want to go live on a daily basis.
So here's the technical challenge that we have.
I need to have some form of basically a switchboard.
I'd like for it to be in software so that, you know, I can, I can take it on my laptop
and manage it wherever I go, which means by definition, you're looking at a VoIP system.
I know there's an open source PBX called Asterix.
It would be way too way above my head to set this thing up and configure it and get it
going.
But let me just lay out the technical specs and maybe someone out there can help me.
So I would like to be able to jack into my system.
It can be, I would love for it to be hooked in through the core audio of the Mac, which
means it has an input channel and an output channel.
Because then I can control through my own software with able to live.
I can control what I'm sending back down the line.
Okay.
So that you don't get all that echo, et cetera, et cetera.
I need to be able to stack up, say at least five calls, put people on hold and then
be able to selectively bring them in, you know, basically switch them onto the show.
And of course, it would be even better if I could conference.
That's what I really want.
And because I want to make it easier, I want people to be able to pick up the phone
and call in.
Skype, it does not work on call in.
I hear people call talk shows on Skype.
It sucks, you know, because it just it sucks and that's more, I think, a function of
the headsets people are using, then Skype itself.
So just I want you to be able to pick up the phone, okay?
And with the way bandwidth is moving and the way 3G and HSDPA modems are working, you'll
be able to listen to this thing, if it's streamed live, which is another part of the
technical equation, I need a really good, and by the way, I'll be happy to take this as
a service.
If this were like a cloud thing out there, boy, with that rock.
So the two things I need, one is a great streaming server.
And I want it to be a service.
I don't want to have to set anything up or configure.
I'm happy to pay for it.
Just so that anyone can listen to this to a live stream and has to be simple for me to
jack into.
Second one is the phone bridge.
If that were a service, oh, hallelujah, wouldn't that be fantastic?
Something I could really, really use simply because I don't have a producer here.
So the way I would do it is I'd stack up a couple calls before I start.
I get going.
I'd talk to some people.
I'd play a song.
During the song, I could take a few more calls, stack them up.
You know, that way we can, you know, really get a conversation going and really get some
real-time feedback and really get into helping each other get through the times which
will be more than challenging.
Of course, there are some snags along the way, not just the technical hurdles that I'm
looking at, but let me see.
The new world order actually wants to take down the internet.
I'm sure you've heard about this.
Adam, I always talk to you about the internet watch foundation.
I'm sure you know what it is.
I'm sure you've read that article off.
Yeah, internet watch foundation is what he said.
We're relating to it.
Basically, they are now blocking internet access for people who are on the UK's biggest
ISP.
Yeah, okay.
So if you had not heard about this, this was a big news a couple days ago.
The six big UK internet service providers are blocking access to Wikipedia, a mid-child
pornography allegations.
So of course, the fact that they're doing that means that they're super-narsheds.
You know, Virgin, what we got plus 02 I believe are doing as well as the probably includes
all 02 hand sets as well.
I'm guessing maybe I can't be sure of that one.
But you know, that we're blocking the blocking with PDF articles, which is, you know, probably
the best GPS thing to do ever.
Oh, I agree with those people, and if you don't know what I'm talking about, just Google
into our watch foundation, I'm sure you will find out, but basically, child pornography
is a disgusting thing that should be stopped at all costs, however, that does not mean
that you have the right to filter what I can do on the internet.
Oh, of course, the legal repercussions in me actually going to one of these child-porn
websites and you know, download your watch in the material, and best, you know, the police
provides a common number.
I see you for the deal.
I'm trying to stop.
Oh, sorry, I had the mic close there.
So I've got a couple of links here about this story.
Let me just get some headlines for you.
This is from wikynews.org.
Wikynews has learned that at least six of the United Kingdom's main internet service providers
have implemented monitoring and filtering mechanisms that are causing major problems for
UK contributors on websites operated by the wiky media foundation.
Of course, they don't actually want wikypedia they hate.
When I say they, I'm talking about the powers that be, the energy elite, the new world
order, the shadow government, because it's an authoritative place where there is no authority.
And by the way, I've gotten burned by it, too, long story.
The truth is not really in my profile on wikypedia, but of course, as most would say
where there's smoke, there's fire.
So anyway, so I'm not doing anything about it.
You can think about me whatever you want.
I know the truth, but of course, that completely undermines the power of the powers that
be.
The filters appear to be applied because wiky media sites are hosting a scorpion's album cover,
which some call child pornography.
The scorpions are German rock band who have used several controversial album covers and
it perhaps best known for their song, Rocky, like a hurricane.
And I think winds of change was probably a bigger hit for them, honestly.
So, you know, this is, you're going to see more and more of this.
And I've warned you about it.
The easiest way to implement laws, yeah, actually, I'm looking at the album cover here,
Virgin Killers, yeah, questionable.
It's a 1976 album cover.
It also appears on Amazon.com, many other sites.
Let me see why, do I want to see if I find this offensive?
I don't know.
I think the scorpions in general are kind of offensive.
But that doesn't mean that there's not free speech in that this is child pornography.
Very much like the case in, I'm going to say, was this australia?
No, what do we got here, or kinds of alarms going off?
Let me see if I can find that link.
I from Australia had a picture, and I'm sure I've had this picture on my PC at one point
or another.
It's like a goof, and you know, a spoof with the simpsons, and then it all screw
with each other.
The guy gets fined.
He gets fined for child pornography, because it doesn't matter if the, it doesn't matter
if their cartoons are not, if Lisa Simpson is getting boneed, it's considered child pornography
and not satire, humor, or free speech.
You see what we're up against here?
Let me see what else you got on your comment there, my friend.
I'm just not getting the police or the government or, well, in this matter, really, the EU,
I should have said, all right, filter what I can see on the internet, you know, this is
supposed to be a democratic country.
Yeah, yeah, okay, look.
It's not a democratic country.
Now, all right, certainly not.
So funny, look, you know, I've got to learn a whole bunch of new rules and processes
and procedures.
We've been reasonably okay here in the affluent suburb of Surrey hanging out and
Gilford yesterday.
Of course, I don't have my parking permit yet, so I had to pay the machine and put
a ticket in the window, and I had paid until three PM, I believe, with a new place, you
know, taking deliveries and stuff and setting things up.
And as I look at my watch, it's like, oh, shit, it's like 320.
And I look out the window, and I see a guy taking a picture of my, of my car.
They always do that now these days to prove that you were actually in violation, they, they
take a digital picture.
And I see a truck roll up next to my car, and I'm, you know, oh, man, and I start
booking down the street, they were ready to take my car away for 20 minutes overage
on parking.
And they have this, I don't know if you, you know, I've seen many, I've been towed many
times in my life, of course, but I've never seen this device.
It's literally like one of those claws at the, at the, at a carnival fairground, you know,
where you can, where it kind of picks up one of those gifts inside, and it shakes a bit,
and it usually drops out of the claw, you never really win a prize.
It's one of those things.
And they just pick your car up and put it on a flat bed and roll it away, and you know,
you're probably not done for three or four hundred pounds at the end of the day, including
the fine.
And so I must say they were very nice.
I said, oh, please, you know, I'm moving in, moving house as we say here, please don't
impound my car.
So they let me go on that.
It's still got the 60 pound fine, but after 20 minutes, man, those guys don't mess around.
Of course, they have, I've looked at it online.
They have 12 cameras surveying the, the slaves, make sure you're not in violation of
any laws you slaves.
Hi.
Let me see, okay, I'm, I'm just going to wind up by saying, on the internet watch foundation.
Yes, we definitely need to step up, stand up, and fight against this.
But as long as there's child pornography, claims involved, it's going to be very difficult
for anyone to go against this because of the public side guys.
And it's just used, um, and viciously used to get laws pushed through for the safety of
the children.
And of course, at the end of the day, it's exactly the same people who are not very concerned
about the safety of our children.
Look at the vaccines.
They're putting into them, look at the education that they're receiving.
Look at the, uh, the availability of, uh, of government sanctioned alcohol, uh, certainly
in the United Kingdom at the government doesn't love you.
They don't love your kids.
They hate you.
So we need to stand up.
We need to do things.
And we need to protect the internet.
It's going to be very hard.
But at the end of the day, the network is the network.
And I'm counting on the hundreds of thousands of brilliant systems administrators, engineers
and developers who will come up with ways to circumvent any type of BS filtering system
they put in place.
We will, it will mean that we'll be severely, um, hampered in how we get our messages out.
But we absolutely, as long as there's packets flowing, we'll be able to get something out.
I'm, I'm convinced of it.
And while we're at it, let me get some news out for you in these trying times today.
You're looking for, uh, good Christmas gifts.
You're looking for a good deal.
People are looking to not spend a lot of money.
There's a couple of things you can do.
And I've got some fantastic deals for you brand new, actually, to the daily source code
is 15% off all items at finishline.com.
This is, uh, and this is really working.
I just put the banner up on the site.
It is, uh, being used with the code, Niveo, DSC, um, any purchase of $60 or more.
You get 15% off.
They've got, uh, well, you know, Adidas, Puma, Nike, you name it.
But there's more.
There's more that you can order online and get for great discounts three months,
e-harmony first month for free, find your perfect soulmate.
Lot of people using this offer, uh, with the, uh, with the DSC code.
Also $30 off weekly budget rental cars, or 10% off any amount with my code at budget.com.
DSC, Brookstone.com.
If you're really looking for a Christmas gift, um, you can order all these online.
We have, um, 10% off, uh, Brookstone.com, again, with the DSC code, uh, the, uh, the champion
of all sponsors of this show for years, godaddy.com, use code, DSC, three to get 30%, uh,
discount off of your entire purchase.
And of course, e-music, 35 songs are free, no, no obligation, uh, yours to keep for free.
If you sign up, you have no obligation to buy anything, you get those 35 MP3s, um, gratis.
So when I was thinking about telling about all these great offers, which people are using
and I appreciate it.
It helps the network.
I don't actually get any, uh, any payments from this, it goes straight back into the
company.
Whenever you hear a mevio, uh, network show or one of you see a video show using their
codes, you'll know that the producer is actually getting paid by using those code.
So you're supporting that producer at the same time, you're getting the best deal available
for yourself anywhere.
Um, you like commercials?
Do you like the way we're doing?
Here's a guy, uh, actually, uh, he'll, he'll do the introduction himself.
I have not played this song in a long, I don't think I've ever played it on the daily
source code.
It's always been one of my favorites.
It's a live piece from here it comes, Barry Manalo.
And if you've never heard this, I think it'll bring a smile to your face when you hear
all the fantastic stuff, Mr. Manalo is written throughout the years.
All right.
Now what we're going to do for you here is what we're going to do what we call our VSM.
Now, all right.
Now this VSM, VSM stands for our very strange medley.
And for those of you who don't know what I'm talking about is a medley of, of songs
that you probably know, but I don't think that you know, I had something to do with it.
Okay.
Now, um, when we went out on the road last time, I put it, we had it in the act, you know.
And, um, and all my artsy friends came to me, all my artsy, falsy friends came to me.
And I said, Manalo, how could you do such a thing?
How could you put such a piece of garbage in your act?
And in a, of course, all my, all my trash, your friends came to me.
And I said, I love that medley that you do.
Hi, guys.
And you're all sitting out here tonight.
And so how could I resist?
So we're going to do our little VSM for you.
Now, next time you hear any of this stuff coming at you from your radios and televisions,
you got to think of us, all of us up here on the stage, okay?
And then you can turn all of your radios and televisions into me.
See if you remember this one.
As far as you're in the kitchen, we're on the flip.
We're gonna be the door when I'm down on the wall.
She's out of sight at kids in the way.
No time to talk on this picnic day.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get up again and take your finger like a kid.
Go, have a battle, come on.
Good bye.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Say hello to your family.
Come on, everyone.
And can tuck your pride again.
Have a barrel of the war.
Oh, yeah.
How can we forget?
Whenever you're driving,
I'm wherever you're bound.
Like a good neighborhood.
Speak for me, say.
I bet.
You're your fate.
Don't let the fire up out.
With your pride and I'm here.
To do goodbye?
Contour in us, it's got Spain.
I'm just on, hold me, it's tight.
I'm stuck.
All I'm ready.
Drag me this all these.
I got a bad full moon.
I've been in it too, God's been in it
I've been from far,
When the world is closed, I've been there
But don't bring calling me, I've been there
Yeah, I've been there
It's not a call
Call out by the call
Go dream, doctor, ever
Let your memory
All in your heart
Hmm, it's the most original soft drink ever in the whole
Why world, doctor, ever
Dr. Pepper, doctor, ever
Join the best sleep in your heart
Feel free, feel free
Don't let me be up, feel free, feel free
All close and anxious, it's a pity
I'm anxious, feel free, feel free
Feel free, feel free
So much light, to be lived
So much reason to try
When you feel it, you'll get
You can't get on too
Oh no, I've been feeling inside
Right to the day, so get it on
Get it on the way, to make our own
So get it on, get it on
To make our own, make our own
See it, see it, done it
Oh yeah, come on man, that's just good
That is good, I love that very
Manalo, the very special medley
I don't think that's been recorded anywhere
Other than the live
Situation, the true American art form, the commercial
And when you hear that man
I mean, you know every single one of those songs
If you're from the United States
You're like, oh shit, very Manalo wrote that
Uh-huh
Oh yeah, yeah, all right, let's see
Things not just happen in the European Union
And the United States, but of course in Canada as well
He had him here from Portland
So what's up with this candidate think uh
Suspension of Congress from Harper
By decree of the Queen
Yeah
And uh, why is it on Fox News or CNN
Or my local paper the Oregonian?
Dude, it's because no one gives a shit
Where it's all about local stuff about the dog and the tree
And uh
Yeah, we'll we'll toss the uh the Illinois governor Senate
Sailtheid and see thing a bone
You know, we'll mention that for a second and then it's right on uh to uh
Oh, crack Dan or a child molested or anything to distract you
You know, if it bleeds it leads but
When it comes down to real politics now the world the world really works
That means for me this not interested in giving you that because
You're not interested
You may be my friend
But most people are not
It's changing slowly
You've got to do your part to wake people up explain to them why this is not
Explain to them that the queen of England basically runs Canada
And I presume Australia as well and maybe there's a whole bunch of other former colonies
She's in charge of technically
So uh yeah, you're not going to see that on the news not not for a while at least
Or
Anywhere where is the outrage this is crazy
They're not working for us
They're screwing us
Yep
Hell yeah
Uh, a link that I picked up from the drop for drop.io slash daily source code this was
Um, let's see it's not of it. It's not a mainstream article but I did like the article itself from spiked
Online
The title is are EU deaf or what
Four times European voters have said no to European Union document
mme now there was a referendum in Ireland on June 7th
2001 that was the niece treaty
In France and Holland on the 29th of May and the 1st of June 2005 that was for the European
Constitution voted down out goodbye get out and most recently again in Ireland
Well God bless the iris the 12th of June 2008
They voted down the Lisbon Treaty the only country the only member state
There was allowed to uh have a referendum on the topic the rest of the
Member states jammed it through their own
Their own represent representative governments despite
Outrage although not outrage enough clearly from the populace all four times
European leaders responded by effectively saying you know no doesn't really mean no
That's right 11th and 12th December that's tomorrow and Friday
European leaders will be meeting to find what they call a quote solution to the quote
Irish problem
Irish people out there
Yet green chuckle heads calling and let me know how you feel and I know you're out there and listening
I'd love to you know this is what I'd love to have a live show now
We're boom someone from Ireland could call in
I know it would work. I know you're out there. I know you're listening
We really need to talk about this because they're gonna do another vote
They're gonna try and ram it through and they need it
They need it for this new world order for the world government that Gordon Brown now is basically
I mean he's now the hero he's taken over the EU
Drive towards a one form of financial government and and in general
Just a one world government. I was just talking with with the lady pee about this
About Amsterdam about them shutting down the coffee shops and and severely
Restricting the sex services industry
What I'll call it okay hookers, but the sex services industry
And she says what is that that's crazy? Why is it honey?
It's no coincidence that this takes place on the same moment the very same moment that it's happening in the United Kingdom
And it's happening in other countries because they're harmonizing it
They want us to have one set of rules one world no more sovereignty
You all your base belongs to them literally. That's what they're going for
That's what they want that is what we should be fighting against so the
Particularly in Europe the EU Lisbon treaty must be stopped at all costs because that is a technical document
Which actually sets them up to put in place a one world government starting with the European Union
They're already acting you can read it now in mainstream articles that acting under what they call the Lisbon principles
So even though it's not law
They're already acting under this humongous confusing legal document that they put in place
So they could do all these things
We got to be on the lookout. We got to be careful and we've got to act
And we can look at history for ways to
to react and for ways to protest. There were some very successful
things going on in the
In the past couple hundred years and here's one coming back. I think that's actually took place in oh seven as well
Hey Adam how you doing this is David Rhode Island and uh just want to give you an update
Just what my tickets for the Boston Tea Party
You can get the details at the Boston Tea Party zero eight dot com and what it is is
Isn't this where we raised the shitload of money for Dr Ron Paul when he was uh when he was running for
For the nomination for Republican candidate
I think it was I think we raised a lot of money for a Boston Tea Party. Oh seven
A meeting in support of a new monetary system
actually
Dr Rand Paul is going to be there
Someone I never heard about before but it's actually Ron Paul's it's fun his son and
Because his brothers also act involved also heard him around that interest is going to be there with
group of
other speakers
nationally known and everybody's going to come out in support of
Real money real monetary system nice and tickets are
1776 that's $15.76
So of course very happy to be part of the new revolution once you understand
How much of an impact the current
The up currency we have is and how it's
destroying economies and lives
You really have no choice but to
seek an improved
Real currency and we're all going to get out and support that
This coming Sunday December 14th
If you're not in the area there's a live webcast so I encourage everybody to go to
Boston Tea Party zero-weight dot com check it out
Yank the bank and end of it. Yeah hell yeah good work. I was waiting for that yank the bank
It's the central banks and the federal reserve
Federal reserve now
Ben Bernanke he's saying oh well we can't do it on a motive bailout. You know this is only for my banker buddies
This is not actually to improve the world or help the United States populist no no no
Fuck you if you're going to be out of a job. We don't want you to have iron money it's hard
That's what's going on you watch
Poor old schmuck's there in capital hill thinking they're going to do some good they're getting yanked on both ends of it
First of all by the auto makers
And then by the fed who does not want to give our money to anyone but themselves
It's so blatant so clear wake up people the new world order is forming
And we've got to stop him
Yank the bank and the fed
And take back the power of your own government wherever you are
Yeah
Yeah, back in this
One, two, my mind died
What?
But we like loves in numbers, they provide an effort that this
Who wanna got a rule
Like that's a way to run
The shade you want, the rate does fluctut around
Here what still your turn
I'll take you Bolo that point you open the blood
Sh the pool just saying no back out was trace
While the start is stepping on the left of pull the company
which is clearzy from scientific war
What in the world better will when the world starts getting so much
And retaliate, no matter what you'll be r Vielleicht
Not that you won't be my worst
20, 20, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10
10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10
10, 10!
If a Gaurant shot!
What if aonsiderer shot?
I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I
never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've ever seen you, I've never seen you, I've ever seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've ever seen you, I've never Zie you, I've rarely known you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've ever seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, I've never seen you, you,
I've always loved the Matrix soundtrack of Wake Up.
Oh man, great song that is.
I was just looking for a, for a little bit of background music.
I wanted to do a little, a little runlinks that pass the drop.
And I look at the final new stories for today,
but now I can't seem to find a second I had.
I'd like just like a little bit of background music.
Where is it?
I've got so much stuff I've been downloading.
Let me see if this is any good.
Hold on, let me, uh,
maybe you'll just have to skip it.
There was a great, there was a really good instrumental song that I heard.
Um, let me see if I can, it was, I had a cute up earlier.
Uh, maybe it was this one.
Hold on, let me see.
No, all right, I can't find it.
Forget about it.
We'll just cruise by the drop and we'll do without background music.
Okay, so here's what's brand new as of,
2012 PM, uh, UK time on December 10th, 2008, uh,
US car giant bailout.
This is probably what I was just talking about.
Uh, this is where, uh,
the government, the Federal Reserve, the government, the Federal Reserve,
which of course the private institution of banks,
they don't actually really want to bail out the, uh,
the big automakers with their money.
They want to give it to their friends.
They don't feel that that's an appropriate use of funds.
That's going to be very interesting.
In the meantime, Goldman Sachs,
one of the top five US municipal bond underwriters.
Okay, municipal bond is basically a, um,
a loan, usually by a municipality, like, uh,
the state of New York.
So the, uh, the underwriters are saying, you know,
you should buy, uh, default insurance on New Jersey,
amongst other states.
You could probably do it on New York as well.
Because, uh, you know, the basically their analysts are saying,
you know, the New Jersey's probably going to default.
So you should bet against New Jersey being able to actually pay for their debts.
This is Goldman Sachs, the recipient of, of,
of most of our money that we've been giving.
And what kind of cock suckers are these guys?
That's fucking crazy.
That's a Bloomberg story, by the way.
Another Bloomberg story.
Congressional panel overseeing US bailout citizens, uh,
uh, treasury.
Oversight committees that are by Congress criticize the US treasury
for not using the $700 billion bailout financial by, by, by bailout
to help average Americans.
And questions.
It's commitment to stem home foreclosures.
Oh, sure.
Uh, hello.
Uh, they're not actually doing what they said they would do.
How dumb are you people?
You know, you let them turn off the phones and turn off the email
and the website so we couldn't actually tell you what we actually thought
and that we did not believe.
This is a good idea.
You want to head and did anyway.
Now you're saying, well, well, well, well, well, well, well,
well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well,
uh, make me angry.
Well, this is an interesting one.
Gunt's for food and Los Angeles.
Oh, unfortunately, the, uh, I say someone screwed up the, uh, the URL.
Let me see if I can change that and you got to be careful
when you post links to the drop.
Sometimes they can screw up.
Here we go.
Los Angeles from, uh,
what's the AFP?
That's not just associated.
Is that associated financial press?
An annual guns for gifts and disease scheme in the crime-ridden Los Angeles District of
Compton saw record spiking yet another sign of the A-ling U.S. economy.
It's the guns for food program.
Give us your guns so that if you get really hungry and angry, you won't come after us.
And we'll give you some food.
Nice.
Don't give up your guns.
I'd say, go out and shoot some foxes or, yeah, by the way, how many foxes are walking
around in, of the streets of London, and I'm not talking about cute-looking girls.
I'm talking about actual foxes walking around in the daylight.
Oh, man, there's so many more things.
I'm going to be noticing once I live in the city.
It's going to be an out-rage.
Let's see what else do we have.
Poor families, pressed into vaccine trials by drug companies, 12 babies die.
I don't even have to go into that to know what that's all about.
Peter Schiff on your money.
Yeah, that's actually a pretty good YouTube video.
There's another good one.
Remember the guy that I was telling you about who founded the weather channel?
He is now along with 30,000 scientists, is suing Al Gore.
I'm just going to play the beginning of this clip.
Let me ask you, I want to sue Al Gore.
This is from Fox News.
It's a YouTube clip, link in the show notes at deadlysourceco.com, crosspass, crossposted at
curie.com.
I'm going to show Red Eye, which I presume was on in the middle of the night.
But listen to this.
You're a fraud.
The illegal challenge will settle the global warming debate once and for all.
These John Coleman and he founded the Weather Channel, my favorite channel has some of the
hottest women there.
And now he works as a Weatherman for...
I like that.
My favorite channel has some of the hottest women there.
This guy should be doing the show with me.
And San Diego, he knows warm fronts like I know cold cut.
So, John, why do you want to sue Al Gore?
Well, the deal is this great.
We have tried and tried and tried to get a debate on global warming for scientists on the other side.
Al Gore, any of the scientists behind him over the UNIPCC, without the heavy debate with him.
But they said, oh no, the debate is over.
Yeah.
Now that you hear that?
The debate is over.
They don't want anyone talking about this.
We're all set up.
We've got all the carbon taxes in place.
You know, to actually get a parking permit, I have to know the CO2,
milligram, or gram per kilometer of my vehicle.
We've got the carbon credits being rolled into the new financial system, which is being worked on.
We'll probably hear about that in February or March.
It'll come out of the European Union.
And as the dollar collapses, and it's going to happen because of all the money we've been printing.
Everyone in the United States will be a part of this as well.
So, no debate because this is done.
We've got to push through.
It only took a couple of years.
We're done.
We're done here.
Our work is done.
We have 30,000 scientists, 9,000 PhDs, who have signed up to debunk global warming.
And they still won't listen to us.
You realize that Fox is the only cable network that will put us on the air.
CNN won't.
That other thing in Western BC and CBS, ABC and BC, they haven't.
They saw that.
We are, we can't get on the air.
But once the internet, you wouldn't even know I existed.
The whole deal is that somehow we have to be heard.
So we figure maybe a quarter long.
Now let me ask you.
Why hasn't our responded to you?
Is he scared?
This is good.
And now you're going to hear how the system really works.
Okay.
So why?
Why is it so hard to debunk Al Gore?
Well, the system is working in his favor.
Listen, as Mr. Cole brings it home.
Or is he just pretending you don't exist?
Well, I think you can guide us as just a little net.
So he's a former Vice President of the United States.
He's got an Oscar.
He's got a Grammy.
He's got a hundred million dollars.
He's got a Nobel Peace Prize.
He's got a staring.
That's the worst.
Are you saying you say?
All right.
You should go take a look at that clip.
It's entirety.
Will worth the price of admission.
Which, of course.
It's free.
Let's see.
What else do we have?
Obama sending mixed messages on marijuana.
Oh, yeah.
It'll be another lie.
He's going to come after people using medical marijuana.
You watch.
Just another lie.
When else did I have in my own list there?
Okay.
Let's continue down the drop.
Let's just see what else we've got.
What do the Clinton's have on Obama?
The salon article, not bad.
Given Obama's elaborate deferrence to the Clinton's beginning with his over accommodation
of them at the Democratic Convention in August,
a nagging question has floated around the web.
What do the Clinton's have on him?
Well, I would say their own body count would be the thing they have on him.
It's like 40 people that have committed suicide or have died under other
strange circumstances as it relates to the Clinton's.
And this has got to be my favorite.
This, this tops it all.
Now, just so you know, in television land, where it is very hard to pay for the
shows if it's not a reality show with big sponsors, big audience,
calling voting.
We're all the nice little good slaves or hypnotized and watching bad singers.
And it pretty much doesn't fly.
So the government does find a lot of love.
Something with all your heart.
We are.
Hold on.
That's the trailer.
I didn't even know that was going to auto play.
That's cool.
So the government pays for a lot of programming.
This is definitely paid for programming.
It is coming soon in January.
It is a new reality show that will make you realize just how safe we all are is called
Homeland Security U.S.A.
On your heart.
We are hurting home friends.
You'll protect it with everything you got.
Tuesday, January 6th on ABC.
modular using their children is covered in trying to drug us in.
That's just a spectacle.
A new series about the heroes who keep us safe at home.
Really across.
We know what we're doing.
They have nothing to be afraid of anymore.
We're going to make sure that they're okay.
Since Homeland Security U.S.A.
From here's Tuesday, January 6th on ABC.
You are safe.
Stay in your homes.
Nothing will happen.
Protect us from harm.
Ha ha ha.
Oh my god.
I can't wait to see that.
Oh.
That is just that's outrageous.
Absolutely outrageous.
Homeland Security U.S.A.
There's tons of trailers.
Yeah.
People are despicable.
They're using their children to smuggle in drugs.
Unlike the U.S.
Government would just invade entire countries.
And then flies the drugs in on government.
They're craft.
Well, so we have.
Let's see.
Labor government in the UK.
It makes it even harder to sell your home.
Of course.
They don't actually want you to get out of any trouble you might be in.
Man.
There's just, there's, you know what?
This is why we have to move over to a live scenario.
So we can go through seven or eight stories in a day.
What has it been now?
But an hour.
I think I've definitely hit my tax.
Oops.
Sorry.
Didn't need to roll out the man alone.
Man again.
I want to play a little bit of a happy French song for you.
I think it will lift up your spirits and make you feel better.
To do the mall on a store school.
To do the mall.
Tady, Do what I really want to do
as if
I love you
We're looking for each other
to feel that rev'ed
our own set
But it wasn't very well
But answer!
Time is up
Mobile
I actually help with the translation of the song in the show now.
It basically means taking easy slow down slowly will be okay.
And only the French can sing in that way a fantastic song at the end of this daily source code episode number eight hundred and ten.
We will talk again for the football Friday.
No doubt about that as we move closer to the big move day.
Engineers gear heads bit heads people out there with ideas from my two technical challenges.
A about a great streaming service so we can stream live.
B about a phone switch preferably a service so I can really stack up phone calls,
put people on hold conference and do all of this from the comfort of a web browser or something easily configurable on the machine.
It can be void by any other system.
I don't care as long as people in just calling with cell phones or regular phones and we can have a nice chat.
And of course for you guys I'd love to hear back from what you think about the idea of taking it live.
Around 3 p.m. every single day united kingdom time.
So to do to do to do some all take it easy enjoy your freedom and live your life with passion.