Delta Sierra Charli, 808.
Daddy, what's it gonna be like in the year 2000?
Well sweetheart, for your sake I hope it'll be all peaches and cream, but I'm afraid
the end time is near.
The cataclysmic apocalypse referred to in the scriptures of every holy book known to
mankind.
It will be an era fraught with boundless greed and corruption, where global monetary systems
disintegrate leaving brother to kill brother for a grain of overcooked rice.
The nations of the civilized world will collapse under the oppressive weight of parasitic
political conspiracies which remove all hope and optimism from their once-faithful
citizens.
Around the globe, generations of polluters will be punished for their sins.
Unshielded by the ozone layer they have successfully depleted, left to bake in the
searing naked rays of light, wholesale assassination served to destabilize every remaining
government, leaving the starving and wicked defend for themselves.
Late Thursday, Renegade Cyborgs created by tax dodging corporations wreak havoc, pissed off
and brought its tired of being slaves to a godless and gutless system, where the rich
get richer and the poor get fucked over and out, unleash total worldwide destruction by
means of nuclear holocaust, annihilating the carafide masses, leaving in its torturous
weight nothing but vicious, carnivalistic, mutated, radiate, and horribly disfigured
the cords of Satan, the killings, bent on revenge, but against them there are so few left
alive.
Starvation reigns supreme, forcing unlocky subargesting anything in any uninterpath, massive
earthquake scrap the planet's crust like hollow eggshell causing unending volcanic eruptions,
creatures of the seven seas unable to escape to certain earth upon land, boil and
alert the person, disease and surface the earth, plates and viruses with no known cause,
or cure a flame waste to whatever does, but, and you and John had improved himself to be
helping more of the race of hopeless scavengers, fall victim to merciless attack evanes,
a hundred-pointed array of injuries, and seek to control the watch over the ants, this extinction
nothing of ant, the final world front, and there is only one year left.
Well, that's cool, I can hardly wait.
You don't have to, because here it is.
You don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have
to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you
don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to, because you don't have to,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh eh eh, eh, eh ohénari.
It's Charlie coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford, run a west side of G-town
Thanks to good fun of the show Ray for helping me prep today's program for you
And of course thanks to Gilford coach Red Bull and not a music for give me permission to play this one
Bombay, of course, playing that in recognition and in memory of those hurt and
And the families of those hurt and killed in the attacks in Mumbai, also known as Bombay
Oh man, isn't that just horrible? I'm always little bit suspicious though
We've had several attacks and bombings and explosions take place in the last couple of years
And only when they immediately say it's a terrorist attack, do I get really suspicious?
Because usually you don't hear about it, you know, it's just something blew up, something happened
But it's not a terrorist, this immediately was a terrorist attack
I'm reading in fact in the times online in the UK
Saying that they were Islamic terrorists, okay, so they know a lot already, apparently within just hours
Of a taking place and of a, oh man, it's messed up. So I'm a little worried that this may be some kind of play
Of course, the attack is real and what happened is real. I'm a little bit worried that this could be
Be used to do something nasty to Pakistan, which I believe is pretty much been on the agenda for a couple hundred years
Hey, it's Thanksgiving of Thanksgiving as my family likes to say in the United States of America
The day we all actually the one of the holidays I enjoy most because it truly is still recognized as a time to get together with family
Sit down enjoy a meal together. Of course the origins are somewhat different
At least we were all taught the story goes that we sat down with the Indians and we made a feast with corn and turkey and we were happy and thankful to our friends the Native American Indians
In reality, I'm sure it was a little bit different, but anyway, I love the holiday because everything's closed
There's no gift giving on the holiday itself people bring food people cook for each other travel
Hundreds if not thousands of miles to be with their families and we have a very strong tradition of that in our family
And unfortunately, I can't be there this year, but but Patricia and Christina have always enjoyed going up to going up to the homestead there in our month New York
So I'm happy Thanksgiving to all of my family who are listening and
We do have a lot to be thankful for even though I mean I got a list here
I have a list of links that is and when I do wish I did a show on Monday
It's only three days the list is outrageous. I can't even get to every single piece on the list, but I am outside of the the obvious being thankful for health and for family being in good health
Mostly in good health, I should say
I'm thankful for drop.io
I really am what a fantastic system. It's hard to pinpoint how a web application is going to work and when the the guys behind drop.io started I think their idea was to have some kind of
The basics of the idea was it's anonymous is no registration you can keep it private or not very simple. It can auto destroy you can get rid of something quickly
It's not index big by Google, which I like very much although it sounds counterintuitive. I love it
Mainly because there's less spam, there's no comment spam
And the community stays a little bit more closed. I don't necessarily want people searching and then coming into our drop because
You need to be eased into that. You need to have some kind of background or understanding of what's happening
Or you just hit there and go what the hell is this? This is a bunch of nut cases
And it's those nut cases those chuckle heads out there hundreds of thousands strong
Not quite a million yet, but hundreds of thousands strong on a on a weekly basis who are contributing who are awake
So to speak, who are participating in the awakening of others helping them see the true reality and the drop really functions is a great central meeting place
It's kind of a weblog a wiki a forum all built into one. They just did a whole new redesign. If you haven't seen it drop.io slash daily source code
Feel free to join in. So most of the links are from from the drop. Of course, I'm also very very happy with the worldwide web in general the internet
Tim Berners Lee mark and recent
I guess see even go back to what's his name Bob Medkath
Winvented to Ethernet Vincent surf all these guys
And that is our true salvation. I was thinking about this, you know, and I don't know if we do we have don't think we have any
Oh, yeah, there is some Australian internet filtering news that I'll get to about halfway through the show
But knowing you have to understand that there are hundreds of thousands of
skilled workers
You could call them IT specialist or you could call them system admins, but in general a lot of them listen to this show not hundreds of thousands of them, but tons of them
These are the true heroes that will keep us alive keep our communications alive. I mean, I do want to get into it now, but
There will always the network that was built and which Al Gore foolishly took to credit for which is okay because that means his
His energy at least power friends will but just only have more reason to be pissed off at him
Because they truly did build it in a way that
Even physical destruction of portions of the network just will not take away the communication capabilities of it. Now we may have to jump through hoops
And we may have to go around around fire walls and through tunnels and gosh knows what else, but there's almost no stopping it and that of course is what we need to use and we are using it in exactly that manner, not just with the show, but other things like
Like the drop
All right, should we get straight into it then? Because as I said, there's just a ton to do
Let me start off with some news from the world of medicine and science and again, all of these links are in the show notes a daily source code dot com or crosspost that at curie dot com
This is and I read this on pop of a wired
But it's like nothing new there of the 33 new drugs approved by the food and drug administration in 2001
2002 one fifth of supporting clinical trials were not published in medical journals according to a new study. There's a nice link there the results
They were published were often more positive than what companies presented to the FDA and their applications
In fact, most of the negative trials are never published
I'm trying to we've we've talked a lot about this we've talked to particularly as it pertains to vaccinations
My biggest or current pet peeve
Or our outrage is directed at the makers of guardazil and was at service
These so called ovarian cancer prevention vaccine, which was poorly tested rushed onto the market
The already built up in the pipeline of these two drug companies
They've coerced the government into making it mandatory or governments making it mandatory in many countries or in certain situations
And it winds up hurting people hurting people and killing them
And it's not like this this isn't mainstream information think of viox
Which was pulled from the market after killing 27,000 people through heart attacks a side effect that was glossed over in the company studies
Right on the heels of that is kind of frightening news
And we talked a lot about the avian bird flu and this is going to be another vaccine they're going to start offering it
I hope the god they don't try to make it mandatory
synthetic virus supports a bat origin for SARS while we all remember SARS right severe acute respiratory syndrome, which came and went
Bubbubbum kill people who was gone
So we needed to kill more people
SARS establishes response strategy for emerging infections
I mean this is a setup. It's a wind up the drug companies already you can look at their annual reports
I love looking at annual reports because
You know this shit you tell your shareholders better be true because you get called on it if you're a public company once a quarter and otherwise other intervals
And there's billions of dollars in the pipeline in other words what the drug companies are expecting to make
With vaccinations for pandemic flu so basically what they're doing is they're creating the virus
Under the guise of
Yeah, we just need to get the antidote, but they're creating viruses and I mean I thought this until I was a little kid before I even knew what the hell was going on in the world
I always thought maybe it's a part of my mind that is business like
And maybe the same moment in the part of my mind that's evil and maybe that's two sides of the same coin
But I always thought to myself well man, you know whenever
Whenever it's winter time it all seems like all around the same couple of weeks
There's all these ads for the flu and for you know
Flu-like symptoms
And I always thought to myself you know I did that those fuckers
I'd probably just like thrown shit in the atmosphere and then they give you the the flu medicine
And the advertising on television. It's always perfectly timed
And since I was maybe 14 I was thinking this and now of course I know that you know these things actually do happen
And we're ramping up. We're ramping up for the bird flu mark my words
Some disturbing news after we heard about the melamine which was found in baby food and formula from China
Here they are again the FDA has said it found trace levels of melamine
In one sample they took of US made infant formula
And a few samples of other products like nutritional medical supplements made by US manufacturers of infant formula
But of course the FDA says literally right here. This is the Wall Street Journal
It's safe. These are extremely low levels. It's safe. It didn't cause any concern at all not from a health standpoint. No of course not
I got to talk to John C. to work about this over the weekend
I'll get a kick out of that of course that's poison as it has no business being in our food
And it's used to up the protein count
That's why it's it's a scam
The FDA says the melamine
Is safe to eat below 2.5 parts per million. Maybe it is but it shouldn't be there at all
Should be no reason
The only reason it's in there is to up the I think it's the protein count something like that
There was a reason for it that had to do with what basically what you can put on the label
And it's it's severely hurting kids
I had a great discussion with the lady Patricia this morning who had a was like she had a four day
Stint in the in the Netherlands. She's going back tomorrow and actually I'm going over for the weekend
As she's doing a huge benefit
Children's benefit which is it's one of these extremely high society parties
With the the 500 richest people of the country and then us
I'm taking my buddy Michelle over as well. He'll get a kick out of it
Any so there's a it's a huge to do there's a silent auction which usually raises a lot of money
You know, it's all about the arts, et cetera, it's for the Lilliana phones which you probably won't recognize but it's a children's charity
Which has been around for a long time and they asked Patricia if because you know Patricia doesn't sing right she only sings
In really two cases she'll sing for a lot of money
Or she'll sing for free if it's for the right reason and this is one of those
65 piece orchestra her dad is going to a company her on violin on one song
I think she's doing smile the Charlie Chaplin classic
Trying to think what else she's doing she's doing New York New York
And I can't remember
Anyway, so the telling you we're talking about Holland and
And her impressions but of course you know when she's over there she you know she kind of dips her toe in the water
And this is it is really nice to be able to travel around the different countries within Europe or the globe in general
And just you know here how people are thinking
And the Dutch pretty much have been thinking oh you know we're we're clear of this and that's what the government has been saying
Yeah, we're we're clear when there's no economic problems no problem in the housing market
We rock we rule don't worry go back to bed nothing to see here
Please continue to consume your television shows
And a while back earlier this year they announced that they would be starting something which is just
Well, you know what it's about when you hear about the electronic child dossier
So the minute a child is born in the Netherlands
A dossier is open for them and that's not a vanilla folder. You know it's in the big database
And all kinds of information is entered into that database throughout the child's life
I don't know if there's actually a and hasn't started yet. It's going to start next year
And so now they're talking about you know how it's going to be used what's going to be in there and what turns out
One of the pieces of information which just proves that it's not about babies or young children
Actually take children going into at least adolescents
There will be a description of pubic hair that's right an actual field in the database for the description of pubic hair
And the options I'm translating directly from Dutch here are two options dark
Was it dark curled and hairy and a second one is adult hairy
I told this Patricia
You know because she's she's like well, you know, I don't mind CCTV cameras everywhere because they've tracked down hundreds of thousands of children who were abducted and I said yeah, but we know where's the limit
Where does it stop if you have nothing to hide then I guess you won't mind entering your pubic hair information into the database
What's that necessary for I said you're going to question you know, you know, where's your where's your where do you draw the line
And then I showed her the the new x-ray machines where the basically looks like your naked
Which are being implemented and she's like well, I don't want that I said yeah, but I thought you had nothing to hide from the cameras. So what's your problem?
Yeah, but that's messed up. I said thank you
And using these mainstream news articles is really what I want you to pay attention to when you're trying to wake someone up when you're trying to let them know that
That that something is going on in the reality that they have built up around themselves with help from
Our government and our government controlled media
This is the kind of stuff when they read it in like the Wall Street Journal or or another mainstream publication they read these outrageous ludicrous things that are taking place that's our task that is our task for the coming year
As we give thanks on this day 2008
You can stand me up, let the gates of hell, but I won't let them know
Stand my ground, won't be turned around
And I'll keep this world from dragging me down
Stand my ground, and I won't let them know
Hey baby, there's no easy way
I'm standing my ground, and I won't let them know
Now I know what's right, I get just one line
And a world that keeps on pushing me around
Stand my ground, and I won't let them know
Hey baby, there's no easy way
And I won't let them know
Stand my ground, and I won't let them know
Hey baby, there's no easy way
Time for any wall back down on the track
It's a super nice guy, Tom Petty, I've had the pleasure of meeting him a couple of times interviewing him
And I actually got into his head a little bit on the radio interview
I can't really do that in television, it's always so superficial and short
Basically getting nothing out of him
But on the radio man, this guy is a true American rebel, fantastic Tom Petty
Not with the heartbreakers there, I don't think I won't back down on daily source code 808
One more piece of medical news, which is kind of cultural that I want to pass along
Indonesian law has been put in place, which includes a by-law
And this is something to look forward to
Requiring, quote, sexually aggressive people living with HIV-AIDS to be implanted with microchips
So they can be tracked and punished
John Manning-Zung, who supports this bill, says authorities would be able to identify track and punish people
So the interesting thing here is that a microchip implanted would be
Enable the government to identify track and punish
One simple microchip
Identified track and punish people living with HIV-AIDS in the country's province of Papua
Who intentionally spread the virus and they would be fined up to six months in jail with a $5,000 fine
Now I do believe we need to do something about these types of illnesses
But this is going a little bit far, but of course it comes right in line with the Lisbon Treaty, which is
Somehow going to be, well, in fact the European Union is already stating now that they're going to act under the
Lisbon principles, which is I really love that
No one as far as I know is opposing this
So under the financial principles
The banking sector is going to change around March April, the way money runs throughout the world
But in that Lisbon Treaty under the Human Rights portion, which you really have to find from four different documents
As protocols and all kinds of separate, they would just pull the whole document apart to make it difficult to understand
Bless the Irish for either understanding or for knowing that this could not be good regardless and saying no in the referendum
Even though as I said the principles of the Lisbon Treaty are now being utilized and put to use
Right there under human rights, it said you have the right to freedom unless you are homeless
Mentally insane
Addicted to drugs or alcohol or if you have a communicable disease
It doesn't even specify which one then you can be incarcerated
So what's the next best thing?
Ah, it's even better than that, just chip the people
Chippem, chippem, chippem
Alright, so now of course those of you who've been listening to this show know that I got to talk about the bank bailout
Oh man
Which by the way, I read is it a Webster's dictionary who proclaims the word of the year
I read in a Chris Perillo email news brief that he sends around that bailout has become the word of the year
And they added an additional $800 billion
Just two days ago to the bailout
Which now I kind of lost track but I'm sure but I hope by now that you have heard that the total cost of the bailout is in the trillions
It was I think it was 7.4 trillion
Before this additional $800 billion
Now I just want, it's so hard to put this all into perspective
But let me give it a shot first of all
This money is
Money that is guaranteed by the United States so even though the federal reserve is handing it out
And lending it out in some cases, in other cases buying
Assets pieces of paper that guarantee some other pieces of paper that probably have no value
And the way they do this is they basically print it now
You don't it's not actually a printing press that is rolling
There's a spreadsheet and in the spreadsheet they say okay, we're going to add another two trillion dollars and we put it over on the
On the AIG side or the city bank side or whatever they need to
And because it's all just numbers there's no money changing hands
This is the this way you got to kind of get your head around is that this is just trading numbers is a finite number that we can go to and they're just making that number bigger every single day
Which has to be
Backed by money one way or the other
And that means that it will be paid for in taxes
It has to be or it has to be borrowed from another country
And also it's not like you know if we borrow money from China from a sovereign wealth fund that some
Guy turns up with a huge check you know like one of those lottery winner checks. Yeah, it's just like a little all right
Here's a little note in the database the IMF tracks it the bank of international settlements track all that it's a system. It's a network. It's a computer network
Let me see if I can put this into a perspective for you how this is bad for us
So let's say
We'll equate
A dollar to a guitar pick
You've been to a show you've been to a concert and the guitarist you might have 15 or 20 guitar picks stuck to his Mike stand and then
Some of these guys are really cool, you know, a little hand motion they flip it out into the audience and people love those and they're usually special autograph model
You know, it'll say whoever's a guitar pick it is and of course if you get an autograph and it might have a little bit more value
But let's say because I have a guy I won from geyser butler who was a base player for for Aussie
Which he gave me in Russia
Now let's say that's that's worth some money. You know, that's like worth a buck maybe if I went to some
Swap meat
If it was the only one in existence
The only guitar pick
And let's face a guitar pick has no value really is a piece of plastic
He threw it in the audience at the at the show
I grabbed it
And it was the only one he ever threw into the audience it could be worth a couple thousand dollars
But if he flips ten of those at every single show then that value is going to come down to probably about a buck or maybe 50 cents
Do you see the analogy because there's more other around it's not that special anymore that is how
Supply and demand works that is just something basic and that's when you know when you hear people on television talking about all the free markers
Well, yeah, that's what should be taking place, but of course there's a little something extra special in the middle called the federal reserve
For other
Globe dwellers and Europe you'd call that the European Central Bank it would be the Bank of England
But particularly the federal reserve is is interesting because it is not a part of the US government
The reason why they name it federal is great marketing exercise just like federal express also not owned by the government
So they have since this is going to be going on since 1913 when the federal reserve act was put into place
They have had the right to print the money what's interesting about this is that they don't have to tell us what they're doing with it
They do not Bloomberg news agency has been trying to understand where all these trillions of dollars have been going to and what what has been purchased with it and from home and
Bernanke says you're business we're not to tell you go look at the federal reserve act of 1913 we own your ass and we own the money now when you can basically
Make more guitar picks or because it's not even something you can hold in your hand
Forget about the paper dollars, you know, I'm talking about the money in the spreadsheets you can also take away
This gives them the power to control interest rates
Okay, and the interest rate is what determines a lot of things what your house is going to cost what your car you know out of can out of pocket cash
We your car is going to cost how much money you'll make what your taxes will be like it is a complete manipulation of the system and you can bet your
Bottom worthless piece of printed dollar paper
That whenever they manipulate it's for their own good because the members and although not even published in its entirety and unknown as far as as far as my research has taken me
We don't even really know who owns or who the member banks are at the Federal Reserve. Yes, some of them are out there and there's some there's some stuff on the website, but I
Would say a lot of the banks that are doing quite well or have now turned into banks
I'm looking at you Goldman Sachs
And isn't that interesting and doesn't it make sense that all these guys can be traced back to Goldman Sachs the Federal Reserve the Fed of New York
And the Treasury Department they've been at this game a long long time and now it's blowing up in their face and
What they're doing is they're just handing out money and I love hearing oh, well, you know, it really does it sounds shitty for me to have to say if we hadn't given all this money away it would be a lot lot worse
I always why is there no journalist saying excuse me could you please tell me how how much worse?
You know, are we talking about no food riots?
Are we talking about martial law?
How much worse could it get we've got millions of people who are losing their jobs people who are getting kicked out of the homes
How much excuse me and Mr. Paulson Mr. Secretary Hank I have a question how much worse can it get?
He's not going to answer that because that is exactly the truth and he and his buddies are all getting out with our money
So let me give you another little statistic in the past eight years the Bush administration has built up a debt a national debt in the US
It was around nine trillion dollars
So yeah, it took him about a trillion dollars a year and of course that's all money that we borrowed from from other countries and spent it on killing people and in defense defending as well
but on a lot of war stuff
And within the span of a couple months that number is about to double to double
Something that took eight years to build up this huge debt we're doubling it now and it will take many many many years to pay off
We don't even know if we'll get any of those loans back and then and none of these guys give a shit because they've got their money
They've got their bonuses, they've got their homes in Paraguay
Where George Bush has a nice compound
And they do not love you your government does not love you
Hillary Clinton proposed a universal health care
System which I have to be very honest, I never looked into it
I was quite asleep happily in my matrix at the time
But I did go back and look at the numbers and see what it would have cost
At the times he was talking about a hundred and ten billion dollars
A hundred and ten billion to basically fix health care
So let's say in today's dollars, I'll just make it crazy because what you heard about with the pharmaceutical companies are doing
So maybe it would have to be five hundred billion and it could have been fixed five hundred billion dollars
Now look at all the trillions that are being spent on the banking industry
Your government doesn't love you, they don't want you to be healthy
They hate you all of them
Look at what you could have fixed education
So much could have been done with this money or just a fraction of the money a little teeny tiny crumb of this money could have done so much good
Excuse me, that's just I'm literally getting nauseous when I think about it
Let's move on beyond the subprime bubble the other seven deadly bubbles
This is from Silicon Valley watcher. Oh, yeah, this is I'm not going to go through all of this, but if you really want to see how how screwed America is certainly
And why it is inevitable that the dollar will collapse
It's just going to happen and it could be it could happen in March or April when the European Union or the rest of the G20 comes back to the table and says America, are you in or not?
And I think damned if we do damned if we don't the new reserve money will not be the dollar
It'll be something else
Maybe it'll be something called like the greeney
For some kind of carbon carbon thing
But definitely look at that link it's in the show notes daily source code dot com and of course cross posted it at curry dot com
Yeah, and just to show you how how much they they hate you and and love themselves
That is a great a great article about city group and AIG still spending hundreds of millions of dollars and sports team sponsorships
You know, now I must say that if you're really taking the bailout at face value and saying, okay, you know, these companies need to operate and otherwise, you know, blah, blah, if you're really by into it
Then it makes sense that you know, it's it's partially a marketing exercise. I don't know if you need hundreds of millions, but
You know, a lot of commercial companies keep sports going
So I will put some defense on that side
But at the end of the day, I mean, holy moly
Let me see, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're like this little voicemail call here just to prove that
Hey, where'd it go? Here we go. Just to prove that your bank really does hate you. Hey Adam, this is Roy from Delft and the other ones
I'm listening to the DSC and no agenda now for about a year and a half or so and I find that sometimes you're a little out there
It was quite entertaining. Oh, I think I sort of got hooked because the first show I ever listened to was a food bar Friday and the mix of tech talk and music hooked me good
Anyway, I wanted to share this story with you. I moved here from Chicago about four years ago and when I did I left my old bank account open
It was the first checking count. I ever opened when I was 16 at a small local bank in the suburbs of Chicago
But since then, it had been swallowed up and merged and merged and merged and now the account is was with a very large national bank and to avoid all the handling and telephone
I had changed into an internet only account somewhere along the way. Oh, yeah, they love that man. There's these internet only banks. Oh, yeah
I just can't wait for to be linked to my new national ID card here in the United Kingdom signalling out foreigners. I still had some bills to settle and I thought
It would also be handy to keep the visa debit card open for when I travel back to the states. That's actually a very good idea
If you are in another country and it's very difficult these days by the way to open up a bank account in another country because you have to prove residency now
If you have the opportunity and you can find a way to do it not a bad idea
It's this is that the a lot of people ask me about my investment strategies or what I do with my money and I'll just repeat it. It's in physical gold
not here
Don't come to the house. You'll be disappointed as well as in currencies and I have multiple currencies and multiple banks and multiple countries
So and credit cards for all or debit cards, which I prefer for each of them
And it you'll find it a very
handy
With the fluctuation and I if you look at the the pound it was two dollars to the pound now. It's one fifty
the euro now around one twenty five
That was close to one fifty
And you start making decisions based upon where you purchase and what kind of monetary union unit you're going to go into buy
And it's a very very good idea in general
It's a very good idea
Unfortunately, of course everything you do is tracked and traced and put into your into your database right next to your
Pupicare details
We used it for years without incident or trouble until this summer
We took a trip back to Chicago in September at the beginning of the summer when we were planning the trip
I checked the balance on that account just so I knew what I would have in there
Planning proceeded and we booked a trip on everything
We had to get an American passport and to the states for my eight month old daughter
Even though she had her own individual Dutch passport
But that's a whole other story. Oh, yeah, I'd love to hear about that one. Yeah, this is a US immigration. Oh, please please
Stop already. I know it sucks
Anyway
About a month before leaving we decided to order some things online using the visa capabilities of the debit card
And we wanted it delivered to where we were going to be staying
We had about eighty dollars on the account the last time I checked so we placed an order to a link seventy four dollars
No problem, right?
But the skeptic in me decided to check the account balance so I was shocked to find out that I was twelve dollars in the whole
The activity on the account showed nothing except for the bank itself taking six dollars a month for the last three months as an inactivity fee
I had this thing exactly the same thing happened to me. I had a US bank account bank of America
Yeah, exactly we know what happened to them
And it was like I put 10 grand into the account and it was it was an online account
I did set it up in the bank itself though in the physical location
And what happens is you know, so you put it in and then they take like some bullshit fee then it becomes nine thousand nine hundred ninety five
And I noticed that every month they were deducting twenty bucks because I didn't have the minimum ten thousand dollar level
Well, yeah
Oh, no there's scum absolute scum stealing thieving cock suckers
They were literally stealing six dollars a month from me for not using my account
So I called customer service right away because I didn't want to end up with overdraft penalties
Which I think also started about fifty dollars and then twenty dollars a day until it's wrecked
I hate this oh man, let me just say you get it's a long comment to let me listen a little bit near you
And you would be sent a notice by mail again
I asked I pointed out the old yeah, we sent it by by post but but it's an internet account
Yeah, I know that but they weren't at all surprised and they didn't try to talk me out of it. Oh, when you close the account
So I guess basically the lesson from all this is that everybody should know that if they have money in the bank on an account
Does it mean if they aware that if they don't use the account then the bank itself will just start stealing their money
Yep, which I think is totally wrong and bogus, but it's not much I think I can do about it as an individual
Anyways, Adam thinks for all the great shows and I'm going to keep listening
They work for us
No, they don't they should be but they're not anymore
So I've kind of tried to explain the central banking problem. This is why I was so incredibly happy
And it's ramped throughout the whole banking industry by the way, and you probably have now figured out that when the banks don't lend money
Then everything kind of grinds to a halt
That's why you see big big box companies going out of business Woolworths now in receivership here in the United Kingdom
And that's because they were used to using or basically living beyond their means everyone has been living beyond their means
Some to an extreme based upon debt
And I think just and this is very encouraging to me. It feels like we are now and this is what they call by the way
Deflation we've gotten smart
And we're just staying away from the stuff we don't need anymore
That's why you hear the government say hey, please go out and shop
We're going to give you some money to shop. We're lowering the value add attacks the sales tax
Go out and shop because they need money to be flowing
And probably the best thing we can do, although it will accelerate the problems that are coming
We have to take the pain anyway, so we might as well keep the money in our pocket
Or buy things that have actual value if possible, home, land, anything that really is physical
And I'm not talking to a piece of winky, blinky plastic with headphones
Like real stuff
Which actually excludes a lot of things, not to think about it
But yeah, gold, gold and silver, you might as well do it
If you're not going to spend it, put it into something that will retain some form of value
That's what I'm doing at least
But the beauty is that we're all kind of thinking and working together in this
In a strange kind of way
And the government hates this
And the bankers really really hate it
They do not want you to stop spending
So that's why I was so happy that this weekend in 38 or 39 cities across the US
They had the end the fed day to end the federal reserve
Now this is something that we could have been talking about a year ago or two years ago
Or geez, almost 100 years ago, if you look at it
And many presidents throughout the American history have gotten rid of central banks
And have paid the price for it, many of them with their lives
Lincoln
Jefferson
Kennedy
Because they uncovered the true evil ways of the central banks and the owners of the central banks being the true elite
The true owners of the earth
So I really want you know we couldn't have talked about this because there was no bank bailout
There were no trillions of dollars being spent on bullshit and that was not being explained
And people are going to get pissed off at this now
So the idea of end the fed is good
It's good and we've got to propagate this and let people do their own research
But end the fed it's a great slogan
I like it, it doesn't work for the European Central Bank
So we have to figure out how we're going to work in Europe and the Bank of England and other central banks
Cut the central bank, annihilate the central bank
And send the central bank to hell
We've got to come over with a couple of slogans and the fed is a really good one
And it's not that hard for people to understand and it's certainly not hard for them to channel their anger, frustration and other forms of energy
Because they're seeing that we're being robbed
And it's pretty much, I think now it's almost like a mainstream type of conversation that can be had about what's happening in banking
I don't entirely understand it
Russian economist certainly understands it
Professor Igor Panarin, if you have not read this
This was listed on many different sites this past week, this one I'm actually getting
Excuse me, from the drug report
And this Russian economist
Economist or analyst
Well, he basically lays it out real simple the dollar is not secured by anything the country's foreign debt has grown like an avalanche
Even though in the early 1980s there was no debt by 1998 when I first made my prediction
It had exceeded two trillion now it's more like 11 trillion so he's he's counting the he's already behind on this
Of course this was November 25th three days ago. Yeah, it wasn't you now it's more like I think probably close to the 15 trillion
Quote this is a pyramid that can only collapse now what he's predicting
That the US will break up into separate parts
He's predicting the Pacific coast with its growing Chinese population the south with its Hispanics
Texas which will be his own of course Texas will be its own
Its own country
Where independence movements are on the rise as he writes and the Atlantic coast with its distinct and separate mentality
Five of the poorer central states where their large native American populations and then of course there's northern states
Where we've got a lot of influence from from Canada
You know what that is not unthinkable
Because the states really is in a way it's like Europe you know the EU is the United States of Europe
And the USA United States of America the you know they call them member states here so you could say Britain is
Or Britain be what could we equate that to
There probably the East Coast I'd say
It could happen
It really really could if the shit comes if the shit starts to hit the fan particularly
When it comes to
When it comes to the dollar being devalued or eliminated or replaced overnight
You're going to see a lot of problems and look at what's happening in Iceland
The people are now starting to revolt it's a very very small country
And it was like 300,000 people live there most of them in Rikivik
They're now storming the police station
You know they want the government fired
And guess what they get pepper sprayed of course
This is not to tut the horn, but just so you know that I'm not crazy
This is from the BBC and whenever you know we've talked about something
And we've had our opinions and I've had a strong opinion right or wrong whenever
More news comes out about it
I really do want to put that in front of you a former Georgian ambassador
Has caused an uproar in Georgia this obviously being about Georgia and South of Serbian
Atlanta Georgia and he's saying erosy hit Marsh Vili
He says look Georgia started that whole thing
He said Russia was ready, but the Georgian leadership started the military action first
There you go
By Chuck us Vili's own guys say in that
Up in Canada
And this is why I'm so worried when I when I compare to
To Iceland Canada's two largest banks Monday
Move to raise fresh capital to shore up their reserves
As the worst financial crisis since the depression continued to weaken the country's banking system
This is from the financial post
And the problem is that their central bank and this is why I say it's really falling apart at the seams
The Royal Bank of Canada
Says we basically don't have the money
We can't lend these banks the money
So they only have a couple options follow the the American model of just printing it causing inflation
Or who knows
Britain going bankrupt you think it's not possible
Absolutely when you read this fantastic piece from
It was at Ambrose Evans Pritchard
Which is in the show notes it's
Ambrose writes for the telegraph
Let me just see if I can get a highlight here
But he really walks down
All of you know because the numbers are much smaller here
So when you look at the deficit of 118 billion pounds or about 170 billion
Dollars that's the entire
deficit of the United Kingdom, but he really breaks down all these numbers and the credit default swaps
And he's seeing that the country is essentially bankrupt
And he's saying it and he's breaking it down so beautifully
And that is of course why the United Kingdom announced a 40 actually it'll be more be more like
55 to 60% tax rate income tax on those making over 100
They say 150, but I think the actual number will be about 100,000 pounds a year
Upper middle class okay, if that's not it's rich, but it's in the United Kingdom that will be considered upper middle class or at least it was considered that
And I don't think people will be able to sustain it now the best article of the week goes to Robert Kiel Sochi
I guess he has a column on Yahoo, is it Yahoo?
Hold on a second
Sorry, I really
I don't have any tissues up here so I close the mic for that disgusting noise
Robert writes how the financial crisis was built into the system and I love this article this is probably the simplest explanation
Of what is happening how the central banks are bringing us down and he is going one step further. He's saying they plan this
And he starts off by 1910 seven men held a secret meeting on Jekyll Island off the coast of Georgia that would be Atlanta, Georgia
It's estimated that these seven men represented one sixth of the world's wealth
Six Americans representing JP Morgan John D. Rockefeller in the US government and one was a European representing the Roth child in the war burgs
If you've been listening to this show, these names are not foreign to you
And if you know anything about banking these names are not foreign to you
And then of course 1913 the US Federal Reserve bank was created as a direct result of that secret meeting. He goes all the way through he actually equates a lot of what's happening
In some Bobway or what has been happening to what can happen in the United States in Britain in Europe anywhere in the world
And of course he doesn't actually say what we can do about it because we may be and we're probably too late really to stop the downfall of currencies
But we certainly can rise in opposition of the central banks if you want to pass something on to anybody if you want them to know
How this central banking is killing us and why it should be stopped and the Fed annihilate the central banks pass them that link
It's Robert Kiyosaki again in the show notes a daily source code dot com cross posted at curry dot com and I just want to say a lot of people tell me all the Roth child
You know I don't know where you're getting your information from you know they they don't you know their banking isn't that you get listen
Even though I hate saying that listen look listen
Please pay attention is what I mean
The Roth child's huge
If you ever remember there was a huge ISP in an service provider called world online
It was set up in the Netherlands at a huge public offering which failed a lot of people lost money big lawsuits
I think it was part of the beginning of the down to the bursting of the dot com bubble that particular IPO
But I knew Nina Brink the CEO quite well
From a number of almost business dealings thank goodness and ever actually did any real business with her because she is truly an evil person
But I remember her talking about because she would talk a lot is quite animated when she spoke
As she would talk about
Oh, yeah, this deal and I can get it these people and and you know I can this is where the Roth child and we can do business with the Roth child
And I can remember
She almost looked like she was horny when she said that she had opportunity to work with the Roth child
And she is anyone who knows her and the Dutch chuckle heads and the former arrowheads will agree with me as she's all about money
And she I mean she literally would get moist. I could tell smell
She got moist from just the idea
Of the Roth child's because they aren't the true elite and owners of the globe
And of course the other way to get rid of these guys outside of central banking is to get rid of the use of oil
Really any type of centralized energy and I know it's out there will be looking at a couple of links later on in the show. Of course
It's out there something where you can like rub your hands in a circular motion spread some salt water on it all the sudden you got like power
And we're going to figure that out
More study of Tesla is necessary for that
Let me see some I just some things you can look at over over the weekend
This is from the august review dot com Obama merely a fob for the global elite
Well, I think that should be pretty clear by now that look at the people he's bringing into his administration
Particularly on the finance side. Oh, by the way Robert Gates defences Secretary East and he keep the same guys in there. Why not? Hey, that's changed for you
Yesterday I was watching the tonight show
Jay Leno had I forget her name. She has a talk show on the e-network. She's a comedian's kind of funny
Actually, I think she was funny on Jay then she is on her show. I forget the name and she said something about Obama
And you know about how happy she was and it was dead silent
Where's a couple of weeks ago you would have had people erupting in cheers. Yeah, change just weekend
It's like, you know, it was like the Super Bowl and now it's over. No one gives a shit
No one cares everyone's disillusioned already and those who aren't and that that was just an audience vibe
You know, you can get an audience to do almost anything. It's so easy to get them to cheer
But when she took a very open
Easy route to get the audience riled up. It was dead silent pay attention. You'll see the same thing on the John Stewart show
You'll see it no longer is it Obama changed. Yeah, the audience goes crazy. Nope
Because they're feeling it. They know what they're living in duality the the the veil of the matrix is starting to be lifted bit by bit. It's exactly the same people coming from the same
Environments by the way Chicago or man the gangster heaven
Lots of Chicago influence in the in the Obama administration
But particularly on the finance side. Oh, man summers and
The new treasury secretary
Timothy Geitner
The same guys it's for their from
The federal reserve the treasury Goldman Sachs trilateral commission a council on foreign relations
It's all the same thing. They're not going to change anything. There is no change
And you should be pretty damn pissed off about if you voted for Obama
Here's the one that scares me the most this is from the Denver post and this is
Where I think unfortunately were headed in fact this article starts off with with the line one one more palpable sign of a desperate economy
Check this out
The Miller's the Miller family has a farm
And as the I'm just on jumping around because I want to save the payoff the big punch line
As this prolonged Indian summer continued the Miller's had decided to give away produce because so much was left over at the end of their annual fall festival
And of course when the deep freeze comes it'll kill it off so they had to give this food away
They expected you know over the course of a couple days maybe five to ten thousand people would show up
What happened is 40,000 people came to get free potatoes carrots leaks car snaked around corn fields parallel parked along Route 66
And one nineteen all for free food 40,000 people
Food banks
Now dishes out exactly twice what they did this time last year and they're out there's no food left
And I'm not talking about the stuff you buy in the supermarket that's not actual food God buy some real food God buy some carrots
See what they cost by the way
Yeah, we're going to have to get to the protest we're going it's going to have to happen pretty soon
As I said they're right you pick it's taking place in Thailand
I put a link in the show notes as well about the Bangkok airport protesters are shooting and being shot at at the airport
They want this you know they got they've had a coup several coups take place
They want this government out
Voting apparently doesn't work anymore, so now they're just taking over the infrastructure
This is where we're all headed eventually if we don't stop it in some other way
And we can start by ending the Federal Reserve, annihilating the central banks and do not be afraid to resist
And it's all you'll be just a lie
They tell us what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's
up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, but what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up
Break for yourself, you're my friend signer
You're always where you say, you're my love, right now you're here
I'm your friend, you're my friend, you're my friend, right now you're my friend
You're my friend, you're my friend, right now you're my love
Break for yourself, you're my friend, okay now you're my love, right now you're my love
Break for yourself, you're my friend, you're my love, right now you're my love, right now you're my love
You're just going to end for fun and the resistance of Chuckle 8-0.
And that resistance, Charnal Heds, that's us.
Yeah, so many people asked me.
Adam, what are we going to do?
I hear you.
What are we going to do?
Easy.
All that you have to do.
And those who want to do more will stand up all by themselves.
All you have to do is just tell more people about what's really going on.
Help them cut through the matrix.
See what's happening.
Turn them on to this show.
There are other programs.
In fact, there is a show called cutting through the matrix.
I think I haven't listened to it, but someone sent me a link.
That's why that stuck on my head.
If you want to hear great guess, I don't agree with everything he says.
The extent he takes it to, although extremely interesting, the Alex Jones show.
I love listening to the guests that are on his show.
He has just phenomenal booker.
Not hooker.
Booker.
Who gets great guests on his show.
Man, do I love that?
And they corroborate everything we're talking about.
Turn someone on to one of these shows.
Send them to drop.io.
Let them just look at these articles.
It's not like cookie internet stuff.
It's BBC, Wall Street Journal, New York Times.
You can even wired magazine.
You can't call a cookie.
So that's the resistance that will come from us.
But it'll come from in many other forms.
I talked earlier about systems administrators.
True heroes of the internet, unsung heroes I might add.
When you're talking border gateway protocol and you're dealing with routing issues.
Oh, man.
There's so much crap that goes on on the big iron side, the pipe side.
Just to get stuff flowing to keep it working.
There's a lot.
And it's a community of people.
And I think that most of them are really on our side.
And we'll help us route around any kind of crap that governments try to push on us.
There's just too much networked in too many ways and too many holes and ports and pipes and protocols to not be able to continue to communicate.
But we're going to lose a lot of people.
A lot of people are going to fall off the edge of the earth because they will not know that there is a real internet.
And then there's the fake government sponsored internet, which will be taken over pretty soon.
But I wanted to, I mentioned this in reference to what's happening in Australia.
And now you know that the government is talking about censoring the internet at the ISP level.
And now there's a backlash that's, and this is really funny.
A backlash that is coming because in the Australian daily telegraph, they, they talked about some filters that were set up.
Where, and these are types of words that got, that got filtered out.
Sialis, which, you know, whether you think it's good or bad.
I mean, it says nothing to do with pornography, other than that, you might use it to make some pornography.
Communication's minister Helen Cunan is quoted in the article saying that her own department's filter would not allow her to order strawberry muffins online because of the word muff.
Stuff at Martha's muffin.
They have another, he has a good one.
The home office consultation in the United Kingdom were surprised to find some submissions automatically rejected by a filtering system set up in one part of that department.
The consultation was on the subject of extreme pornography and the filter took exception to receiving emails with the word pornography in the title.
Idiots.
This is what gives me, it's make me feel good because we're so far ahead of these black jobs and particularly the cis admins will find plenty of ways to get around it.
This is our true salvation. Again, I'm so happy that we have the internet. Oh, man.
Government loses at least one PC a week. Another article from the BBC.
That, of course, will be soon be computers containing information about your pubic hair.
There's an, I'm just rushing through some of this stuff because I don't want to go through all of them. You got to do some of your own work and emphasize a lot of this is on the drop British broadband.
I think this is pretty much a setup. You'll see that broadband actually in a pretty sorry state here in the UK. I'm expecting the government to come up with just internet to same thing.
Although I don't know if my pubic hair will have to be listed. All other types of biometric identification information will be put on my new ID card. The scheme.
Will be launched.
I guess the beginning of the year.
And it's, it's meant for me. Who knows. Maybe they put this all scheme together just for me.
People living in the United Kingdom who are workers from outside the European economic area, but are married to an EU national and therefore have a quote right to work in the European Union. That would be me.
They're being singled out as the first ones to have to have this ID card.
And it will contain, there we go. Document will feature the holder's name, date of birth, their visa status, right to work as well as a photograph fingerprint record and other biometric data.
That's an easy throw away isn't it? It's almost like with links to Al Qaeda with other biometric data.
I'm sure maybe some DNA.
And if I don't, I won't be led into the country. I can't travel essentially. I'll have to get that.
But of course, I was talking to a guy who was, you know, we're in the middle of this move and I was talking to a guy who came over to do some stuff, some like inspection stuff.
You know, it's like, you know, he said, no, how long have you been here? So we moved about four years ago. We really loved the United Kingdom. We, uh, we chose to come here. We always want to live here.
But I'm a little, on this point, it's not the word, but I'm surprised that I don't see that fighting British spirit. You know, where's the wirey pale stringy hair,
uh, angry on the street, burning shit up, you know, remember the Maggie that's your days, you know, the punks. I was watching a channel for ITV, ITV, I think last night, but just before we went to bed or before we went to sleep, we were in bed.
It was about the clash, Joe Strummer. Oh, man. That's, you know, where's that revolution? And he said, uh, where'd he say?
Bohica. I said, Bohica. Yes, it Bohica. That's, uh, that's what's happened in the United Kingdom. Bohica. So what's that? Bend over. Here it comes again.
Hey, Adam, hi, doing. I'm good, man. I'm thankful.
It is. Hey, there's number one, four, nineer. And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
All right. Oh, I know the song. It's, oh, man, we played that. It's like a weekend weekend lover weekend. It comes a weekend. I don't remember young.
Number two. Uh, Uh, uh, Ehh. James inflame. Uh, I think was it's uh, living daylight. I think it's definitely uh, uh, with the James Bond theme. I think it's living day nice. And number three.
These people, he's got a fight for your right to part-chain, so I'm curious if I got
the first one right.
That's a little different.
And it's time for the answers.
Hit me.
And this is answer number one.
This is class action.
I've got to wait for the host for a long time.
We can.
Here comes.
That's another number one.
Yeah.
Got one star.
And this is answer number two.
Aha.
Two stars.
Twenty-and-and-and-and-and-and.
They try it.
Where we go.
Awesome.
That's a show.
The new new day light.
The three stars.
Of the three
I turned one
Where are they?
They always turn.
I can't believe but she still says no.
You got to fight for your right.
Fight for your right is answer number three.
It's gone.
This concludes hit this number 149.
So Adam.
How did you do?
I got five stars out of possible six.
I'm actually amazed.
I got that first one right.
By the way, somewhere there's a recording of me doing that
Eastern Voice on on stage with a band called Hello Weez.
We'll have to find that video.
Alrighty.
The answer is the dish and any other hitest.
And also the iTunes link so you can buy the tricks.
Featured on the hitest online.
Now to be founded hitest.meepio.com.
Thanks again for playing Adam.
Come on.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week.
Don't hit this.
So until then.
Have fun.
Take care.
And remember to try to think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
And of course, I'm thankful for your contributions to the Charlie every week as well.
All right.
We're almost near in the end of this Thanksgiving extravaganza.
A video I definitely want you to see, which is not worth playing because the guy speaks,
and it's hard to understand and buckminster Fuller.
I've never heard of him.
But he has this concept, which has just stuck in my mind.
I don't want to dwell on it too much.
But he was saying until we elevate ourselves in our thinking,
to understanding that we are basically
hopeless, incredibly advanced beings of energy that are held down on this globe,
called the Earth by a force called gravity.
And that we don't actually ever go up or down.
We go out or in.
I.E.
You go outwards from the planet.
No matter where you are.
Or you can go through something or around something.
But you don't actually go up or down.
You go out or in.
In towards the center.
Out.
Towards whatever else is out there.
Until you actually realize that the sun is not setting,
but that when you and this is something that I actually can do now,
I can feel that I am on the earth.
And I'm held down by gravity.
And as I as the earth is moving.
And spinning around the sun.
That's why the sun goes away.
If you still feel that the sun is setting and going down,
then what Buckminster Fuller says is,
you essentially fail humanity's final exam.
Very interesting.
Extremely deep shit.
Have a look at the video.
There's a couple of him on YouTube.
I'm not very familiar with Buckminster Fuller,
but he's an old dude who's pretty fucking smart.
Very interesting.
Just as we kind of wind up with some cool news.
There's now something called the Truman Show Syndrome.
Sufferers convinced they are actually on reality TV.
I laugh, but only because I still can.
And I can understand how people would have that.
Another Patriot standing up.
Chester T. Kelly.
And the reason why I mentioned him is I really like his website.
And I like how he's thinking.
He's up for independent congress and a general election,
December 6th.
Where the hell is it?
Chester T. Catfish Kelly.
Where's he run?
Oh man.
Anyway, the website is both parties are screwing you.com.
Hey, let's listen to what this guy has to say.
Well, let me, yeah, this is a YouTube video here on a site.
Let's see what Chester T. Catfish Kelly.
Cool.
Nice production.
Oh, wait a minute. Are you not hearing this?
You may not be.
Ah, shit.
Why is that not working?
Oh, man.
I'm hearing it.
But you're not.
Well, maybe if I.
I want a second. Let me just make sure.
This is kind of irritating.
Oh, man.
I've just re-routed everything.
Now it should work.
Let me save.
It doesn't work.
We'll pass on it.
Well, shiver me timbers.
Oh, crap.
Maybe it's the wrong.
No auxiliary out.
Shit.
It's going to sound flower.
Why isn't that just working?
I don't get it.
If I do this, no.
All right, forget about it.
Anyway, take a look at both parties or screwing you.com.
That definitely worth it.
Something I'm going to talk about with John C. Dvorak.
You know, I really want to get into it.
I tried last week, but it just didn't work about these.
Somali and pirates.
The whole reason we call them pirates is bothering me.
And maybe these are just people who are pissed off that we've taken all the fish out of their waters.
And now we're taking their oil either away from them or around them or whatever.
Maybe it's just a protest.
But whenever you call someone something like that, just because it's on the high seas.
They're called pirates.
You can get this idea.
All right, shiver me timbers.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
It doesn't sit well with me.
What does it extremely well with me is this next report from the New York Times.
This is about the changing of the guard of the presidency of the European Union.
A real chance here, a real chance.
So at the Czech Republic, I believe, is the next in line.
I think.
Maybe I'm wrong about that.
I thought that.
I'm just reading through this real quick here.
Anyway.
The.
Oh, man.
I'm trying to read this now and trying to bring it to you straight.
You have to look for yourself.
But anyway, this is the the president of the Czech Republic.
The president in class, he's a 67.
And he's causing a lot of shit in Europe.
I thought.
Yeah, here it is.
The Czech Republic is about to assume the rotating presidency of the European Union.
There you go.
So this guy will be.
Like.
It's our cozy.
I presume that's how it works.
I think that's the way it works.
He has come out against the global warming scam.
He calls straight out the financial crisis as bullshit.
And theft.
He has branded Elgor an apostle of arrogance.
And has accused the European Union of acting like a communist state.
I love this guy so far.
Well, that'd be a hoot.
They'll have to kill him.
They'll just have to kill him.
They can.
I'm telling it.
This is what happens.
Keep your eye on the guy from the Czech Republic.
And then for the arrowheads former listeners to the radio show in the Netherlands.
Take a liquid Bloomberg news agency has to say about.
About what's happening with the financial crisis.
The Dutch government.
The Dutch queen from the House of Orange.
So one of the elite families of the energy elite.
They own a significant portion of royal Dutch shell.
And as far as I'm concerned.
Incredibly evil.
Bernard, who was passed on.
Was the founder of the builder bird group.
So that should tell you enough about that.
Even the queen in her recent.
Public outings.
Hey, everything's fine.
Nothing to see here.
Go back to watching television.
It's all fine.
Well, the boom of the 80s has left the Dutch saddle.
With the highest level of mortgage debt in the entire euro region.
With the economy sliding into recession.
And the Dutch have our mortgage to the Hilt 98% of GDP.
That's what the mortgage debt equals.
And most people have borrowed up to 4.5% of their annual income.
And a lot of them have 110 to 120% value of the property mortgages.
And trust me, they have put all of that money into their homes.
The Dutch homes are beautiful there.
I mean, I'll say immaculate restored, modernized.
Everyone has new kitchens.
New living rooms.
Beautiful.
It was a complete banana.
And now a lot of these arms.
These adjustable rate mortgages are going to come do.
And the Netherlands has no industry at all.
If you look at the United Kingdom, which has very little industry.
But essentially 30%.
This was just in the financial times the other day.
30% of the United Kingdom directly or indirectly works for the government.
So this is going to be the same in Holland.
In the lowland, the low country.
The only thing they can do is be in the service sector and provide stuff to each other.
No one's making anything there anymore.
And I feel bad because it's going to hit really, really hard in the Netherlands.
It's going to be horrific.
I think the lay also be huge.
The burden, because they do have socialized medicine and social security and very good benefits.
For people who have no income.
But of course, it's a very an increasingly smaller size of the population.
It was going to have to pay for that.
And that will be provided for by partially taxes.
And of course, devaluation of the euro by printing more and pumping more money into the economy.
You know, more guitar picks.
And let me just end with thankfulness for all the people out there.
The cooks, the idiots, the tinfoil hatwares, the people who are ridiculed,
coming up with alternative ways to come up with energy.
Because if we can actually get rid of our dependence upon oil, fossil fuels to burn,
made by huge industry, if we can figure out how with all of this energy around us were made of energy.
Certainly there's got to be a way to harness that and be able to create it easily at home for free or cheaply.
Why would we actually have to be on a grid?
Anyone who's working on that, I love you.
And appreciate your work.
And there's always a cup of coffee in a sandwich at the Curry,
Manor, Castle Cottage, or Future Terrace for you.
And so I leave you with a beautiful article about the flow, the Viveis Hydropower System,
making energy from slow currents on the CBED floor.
This has been around for many, many, many, many years.
Let's not forget that this stuff is out there.
But that there are ways beyond solar, beyond wind power there.
There is more out there and that we definitely have to support all of the efforts.
Oops.
There we go.
Come on.
It's what I was looking for.
We have to support all of the efforts that are ongoing.
Because that's how we create our true freedom and independence.
When the true owners of the globe don't have control over,
that would give us electricity, heat, transportation.
This is from two of the, without a doubt, best living songwriters
in the United Kingdom, the Gallagher Brothers.
Oasis.
I'm Charney Itzeroy.
Here's the sound.
It reminds me of where we are.
Looking back at all the things we've done.
We've got to keep on keeping on.
Out to sea.
It's the only place I ever see.
Can give myself some peace of life.
You know it's getting hard to fly.
It reminds me of where you belong.
Always you had behind the wall.
Because if I had to go, it reminds me of where you belong.
It reminds me of where you belong.