Delta Shara Charley, $7.92.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
In the next generation radio contenti my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm just in this house curry.
You will not be able to stay home, brother.
You will not be able to plug in, turn on and cop out.
You will not be able to lose your cell phone,
scan and skip out for me and join commercial
because the revolution will not be televised.
The revolution will not be televised.
The revolution will not be brought to you by zero.
And four bars without commercial interruptions.
The revolution will not show you pictures
and mixing the volume up your goal.
And leading the talk by John Mitchell.
The world able to inspire all act new,
feed, hold most compensated for my heart of safety.
The revolution will not be televised.
The revolution will not be brought to you by zero.
And will not start at the world and see McQueen.
All bull, wake up and show you.
The revolution will not give your mouth sex to me.
The revolution will not get rid of the nerve.
The revolution will not make you look five-power.
The revolution will not be televised, brother.
There will be no pictures of you and when they may switch in their shop
and cut down the back of the dead run.
The revolution will not be able to predict the winner.
The revolution will not be televised.
They're taking their money out.
So it is a full blown run on the bank.
Just not the retail version or the version you'd expect to be televised.
Because as you heard, again at the top of the show, the revolution will not be televised.
Nor will the downfall of the American Empire, which is surely where we're headed.
Congress must not be allowed to pass this bill.
The only thing I the only way to solve this is we might as well just take the hit now.
I mean, I've been in business for half my half my life.
And through ups and downs and sometimes you just got to take the pain.
Sometimes there's just no fix and there's no fix.
There's no plan.
Just given one guy a former insider, CEO of Goldman Sachs,
giving him the right to spend our money, which have already been doing.
And I don't even know if Congress approved this 85 billion bailout or another.
I mean, they've already put $4,500 billion into the market with.
As far as I know, not even asking Congress.
So you know what's going to happen is they're going to clean up all these companies.
They will reset, but everyone's going to get bailed out.
And that means, and typically I have no problem with CEOs making a lot of money.
Because whatever, I don't give a shit.
But if it's my money, yes, then I give a shit all of a sudden.
I grossly give a shit.
And it's not going to happen.
So you must write your congressman or congresswoman.
You must tell when this bill cannot pass.
And you must threaten them.
Literally threaten them.
That you will hold them accountable.
When it all comes tumbling down, if they vote for any type of bailout bill like this.
If any type of bailout bill period, we have to let it blow up.
It has to blow up.
And here's the question I have.
This is the one piece of, I guess you've called, rhetoric, which no one has really expanded upon.
The whole reason for this.
This is really the big lie that everyone is overlooking.
The whole reason for this bailout is because the authorities, and I've heard President Bush say it.
I've heard Hank Paulson say it.
I've heard Ben Bernanke say it.
I'm hearing everyone on CNBC say it.
The alternative.
Well, we don't want that.
I would like to know my options at this point.
If you don't mind, Congress, President, Secretary of the Treasury,
Pop it of the Fed.
I would like to know what the options are before we make any decisions.
So please tell me.
And ask if you're at a rally for Obama or for McCain.
Either one of these jibronies.
Ask him.
Hey, you know, so we have to build these guys out.
What's the alternative?
What is the alternative?
What really does that mean?
How come no one has told us what the actual alternative is?
Does it mean that all these guys who've been stealing money and setting up this huge house of cards,
this Ponzi scheme?
Does it mean that they get their asses handed to them?
Is that the horrible thing?
Does it mean that we go broke as a country?
Does your plan have an alternative result?
We deserve to know what the actual alternative is to the bailout package?
And it just will not suffice because everyone's going along with it.
Everyone's going like, like, like, sheep.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
No, we don't want the alternative.
Why not?
What is the alternative?
That everything goes bust and we have to reboot and start over again.
And God forbid, we actually have to put our hands out of our sleeves there.
And we're all the sleeves up and do some work to get something going and to rebuild.
And maybe even while we're at it, replace the financial system.
And perhaps replace a lot of the way the governmental system works.
I don't think they want the alternative.
That's the problem.
It's not the, I think it's probably the best alternative for us.
We've got to take the pain.
We've got to write it down.
We've got to cop to our mistakes and we've got to learn from it.
So when they say to you, and I'm talking about they being the Bush administration,
the president himself, I'm talking about Bernanke.
I'm talking about Paulson.
I'm talking about Obama.
I'm talking about McCain.
When they say to you, oh, you don't want the alternative.
Actually, I think they say we don't want the alternative, which is right.
You don't want the alternative because the huge lie will be exposed.
That you have let the American public and to a certain extent the world,
because this is not just the American credit crisis, Britain.
Don't be fooled.
Europe, continental Europe.
You're in bed.
Just as deep as we are, the European Central Bank has been pumping hundreds of
billions of euros into the economy as well.
The same Ponzi scheme, the same banks, the same shit.
It's all coming down.
The only thing this bailout package will do, perhaps, is delay it, so that all
these big fat rich motherfuckers can get out to their homes in Paraguay and
hide while the inevitable happens anyway.
We have to go through the pain.
Don't take my word for it.
Listen to the distinguished gentleman from Texas.
This is on Glenn Beck.
The United States.
He had controversial views cause a lot of people to dismiss him as out of touch.
I'm actually just going to pause this for one second.
This is a two-parter that I want to play for you of Dr. Ron Paul,
Congressman Paul, on Glenn Beck, on the 18th of September.
It's good that it's two sections because the first part is about what has
led up and where we've come to at this point.
And I'll probably jump in right after that.
Then the second part takes us through what we really should be doing with this bailout package.
And I think you'll see that the good doctor and I agree on, I think just about everything.
So let's listen to this bit of Ron Paul on Glenn Beck.
On, by the way, is usually not a fan of Ron Paul.
On the Franger worse, and some things he is on the Franger.
It is, unfortunately, our loss that people, you didn't have to vote for, but you should
listen to him.
I don't agree with Ron Paul on everything, not by a long shot.
But one thing I do agree with him on is the economy.
And when you look back at this man's economic positions.
And you see the red flags that he was talking about, I mean, years ago,
you've got to give credit where credit is due.
Now, let me give some credit to Glenn.
Glenn Beck as well.
This guy, you know, I'm like it.
I am.
He's switching on.
And he's remembering.
Because if I had a, if I had a little bar of gold for every single time, someone sent
me a YouTube video, Ron Paul talking about this exact same scenario since 2003.
Well, you get the point.
Now, what I'm wondering is, have the billions we've spent on the bailouts of Freddie and
Fannie and AIG, is that even constitutional, the Maverick himself, the actual Maverick
Now, remember, you're listening to a congressman of the United States.
Okay.
This guy has been around for over 10 years in congress.
He's been a part of all the meetings.
He's been preaching over and over again about the monstrosities taking place.
And here he is confirmed in everything he has said.
So for those of you called him a cook, called a supporters of cook and nut cases
and wackos.
I think it's time for you to listen up.
And by the way, we don't condemn you.
I don't condemn you.
It's never too late to join on board, wake up and see what's really taking place.
Congressman Ron Paul.
Congressman, held me out on, held me out on this.
The, is this constitutional, I mean, I was sitting here watching the bailouts happen.
The president's not there.
It's just the Treasury Secretary and the Fed.
And then a bunch of people are like they're going into a pawn shop.
How much you give me for this?
I think your suspicions are correct.
It's absolutely not constitutional.
But the monetary system is unconstitutional.
And these problems have been building for decades.
So what Treasury did and what the Fed did is unconstitutional.
The constitution rules for Congress to regulate the money and its value.
And they're totally neglectful.
They didn't do anything about this.
They're just sitting on the sidelines sitting on their hands.
But Woodrow Wilson helped create of putting the Fed in here.
That makes it constitutional.
But if I read the constitution, isn't Congress in charge of the first strings.
Only Congress can spend my money, right?
You should definitely, if you have a chance, do some homework.
If you've only been listening to this show for the past couple months, go back a year or so.
And you'll listen to when I had my own awakening and understanding of the Federal Reserve.
Never forget the line, the Federal Reserve.
And I use this with people all the time to say, well, the Fed's supposed to manage everything.
The Federal Reserve is as governmental as federal express.
I'll never forget that line.
And it is absolutely true.
It's made up of commercial banks.
And we have given them, given them the right to control our money.
And I woke up to this over a year ago.
And well, here we are.
Now we're seeing what that awesome power actually entails.
And how illegal it really is.
And they're getting around this way.
They spent $85 billion yesterday.
And they say, well, it wasn't appropriated.
We just created the money.
But they're stealing value from your dollar by increasing the supply of money.
They defy your currency.
You paid a tax by higher prices.
Please understand this.
And I just can't help but interrupt.
I've really gotten clued into this.
And I just want to make sure everyone understands.
They printed that money, okay?
It wasn't money that was in a budget that they took out of somewhere else and put it
towards saving AIG.
They printed it.
Well, they didn't really print it.
They just put it into an entry on a spreadsheet.
That's how they create money.
And they have the authority kind of by the Federal Reserve Act to do that.
And when there's more money in circulation, then your prices go up.
That's basic economics.
I shouldn't have to teach you that.
And the whole process of appropriation and the Congress being responsible.
Totally neglectful.
I've right now this week I got to thinking Congress ought to just go home.
I think they're relevant if they don't take one themselves.
The role that they're supposed to perform.
Do you think we're headed towards 1929, 1979, or a 1989 style Soviet collapse?
It could be the 89 Soviet collapse that won't be the same.
But the system will have to be revamped.
And how long do you think before?
I mean, today is another anniversary.
You wanted a couple of weeks ago and you gave a speech.
I don't know.
Two years ago and you said, this is coming.
And I had you on that anniversary.
That speech you were dead right.
I think today is another one where you said in 19, where was it?
19, or 2003, you called again for things happen.
And that's what's happening this week.
So how long before before we see the real ramifications of this?
Well, if one understands Austrian economics, you can predict trends.
But you can't predict precipitating events.
You can tell when the foundation has eroded.
And it has eroded.
So the precipitating events that causes the panic is an emotional reaction.
But the fundamentals are such that we're on a verge of a collapse.
It could happen.
If we do something foolish or stupid or continue to do some things that we're doing today
by bailing on everybody any day, and nationalize all our industry.
Eventually, the world will give up on our dollar.
We're still benefiting.
Believe it or not, with the privilege of issuing the reserve currency of the world.
And now, so many people hold the dollar.
They're cooperating with us on this fraud.
And to the exclusion of the Congress, Congress neglects their responsibility
that Federal Reserve should even exist under the Constitution.
There's no explicit authorization for a central bank.
And the treasuries just complicit in all that we do.
Economic law will end this eventually.
I will tell you, Congressman, that I, well, I'm not a conspiracy theorist
by any stretch of the imagination.
I will tell you that it almost feels like we're being set up by players that, for instance,
the Secretary of the Treasury right now.
He worked at Goldman Sachs.
He was a big guy at Goldman Sachs.
I love this.
This is Glenn Beck's Awakening.
It's like, you know, I'm not a conspiracy theorist,
but, you know, meanwhile, the back was mine.
Holy crap.
All that should have been reading about the illuminati and, you know,
all these different levels in the pyramid.
It's freaking true.
So I better say, I'm not a conspiracy theorist,
because I don't want to be labeled one.
I don't want to be labeled a kook.
Come on Glenn, you're almost there, man.
You're almost there.
All of the players, they all know each other.
It's this the old boy network here.
And they cannot be this stupid to not see what they're doing.
Now, I don't have the final answer on that,
because I'm bewildered by that too.
You see them making a lot of money.
They love the system.
But I think what happens is they believe they can control it.
You know, they have this president's working group
on financial markets, the plunge protection team,
and they're always believed in they can be bailed out.
But eventually the markets are more powerful than all those
who do this planning, whether it's central economic planning
through banking and monetary affairs,
eventually the market rules in this.
That's, you know, that's so right.
That is so right, particularly with no regulation.
When it's just applying demand,
if that's just the only principles that are left,
the market absolutely rules.
I mean, I've had enough education to know that.
It's, when if it's only purely supply and demand,
and there are practically no rules,
which is pretty much the financial system as I might add.
Clinton did a lot of that deregulation.
Darlings of Wall Street, the Clintons are.
Then the other market doesn't discriminate.
It'll kill whoever it has to kill to go the way the market flows.
Those are true, actually, I would say those are true forces of nature.
That's what's happening today.
The market is shouting that you've overstepped your bounds,
and you can't do it any longer.
So it'll bring us to our needs.
Congressman, the Democrats are saying this is Bush's problem,
and, you know, the failed economics,
the right is screaming.
This is Congress's problem and the Democrats.
I think it's both of their problems,
but yet it's so much more than that because this is,
and this isn't seemingly getting very much attention,
connecting these two.
The politicians are saying one thing,
but the rest of the news on TV is showing this is a global problem.
This is happening all over the globe.
Is that Congress's fault, too?
Is that the president's fault?
Did we cause it in the rest of the world?
Or have the central banks done the same thing
to the rest of the world?
Let me answer that.
The central banks, the whole idea,
the whole system built on money,
making money from money.
That was it.
That's the whole problem.
All these central banks.
Bad idea.
Now, the C's were planted in 1913.
They really came to the boom in 1971.
It was made worldwide because we have a total fiat currency created
by the Bretton Woods Breakdown in 1971.
But the world accepted the dollar as a reserve currency of the world.
It literally said,
you can put your gold as much as you want,
so everybody's in bed together.
So this idea that if you think the dollar is going down in value,
that you can protect yourself by going to the euro,
the yen, it's not going to work.
Only hard assets will protect you
because prices are going up.
And the world economy is global.
Global economies are good when they're market-driven,
but when they're driven artificially by central blanks,
colluding.
So it's not just our central bank.
All the central banks talk to each other.
But we and the Congress can't even audit them.
We don't even know this.
We can find out more information about the CIA,
which is rather secretive than we can about the Federal Reserve,
and just like the other day when they come up with these bailouts.
You think they even consulted Congress?
It's been $85 billion.
And Congress just doesn't do anything.
We're nationalizing these industries,
and there doesn't seem to be any that much concern.
Yeah. Well, there is here Congress,
but I would take a quick break.
We'll be back with some final thoughts with you.
So there you have it.
Congress is just sitting on their hands.
I'm almost going to do that.
Sitting on their hands, doing nothing,
letting this all pass by.
These are the people that you elect.
These are the people that you put into office.
And the same thing is happening all over the globe.
It's only so little more abstract in Europe.
People aren't even aware in Europe of what's going on.
The exact same issues are taking place.
Maybe there's a news article here there,
and we kind of joke about the banks.
But it's the same peril.
They're all on the verge of breaking down, falling down.
I just got to play this second part of this interview.
It's a little bit shorter this piece, but it's well worth it.
Because Ron Paul really really does.
I've seen this financial situation coming for a very, very long time.
I know that you're being tracked now.
Finally, the media wants to talk to you.
Yeah.
You're from me because everything you've been talking about is now coming to fruition.
Yeah, that everything he's been talking about is now coming to fruition.
This could actually be some form of the turn in mainstream media.
I'm thinking about this more and more that I've seen it on CNBC,
which clearly is being used to leak all kinds of news.
They've got their operatives everywhere.
I mean, I'm seeing it literally guys taking cell phone calls
and repeating rumor and hearsay on the air as it comes through.
And you see the markets right there.
You see it react in real time.
I mean, this is fascinating stuff.
You are witnessing a humongous event.
So you do have to pay some attention to television.
I recommend CNBC during the daytime hours.
It's just so phenomenal to see the news come in.
See the markets respond and see the experts who live
literally do not have an answer and how worried they look.
You can see it in their eyes.
You can you can feel it.
It's an everyone's turning around to Dr. Ron Paul.
Go figure.
All the cooks, all the freaks, all the idiots, all the nutters.
It seems to me, Congressman, that we are ending up with bigger and even more powerful banks.
We're losing everything small and retaining only thing that is very big,
global and powerful.
How do we ever escape the global clutches of these gigantic financial institutions
and the Fed when we are now handing them all of the power?
You know, I really don't understand why we feel like we're in their clutches.
They don't hold anything.
They hold their own problem.
Yes.
The underlying issues are devastating for homeowners in particular worldwide and what will happen
to currencies worldwide.
We got to go through it, people.
We just got to go through it.
I don't think you're going to go for that.
I pot upgrade this year.
It's going to be very difficult unless we have a real serious discussion here in Washington
where the mistakes were made.
If you do those mistakes and devise another system, it's going to continue that way.
And the big guys are going to end up owning everything.
You say, oh, no, it's the Federal Reserve and the taxpayer.
But somebody's involved.
Somebody's going to be controlling that.
Somebody's going to be benefiting.
You know, these CEOs aren't suffering.
They're still getting their parachutes and their millions of dollars.
So the big guys are protecting themselves.
But eventually, always comes about.
Monterey history shows that this type of a monetary system will not last.
And eventually, they have to sit down and devise a brand new system.
The biggest question is, will it be in a free society?
Or will it be in a totalitarian society?
And right now, we're moving rapidly toward more government and bigger government
and control by big banks and big corporations.
There's your choice right there.
There is your choice, chuckleheads.
Do you want this to be determined under a totalitarian state?
Well, how we're going to re-jigger the financial system and the way we do business?
Or do you want to do it as a whole bunch of free thinking people can sit down and work together?
Across boundaries and borders and countries and continents?
Doesn't it sound like that would be a much better way to do it?
Ask your candidate.
Ask these two puppets.
These actors, McCain and Obama ask them what they're going to do.
When they take over the presidency in three months.
Ask them what they're going to do.
They don't have an answer.
They just blow and smoke up your ass.
They do not have an answer.
And they don't want to do anything to change the status quo.
They're under control.
They've been bought and paid for by the same guys who are about to take a trillion
dollars of our money.
Very frightening.
Is this, you know, I said at the beginning of the show that I said,
I don't know about a year ago.
One day America, you're going to wake up on a Monday.
And by Friday, your country will not be the same.
This is not necessarily how envisioned it because I thought people would wake up by Friday.
Is this that week, Congressman?
Now this is the preliminary.
It'll be worse weeks.
That's right.
Worst weeks to come because the seeds have been planted.
You say, what can you do to prevent the recession and the correction?
You can't do anything.
When you cause the problem of over-investment, malinvestment, excessive debt,
you can't solve the problem unless you do the liquidation.
And that's the painful part that nobody wants to accept.
And we haven't taken care of that problem.
So unless we understand that and the people understand it,
they won't know why we have to go through this problem.
Congressman, I've only got about 10 seconds.
Yes or no, has anybody in Congress come to you that wouldn't necessarily on your page
and said, you know what, Congressman, don't tell anybody, but you're right.
More every day, but not those in leadership yet.
Thank you very much.
From New York.
Good night.
America.
I love that.
Dr. Ron Paul lays it down and he's not being smuggled about it.
He's still ringing the alarm bell loudly.
Please contact your Congress person.
You're representative.
You've got to contact them.
You've got to tell them.
You'll hold them accountable for the biggest privacy in the, in American,
recent American history and their careers.
And we'll hold them accountable as traders.
Absolute traders, because that's what they are.
If they pass this bill in anything close to the form that it's in.
Now, in fact, I believe if at all.
Let them burn.
That's what I say.
Let them burn burn.
Well, we get sins.
You bet.
No way to stop that.
But let them burn.
Well, I'm talking about Dr. Ron.
He is now.
There's a posting on his campaign for Liberty blog,
which I have a link to in the show notes.
Of course, daily source code dot com.
Curie dot com where I cross posts as well.
And he is.
Here we go.
He's endorsing Chuck Baldwin.
The candidate for the Constitution party.
This may come as a surprise to a lot of non-Americans who say,
Well, wait a minute.
Can't you only just vote for Obama and the.
And McCain?
No.
Not true.
There's plenty of other ways to get on the ballot.
There's plenty of other parties.
Cynthia McKinney is running.
And Ron bars running for the libertarian party.
And for the Constitution party Chuck.
Am I saying that right?
Yeah, Chuck Baldwin.
So I don't know enough about Chuck Baldwin yet to throw my full weight and support behind him.
But I would almost say I can almost do it blindly if Ron Paul is behind him.
And then here's a quote that I ran across today.
It's always a kind of interesting how the quote of the day side always gives me something that really fits in.
And I'm going to give you the quote first that I'm going to tell you who gave the quote.
So this pertains to the $700 billion line of credit that under no scrutiny or oversight.
The Bush administration wants Hank Paulson to be able to use to essentially bail out his buddies,
fix all the stupid shit for themselves.
And at the end of the day, still try to kill all of us.
Here's the quote.
If you tell a lie, big enough.
And keep repeating it.
People will eventually come to believe it.
The lie can be maintained only for such time as the state can shield the people from the political,
economic and or military consequences of the lie.
If thus becomes important for the state to use all of its powers to repress descent.
For the truth is the mortal enemy of the lie and thus by extension.
It is the greatest enemy of the state.
So it's pretty clear what the lie is this time.
We've heard all the lies.
We haven't forgotten the lies that got us into Iraq.
I would say we have high suspicions about lies surrounding 9-11.
But this one, this one, my friends, is happening right under our noses.
We've got the infrastructure.
We've got the new media set ups.
We've got the networks.
We've got the links.
We still have the bandwidth.
We don't have the censorship.
We have to tell people about this huge lie.
And we should just let's be real true patriots.
Let's be real Americans and take it now.
Okay.
Let's take it.
We need to take the pain.
It might as well happen now.
It's inevitable anyway.
And at this point in time, we still may have a chance of controlling our own destiny.
Hi, this is Frank Hoover from Seattle, Washington.
Listen to your show for a couple months now and have enjoyed it.
So much that I thought I'd pay a little homage by aggregating from your own news.
Last episode, 791, you gave a reading of the fourth right.
And it struck me.
The thought that we could be as weak as to allow ourselves to be fooled and by the sheep.
And that's disturbing.
But then I thought that a few weeks when you mentioned Americans and their caravans.
Or motor homes.
I miss your funny comment.
You said something like, yeah, this was about Americans who have been kicked out of their homes.
And what they're doing is they're saying, hey, screw it.
Okay.
This is the frontier.
We know how this works.
It was only a couple hundred years ago when this is how we had to do it.
We'll live in our motor homes.
Screw you.
We'll survive.
We are survivors.
Look at these Americans who can't get them down.
So as an American, yeah, I kind of love that comment.
Especially since I was traveling through Egypt at the time.
So here's my prediction or aggregation or maybe even just plain old hope.
Yeah, Americans are strong.
And we'll abandon our government when the time comes.
And by abandon, I don't mean, you know, give up on the whole bankers.
You know, it's nice that a little safety net.
But the same time, I think, I don't know, it was before my time.
But maybe in the six years, we did something like this.
You know, just as a people gave up on them.
And forced them to set up the same straight.
Or at least that's hindsight or prediction of future.
So yeah, they work for us.
You know, you're absolutely right.
I think that there was quite a quite a movement going in the 60s.
And of course, that all got killed with John F. Kennedy,
who I do believe, although, yeah, sure, you know,
where his wealth came from and his family and
how man he had some of the right ideas.
It's always interesting how the good guys go.
The 16th president, Abraham Lincoln killed.
Yeah, I don't think he liked that.
I don't think he liked a lot of the ideas that are still in play today.
And this seems like an opportune moment to remind us of how great
and how courageous John F. Kennedy was.
Certainly when he gave this speech to the American newspaper publishers,
the Association, it's a well known speech,
but it's about what he already identified.
And with his words, which just clinks,
they just sound so eerie now to me about secret societies
and shadow government running the world.
And what we have to watch out for it,
it warns just listening to it once again.
By the way, the quote that I gave you was Joseph Gubbles.
That was Hitler's PR guy.
Press is awaiting a declaration of war.
Before it imposes the self-discipline of combat conditions,
then I can only say that no war ever posed,
a greater threat to our security.
If you are awaiting a finding of clear and present danger,
then I can only say that the danger has never been more clear.
And its presence has never been more imminent.
It requires a change in outlook, a change in tactics,
a change in missions by the government, by the people,
by every business man or labor leader, and by every newspaper.
But we are opposed around the world by a monolithic and ruthless conspiracy
that relies primarily on covet means for expanding its fear of influence,
on infiltration instead of invasion,
on subversion instead of elections,
on intimidation instead of free choice,
on guerrillas by night instead of armies by day.
It is a system which has conscripted vast human and material resources
into the building of a tightly knit, highly efficient machine
that combines military, diplomatic intelligence,
economic, scientific, and political operations.
Its preparations are concealed, not published.
Its mistakes are buried, not headline.
Its dissent is a silenced, not praised.
No expenditure is questioned, no rumor is preded,
no secret is revealed.
It conducts the Cold War and short, with a wartime discipline,
no democracy, whatever hope or wish to match.
Nevertheless, every democracy recognizes the necessary restraints
of national security, and the question remains,
whether those restraints need to be more strictly observed,
if we ought to oppose this kind of attack as well as outright invasion.
If you're a crime and America,
thus we'll all win free, and I will still be real.
Condition to respond to all the threat,
if we're a crime, because pieces are the soviet,
is the truth.
Just say we will bury you,
I don't subsperate through this point for you,
so shadowing the right thing to do,
if the rushes look at your true true.
How can I say my reason?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
There's a noise coming from the grass and getting to put the words in the mouth of the grass and getting to the nose such thing as in the home
So I don't leave any hope, it's the rain, your stress, your heart's echoing you
I don't subscribe to this point of view, believe me when I said to you, I hope our rushes love that children to wear
I never in a million years expected this song from staying to the top of the road
I never in a million years expected this song from staying to be a topical twice in my lifetime
Really didn't, with all the Saberadling towards Russia makes sense
I want to read you something from a little did we call the Declaration of Independence
We hold these truths to be self-evident that all men are treated equal
that they are endowed by their creator with certain unalatable rights
But among these are life-librity and the pursuit of happiness
that the Secure of these rights governments are instituted amongst men
deriving their just powers from the consent of the governed
that whatever any form of government becomes destructive of these ends
it is the right of the people to alter or abolish it and to institute new government
There you go
As we told King George, I think we should tell the current King George exactly the same thing
And I will be going to the United States tomorrow for two primary reasons
Well, it's really one reason. My people are there
We've got 60 some plus people working in San Francisco
They're still trying to be part of the real economy
And I want to help them we've got some extra projects
Some stuff that really has to I just want to get finished this before the end of this year
Excuse me.
I can't help it
But also I think it'll be good for me
Because I do feel somewhat disassociated with my homeland at the moment
So it will be good for me to be there
And I'm going to stay there for a couple of weeks
I'll be reporting from what I guess will be a form of the front lines
Okay, along with that with those thoughts comes the army times which is publication for
Actually they call it your online resource for everything army
Starting October 2nd
We will have for 12 months
They'll just read this literally beginning October 1st it says for 12 months
The first BCT Brigade Combat Team
We'll be under the day-to-day control of the U.S. Army North
That's a North Command North Com
The Army Service component of North and Command there it is
As an on-call Federal Response Force for natural or man-made emergencies
And disasters including terrorist attacks the army
Is now going to be I presume
Pretrolling the streets
You need to look through this article to understand what you're going to see and how
How the view of our streets actually may change
Fascinating, fascinating this is taking place right before our very eyes
It will not be televised
The demise or the destruction and certainly not the revolution so you owe it to yourself to keep your eyes wide open
And as not a link that I'm not going to read the whole thing
It's on the Huffington Post
Larissa Alexanderova
And it starts with if you must break the law do it to seize power
In all other cases observe it
That's Julia Caesar
That's the quote that it starts with
And it's a really well written piece
Understanding about this monstrosity
This taking place right before our very eyes
And that we should not stand still and allow that to happen
Please get in touch with your congressmen your representative
Let them know that you'll hold them accountable for treason
I got gas now
Meanwhile amongst all of this
The news does still continue
Pulling this from wired magazine
U.S. Attorney General Michael McCasey
Denied Saturday that the Bush administration in conjunction with the nation's telecommunications companies
He's had devised a quote dragged net electronics surveillance program that funneled Americans communications to the national security agent without court warrants
He's saying it's not true
Remember that name
Remember that name, Mucasey
Specific information demonstrating that the alleged drag net has not occurred cannot be disclosed on the public record
Without causing exponential harm to national security
So here's another one of those big lies
You know we can't prove that it didn't happen because if we actually had to show the evidence
Well then it would be harmful to national security
You know at this point who cares?
Let's just lay it all out. Let's just understand it. Let us all understand
We're willing to help we're willing to stick up for our country
There's
This is a link I should have put earlier on in the show
From the independent
Actual mainstream media proof if you can call it that
Coming from the independent up to 10,000 members of staff the New York office of layman brothers
Remember they went absolutely bankrupt
We'll be sharing in a bonus pool with two and a half billion dollars
So even at lower levels everyone's getting bailed out and getting their bonuses and it's despicable
It really is
You know when it's your own private company and when you're you got all kinds of shenanigans and you screw up the world
Okay, shit happens stupid of us to let your fucking game screw up the world
But I just can't I can't bring myself to pay you for it
Makes me nuts
Ah
Interesting that a lot of the links on the drop daily sort a drop.au slash daily source code
Or about the ongoing conversation about vaccinations
Hey Adam how you doing Dave and Rhode Island just want to get in touch with you on the mandatory vaccinations
They tried that in Texas and the governor was making it a mandatory thing
State-wide and there was a huge pushback on it where the congress actually stepped up to the right thing and voted against it
The governor threatened to veto and it caused a lot of controversy and it came out that he was actually
One of his largest contributor was the manufacturer of that drug
No kidding
So your instincts are totally right on and I'm glad to see that you're following this because
Apparently they've moved on it didn't work in Texas. They're probably going to try and do a
USA sweep
That didn't work so apparently now
They're going on to the UK in the rest of Europe. Oh, yeah, South America. He's up to good work and
Got a lot to say, but I'm glad you're on everything you're on and keep with it
Thanks, man. Take care. Yeah, so a couple articles for you to read through in the in the show notes
Death toll link to Gardysil. That is the the name of the the vaccine
Right the top of the story here a
Nothing I can't even pronounce it the nathalatic shock foaming it the mouth grand mouth
convulsion coma paralyzed a few of the startling descriptions included in a new federal report federal report
Describing the compilation the complications from Merx Gardysil medication for these sexually transmitted human
Papaloma virus HPV which has been proposed as mandatory for all school girls
This is from June 30th 2008
Now I think that that you're right on in the in the in the first case. So the the basis of this new
Vaccination scheme, which is being rolled out worldwide as Merck is a worldwide company is because
Their patents are expiring on existing drugs, which means
You know, basically they make a little bit of margin over what it costs to make him
You know, this is why you have a polio vaccine, which is cost maybe four bucks, but this
Gardysil
You know, you need three of these shots so it's about five hundred and twenty five dollars per
Innocent child that is getting injected so it's a huge money maker and the way to roll that out
Of course is through legislation, you know, we've never really gotten into the pharmaceutical industry
In any great depth here on the daily source code, but I certainly should do a I could probably do a full show about it easily
To show you how it works and and how they just want to give us stuff because hey, the man they make a shitload of money on that
But in this case, you know, it seems so highly unnecessary and then the second point comes into play
What is actually in these vaccines
A lot of people are blaming vaccinations for
Autism and violent death
Really, you should look at this death toll
Now this is a video mercury autism and the global vaccine agenda
Obviously not going to play that now. You should take a look at that. Just do some research on this because
He really is taking place federal documents reveal a total of eight thousand eight hundred and sixty four vaccine adverse event reporting system records
So that means almost nine thousand
Adverse reactions to guard a zoo up from a total of three and a half thousand which had been reported in the document just last fall
Okay
Who knows and this China thing man if you've been following that this melamine in the
In in the dairy products that's killing babies
Now the way I understand that the Chinese already are only allowed to have one child per household. I think that's the law
And now this one child they have is being poisoned
I've I wanted a little bit more about about this poison called melamine
Which is basically it's a cleaning agent. I think it's if anything. It's a detergent cleaning agent
And this I pulled up from my favorite source that of course will be Wikipedia
Melamine is sometimes here comes unethically added to food products in order to increase the apparent protein content
Very important when you're shopping for baby products baby food baby milk
There has the right protein content. It can be sold as such standard tests such as the
Killed dow and do must test eliminate protein levels by measuring the nitrogen content so they can be misled by adding nitrogen rich compounds such as melamine
So obviously added
For profit and for benefit of the corporations that are making these products to lie to consumers and kill babies
And I think this is a big one. I think this is a huge scam
And we're just seeing this in China, but this melamine I bet you in all kinds of all kinds of shit with they need to up the protein content wake up people
Pay attention to what you're putting into your face and into your body
Hey finally I got my go daddy codes. This is some really good news amongst everything amongst the financial crisis when you want to register
Hold your concrete hold your representative accountable for treason dot code dot UK we've got a great deal
You're going to love this for the first time now go daddy is making available and you can get this
At go daddy dot code dot UK
50 five zero 50 percent off dot code dot UK domains for the first year if you use my new codes
This is DSC 50 DSC 5 zero
50 pounds
If you spend 50 pounds which by the way it's pretty easy to do when you're you get a little web log and you want some special domain name services you can get 25% off
Of anything you spend of 50 pounds or more if you use code DSC 25 five and the all these in the show notes, of course
And for dot com domains 30% off if you use DSC 3 zero DSC 30 so I'm just want to say I'm really happy that we got these new codes
We can really do some great great discounts for our fellow chuckle heads in the UK and obviously for those of you outside of the UK and the states or else where paying and dollars
While it lasts while the dollar has still has some value domain name for six ninety five DSC 3 and of course a couple other codes
You can find all those in the show notes at daily source code dot com
Let's see they hit the phone lines again for a second here
Mr. Curry this is a Greg from Dallas. I just wanted to congratulate you on your transformation with Mr. Devorac
And his I think you're you're talking about no agenda from over the weekend. I know exactly what you're going to say
I'm standing work when he said bomb fuck north Dakota. I knew he was in and it's when it
Well it outstanding got to go you know
I've been thinking about that because John kind of sounded a bit out of sorts now granted he was in Seattle
We usually do the show on Saturday and set of Sunday, which was you know my issue this time I was traveling and we had to do the show a day later
He didn't have the regular set up, but still I think that in a way
He sees through all of this he he's true. He's a very smart guy. I think he does see the agenda set out by the evil energy elites
But he's just you know, he is a kind of guy that wants to back up his statement
So maybe there's not enough empirical evidence that he has or but yeah, I think he's in what we would call the classic state of duality
I could be wrong, but it certainly certainly feels like that and yeah, because he I heard him say that too. I was like, wow, man
You don't usually use words like that. That's mighty strong
Two more news articles. I want to give you the next one is from the BBC apparently 2% of the pound coins in the United Kingdom are fake
They're counterfeit and it's not easy to tell when you look at this new story. There's actually a little video that you can take a look at
But 2% from what I understand is very high and you can actually still do quite a lot with a with a pound coin, you know, you get 10 of them together. You got a 10 or you know, you can buy a meal for that
But people do tend to lose confidence in money when they find out there's a lot of it that's counterfeit that's going around it and they stop using it
And thought that was pretty interesting. I had no idea that there were 2% of counterfeit coins
And then this final this final note that I want you to you can take a look at it. This is revolving around October 14
And are we indeed going to see something show up that would be of extra terrestrial nature and there's this guy who I didn't know about but apparently he channels information from the galactic freedom of light
Adam de Grey is his name and he's confirming October 14th as it goes into quite a lot of detail about the size of the ships, how they'll appear, what the basically what the program is and I like everything that's in there, you know, I'm very hopeful
That there is indeed something that will come and save us from imminent death
But he, what I don't like, I kind of really hate this
Since it, you know, when this is exactly what John DeVorek, John C. DeVorek predicted. So he says here, since it is impossible to predict the future this event is in no way shape or form concrete in happening on October 14th, 2008 simply put it depends upon the
Project Signature of this event and its fluidity within the flow of manifestation between now and this date
And then the question is so if it doesn't happen the 14th, when can we expect to see it
If it doesn't happen the 14th, it will be somewhere between October 15th and February 1st, 2009. I hate that. I really really really, you know, make it happen already
Okay, you know, this is how you, this is how you start to lose faith
All right, what have we done so far
We're at
Okay, over an hour, I think, you know, I got some conference calls coming up. There's one more thing I got to play for you. It is time for another installment and a perfect ending for today
For this program, especially since I'm traveling, it is Ray on the Charlie bringing you the soundtrack to my life
Which is kind of eerie because you know, it's like here's my life unfolding before me, but it's also really nice to remember stuff
And the song that he's chosen today, which is indeed a true soundtrack as true track on the soundtrack to my life
Is one that I hope to play many times for you as chuckleheads. I hope you don't have to play it from me all to see
The game won't harm the world
Let's take a look at the landscape on a road trip through your life, or should I say death?
This episode of hadn't carries the soundtrack to my life, rings us up to a little date, somewhere in the future
It's gonna be a sad day
It's gonna be the day when we are saying farewell to our body and
Some friends of mine
God I love this
This is Jackson Brown with the loadout
Enjoy, it's long, but you'll dig in
soundtrack my life
Eventually, the loadout morphs into stay
This song was recorded live from August 27, 1977
In the merry weather, most pavilion in Colombia
It describes the daily practice of a band and its road crew on a culture tour
And the emotions evoke throughout such an era
In the end, Jackson Brown backs the audience to stay for an encore
And includes an extensive playout
Adam carries the soundtrack to my life, takes a trip up future lane to his funeral
The first to come, and the last to be
Working for that little way
There'll sit out in another town
Tonight the people were so fine
They waited, they waited long
They waited, they got along the feet
And made the show
And that was sweet
But I gave her sound
I was trying to love them full and cheers
That's the sound they'll never know
Well, then cases out in the thinnest
The hall then trussers down and get them up in the ramps
Just when it turns to me
You know you guys are the chance
But when the last guitar's been picked away
You know that I still want to play
So just make sure you're got all set to go
Before you come from my piano
But the bands on the bus
And then waiting to go
Gotta run on to the show
And to go
Or to enjoy
I don't know
These towns all look the same
We're just past the time in the mountains
And we're around backstage
Till the lights come up
And we hear that crowd
And they remember while we came
Now we go
Country and western
All the bus
We got this way
And a track that presents the studio
We got a rule of things and magazines
We got troubles on the C.P.
And we got to retire on the video
We got to go
Or to go
I'm a soul to stay
Just a little bit alone
Please, please, please
Say your words
Jason Brown was born in Highland
Jeremy, who is fathered in her conservatism
A self-assessment station
He's introspective, very ex-mailing
All the more, the sound of the California
Confessionals in the sunlight
The late 60s
And the early 70s
Oh, you
Hey, hey, hey, hey
I'm a little bit alone
I'm a little bit lonely
It's steady
I'm a little bit alone
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Take a little time
And leave us all behind
One thousand four checks and rounds
And ducted to rock low
Whole faith
By fellow American musical artists
And good friends, Bruce Springsteen
Everyone piece and justice
They're unknown within their fraud
That poor boys, no need
end rage rush and scrape
They're according to the state and society
Dunno, ah, there's no rights
I guess I can't say I had to, anyway,
but it's because we may not believe who this is
As if you've brought the perspective
All the time, what's he Got
Still have to decide
What you have to decide on the top of his head
I'll talk shit and swear
I'm the one who made that I am.
Jackson Brown, the world out.
Jordan, it's all.
So in it, all of us are glad to be lying to you.
We create more and talk.
And give it even life in your after.
And how about the song?
Is it the only one you love you or play list?
Be our guard true, the soundtrack to your life.
I follow the road trip through his life.
I'll drop the aisles.
Rayleigh Charlie.
Now take care of him.
If you like, I'll bet next week.
With a soundtrack to your life.
I'm 18.
I'm attracted to my life.
Oh man.
Ray, thank you so much, my friend.
Yeah, okay.
Let me explain that.
Yes.
This is the last song that should be played.
Regardless of whatever.
And I don't want to be entombed.
The lady Patricia wants that.
She wants to be a lady and a velvet bag.
A marble tune.
With other people, by the way.
She doesn't want to be lonely.
Me?
You can just burn me the fuck up.
And smoke me.
That is a directive.
That is exactly what I want.
I want my friends and family to grind me up with some good-ass
gonja and smoke me.
And this should be the last song.
Okay.
So, man, this is a lot going on.
I got to tell you that I feel very, very positive because I can see a lot of outrage
people getting pissed off and thinking about taking action.
All you have to do, you can do it from right now wherever you are.
Look up your representative.
Congressman Congresswoman, send them an email.
It doesn't take that.
You're sending emails all day.
Send an email.
Send two.
Send three.
Send 10.
Send one to all members of Congress.
Tell them that you will hold them accountable for treason.
If they pass on this bill and that we have to take the hit now and we should start as soon
as possible and control whatever landing we're going to have.
It's just the way it's got to be.
Anything else is wrong.
It's so easy to see that it's just prolonging the inevitable.
Now, for those of you listening, I know how you feel.
I know that you feel free and I want you to enjoy that feeling because you deserve it.
And until we talk again, which will be from San Francisco,
live your life with passion.
Another fine, medial presentation.
Stick it in your ear.