Delta Sierra Charlie 720.
It's FOOBOR!
$60 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
The next generation radio contenting my ears.
I like to think I'm flying in this dream.
I'm just kidding.
It's FATO Curry!
It's FOOBOR!
It's SMATO Curry!
It's FATO Curry!
That's...
It's not something that hits you right between the eyes, but you creeps up on you.
DJ Matt Height, step to silence, scored for you specifically for mashuptown.com, the official supplier of mashups for the daily source code.
It's episode number 720. I'm Adam Curry. I'm ready for some good times on this Friday. Hope you're ready because we're gonna go baby.
All right, get ready to sing along.
I don't want you, but it's ever so important to have around my heart.
And party like a rock star.
After all the nights we spent, coulda ring on the count.
And all the parties are best of, because you didn't feel like going out.
I can't see you, Stephen Tyler, didn't put up with crap like this.
It's not a making up for what I missed.
I got a body like a rock star, hit a bunch of strip bars, wake up, naked in a hotel room.
So my TV at the window, scored a bunch of endo, hit a thing to get, my mind, I'll be you.
By the telephone, pull the ramp around my car.
And party like a rock star.
Oh, damn, oh, come on.
And the more I think about it, the less it hurts you side.
I'm gonna party like a rock star, hit a bunch of strip bars, wake up, naked in a hotel room.
So my TV at the window, scored a bunch of endo, hit a thing to get, my mind, I'll be you.
And party like a rock star, hit a bunch of strip bars, wake up, naked in a hotel room.
By the telephone, pull the ramp around my car.
And the more I think about it, the less it hurts you side.
With at it, job, I'll love this song.
JTX, got a party like a rock star from the B0d Save Music Network, a music bottle of labshow.com.
I'll see that one get some play around. She's good.
I love this thing. I don't know where these guys came from, but the guy I used to do video is Well.
I linked all of the songplay out on the daily source code, of course,
In the show notes for each episode at dailysourceco.com, today is a phenomenally beautiful
day.
In fact, I'm so happy I chose today as my big production day, or I'm going to sit inside
and just look out at the blue sky, I'm not a cloud at all.
I see some contrails, they portrayals from the planes, we see that would be a gattwick.
I just had to position myself, it was a gattwick or a Heathrow.
It is a whole man, it's just these are the days that you got to live for.
But it being Fubar Friday, we have a show stacked up with all kinds of stuff.
And in fact, I want to just kind of stick with the UK for the first part of today's Fubar
Friday.
First of all, a little correction was to always appreciate being corrected on language,
use of, and or pronunciation.
Hey, Adam Man, again, one more thing that I just picked up on this into the rest of the
shape.
And I've been wanting to say to ages, but I just forgot I guess, it's not only in the
UK, you have no idea how much it's squealing.
I don't know.
Anyway, this is what it's about, not only in the UK, but in the UK, and for the listeners
in the States, and actually all countries around the world, I think it'd be very interested
with the situation here.
And I've started to make a little bit of a study of what is happening here.
And in the knowledge that Patricia and I, the lady Patricia and I always wanted to, I
mean, hey, she's the lady.
I mean, what do you expect?
We always wanted to live in the United Kingdom.
And we kind of said it as a long time ago when we were still living in Jersey, in New
Jersey, in the States.
And so we finally got here.
And although we didn't really have any expectations.
And if we did, certainly, the humor and sense of irony of the Brits has surpassed all
expectations.
You know, we're totally in love with the British people, with living here.
But there are some things that I've started to notice.
And I've made a bit of a study about the, I think it's almost a general apathy amongst
the population.
And there's a couple of calls I want to play for you, and then we'll kind of get into
it.
We just, well, let's listen to a little bit of anger.
It's always.
I don't think it's Mike here, sounding Western superman at the moment, Alias.
I don't know.
Yeah, Golden Brown.
He's a fucking tool.
He was, was a fucking tool.
He, when he was just a bloody, what needs in the prime minister?
I don't know.
No, I don't know.
Yeah.
No problem.
What's the door fucking echo?
I don't know.
I got, I got some reverb.
I know what you were hearing on the phone.
Yeah, so I have definitely changed my opinion.
I certainly was in the, I was hoping.
Let's put it that way.
I was completely hopeful that Gordon Brown would, you know, despite his, you know, or regardless
of his background, his political achievements, et cetera, just the appearance of the man
being a patriarch of the people, kind of, you know, really leading the country.
I thought that you had that in them.
I think he has a lot of those qualities.
But I definitely have to reverse my opinion of the, of the prime minister of the United Kingdom.
Now that I've kind of seen what he's been doing.
Of course, that goes into a number of things.
One is, without a doubt, the northern rock crisis, which he basically just took tax payers
money, 24 billion pounds.
So that's about 50 billion dollars worth to save shareholders.
Or at least a temporarily safe shareholders from demise.
And how many shareholders are there?
So this bank, like, like a thousand shareholders, which I just find to be a disgusting
practice.
And it's completely wrong.
And what I'm missing, and I'm going to build up to something here.
I'm really missing the outrage amongst the populace here.
You know, how, how can people stand for this shit?
I add a mech agent take here from London, not too far away from you.
Just a couple of things about the northern rock.
And the fact that there hasn't been up and up for all here, as you mentioned.
And I think the reason for that is because people perceive that as being the government
doing the right thing, maybe this time.
It's not, it's not about the saving of bank.
It's about the saving that under the thousands or perhaps millions of people who've got
money tied up in there and threw no port of their own.
Just come to choose the wrong bank, perhaps.
So I think the uproar would come if they didn't set in and do something.
Me, I'm fortunate I ain't dangerously near 50 now.
I ride a brand new Honda CVR 600R.
And finally, I love you, I mean it.
And I've said it in the 80s.
And I'm still saying now, great year.
Thanks, man.
I appreciate it.
Well, there is a misconception here, because actually, the taxpayers are on the hook for over 50
billion pounds because there's an insurance part that, yes, the government is responsible
and does ensure deposits all deposits on all accredited banks.
I'm not quite sure what it's called here in the United States.
It's the FDIC, which means no matter what happens, your deposited money is always
insured and you'll always get that back.
So that insurance by itself is already 24 or 26 billion.
I don't know the exact number and I could be off by a billion.
But what's a billion amongst friends?
So the guarantee they placed is an addition to that.
So I hope your blood is starting to boil a little bit because, you know, they're not really
talking about this.
And of course, why would they?
Because Adrian Pegg, who I know I've met and I know personally is a very smart guy.
Even he's gotten snowed over by this.
Why is the dog barking in the middle of my rant?
Stop it.
So maybe that will start to create a little bit of outrage because it's just completely wrong.
And now, essentially, there's either an internal buyout, which will make several people
extremely wealthy.
That's the proposal from the current management of the bank.
And then there's of course, you know, the one party has withdrawn their offer or had
didn't even put an offer on the table.
They withdrew from the, from what's called a contest.
So Virgin money is still in there.
And what they're doing is they're going to bring in 250 million pounds.
And they're going to bring Virgin money.
The existing company into it, which they value at 250 million pounds.
You know, that, of course, remains to be seen.
I think they, you know, they're last quarter.
They reported maybe 30 million in profit.
So it's not like a huge operation.
So, okay.
So that could be half a billion.
And then they'll go get another half a billion.
And I'm telling you where it's coming from.
It's going to come from China, which is why Richard Branson was in China with Gordon Brown.
I mean, this is China has, has, has welcomed out in the United Kingdom.
I'm not condemning it.
I'm not condoning it.
I'm just saying.
So that's a big mess, okay.
And it's fucked up.
And I'm going to get to this, to this wire tapping thing in a second.
But first there's one other thing because, you know,
I'm building up here to how controlled the UK population really is.
There's taxes and payments for everything.
You want to take a shit.
You got to pay some kind of tax for it.
Now I'm not complaining because I choose to live here.
And I'll gladly pay the shit tax.
But there's stuff like the congestion charge we've spoken about before.
It's kind of getting weird.
I thought I'd send you a recording on my thoughts about the congestion charge.
I live outside London about the same distance as you.
Which is about the 20 pounds return ticket.
Yeah, that's right.
Actually, no, it is.
It's 20 pounds return from me.
And I take the train into the city every single day.
I usually will take a car service back so that I can use my phone.
Yeah, just not to be rude to people and also just for the connectivity.
But on the way in, it's always on the train.
And if you take a regular ticket, it's about 10 pounds.
It's about 20 pounds one way for a first class.
Which I have to admit I sometimes indulge in that.
On the train into the big city.
Now, what I'll do is I'll look at a very basic costing of how much
it's going to take to get into Central London.
If I look at the congestion charge, which is 8 pounds,
parking in Central London, which is generally about 10 pounds,
then already on my own.
It's cost more than the price of a rail fare.
So rather than drive it.
One car, 3 empty seats into Central London, I'll take the train.
Yeah, don't please don't forget the actual cost of driving.
You've got to add some money there.
I mean, your car doesn't run for free.
In fact, what is petrol here now?
If I were to translate it into US prices,
probably about $809 a gallon.
And just cramming like a sardine with everybody else.
But just for the sake of a single journey with just me,
it's the most efficient way of doing it.
And it's the cheapest way.
Now, if I'm taking the family or if I'm taking more than one person,
it's starting to become more financially viable,
to actually have four people in the car.
And each of us paying their own share.
Obviously, for parking for the congestion charge and everything.
So the way I look at it is if the congestion charge stops just one person like me
from taking a full, sorry, from taking an empty large vehicle,
into central London for no reason, other than vanity really.
And yes, I would prefer to listen to my iPod.
I would prefer to have my own heating control.
I'd prefer not to have stinky armpits of the person next to me.
And this is exactly my point.
I was hoping you wouldn't get to this point.
And indeed, you got to it.
Of course, look, I take the train because,
well, exactly all of those issues you mentioned.
I mean, you've got to deal with traffic.
You've got the congestion charge.
You've got parking to deal with.
And by the way, it seems like since the congestion.
Why call it a congestion charge if you, or,
I mean, the intent, of course, was to bring congestion down.
All it's done is bring congestion up.
And I'm in the city often enough to be able to evaluate that.
So somehow the system didn't really work.
So yeah, taking the train is a great idea.
If you have to start at 9 o'clock in the morning.
And honestly, I never take a train any earlier than 10.
For this very reason, even if you buy a first-class ticket,
you'll be caught standing up because they don't have enough trains.
The trains, well, I have to say that the Southwest train service
to Guilford is, I'd have to say, quite good.
But that is more the exception than the rule.
And there's a lot of complaints about just not enough capacity.
There's all kinds of issue with rail neds who take care of the actual rail rail infrastructure.
It's shit.
And you ask anyone here.
And I'm surprised because Southwest must be, as I said,
really the exception because what people complain so much.
And this is really what I'm amazed at.
Where is the protest here in the UK?
Where is the outrage my British friends?
It appears to me that some of the great British spirit,
perhaps was broken in, I guess that would be the 70s.
When Margaret Thatcher really broke the unions, broke the coal miners unions,
I have a feeling she broke a lot of the spirit.
And then, of course, 10 years ago, everyone here was promised that the new labor.
In fact, there was a song.
I think it was to, to sunny and shares.
You got you babe, you know, the new labor and everything's going to be different.
Everything's going to be better.
It can't get any worse.
And of course, everyone feels that it got a hell of a lot worse.
And now we're in the middle of this credit crisis, which, by the way, my British friends,
you were fucked on that, okay?
Here's what happened.
Here's what new, here's what new labor did for you.
So let's just say Tony Blair and Gordon Brown.
If he was the chancellor of the ex-checker.
I love that word.
Ex-checker.
So these guys were responsible through the Bank of England for lowering interest rates.
It really consistently lowering them, keeping them very low, keeping those interest rates suppressed,
so that everyone would go out and spend money.
And boy, did you guys?
You spent it on houses, you got massive loans, all kinds of credit cards, and other kinds of debt.
And you bought all kinds of beautiful shit.
There was a show on Panorama last night, where Panorama's episode last night was about this very
topic called, it was the night before, repossession, repossession, repossession, a fun play on the relocation,
relocation, relocation.
The party is just over.
And now people are stuck with huge debts that they are unable to pay off.
I mean, it is exactly the same thing that happened in America.
Only in America, we're used to this.
This is how the system has worked for years.
And of course, it had to come to an end at some point, and I think we're coming to the end in the US.
But over here, I'm telling you, you are systematically fucked by your government.
Okay?
They made you get credit.
They made you spend all this.
We all had a great big party.
This is the most expensive country in the world to live in almost.
And we're now, now here we are.
We're screwed.
And what is the government doing?
They're bailing out the fucking bank for Christ's sake.
The bank, not the people.
They're taking your money and bailing out commercial entities.
That's wrong.
You know, sometimes I wonder if this, you know, the inherent on the hatreds of big word,
we're kind of despisal of the French by their British.
If it's not based on a little bit of jealousy, because you guys may have your fundamental differences.
But one thing you just have to admit, when the French don't like something the government are doing,
they get up in arms, and they don't just go on strike, they go to the streets.
And they let their government know, they say, hey, you know, dudes, you know, we're going to burn this shit down
if you don't change the way.
What are you going to raise taxes on gas?
I don't think so.
We're going to riot.
And you don't see that anymore.
Are you not, is it allowed by law?
Are you allowed to go out and protest?
I don't see anyone protest ever.
And now, now what's coming to light on top of us learning that private information,
is dealt with in a very cavalier manner here in the United Kingdom.
It's putting, put on burnt on to unsecured CDs and DVDs.
It sent through the unsecured mail.
It's getting left on laptops that are getting stolen.
Yeah, just all kinds of disregard for our private information.
Now, a conversation that started about the wire tapping or bugging of ministers of parliament,
has spread, and now what's coming to light is we're learning that in the United Kingdom,
there are 800, eight, I'm going to repeat that 800 organizations that have the right to wire tap you,
including the Department of Agriculture.
And the only level of seniority that you need to have,
it's like a senior manager can request without calling an intercept.
Well, let's just call it what it is Gordon Brown.
It's not an intercept.
It's a wire tap.
This is the surveillance state.
It is the snoop dog nation of the world.
The British people, and I'm just going to include myself in that,
are being watched everywhere 24 hours a day.
And the freaking Department of Agriculture, if they're pissed off about your law, I guess,
can request a wire tap.
They can have your internet connection bug, so they can look at all the websites that you're visiting.
They can request all of your, all phone calls that you're making.
That you cannot deny that this has got to be pressuring you.
You've got to be a little bit freaked out about this.
This is just, it's wrong.
And there just seems to be a general apathy about it.
No one's really saying anything.
And I was talking to a cab driver, the other.
I love talking to cab drivers, man.
They would give you a real sense of the street.
And he was saying that, and this is, I thought this was very interesting.
He said, we have no voice in Britain.
We have nowhere to go and complain.
And of course, then I start asking about protests.
And he says, no, I don't think we really do that.
You know, we keep it all inside.
Which, of course, I lead to the logical conclusion of why we're drinking smoking and eating
ourselves to death in this country is because we're unhappy.
You've got to let that out.
Now, I know that, you know, so maybe it's not within the British culture to go out and demonstrate and protest.
But it's getting time, my friends.
And I really want to hear from you about this.
Okay.
I really want you to call in and give me your thoughts.
And I think you need to take it to the streets.
And we could do it in a civilized manner.
Or, you know, maybe we do some flash mobs.
I'd be happy to coordinate that and participate in some, you know, massive flash mobs, which is a form of protest.
It doesn't have to be non-violent.
I think we have to scare them that we're much more organized than we are because clearly we're not.
And I will stand up in front because I'm living here.
And I got to tell you, this is, it's, it's mess up.
It is the Snoop Dogg State of the world, the surveillance state.
You have absolutely no privacy and they're taking your money left and right.
And this guy Gordon Brown, he's in charge of the whole deal.
And you've got to be really, really careful at this point.
And something else I've noticed.
Where, where are the people we can look up to?
What's, what's my daughter?
Is my daughter supposed to understand what's going on now?
And she's just as apathetic as the rest.
She's 17 like all her friends, 17 and 20 years old.
Now, they don't see leaders.
They see guys who were trained as politicians.
You know?
Are there any teachers to look up to?
Please, be honest with me.
The public school system here in the United Kingdom is screwed.
My daughter went to, well, they call it private school here.
But, you know, basically, state school.
She went for three years.
It was atrocious, absolutely atrocious, created a complete class society.
Where you can only really get a good education if you pay for it.
Or if you go into massive debt, massive, I'm talking kids who graduate from university with
30 or 40,000 pounds worth of debt attached to their name.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Sure.
It's, it's really easy terms to pay it off.
But 40,000 pounds, 80,000 dollars in debt.
Where is you could probably wipe out all that debt with the bailout.
You handed over on a silver platter to these commercial bankers.
Ask yourself this, Britain, and really ask yourself whatever happened to your heroes.
Whatever happened to you, Leon Trotsky, he got a nice pick.
That made us used by whatever happened to you.
Do you blend in to create a mirror and such a panzer.
Whatever happened to you, heroes.
Whatever happened to you, all the heroes.
Other Shakespeareaus.
They must have owned them.
Whatever happened to the heroes.
No more heroes anymore, no more heroes anymore.
Whatever happened to you, heroes.
Whatever happened to you, all the heroes.
Other Shakespeareaus.
They must have owned them.
Whatever happened to you, heroes.
No more heroes anymore, no more heroes anymore.
That's right.
The strangest new all about it.
Twenty-five or even twenty-six years ago.
Whatever happened to you, all the heroes.
United Kingdom, I want to hear from you.
Is it just footballers and their wags?
What is going on in this country?
Surely it can be better.
Let's not leave it full-barred forever.
You know Adam, I hope you play this.
This is important to me.
All the time you hear people saying, let me talk about the press of rules and technology and
spying and monitoring surveillance.
Okay.
Well, if you're doing nothing wrong, what do you have to fear?
My reply to that is, if I'm doing nothing wrong, why do you have to look?
I'm calling casting with Adam Curry.
Hey Adam, are you ready to be stumps?
Hell yeah.
Cause he is the princess.
Bring it on.
I'm ready for a full-barred.
It's just a number one-to-eight.
Okay.
And we're going to start right away with intro.
Number one.
Oh, come on.
Eight.
Salt my intelligence here.
I mean, that's easy.
That is, of course.
Kiss.
And I was made for love and you must have been late 70s.
Number two.
Uh.
Uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh it's Paul Kirk.
Uh I want you, I love, uh uh uh.
Hang up, something.
Oh, man.
Uh okay.
You got me.
I have no clue what that is.
And time's up.
Yeah, oh yeah.
And these are the answers.
From 1979.
There's this answer number one.
This is Kiss.
Tonight.
I don't get it all to you.
I was back without the new baby.
You were back with love at me.
And I can't get it all from you.
I was made for love when you kissed this answer number one.
I tell you this is answer number two from 1983.
How is the title like?
I don't need a approval from a chosen few.
Tell me what I do need.
I need you.
That's it.
Told you.
I need you.
Answer number two is fall character.
And I need you.
I got a point for that.
And this is answer number three.
That hell is this.
One new y Release A ho!
A releasing number three.
The rap!
Why are you my baby?
You might be bad.
You got me on number one.
Oh, eight.
And that's it for this week.
How did you do Adam?
I think I got two out of three, honestly.
The answer is hit test and also the links to iTunes
so you can buy these tricks online if they're available.
How did we found it hit test.potshow.com?
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Everyone else, thanks for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for 109.
So until then, take care.
And bye-bye.
Deep back.
Hit test at gmail.com.
info.
youngpal.com.
JNPOLVT.com.
Oi, Adam.
Yeah, you miss Adam, Terry.
It's Chris Lane here.
I've got a bone to pick with you.
Every single time you do a bloody food bar Friday,
I end up going to the iTunes store,
giving out my wallet and finding my credit card.
You are billing me, roughly,
about size pounds a month.
This isn't good.
I do not like spending money,
especially when I'm buying money on songs.
I really, really, really, really, really like something
to put the artist on you.
Just so I'd like you know that.
Of course, not really that best off of it.
Keep up the good work.
Where did now love you?
Meen it.
Love you.
No home, no meme it.
Have you win?
Great hair.
Something wrong around about possibly
you're going to think cock too.
Not really, you mean or nail 18 middle class university.
All right, that's it.
Anyway, I'd like to, all right.
Let me tell you, man, this is the only show
this free that's still cost you money.
I don't got a win.
Take the sauce code.
I got a kicker, he's sauce.
I don't got a win.
All right, the bookmark continues.
Rock on stand in the way.
You may crank it up.
Spread a wings and shoot fly.
No, it's all to be free.
When you're slave to get back.
LAY!
Now let it be, now.
You've become the star of me, yeah.
Cities are superstar, yeah.
I don't care what she says.
They no love when you're born.
Like I can't give them a littlestock.
I get to my bed, she won't unlock the door
This time I got to unlock the door
It ain't too late to start yet
She won't be the right of the world
I'm on fire, I'm on fire
This pain I've got to let it get to go
It ain't too much to stop it
Which is genuinely a juggler
I don't want my soul to feel
She wants to feel it
I don't want my soul to feel it
Yeah, I love it
Curricing of surgery time
He knows how to bring it on
From pot safe music network, Big Head Todd
Has nothing to do with surgery
But it is the the
The whole second we pull it up here
There we go
Big Head Todd and the monsters
Her own kind of woman
On football Friday episode 720 of the daily source code
Got some fun TSA stuff for you
Not just transport security administration
But also the Homeland Security
Department
What is a DHS Department of Homeland Security
In general, first of all
And I told you that this was the entertainment of the week for me
And it's just kept on going
On the TSA weblog
And you can probably just google this one
It's all over the net
The TSA posted a note
Apparently a lot of people recently at San Francisco
Myself not included I have to say
When passing through TSA security
Checkpoint Charlie
We're requested to pull out all electronic gadgets
Not just their laptops
But blackberries, crackberries, nukyophones, cables
You know everything
And the question was of course
Is this standard practice
Or is this something that's only happening at SFO
And they responded with
You know just a really infantile response
It's almost comical at this point
It's almost like someone is trying to be so hip
They're trying to write in bloggo speak
And they in fact they even talk about the blogger sphere
With an E
That's what they wrote on there
That comments
And they said well the bloggers win it
You're right
This was not sanctioned
And they shouldn't have been doing that
So you've changed something already
Which of course a lot of people are scoffing
But bottom line is
Dude we changed something
We actually
We actually achieved something
You know so let's not go over this too lightly
Let's not make too much of a comedy caper out of it
Because even though the language is infantile
And it's all extremely lame
We called them on something
And they responded
So I think we should keep going with this
I'm rather excited
On the other hand
I'm very frightened
Are you going to love this one
This came in from
David Johnson sent this to me
Actually sent it to myself and to
John C. Dvorak
And I can't wait to talk about this on the next no agenda
I have to do it now
This is kind of interesting
So we sent a link to a market watch
Press release
Which is pretty much
It comes off of PR news wires
So it's put up by the company itself
And this is a release from
Virtress systems
Let's see
Major General Perry
No, I'm sorry
V. Dolby
USA retired
Virtress systems chief executive officer
I guess he has some connection to the military industrial complex
Today announced the delivery of the first ten
Small arms training simulators
Of a 24 system order
From the Department of Homeland Security
So nothing really crazy about this
You know these are it's rather interesting
It's a virtual small arms training
Simulators
So basically teaching
Some agents or some department
How do you small firearms in a simulated environment
But here it comes
The ten small arms training simulators delivered
Our part of a larger 24 system sale
Two the transportation security
Administration
Totally nearly one million dollars
So you know I asked the question just a couple of shows ago
I said what is the only difference the only visible difference between
The TSA and the CBP
The Customs and Border Protection Agency
Who you will both encounter
Upon international arrival into the United States
Or actually upon departure
Well the the only difference is the TSA guys the people who are the security checkpoints
They're unarmed
They have no weapons quite honestly
I wouldn't trust any one of these baboons
With a weapon
And low and behold
It looks like the TSA
Is going to be receiving small arms training in simulated environments
Of course the simulated environments would include
People at checkpoints getting an art on airplanes
So this is a warning
It looks like they're going to be arming the TSA
Now something I'm very happy about Brian Noisent me this
The EFF as you know no love lost or won between myself and the EFF
I find it to be somewhat elite organization
But they're doing something very
Interesting to me
They are suing the Homeland Security
Administration
Under the Freedom of Information Act
Because they did not
Oops, sorry about that
Because they did not respond in a timely fashion
Two questions about the lookout list of CBP of the
Customs and Border Protection Agency
And this is it's a fantastic read
I'm going to put a link in the show notes to the article
As well as to they have a PDF file which is of the
Of the actual complaint that they're filing
So they really had no other choice
You know they asked all the right questions
Of the EFF they did a full blown freedom of information
Act
Excuse me
Freedom of Information act
Which of course these bone heads screwed up
And didn't get back to them in a timely fashion
So then there's grounds for lawsuit
Actually that's the only other thing you can do next
Except you know except nothing
But the questions in here it's all about
The searches, the secondary searches
Why people can't get off the list
Why
My copies are made of business cards
That's exactly what happened to me
You know why cell phone numbers are taken back
This is something really weird
I apologize I'm not quite sure what's going on
With the setup here
Let's just hope it hangs together
Um
Laptop computers
They read email
I mean they really go through even though I do understand
There are still some fourth amendment
Rights that do
That are valid during this type of search
Essentially they do have the right to search
But you know there's lots of really good questions here
And I'm very excited about it
Have a read through it. It's a pretty big document
It's about what's at 20 pages or so
Um and I could not be happier that this is taking place
Because we really need to understand
What's going on here
Particularly if now that the Department of Homeland
Homeland Security is also going to start arming the
Other end
We've got some stuff to talk about
We have the right to know some of this shit
So anyway
Interesting stuff happening with the
With the Homeland Security Department
And of course I'll keep you up the speed and up the tabs
Let us imagine that there's a podcaster out there
Who's driving passion is the automobile
Sorry about the weak pun
Anyway, he or she is
Car crazy and has informative or entertaining
Or just off the wall stuff to say about cars and motoring
To share with pod show listeners
Maybe his or her daily show includes music
On safe tracks for the road to nowhere
Or maybe the dark desert highway
If your show is like this
I'd like to link to it on one of the leading automotive themed blogs in Germany
In Germany
Well there'll be links to shows in English
Which shows Adam well knows is understood by many in Germany
But podcasters whose shows are in German
Well, maybe they can get a step closer to quitting their day job
Meldoich podcasting out to not an outside shunt
Thanks Adam for enabling this shout out
Malcolm from Abu Dhabi
Currently back in the area
You're out there
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
You're out
You're out there
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a nod
To the hardest work in law here
It's Jersey time
Yeah
Oh, yeah
You're out there
What do you say
He might even win this case
Jersey time
Yeah
Oh, how's it going Adam
It's Jersey time the official musical
Just of the Chacha
Hey, Gong Heifatroy
Gong Heifatroy
Happy New Year everybody
It's the year of the rat
Present the best pod save music
Now work on the DSE
Then everybody's favorite
Lawyer
Yeah, I know sometimes the lawyer jokes
Write themselves
But hey, I got somebody good for you this week
She's out of Nevada and she's just really really good
Her name is Lady Sinful
And one better than to celebrate the new year with
Then a really really tight hip hop track
Check this out
It's my city
Bye
Lady Sinful
It's tough
A little departure there for Sir Jersey tide
From the rock to the hip hop
On the football tip on the Chilean
Welcome to my city where we don't play
Big bond, don't sign a pimping all day
L.A.C.A.B.
Better two, one, three
City of Angels and your girls are ready
I love our hood and everything around it
And then we say he does yet still love on this
Back then they came on me now
I'm happy, y'all want me
My, are you my hate or my homie?
It is what it is and you want to run me down
I am what I am through to a running proud
Oh, my court has wide teeth and can't eat
I bet for my teeth
I want my get proudly
My city, my city is my hood so I'm a host
I'm letting me know my city bangs the most
I lean like a troll die here
And tell the love, hey, get up when you're gone
And I'll give a fuck
My city, my hood, my street
My mark, my life, my world is
B.S.I. Rock, or B.S.
In the air, it just city is high
When your words are the hood, don't stop
My city, my hood, my street
My mark, my life, my world is B.S.I.
Rock, or B.S. In the air, it just city is high
When your words are the hood, don't stop
When you're my city, it's like
Slot, fake, it's motherfuckers
The city, it fights, got all the hot
B.S.I.C.A.B.
In the air, it just city is high
When your words are the hood, don't stop
My city, my hood, my street
My street, my street is high
When your words are the hood, don't stop
My city, my street is high
When your words are the hot
My city, my hood, my street
My street, my street is high
When your words are the hot
My free, my black, my life, my world
These beats I've got, go a bitch in the air
If your city is hot
Rep your hood, cus the hood, don't die
Tell me how you're my city, my enemy's our pitties
Smash on a bitch
It tries to fuck with me
I roll like a soldier, I turn like a girl
What I do with you, you'll be sick
In the dirt, five, five, but for a night
But I ain't worth a night
I'll black just see you
And I'll put it outside, L.A. City
No, for low, low, to death
They call me the money
Cause they're your big girl
When you come to my town
You better act right
Just be on the knee on the knees
Come out at night
Puss it too, Tesla, and you look good
It got, watch what you step in
Stay up on the white block
This is my city
This is my hood
This is my box of bitch
What's good?
Westside, eastside, north-town
But without a bitch
You grow ladies and roll here
Show me love
My city, my hood, my street
My block, my life, my world
These bitch, I rock, so I've missed in the air
But this city is high
Wrap your hood, cause the hood don't stop
My city, my hood, my street
My block, my life, my world
These bitch, I rock, so I've missed in the air
But this city is high
Wrap your hood, cause the hood don't stop
You know, we don't talk about it a lot on the show
But every single time
I release a show, there's always comments coming in
About the music
And, you know, usually I don't talk about it
Just because, you know, we all enjoy the music
But this whole idea of the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
The hood don't stop
Better known as up-soul is really catching on
And really a lot of these tunes, a lot of these songs that we play with
They're new or old, they all contribute to the soundtrack of our lives
And of course, also on today's schedule
It's to cut a couple new ones
You can find it up-soul, OPSOL
.podshow.com, so we'll have a new show out
Today, I'm going to cut a couple of them
So I have a template set up and I have enough in now to really start some production
After I do pod finders and all kinds of stuff that I get to get done
But this, this comment came in was just kind of freaky
Hey, Adam, I'm Tim going for Morion
It's interesting to play tell-coat today
That I'll call mash up
It was a fan of a couple of realms back in the day
I'm so out of curiosity, I have to say I looked up some info on him
Interesting, we had discovered that you played the sort of name of dates
Mashup 10 years after Falcon's death to the day
Poor second information from all over the world
We can be a pdf of course
Apparently he died of severe injuries following his collision with a bus in the tube and it's a BCP
Yeah, yeah, he's dead
All right, that was freaky though, isn't it?
But I played it 10 years
The tenth anniversary of his death to the day
That's kind of scary
And I just kind of appeared, man
I don't know
This is a Dutch email that I got in which I'll kind of translate on the fly Adam and listening to the DSA
DSE for a long time big fan of the Fubar Friday
Reminds me of the old days of Korean vendingual that you used to do in Holland on Fridays
You played WOLD last time Harry Chaper and I got a little kind of melancholy
And I was thinking you know could you do me a favor and
Well, could you play another typical
Track from the soundtrack of my life which is really he says a really lame track
But it would be so awesome just to hear it again
He's the track he's asking for is every shala la la
From the carpenters that is not actually the title and I did some searching around and I found what I think will be a perfect
New entry to the soundtrack of your life
You don't I'd suit for which is essentially a remix of the carpenters and of course
It's about being young and listening to the radio and the shala la is in there and it's Fubar
Oh my favorite song
When they played I sing a song
It made me smile
Those were such happy times and that's a lot of love
Now I wonder where they go
But they're back again just like the long last friend
All the song I love so well
Every shala la la la
Every woos no shala
Black, black, black, black
Every shala la la la
And the start is just saying so far
When they get to the port
When he's breaking up
They can really make me cry just like these
Yeah, you're in the mirror, your dumb scream
Please you're in flames
more and more
Dear
Thank you so much for telling me
Back on theOS mode is gone fire
I am a differential that I have
Makes me dizzy
Don't much has changed
If the song doesn't love that I would sing to them
And I'd never rise each word
Those old melodies still sounds so good to me
As I know now, he's away
Every song I know, every woe
Still shine
If the song doesn't love that I would sing to them
All my best memories come back with it to me
Some came and they came and they came
Others like me
Oh, you're so good, you're so good
You're so good, you're so good
It's yesterday
One, two, three, you're so good
Baby, baby, you're so good
You're so good, you're so good
Every song I know, every woe
Still shine
If the song doesn't love that I would sing to them
Oh, that's beautiful, isn't it?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Those of you listening to the DATA source code
Whether you just started Who you've been around
for a couple of years
And episode 720, you believe it
Hey, I got to help a brother in need here
Check this out
I'm Chris from Limitown
Maybe you could help me out here
if I'm not an opaque internet tablets
Flash video does not work
Oh
Every single site I go to that uses flash
Flash video like Ron Paul's website
We'll help you to keep saying that
You need the newer version of Flash
to download there's no version available for the internet tablet.
So, how is everybody doing financial videos?
I am searched high and low on the mail site or on the KSI,
and there's absolutely no reference whatsoever
to people not being able to play Flash.
I know I can't be unique in this regard.
So, what's the deal here?
How do I play Flash?
A few weeks ago there was a month ago I was able to play Flash.
And now I can't play Flash anymore.
Everything's gonna need to update, update update.
Well, we're not on you, get the update.
Okay, okay, okay, hold on, hold on my brother, hold on.
So, when you have phone and report like this,
I've learned a long time ago.
It's very handy if you can tell me about the environment you're working on
and tell me what you did, what you expected to happen,
and what really happened.
Now, I got some data points in here.
First of all, I don't know if you're on an N8010,
or if you're on an N800.
Second of all, I'm not quite sure if the Flash was working previously
and now no longer works.
I'm going to presume that it never worked for you,
and that it's an N80010.
The only thing I can imagine is that you have to get an update
of the whole system software.
If you go to the Nokia website and you'll see,
you go to the N80010 page.
You'll see a link right there is a special download
or you have to download first.
And I think they have a Mac version as well.
I know it's certainly had to have a Windows version.
And then that will keep track of your system.
And make sure you have the latest release.
Could you may just have an old release on there
because you don't have to do anything.
It should just work right out of the box.
If you're getting, if it was working previously,
now it's stopped working, you gotta let me know.
But so please call in the reports like that.
Now for those of you interested in this device,
the N80010, you can go to curry.com.
There's a link in the show notes.
I've got a page there which tells you about it.
I've got a couple more sites that are linked to it like
and at hundredscreenshots.com.
And you can get by using my special checkout code,
my discount coupon, which is daily source code,
a 15% discount on buying this device.
You cannot get a cheaper anywhere else.
I know for sure because, oh, look, we cut the deal with Nokia.
What the hell do you think I was doing in Finland?
So please, I have a little check of that
and get back to me on the flash problems.
I'm sure we can work it out with our famous candy man, of course.
One more for the podcast, I'm using Network Paul Malikon.
Tell it to the bees.
Someone's drank the hive and blacken.
No one's sleeping well tonight.
Now the banners has come.
There's a thing that won't be seen.
I'm sure there's a thing that won't be seen.
.
Why she used all I need to do to my eye.
This is one street that I've been like and no one sleeping well tonight
Now the burn is gone
And you're from love, all the things we've been
And now the last one, the dream that's held in the crowd
I want, I want, I want, I want some air so
John, it's Paul Melanchon but indeed you always want to say John Paul Melanchon
Tell it to the bees, almost done with the football Friday
One a little bit long as I see now, I apologize for that
We just can't and a football Friday without you if you've talked
Checkin' in though, can't we?
No, Adam, I'm going to show you a little bit of a graphic thing
I think I'm catching up a little bit, I'm a little behind
The listening to last week's shows, I'll be done with a caught up
by the end of today
But I want to let you know, so here it goes
I'm 38 first of all, so that's when we fallen in between
In between 20 and 40 there
Born in Israel raised in Los Angeles
Now living in San Diego as you know
I have a master's degree, some advanced education there
I've been listening for a couple of years
I've been listening to my mid 30
And I've been inspired by you multiple times
Towards, you know, taking baby steps towards doing my own podcast
So I'm still hoping to get that off the ground, but definitely
Into the whole podcast and culture
And I'm sharing it with friends and love podcasts, music
I barely listen to the broadcast radio anymore at all
And I look forward to much, much more good time
Listen to you and other producers
And with continued good health, can you?
Christina, Patricia, the rest of your family
And we'll talk to you
Thanks
Come back to the world
I got a survey that I want to talk about after this next song
And I want you guys to fill out so that we can kind of shorten the comments
So if you can get me rather long
But first, cool y'all, and sunshine
Imagine looking that life, the roads, didn't glass
And the policy of the people's glass
I've been on the way, we got that asses
And all the homies got dubs and deets
And when the poor boys pass, they wave and say hi
And wear a grin
And everybody that you meet is a potential friend
And the women that you're right love you for yourself
And not your lens
And I pop and legs and heels for the plurries
And to pretend, and they know we ought to say
So no one hates you for the color of your skin
And that be waiting for this one of the pieces
Home near bliss that simple satisfaction
Like I play the acting grits
Since it's fully alive
Like I'm filling up a first kiss
And once you check out time, you got a smile on your lips
And the whole world is like a neck door neighbor
But to do your favor, you just don't be coming
A million different flavors
And I know it's got enough time to put it all in one run
So I saved the flavors we take
The feel for the ratings of the sunshine
And love was a flower spread
The petals about the planet
And the plants eat throughout every city
And country even adults, and I want me
And try to make some sense in a situation that we call life some
But we're illustration to help ease this strike some
Liverpool penetration to try to make things right in
Hope that what I'm saying
And saturate your mind frame
And help you put the pain and the pain at the everyday struggle
I don't need it all, I want to see all your bubbles
And rise to the top thing
To be hard like a rock
Because you know it's no sky
And let's be let it all sky
So when you face the face with adversity
Disgrossing sea and looking in the eye
And let it know that you can't hurt a G
That you put in the risk of all of the things
And people that you believe in
So educate yourself alone to assess your achievements
And imagine what's right
So you can see it in your mind
I guess it's better like sunshine
Sitting in the sunshine
And sunshine
I don't know what's left
Sunshine
I don't know
Walking in the sunshine
And sunshine
I don't know what's left
Before I continue that mean make one thing clear
It took me a while for the three things
I learned the puppy for myself and career
Got family in my fence
I went to like a whole day
Me like Moses brought the rent see and lead to the promised land
I damn it's blazing
And it feels amazing
I can lay here till a moment
Great and triple like a rain
And throughout the years months and days
Life is to pass by on the days
And I was close to civicity
Just waiting
Living life for the eyes
And nothing but close to your fans
Catching hot maven
It makes you to be a baller
But the answer's all lanes
But now I'm here and I promise to get my home
So mind, body and spirit
And try to lift every question
My life is hell for all y'all can hear it
It's just we remember the words from that
Oh, we're positive to each other
I'm living in the gates of paradise
And I hope y'all remember to
And even though it's where it's close
Each side come to no mind
It's okay because I don't mind
If you share some of my sunshine
I'm living in the sunshine
And try to lift every question
My life is hell for all y'all can hear it
I'm living in the sunshine
And I promise to get my home
So mind, body and spirit
Song was sent to me from Smithbrand.
No real accompanying note other than the subject of the email, Song that fits you so well.
But of course, although not pod say, if I have to agree, I'm sitting in the sunshine,
I don't mind sharing some of my sunshine with you, I ain't that the tree.
Just a quick yonet survey, you know, in Google Docs now you can create an Excel spreadsheet
and you can turn that into a form, so you'll find a link in today's show notes, just
fill out some demographic information and everyone can see the results so beware, you know.
They won't have your name attached to it, but everyone can see the results kind of make an open source
thing, so we get a better understanding of who we are and what we're doing as this group here
we call the knuckles Charlie heads.
It's Friday.
I'm a day Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Thursday, Friday.
I'm a spinal button for the Wii.
So of course, you know, I was rather harsh with my British friends early on in the program,
but I'm pretty serious man.
I think we should start thinking about doing something because you've got to take matters
in your own hands at a certain point and, you know, at least walk the streets and let someone know
that you're unhappy about this and all these little organizations, you know, government organizations
who are striking for more pay, that's one thing, that just inconvenience is awesome.
By the way, we're paying their salaries, so I think that we should really consider this flash mob idea
to stop the snoop dog nation because that's exactly what's going on here and is out of control.
Go ahead, look around, Google it, look at some news articles, pay attention to what people are talking about.
It's really, it's really frightening.
Now I don't want that to be the final thought of the week, of course, because I think that song
pretty much said it all.
I feel like I'm living in sunshine.
I don't mind sharing some of my sunshine with you.
Adam at podshow.com, dailysourceco.com, for all the show notes.
Please live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom.