This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Hey, Miss something, how you doing? You done with your next class of wine?
How do you feel?
Feeling kind of scary right now?
Uh-huh, so you're feeling a little woozy right now?
I am.
What do you wear?
I'm wearing pajamas.
So you got pajamas bottoms and a pajamas top?
Yeah, I'm simple like that.
I was actually...
I was a little Sam, let's just have a pretty alternate...
...and it's sale.
You made a booty call and it's failed.
So you see this?
It's sale.
Boy's are so dumb.
You're kidding me.
No.
If I were in Brooklyn right now, I'd be your booty call baby.
I was just so...
I was a booty call.
And we were all.
What do you do every night?
And if I'm staggering, if I'm not getting someone else?
Really?
Of course.
I think I do everything.
Every night?
I think I'm a little...
...when I'm ordered.
Yeah, there's a pattern.
Really?
It's always the same thing.
The end of the day, always go to the store and buy batteries.
And I'm going to be branded as the girl,
but the real, the serious, common stadium.
I certainly hope so.
No.
I just need to relax.
There's needs to help.
Everybody's surprised.
I'm just gonna take a couple of days for myself.
I wish I had more girls.
I gotta tell you.
I'm not alone.
I don't know.
Cut girl.
Adam, you got girl.
I love it.
Grim and on wine.
I really appreciate this, you know,
because I'm an old guy and this makes me feel really hot.
Okay.
Thank you.
Welcome to the DSC 727.
We're hopefully on this show.
Adam Curry will finally reveal
that he and only he was the mastermind behind.
Millie Vanilli.
Come on, Adam.
Spread the truth on the DSC 727.
With $16 million worth of airplane straps to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and dirty things.
I like to think I'm fine.
To this show.
I'm testing.
I'm trying.
I'm testing again.
I'm testing.
I'm test.
Dude.
I am tested.
I love, I love, I love
So people step by side
Missed I know I just haven't been you
So I know I just haven't been you
So I know I just haven't beenussy
My heart judgement in you
And I feel so depressed
So what's going on?
Because I know I just haven't been you
So I know I just haven't been you
Oh wait, now we're coming through like you
You dream come
Hey Mr. Gordon having you
Hey Mr. Chris such and dead
Can't sit for wait, now we're coming through like you
You dream come true
Love shy Mr. Gorgeous kicking off
Daily source goes up but episode number 727 coming to you from the curry condo
Very rainy northern California the rain has just been following me everywhere
It is total crap where they're hey everybody how you doing
It's your buddy Adam and it is well it's Thursday of course
I had the opportunity to actually do the food war Friday this evening
But things are going so well and with the new set up and I'm happy how everything sounds
And we got people ready to call in in the chat room on the conference room like screw it
I'm going to do a Thursday show and a food bar Friday show of course
The friends down under in Australia
Won't actually hear the Friday show until somewhere around Monday afternoon
So it's been
Feels like the week is almost over although we still have tomorrow to get through
And spend a lot of time in meetings today
In relatively small enclosed areas with lots of guys
So it started to heat up get stinky sweaty and you know
That's what business is all about isn't it?
So we got lots to do today lots of things that have come in on the voicemail
I'm sure there are some folks who have stuff to talk about
Who have called in to the talk shoe system
And actually I did warn everybody if you're listening now
He didn't hear the warning earlier
I thought it actually was not very nice of me to be using this talk shoe
Set up without actually giving anything back to them
The way talk shoe works as far as I understand it is you basically
You can set up a call it doesn't cost anything
And lots of people can dial in it's a great infrastructure
And I wasn't recording anything
So I decided to hit the record button on the talk shoe interface here
So there will be a version of the daily source code that you get from daily source code.com
And then some version of something
I'm not quite sure what it's going to sound like it will be at first for me
And when you go to the talk shoe dot com and you listen to
Essentially what everyone who's on the call was hearing
So probably pretty shitty sounding music
And maybe if people are talking amongst themselves
You'll be able to hear stuff that they're talking about
While I'm actually doing the show
And of course, they got people talking about other things
It would just call it into the voicemail lines
Hey Adam it's David from a Jacksonville Florida
I just wanted to call on maybe a quick comment
First up your pants I cranky geeks was great
Really enjoy that show
Really live into that some of the people that differ
I can usually get on there
Other than the tow crank and in how to show
Sebastian Republic
I also wanted to comment because I just listened to the latest DSC
And the follow was interesting that people
I found that
See they found that you and Leo
You had some kind of
Some kind of snack going on there
Yeah, that was after I did a cranky geeks
A lot of people did say hey man
It was in the comments actually on that episode on the show
CrankyGeeks.com and people saying
What was wrong?
How come Adam and Leo didn't get along?
What was all that?
What was that tension?
And I already spelled that by saying
It was absolutely no tension
We were just having fun and
And besides that
It's video, you know
You have no context of what's actually happening
It was interesting because something I noticed about Leo
He has this very annoying habit of talking over people
And I got to say I love Leo
No homo
Thank you's a great guy
I listened to practically every podcast that he puts
out on twitch.tv
But I've noticed through listening to
Years of podcast for him
That he does have a habit
But I don't know where it comes from
I guess it may be a radio thing
Trying to control
You know, callers and conversations
But just thought that was actually
Want to drop you a line
And what you know what I thought
Also, great hair
Hope you went
Love you to homo
35 nail
More time listener
Every kid
I like great demographic crap
Alright man, thank you
Hopefully Leo is going to invite me
On to Twitter Sunday
He did mention and he said
Dude, this was a lot of fun
You should come on on twitch Sunday
So while I will be in the in town
I will have everything I'll have time
I'm not going anywhere
It was kind of funny because he said
Oh wait a minute
Dave whiner is going to be on
Is that a problem?
I said no, of course not
I don't have any problem with that
And he said, well I'll have to check with Dave
But I have a lot of fun
We could talk about some interesting stuff
So we'll say he hasn't reached out to me yet
So I don't know if it's happening
But of course I'll let you know
And you'll see that Leo and I love each other
Man, it's nothing wrong going on
By the way, thanks to a
Sander Sunder, I should say
Who did the opening for today
Show kind of recap of yesterday
We had miss something from Brooklyn on the show
I see she's already dialed in
So I'm sure that we'll be able to talk to her
Girlfriend Wanker Girl
Let's come down from Canada and
They're together and they're drinking some wine
And listen to the show
You can find Sander's work at podcaststudio.nl
And I got a couple of
You know, I really love it when people send me
Intro to the program
Because you know, it's like having a different intro
Each time is cool
And that saves me a lot of hassle
One time that I don't have to create stuff
And you guys are so incredibly creative
And I received a couple
Different intros for today
So of course the one you heard first
Sander's then you heard
Obviously, well, we all know
PD Love does a great job on doing
Charlie intros
But there's also a two
Oh, man, I damn damn damn
I got to go to my Gmail for a second
Hold on a second. I want to
I want to make sure that I credit people correctly
Two pilots
Who fly a commercial
Here we go. This is from
Glenn FlyingPilot.com
I recorded in an MD80 cockpit
Between myself and my co-pilot
At 33,000 feet
Over Western Kansas
You've always wondered what those pilots are doing
Up front while you're sitting in back
And thinking everything is all safe and sound
And they're paying attention to what's going on
Well, here's what they're really doing in the cockpit
Hey, man
What's that on the horizon?
What's that on the screen?
Bravo
That's it. You don't have to hear it Charlie seven
Twenty seven
Who's that?
Big red retro 80s
Look and do the controls and the pink jumper
I have no idea
Are you sure it's a dude?
Yeah, thank you very much
Oh, that reminds me by the way
I've got a couple of emails about this
And this
I'll let me find this for you
This is a new website that apparently is getting some traction
Because I must have received about 20 different
Twenty different links to it
www.men who look like old lesbians.blogspot.com
Yeah, you guessed it
I'm right up there with the best of them
If you're tired of all those uptight award shows
Head on over to earmuffawards.com
And listen to the third annual
Frat Pack earmuff awards
This is the award show for fans of movies
Like blades of glory
Knocked up and super bad
Who will win the coveted awards or category such as
Best Sexy Best Celebrity Cameo
Or the cheese award
For dubious distinction
Also, tune in as we present our
Lifetime Achievement Award to A-Dick
Andy Dick
E-Tring podcast personalities
From show such as Five Funny by Midnight
Film Spotting
That's what she said
The Matt cast the typical Mac user
And the Frat Pack tribute
The ceremony is broadcasting now
So check it out at earmuffawards.com
Right on earmuffawards.com
Make sure you check it out
So again the rules for
Or rules the guidelines for
If you for basically calling into the show
You follow the instructions
Which you can find at curry.com
Or if you follow me on twitter
I sent out a tweet
A tweet
With instructions which of course
Lead you right back to curry.com
Basically you want to wave your hand
Virtually speaking and tell me what you want to talk about
Just type that into the chat room
And I'll bring in as soon as I can
Couple of other interesting calls that came into the voicemail
This one trip me out
Because it made me realize that
We're really onto something here
I mean like real power and podcasting
Although this message is for Adam Curry
My name is Constance Rockline
I'm calling on behalf of Dr. Murray
Saber and who is running for UN
So when I first heard
Dr. Murray and I was like huh
Wait a minute this is I
Why Dr.'s calling me
But it's Dr. Murray Saber and let's listen
Dr. Murray Saber and who is running for UN
Senate. Murray Saber and would like to talk to you
Over the phone to introduce himself
And talk about his campaign
If you would like to call me back my phone number
I'll just talk over the phone number for a second
5-8-6
Or you can email me
I'll just talk over her email for a second
No time to edit
C-O-N-S-T-A-N-C-E
At M-U-R-A-Y-A-A-A-N
Thank you
Alright so
What is up with this?
I'm like wait a minute
Here is someone who's running for Senate
Calling in to the voicemail line
So you know obviously
Not an insider has no real contact when they know email
Just through the voicemail
Saying that the candidate
Would like to talk to me
Oh
I like it
That's pretty cool
So now I'm a part of the political engine
So of course I went to
TheM.com that's Sierra Elf Abravo
Romeo in the At November
Actually the Murray Sabre in all one word
And well low and behold
I think this is a guy that I can support
Because the first thing I saw was a YouTube video
With the following
Well it's good to be here today with my friend Murray
And I'm very happy to endorse his candidacy
For the US Senate
This to me is very necessary
Because Murray and I have been good friends for a long time
We have strong agreement on all economic policies
And on the social policies as well
So he's going to make a great candidate
And a great senator
And it is right now
Because the economic policies
Becoming so important
This is why we need somebody
Murray out there campaigning
And running and being a senator
Because this economy is going to come unravel
And we need the free market
Hard money approach to this
We have the answers
We know how we got in this trouble
We have to do Murray Sabre is the answer
He's the one that can present the case
And New Jersey will benefit
By his election
So before he jumps in an answer
So basically you're seeing a video of Dr. Rompall
With Dr. Murray Sabre
And standing next to each other
I presume somewhere in Washington
I can see a capital building in the background
And so you look at his website here
And I do this and another one of these guys
Who's switching on
Here's his platform
For interrere and illegal immigration
To cure our economic well
Being by getting government off our backs
And out of our wallets
And I like this one
Secura first class education for our children
So they can compete in the global economy
And I propose federal tax credits
To allow parents to exercise their school
Choice rights
From my adopted homestay
New Jersey
Like it
Okay here's Murray
I want to thank you Ron. I've been on each other for the nearly 30 years
years and that's a pleasure to represent you in the state of New Jersey. I've been around
the presidential forum throughout the state. I'll continue to do so until February 5th
and it's been a real honest any side-by-side with you for all these many years to promote
free markets and limited government. Thank you. Good luck in your campaign. Thank you.
So I don't know much about this guy but I will look into him and of course I'm going to have
him on the show. I always like that. Anyone from New Jersey happened to be listening
in tonight. If you are, just give me a wave in the chat room or anyone who knows anything
about this guy. I love to know about it. And while you guys are thinking about that very
difficult question, I received an email from the Lady Patricia. She sent a to me just before she
went to bed. Actually it was an email with a YouTube video attached to it and I went ahead and
broke all the rules and recorded the song that she sent for me. I think you'll recognize that
if you were around in 1972. Love me, see you forever.
All right, sing along everybody. It must be love, love, love.
Love is love, love is love, love is love, love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love
love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is health is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love
Mach is the first
I know that it's you I need to take the blues away
It must be love, love, love, love
Nothing more, nothing less, nothing less than nothing
It must be love, love, love
Nothing more, nothing less than nothing less than nothing
It's such a beautiful song
And to receive that for my lover, long distance
I just make she feel good all over
Love is see-for, it must be love, love, love
I see DJ Stain in the chat room saying that he's familiar with the song
But not from the 1970s
But from its use in a toilet paper advertisement
Wow, wonderful, don't you just love what commercialism does to me
I see a wanker girls on
Wanker girls, are you there?
Are you there with Miss Something from Brooklyn?
Yes, yes, yes
Oh boy, are you not dialed in on Skype by your darling?
Is that really sucks?
Yeah, you can break it up
Are you actually in Brooklyn with Miss Something?
Yeah, I'm sitting right next to her
Hold on a second, let me just do something here
Let me, I gotta try this one
There we go, okay
I had to mute everybody else because there was too much noise on
Okay, so what you guys, when did you get in?
Ah man, it's not gonna work
What, when did you get in Wanker girl?
You know Adam, we're gonna call back in
Okay, you go ahead and do that
And I'll unmute everybody else
There you go
We'll do my son
What a bunch of noise
All right, well you're dialing right back
Here's something interesting that came in today
Something Apple is intending on doing
Although I don't know if they're actually intending on doing it
But apparently there is a patent filing for the following
Hey Adam, this is Monica for you
Just a story about a patent that Apple's trying to get on
On the man podcasting and basically I understand it is
Taking Snips out of a podcast that's putty been
And customizing a feed
But from different podcasts which seems kind of distinct
You can read about it on
Or at least why I found it was Apple inside your dot com
And it had like Apple looks towards personal advice
On the man podcast
Those interesting ones get come to that
Love you in a homo and all the rest
Bye
Yeah man, thank you
So I looked that up and indeed on the Apple Insider
It looks like
It's kind of interesting
It's something that is not really a new idea
But what this patent filing or whatever it is
It intends to do
Is for Apple apparently or through iTunes
Whatever
To be able to assemble a new podcast
A new file that you would download
Which consists of pieces of other shows
And the examples they have is
Well you may not be interested in the entire program
Maybe you only want one little piece
So you can take a little piece from this one
A little piece from that one
And you can then mash them together
And it'll automatically turn into a show that you want
Essentially
The same thing we have put together with channels with full shows
So you can determine the order that you want
So for instance my channel my on the go channel
You can see it at atom.podshow.com
You can hit play
And you'll see exactly what happens
It has an intro
Then it always goes to the weather report for Guilford
Which is an automatic robot weather report
Then it gets the New York Times front page
And then I think tech five
With John Devorak and then it goes into someone
Longer shows like Pacific Coast, Hellway
And buzz out loud and other stuff that I listened to
And I kind of just hit it once
And it's an automatically generating playlist
But it's the whole shows
It's very interesting if if Apple or anyone for that matter
Intends to chop up
Programs that are created
And to create derivative works out of that
I'm not quite sure how I feel about it actually
So for instance you could say
I'm only interested in having the hit test
Out of the daily source code on Fridays
And I want to mash that together with something else
It's I don't know
I have my kind of my doubts about it
If I think that's a good thing or not
How about anyone out there on the call
See corpaters and you read the same article
Boy that was a long silence wasn't it
Did anyone out there read this article?
No
Okay
Sometimes this live call and stuff really works
And sometimes it just kind of doesn't
Boy do I really need to have a
A moderator or someone who can a hand razor
Or are you on now?
It was muted
Okay
Well let's go back to Wanker girl
See if she's back on
But I'm here
Hey that's much better
Are you calling through regular phone now?
Yeah
The call let me use salsa
Oh that's so sweet of her
So you just got into it
You just got in today
Yeah
I got in around ten thirty this morning
My flight was at five o'clock
Thank you sleeping
Now what I'd like you to do is
I'd like you to explain to the audience
The story behind you
And let me just mute everybody else
Just so we have a better sound
Just a few guys
I'd like you to explain
The story of how you two met
Because I think it was partially through either podcast
Or maybe even pod show right?
That's absolutely right
Okay
Let's turn back the clock
It's time for a moment here
And around I guess it was a year and a half ago
I and my boyfriend is 10 years
We broke up
Lots of tears, lots of trauma
All of that stuff
And so I did a show
I actually
Wait a minute let me ask you
Let me ask you a question
Wanker girl
Did he dump you or did you dump him?
Very complicated question
No I think it's quite simple
But from your answer
I presume he dumped you
Yes, initially somewhat
But then
Sort of came close
And back
What happened?
Did he cheat on you?
No no no no no
He just went a little crazy
And started acting pretty weird
And
What do you mean?
Explain it to him
He sort of got involved with another girl online
Yeah
And I sort of didn't find out about that
So afterwards
And you have a problem with that?
No, actually no
I don't
But he wanted to meet her
And be with her
And all of that stuff
Okay, that's a problem
That is a problem
Yeah
Okay, all right
So you guys broke up
And it was a big big trauma
And at the same time
We have
Something over here who lives in Brooklyn
And she had the similar experience
Or she also broke up with her boyfriend
Or whatever
Exactly
She had a breakup of her own
And she ended up finding my show
And because the podcast
She was well
And I had a show that was all about my breakup
And she emailed me
And from that one email
Let's do many, many, many, many, many emails
Sort of a
Initially sort of
Sort of
What I mean in complaining
Probably a little bit at the beginning
But then it just became
About us hanging out and talking
And I think
After like three or four months
Sort of email in each other
I helped out a plane
And came to New York
And I met her
So this rest is history
Right, because this is actually
Become much more
From what I understand
You two have created some
You know, fantastic female bond
And you've pulled each other
Through this traumatic experience
And now I mean
This is, you guys hook up all the time
Right?
I mean, she's either going up to see you
Or you're coming down to see her
That's right, she's my best friend
Okay
Now last night
She's giving me a cheers
With a glass of wine right now
Perfect, perfect
Because last night
She called into the show
And she was a little bit woozy
And she had one or two glasses of wine
She said she's a lightweight
And she was pretty revealing
And I got to tell you
It was fascinating to listen to
So you guys drink it
Drink it together
I don't know
All of that stuff
Are you guys drinking together
No?
Yeah, yeah
We're drinking together
We're on our second bottle of wine
No way
Oh man
Yes way
Oh way, okay, awesome
Awesome, what are you guys wearing
What are we wearing
Yeah, so you're sitting there in her apartment
Which I think it's about as a big as a box car
And
And you're drinking wine
And you're listening to the show
And now I just have
Are you like
Do you have your comfortable clothes on
You curled up on the couch or
Just give me the scene
So I can kind of imagine it
Well, what obviously make it out of
Exactly, that's what I wanted to hear
Ah nice nice nice nice nice
I love to please the fans
Yeah, no, I know you are
You're not kidding, right?
You guys are sitting there
Half naked, I'm sure
No, I did, of course I do
Look, I've spent three minutes on you already
I need to know all kinds of stuff pretty soon
Yeah, so basically I actually listened to the show
Because I got into the city this morning
And she told me that she had pulled into
And so I listened to the show
And you know, it made me get a little bit
Okay
But it was very entertaining
Okay, all right
I'm assuming that it's just mostly boys
That call into your show
Well, yeah, they call in all the time
But I only put girls on the air
Listen, why don't you guys have another
Another couple of sips of wine
And I'll check him with you later
And see how you're doing
And see if you're feeling a little bit more comfortable
Oh, of course, we'll be waiting for you
Okay, I love that
Hi, that means the candy man
Once again with some audio feedback
This time, some feedback on your cranky geek
Geeks appearance yesterday
Of course, I mean, the four of you, you're all good guys
And you know what you are doing
But I just, personally, I'm having some, let's say
Problems with the show itself
Okay, all right, the first, oh, this is, this is Luke the candy man
He's my Nokia hookup
But we just, we just call him the candy man
And he, oh, he's very opinionated this Luke guy
And he likes to send me text messages
Really long ones that come in in like seven or eight different parts
Because they get broken up after 140 characters
Whatever the limit is
That's always interesting, I'm sitting in a meeting
And my, my phone starts vibrating
And I'm like, oh, I wonder who's SMSing now
I was like, no, the one?
Oh, that's gotta be Luke
Geeks and the four months, it's in, it's kind of for me
It looks like it's, it's everything
That is wrong with television at the moment
I mean, there was no discussion, none of the topics
We're kind of covered in, in great death
Everything was, was rather shallow
And then once the discussion got started
It was cut short by commercial break
So for instance, this item on
HD and video and video uploading issues
And everything you discussed around that
Interesting discussion which was kind of ended
Hanging in the air, I mean the show itself
It's kind of good entertainment
But yeah, when you watch it, you get the feeling
Everybody is kind of in a hurry
Everybody just gives their opinion
But there is no real structured discussion going on
And perhaps that's not the, not the idea behind the show either
But then I'm wondering what does this add on top of what we can see
On television day in the day out already
So it would be, it would be good to have your views on that
And yeah, it would be interesting to hear
Okay, thanks, boy
Wow, well my views on that, Luke
Candyman
First of all, please point me towards the show on television
That is anything remotely like cranky geeks
That even has any of the stories that are remotely like cranky geeks
Or any of the fantastic personalities
Like cranky geeks
Actually, there is a very structured show
I think it's a fabulous format
You have two guests
You have Jonsi Dvorak
Who basically is the moderator of the conversation
But it's opinionated
And the real cool thing about cranky geeks
Is you've got the shill
Sebastian the shill
Who not only selects the stories
But he's kind of there
To prod the conversation
Or to pull back and be quiet when appropriate
I think it's a, it's a great format
And you know, where else will you find out about a scuba car?
But actually the HD conversation
I have not seen that on television anywhere
So I don't know what you're looking for
But look, at the end of the day
Video, no matter where you're looking at it on television
Or particularly on your computer
I mean when people are looking at their computer
And looking at a piece of video
It's only a small piece of the real estate on that screen
There's all kinds of stuff happening there
All kinds of distractions you've got Twitter going
You've got your email coming in
Some other instant messenger
God knows what you've got to run
And we've got to keep people engaged
And that means you've got to be short
You've got to be in and you've got to be out
If we would make this thing any longer
Like it's only half an hour
And we go through seven or eight topics
I don't know, I'm confused as to
Is to how you actually see that that has no added value
Hmm
All right, let's see
Oh, I got the invite from Ranger Craig
Or not invite, I kind of invited myself
To go over to Alcatraz
And see if I could do a show from the jail in the base
Hi Adam
Mike Pico
Long time listener, all that jazz
I was listening to the DSC today
The one for the 20th of February
And it was 720
You're talking to the Ranger from Alcatraz
Yeah, I believe it's Ranger Dan
No, maybe Ranger Dave, I'm talking to him
Ranger by the Ranger over there
Craig
And you discussed the possibility of going out
And spending the night on the rock
For the podcast opportunity
To send some great audio back
And I thought that if you wanted to really draw some
Some attention to the whole thing
You might want to do it for a charity
I really don't have anything in mind
Specifically
And maybe the bail add them out
Type of vibe has been overdone
But I really see that as a chance
To do some good with fame and notoriety
And that's just my thought
If you're willing to do whatever I can from where I am
That's your moment in Delaware
But hey, just thought through the idea out there
Love what you do
Great hair
Love you
Love you, hope you win
And I'm going to leave that other thing off
Because I kind of tend to agree
If somebody's coming to the conversation
Late
Probably not the best thing to throw in there
Do well, dude
All right, man, thank you
I'm not a big fan of celebrities doing charities
Because I feel that in most cases
It's really more beneficial to the
Coat celebrity status of the celebrity
And I give my money privately
And in many instances
Very quietly
Sometimes recipients don't even know
That I've donated or have helped someone out
It is different by the way
With the political candidate
Like Dr. Ron Paul who I continue to support
And who is still absolutely in the running
For a public and nomination
For as the Republican candidate
You never know what can happen
You already see a little scandal happening
With the John McCain there
I mean, nothing too is nothing bad
Nothing nothing nothing nuts
He'll get over it
But anything can happen
You know, it's
You're basically only a heartbeat away
And every single instance
Hey, by the way, has did anyone see
The rumors been around for a long, long time
About Hillary Clinton
Having a
A lesbian lover
And today I saw
It's probably related to the McCain thing
Now all the stuff is bubbling up to the top
But this woman
Who is this beautiful Pakistani woman
Who is rumored to be her lesbian lover
I mean, this is
I actually got kind of turned on by the whole idea
Has anyone else seen that?
Who's dialed in right now?
Anyone see this woman
Who apparently is having an affair with the Hillary Clinton?
I love this
I love it
I ask questions, no one answers
Let's check in, Wanker Girl
How are you guys doing?
Speaking of lesbians
I'm lying down now
And where's this something
Is she lying down next here?
I don't know
She's like a stupid way
She has to consider
I've ever
You guys ever get really close when you're all
I can imagine where you're like
You know, depressed about your boyfriends
And you're kind of
You know, commiserating together
And then you think, you know, screw it
Let's, we're doing away with men all together
And maybe we should just
Maybe we should just try something together
Well, you know, she's inspired us
Oh, really?
Well, you know
Um, what you've been a big
Um, sort of the tone
And I was just sending me to pictures
I think, right?
Yes
Well, you guys would send naked pictures
To each other
Before we knew it, so
Wait a minute
So you would send naked pictures to each other
And that would help you get over the heartbreak
Is that it?
Not quite
Um, how do I say this?
Just say it
Look, it's our, listen, it's just us
It's just you, you me and a couple other people listening
Um, well, um, I guess
Sort of when we first started talking
And then we both had sort of
Our separate sort of online relationship
Takenings
Together
Oh, with other men, okay?
Yeah
And whatever we would send anything
Send them pictures
So each other
And sort of like what do you think
And who's who's like says
Talk louder, baby
You're breaking up
You're breaking up a little bit
But what we would send
We would send pictures to be men
On my, but before we would send them
We would send other and get opinion
Oh, for like approval
Okay, and when with these be just
The pictures of your face
With a little bit of top
Now
No
Oh, wow
Okay, so then of course
What happened is you guys were exchanging pictures
And you got kind of excited by it, right?
Oh, crap
You want me to say yeah
No, forget about it
I wanted you to be honest
That's all right
Well, now we'll initially
We were just, you know, we giggled
And awful lot
Because in particular
I am
I used to make these videos for this guy
I'm lying
And
How come this never happens to me?
I don't understand that
I've been doing this show for
Well, like three years now
I've never received a naked picture
I never get any naked videos
Wow, what, what am I doing wrong?
You have to be lying
You're lying
No, the only naked pictures I get
Are joke naked pictures, right?
So they'll send some, you know, like a photo shop
Or, oh, here's a naked picture
It's like a baby picture, you know
So, yeah, no, I don't get that
I absolutely do not get that
I think that way
I always imagine that
It's actually a lot of pictures
Or
No, not a single one
So fast
Well, we do that a lot
It was actually quite funny
Because, like, basically before we actually even
That each other
We've seen each other completely naked
And it's been completely natural
We've been completely natural
Yeah, I agree
It is natural
And I think you should do it some more
And maybe tomorrow
We are sleeping in the same bed
Of course you are
Now, would you be so kind as to send me some pictures
To a view?
You want us to send you naked
I'll just pictures of us
No, no, no, it would totally naked pictures
Are you kidding me?
And, you know, romantic, you know, like sexy
So, okay, just let me clarify this
That you want me in the cold to send you naked pictures
Of me and her to gather
Yes
Is that too much to ask?
Look at what I do
Look at, look at the effort I put into making this show
Look at, look at all the work I'm doing
Don't I deserve a break?
I don't remember if you can answer that question
All right
I got
It's all found to maybe in girl, you know
You think about it for a second
In the meantime, I've got
I've got Jersey Todd hanging on
I'll be right back with you
Hey Adam, how's it going?
It's Jersey Todd, the official musical
Just of the Chacha
Yeah, yeah, Jersey Todd
Woohoo
Hey, look dude, I gotta tell you
I am getting completely uncomfortable
Being your pod pimp
All right, I'll be your musicologist
But I'm not somebody that's just going to run around
Trying to find pod babes for you
All right
All right, yeah, you know you're right
I am a complete slot for the exposure
www.Jerseytunchof.com
So this week I'll give you a one more pod babe
Her name is Glentonisse
She's out of Kentucky
And I'm just really digging her sound a lot
I know, I know, I don't usually bring you some country artists
But I think this is something really cool
Because you to man
No, no, no, that's something to song
You to man
Hey, I'll talk to you next week Adam
It's Jersey Todd, checkin' out
Talk to you soon
Goin' eat the dog
Dog needs a bone
Hat just needs to be let alone
So needs a singer
And a singer needs a band
Man needs a woman
And a woman needs a man
And she's the man
I need a swat
Blue needs a shot
Teen need the cross
And I need a guy
World they've heard
To make it around
Like I need your love
And in the sun down down
Man, you to man
You to man
Because you are
Here come me to break
Tars and each gang
Roughly to fix
And for it's not to break
But you need another makeer
Honey I need to let you go
You to man
Because you are
You to bet I not enough
No more can do
Do me like you can
Do me
Do the man with the power
You got to throw you got to man
You got my heart in the palm of your hand
You can man
You drive me wild
Do the best I run tonight
No one can do me like you can
Glendonese from the bot save using network
Connercy of search jersey tied
By the way, the toaster will be with us tomorrow with more on the football Friday
He said in a whole mess of song
So, and I need you to be sending in some stuff as well
He's going to rock it out
I'll need it by the end of this week
All right, man, we're already at like 46 minutes
Time flies when you're having fun
Hey, Mike a girl, would you mind putting Nicole on for a second
Just put, put me something on the phone
For a second, please
Oh, hey baby
There you are
Hey, how you to listen
So, while she's out of the room for a second
Because we know each other a little bit better
I have a volume of kind of met when I grow
So, this picture, you can do that for me, right
Oh, I'll work on it
Oh, baby
I would, you know what
And then, oh, here's what I'll do
I'll make sure the range of Craig
That he hooks us up
So, the three of us can get thrown into jail
An alcatraz for the night
Did you imagine that through that would be
I don't know how much
You're such a tease
Uh, never
All right, well
Adam, we're going to bed
Okay, I know
I know, I know that after the things of the show
You need to do, you need to take care of business
There's no supposed to take care of
Okay
All right, baby, thank you very much
Say hi to uh, to blanket a little for me
And maybe I'll talk to you guys tomorrow
Are you probably going out tomorrow?
No, you're not going to be hanging around
I'm doing the show
Yeah, we're not sitting by the phone
Okay
Just send me the picture
So, I can tell everyone how awesome you guys look
Okay
All right, yeah
Thank you
All right, I love you, me
I love you, me
I love you, me, me, me, me, me, me
Okay, bye
All right, so what did I not get to?
Um, there was some northern rock
Actually, I will read this
Uh, this was an awesome article
on the register, which is one of, I have to say
When it comes to certainly UK news
But also some tech news
The register dot was a dot com
I think, right?
Uh, dot code.uk
Um, this was sent in by
Let me check it
Uh, Mark, could I have
I wonder if he's related to the famous Johan
Um, John Oates writes
Check this out
There was an inclusion
Of a paragraph
In the bill to nationalize northern rock
Which is this bank that
In case you're just joining the
Conversation
This bank in the United Kingdom
Who were bailed out by the government
With tax money to the tune of
$100 billion in guarantees
And this paragraph
Exempts the bank from the Freedom of Information Act
So
The legislation to bring the bank in a public
Ownership includes the paragraph
Which states
Northern Rock should not be covered by the
Freedom of Information Act
Man, this thing is really
Starting to stink up the room
If you know what I'm saying
So the Conservatives are the
Or the Tories, I should say
Are now coming up and yelling about this
And saying this is a messed up
I think we're going to see a major crisis
With Gordon Brown
I think, and this is
Uh, this is a lot of stuff going on
This is a wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong
And it's, you know, it seems like
It's just rife in the labor party
So when I get back to the UK
Which probably won't be until the end of next week
Looks like because
Well, we're working on version 3
Of podshow.com
Working very hard
We're working on tons of new productions
We've got some great new campaigns for
Podshow producers
We're also going to be opening that up
To a wider group of producers who are interested
This is a lot of shit going on
Anyway
More tomorrow again
Please, I'd like you to
To think about sending in some tunes
Soundtrack to your life
Anything that you feel is appropriate for the football
Friday edition of the Daily Source Code
And I will definitely see you there tomorrow
If you want to find out about anything that was
Played in today's show
It's dailysourcecode.com
For the show notes links
Music links
My email addresses adamatpodshow.com
And of course
Continue to live your life with passion
Wanker girl and send me something
And enjoy your freedom
Another podshow podcast
Music in your ear