What is your password?
Your password has been accepted.
Delta's share of Charlie.
Seven, two, two.
I'm bringing on a pioneering computerized ramp style.
The world wide web.
This is certainly going to horrify some of the people who are hitting their list and make it to this.
From Tom and Taylor, the camera's architectures of human division.
And he dedicated his architectures for human memory.
Are you honestly going to stop him?
Please like in the information and trust me.
Work in the way.
Well, insurance.
That's what's the problem.
We have a great number of highly educated people who know a great deal about very little.
We're just going to horrify some of the people who are hitting their list and make it to this.
The world wide web.
The views are that information, so we've come full circle, but we've yet been stripped
up still over there.
We used to certainly don't horrify some of the people who are sitting there listening to this.
Initiating shutdown sequence.
We're 60 million dollars worth of airplay strapped to my ass, the next generation
of radio content in my ears.
I'd like to become flying you to the future.
I just want to live, so really good that there's always a thing, so really good
that there's a thing, I just want to live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live.
I need another love system in my house, so I know when people are speaking about these people are speaking me out.
It's getting active everywhere that I go.
They won't leave you alone, this thing's they all wanna know.
I'm paranoid of all the people I meet, why are they talking to me?
And why can't anyone see?
I just want to live, so really good that there's always a thing, so really good that there's always a thing.
I just want to live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live.
Just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live.
Just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just
wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, gonna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, you just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just to live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just want live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, Just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, your your your your, your your, your future, your future, you'll be your future, you'll be your future, you'll be your future, you'll
When we come to front, we've already seen the ones that they started to
Now we expect it every way that we go
All the things that they said, yeah, we already know
I just wanna live
Don't really care about the things that they say
Don't really care about what I just wanna live
Just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live
I just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live, just wanna live
Fuck, fuck, I never even get like it
Take my cobbout out of that tote bag of cake
With a Или, Two yeah see baby, Know me though
Put your body, come in my life, we burn
But respect against that power
And I'm sure you heard it
Got a new self, oh yeah
I'm keep lying to let my head touch you
But put it my face
And keep it in my face
And keep it in my body, we just go on the same
On this war guy, it's all right
I know you know what's in this world and in me
Woo!
Get come down, woo!
Ready and out
Get come down, boys, by the same
Woo! Get come down, woo!
Ready and out
How you like me now watching
We left the same
So what you talking about
I'm running out my mouth
I don't think we're done
We're done in reality, we know this dream
That each dreams know, we know
We're done in reality, we know
Do what you do, yeah my coolies
They true, all school know
That you'll call when they're chosen to feel
We're real, we're out for the time
To war just in case you've got
What's the stage, we're my life
So what you got
You think you know what's in this world and in me
On this war guy, it's all right
I know you know what's in this world and in me
Woo!
Get come down, woo!
Ready and out
Get come down, boys, by the same
Woo!
Get come down, woo!
Ready and out
Get come down, boys, by the same
Woo!
Get come down, woo!
Ready and out
Get come down, boys, by the same
Woo!
Get come down, woo!
Ready and out
Get come down, boys, by the same
Woo!
Hey, you know
I really had no idea that it was that long
I was going for something totally new
On the mashup tip, kicking it off with
For that kind of freaky intro
From radio orphans, the worldwide web
But this mashup is like, you know, 11 minutes long
Didn't quite realize that
Everybody walking a daily source code
Episode number 722 coming you to you
From the attic at the curry manner
And the affluent suburb of Suri
Known as Gilford, some call it a city
I just want to continue to call it an affluent suburb
Yeah, you know
I kicked it off with that kind of mysterious bit
Today because the news that I expected to come out
And of course we've been talking about this for
What three or four weeks now
Now it's all over the BBC Radio 2
How to Big Peace on it
What do I hear crackling here?
Do you hear crackling in the sound?
Oh man, I still got to stabilize all this shit
To the talking about the tax world-wide tax levy
They want to put on to non-domassiled residents of the
United Kingdom and my I got to tell you
You know for those of you living in the UK
I mean, wow, what a lot of misinformation is given out
So I know I've discussed this to some detail
I know agenda and on the daily source code
But what's happening now is you can hear
There's this complete hatred of rich foreigners who are living here
And apparently not paying the same taxes as everyone else
Let me just set you straight
If you work here in the United Kingdom you have to pay taxes
In the United Kingdom this has nothing to do with living
And working here and paying taxes has nothing to do with living here
And paying your council taxes or taxes on any other services or goods
Of course this is only if you earn money in another country
Where you typically would be taxed by the country that you made the money in
The United Kingdom now wants to tax anyone who's living here
Worldwide for those earnings or you can buy yourself
You can buy your way out of it by paying 30,000 pounds a year
So it is not I repeat not
A law made to get those rich fuckers who are not paying their taxes here
In fact this is the entire reason I'm going through a whole tax overhaul
Because clearly we have an office here now
I'm actually really working here
I fly back and forth to California
But it makes sense to pay at least some of my wages taxes on that here in this country
And I'm happy to do it because I'm working here
Of course I'll also be paid here which is which is the name difference
Up until now it was the United States now if I wanted to bring that money in
That I was paid in the United States
I pay taxes on the US
If I want to bring it in
If it was sitting in my bank account for one second or longer
I have to pay it and it actually has to be separated out
It has to be very clear that there's interest that I made on that money
That is taxable when you bring it into the United Kingdom
So if I made after taxes a hundred thousand dollars
I want to bring it into the United Kingdom
I would have to pay I think four or five or tax over the four or five percent interest
Or if I made more money with it then I'd pay tax over that
So it's really the opposite of what people are thinking here
It is actually the UK trying to stretch its tentacles out into other countries territory
And start taking tax levies from money made in other countries
Which of course I believe belongs in the country where the money was made
Where it's spinning around in that economy
No need to go into it any deeper than that
Just that I'm very disappointed to hear the BBC distributing such incredible disinformation
It was I woke up this morning right in early of course
Whoops, sorry about that. You know I take out the trash myself here
You didn't know that didn't you?
And it has to be out by seven thirty otherwise you get screwed
Because we're first on the list for some reason
And I saw the
The
The missed outside I'm like oh man this is not going to be a good day
And then I looked at my pilot whether report and said you know what
Somewhere around noon it's going to clear up and it is now actually a little bit later than expected today for the show
It's five past two
Oh man another beautiful day
Blue skies no clouds little bit of wind
And once again instead of flying
I'm here seconded off with you guys
Adam you're always talking about the weather
How much you like blue skies you don't talk
You don't like anything but blue sky
You don't like talking about snow
You know it's the weather's always crappy
There's great skies and whatever
Why don't you just move the California?
Seriously man
You should you think it was beautiful on Friday you should see it here
Fifty nine sixty it's going to be mid sixty today
The like sixty five it's beautiful man
It's been in London for like weather
Move to where they have weather five
I did
I appreciate thought but obviously we didn't move here for the weather
We moved here because we wanted to be here in a different life different lifestyle different type of people different humor
A huge sense of irony all things that we love entirely
Now I don't think we would ever have considered moving here for the weather
But that of course makes it that much more extra special
When you look at the weather and it's absolutely beautiful
Comic strip
Checking in from the mobile conference in Barcelona
It is our EU correspondent the one and only comic strip blogger
We'll start this
I don't know
You're from Barcelona, I beat you
Do you remember that Queen song by us alone
Of course I did
It feels this way here
So
EU news
The fringe fuckers have a budget deficit or in other words
I printing much too much Euro money
What weekends the whole currency
And pieces of solid Eurozone countries
Anyways here in Barcelona
But mobile where at congress 2008
Formerly known as 3GSM takes place
And now also
Summer weeks and turns to the dark side
It means Windows Mobile
While only Nokia remains resistant
To the appeal of the dark side
And shows more as 60 phones
Powered by Symbian
And this time additionally with mobile TV in standard DVBH
So
Adios
Muchacho peludo
You know
Yeah, that is kind of interesting
I've been following that that
Basically Windows Mobile is a huge operating system
For smartphones and mobile devices
And I guess it was a report that I read recently
That talked about getting all that crap again
Just static
I don't know if you guys can hear that
When I listen back to the show
If you can't hear it, I'll never talk about it again
So apparently
Nokia is licensing so much from Microsoft
Including their Windows media player
Technology
I don't know some other bits and bobs
People are actually questioning why they don't just take a full on
Windows media mobile license
And put that on to their phones
And of course they've made a huge investment in Symbian
So it's kind of interesting to watch
They have to strap on all these different bits and bobs
To make it compatible with the mainstream
Of course the one thing everyone really wants
Is quick time
Which I don't think Apple licenses that to third parties
I could be wrong
But it certainly doesn't seem like people are integrating that
So comic strip blogger I'm sure you're checking with more
Speaking of cell phones
I got a call about a week ago
Someone asked me to look into the headphone jack of my previously submerged iPhone
Apparently there's a little sensor in there
That turns a different color when the phone has met with moisture
I couldn't quite tell looking into my hole
But some other people know about the hole
Hey Adam it's Jack the podcast are formerly known as Jack
And now working in the wireless industry
So just to clarify there are in all cell phones
A moisture indicator
Just typically a square or round little patch
Usually in the battery compartment
Which typically turns red
When the phone has been exposed to moisture
It doesn't have to be a dunk in the water
It could be you keep it in your waste band when you go jogging
And the perspiration has gotten in there
But we'll void the warranty
And typically causes the things to get completely food bar
So if you're sweating that much that it's filling up the hole on your iPhone
I think you got other problems other than
Discolleration of a sensor
I do have that
And the voice of experience as I know
And have been for some time working in the industry
Oh, male 48 middle-class
Living on the beautiful suncoats west side of Florida
And hey, love you me and it great hair
Hope you win
Alright man, thank you. Love you me and the homo
Yeah, so I'm getting my Nokia E61
I hear opening up the battery compartment
I had licked the oh look at that
Well low and behold
There were a couple episodes ago
I licked what I thought might be the indicator strip
Well my licked has paid off
Because it is now a
Let's say it's like a shade of pink
Kind of pinkish reddish and some spots
I only just licked it lightly
I mean, I'm not a real phone snogger
But I guess you're right
I didn't know that. Interesting
So if your phone meets with water
There's no way you can fool them
Oh, we learned something here
That's interesting. Of course, now I can't get my
There we go, get my phone back together
Ah, there we go. That's all good
Thanks man, really appreciate that
Of course, so we had
I had a chucklehead chucklehead
That's a new one
A Charlie and a chuckle chucklehead
We had a chucklehead a listener of the show
Call in that he was having flash problems
With his internet tablet
And I asked him to give me a little more proper report
As to what his problems were
I can basically help you fix anything
On your computer, on your cell phone
I'm really good at it
But when people just say, that doesn't work
Don't tell me what kind of cell phone
I need all kinds of information
What you expected to happen, what actually did happen
You know, send it in any time
So he came back and here's the redux of the flash problems
On what turns out to be the
And 800 with the new OS 2008
This is a real gear head moment
What's cool about us?
We also have a solution for one of the chuckleheads
Adam, Chris and Levittown
With the internet tablet
Flash was working
From running at 800
I don't want you to new camera on the
At 810
Like a lack of a memory card slot
So I got to 800
So it was half the price
I am running the latest software
OS 2008
I just updated it
3 or 4 weeks ago
When I got the tablet
Flash was working
Little slow little choppy could work
And then I started my PC
All the site stopped working
And I had to download the update
So I checked the tablet
And it too stopped working
So I had to get an update
I think this is when they went to the 8264
Flash update for a flash 9
Or whatever it was
So how do I have to apply some of the tablet
It's just a normal upgrade process
And my version is more comfortable now
But I have the latest version of OS 2008
So I don't know how to work around that
Bye
Alright Chris from Levittown
So I got an answer for you man
And it seems to be relatively simple
I'm not hearing all of that
I'm thinking well you know
It could be a couple of things
But if he's got the flash may not perform as well
On the 800 as it does on the 800 and 10
Which of course you can purchase at a 15% discount
From podshowoffers.com
Slash N80010
Use my checkout code
Daily source code for that 15% discount
But of course it could also be something out
Something much simpler
Edom is rolling from dot compass
You all guy who had the issue with the Nokia N810
On show 720 saying that the flash didn't work anymore
I found this on my N810
And if you
Every now and again for some odd reason
It decides to disable the plugins
Now to enable the plugins
You need to open up the browser
Click on the little icon on the bottom
Right hand side
Select
I think it's plugins or add-ons
I can't remember I've not got to open something here
And you go through an N9Able
Which ever plugins that you want
The most important one being flash
And then he's got it
Anyway, thanks a lot
Yes
Mail
Bold
London
Great hair
Thank you
Thank you very much
I appreciate it
You know I think that could actually
Could be the fix and look at that
It came up on episode number 720
We're taking care of it in episode number 720
I'm sorry
It doesn't get much better than that
You know what I'm saying?
At your service
Daily source code
On Tuesday February 12 with Mike Erika
Screaming like a stone
Over the surveillance
Before I know
I'll smooth the rock that my home got had strong
And I'll just look in for my home
I'll just look in for my home
Until I fall through the water
Back through the water
Into the clear green
Where I'm new trained
Screaming like a stone
Many miles traveled here
Many, many more
Left to go
And I am never afraid
Of the things I've found
No, no
And I won't be afraid
If I start slowing down
And I'll just walk through the water
Back through the water
For you to ride back
Into the clear green
And for brand new
And I don't know
Where I'm going to
I just give it no
And take me proud of you
And believe that when I'm done
I know I'm going to crash
You saw the rest
Saw the rest
You saw
Fall through the water
hopes you will know to me
Take me away
Screaming like a stone
Over the sermons, before I know
I'm through the rock in my home, God has strong
And I'm just looking for my home
I'm just looking for my home
And I'm through
And I'm just looking for my home
And I'm looking for my home
music network track from 2006 you can find a link to that in the show notes for this program
at DailySourceco.com for convenience crossposted to curry.com for your enjoyment.
I do want to stay in the UK with a couple more stories just because the news seems to be coming
out of the UK today. More about the Northern Rock Bay allowed. This is a huge lending bank mainly
for mortgages that was hit severely by the subprime crisis although the whole, you know,
this whole shabang has been, I believe, kind of swept underneath the rug by a quick 24 billion
pound that's almost a 50 billion dollar guarantee by the Bank of England. In addition to the
deposits being secured, of course this is a very complicated issue and it absolutely has to do
with a global credit crisis and I got two actually I have one audio comment I'm going to play
for your first and then I have what I will just maybe a new financial savant who's checked in
with some real information about how all this stuff works, how all this stuff works.
I first, a bit of history on this Bank Northern Rock located in the north of the United
Kingdom. Hi Adam, it's a clinic Jones from right now I'm in the middle of the Worcester,
no I'm in the middle of Swindering, Wilchester. Northern Rock is to be a mutual building society
it used to be owned by the depositors and the borrowers but those are really
total greedy fuckets voted to be mutualised in Northern Rock building society to turn it in.
Don't hold back man, I love that. So a company and then they became shareholders as opposed to
actual owners of the company. So they they've voted themselves to become shareholders because
they want to deliver and greed. I got no sympathy with them, they put themselves in
that position. Wilchester, it's like I want my 50 million pounds back please. Thanks.
But I hear that my brother. For that tax that I don't have to pay that didn't actually go
to bailout shareholders. Although there is a contrarian view, Aryan boss I presume from the
Netherlands rights in Adam enjoyed your rant on the Northern Rock bailout on DSC 708. I have to say
the way you tell it makes it sound about right, however you're wrong. And here's why.
First of all, the money is not handed over to Northern Rock. It's a loan. So the tax payers will
get it back with interest but that's not your point nor is it mine. I will just stand still
by that for a second. Obviously it's a guarantee for the loans that Northern Rock has to pay.
So it is at risk. It's not a riskless loan. The real issue though and here it comes as Aryan is
settlement risk. This is interesting stuff. All financial institutions lend money to each other
all of the time in all times of all types of currencies. Yes, I'm aware. This is a foreign exchange
but mainly derivatives where I believe the big problem is coming from. That's me editorializing
by the way, continuing with Aryan's words. They do this to either earn a few cents on money. They
have temporarily available or to cover a temporary liquidity hole they might have. These periods
can be very short. They can be as short as a few hours but mostly they are a few days. This money
can go around the world in a day. In fact, they can go around the world several times in a day.
This of course means that the whole financial sector is very much tied into each other. So what
would happen if one party could not pay one of its day loans? The receiving end would be defaulting
as well as to their creditors. This is why we in banking risk management would call a system. This is what
we in banking risk management would call a system-wide failure. The most well known occurrence
of this is the failure of a small German bank called Bunkhausherstadt to settle their Deutschmark payments.
In a result, a whole chain effect of defaults rippled through the financial world because of
this default and that he has a link to it actually. I guess I'll put that in the show now. So
if Northern Rock would not have had that loan, it would not be able to settle their own outstandings
and that would result in other financial institutions getting into trouble as well. It is nothing
to do with shareholders, nothing to do with deposit holders, but everything with the stability
of the financial sector and that is by the way exactly the remit of the FSA, the financial
services authority and the government. Good point. So yes, the people who basically lent out our
money here in the UK and of course this happens in its own way in the United States with the
Federal Reserve and the Treasury printing up money and providing real low cost loans and all kinds
of stuff to these commercial banks is to maintain financial stability. I totally buy that, but
there has to be some kind of penalty for a commercial company who fucks up because that's what happened.
They messed up. They didn't check the loans. They were writing and it's I'm sure they didn't
check the assets backing different structured investment vehicles that were put on loan to them
by other institutions. This is already cost $100 billion worldwide and it's going to go much
much higher. So my question is should I just start a bank tomorrow and then just make money
until fucking blows up because there's no risk. There's no downside risk for a commercial
institution in this sector to go ahead and do whatever you want, try and skim it all off,
try and make the money, forget about doing all the diligence and checking the background,
just make it and if we blow up so what? In order to maintain financial stability, the government
and other financial organizations will step in. Well, that obviously is a problem.
So that has to be addressed. And Aryan, I would gladly gladly crown you a financial
savant if if you wouldn't mind calling in, record something, man. Just calling on the voicemail
lines. That would be be quite helpful. People sending me lots of email and interesting messages
about civil disobedience in the United Kingdom. If we actually wanted to stand up and say, hey,
we don't quite agree with what's going on here. The best idea so far is to create flash mobs
with people wearing t-shirts that say, you work for us. I'm still really like in that idea.
But it could be legal and that's a point of notice. I had them just quick when I'm
protesting in the United States. It's against the rules of protesting the United Kingdom. It's there.
I think it's three. Maybe five or more in your protest. Sully glad past that as one of
his last pages of legislation under the anti-terrorism laws. Of course. If you want to
probably tell us now, you have to get the permission of the full chief council. Cheers.
Thanks, buddy. So you have to get permission of the police chief constable.
I guess what he's going to say. Sure, go ahead. Great idea. Have your protest. Now,
if you haven't seen it yet, please look at that awesome documentary taking liberties. It's
still on the homepage of Curry.com where I blogged the first episode. It's well worth looking into.
Because I guess you just don't have those simple liberties here in the United Kingdom.
In Patricia and I had just astounded. We moved here because we thought this was like a cool place
to be and now we're finding an out that it's in some ways more Snoop Dogg nation and surveillance
state thing United States is. But, of course, the United States is also up to shenanigans and
shenanigans that have to do with stuff that's going on here about putting marshals on flights
from the United Kingdom. Air marshals, US air marshals. And for that, of course, they want a lot
more information about the travelers. This, of course, is a new story that I talked about months ago.
I guess for some reason now, it's popping to the top of the stack. And prolific program
or has some thoughts on it. I got a prolific program here from San Francisco.
President is still been news on the guy in this morning regarding mishibush wing to put
I'm guys and all flights ever flying USS space. This is very disturbing to me because I do fly
very frequently as do you. And I believe we have the same thing about the US
new airport security rules. How long will it take them to realize that this is actually insane?
And it's not going to make the name or secure. Anyway, 28th single. We're here, hope you win.
Love you no more Chris. Thanks, P.P. Papa, Papa, prolific program are checking in with his opinions.
Yeah, this is, this is really going to mess up travel where you will need at least seven
days in advance before you can travel. So no more last minute, hop on the airplane. That'll
fuck up my schedule for sure. And I believe this will even happen in the US. If you are going to
overfly US airspace, regardless, the government wants you to be identified. And of course, this is
a way to bring in the national ID card. And at least this country, at least the United States,
and maybe other countries like this one as well. And it seems like oops, sorry. It seems like
stuff is just going so fast. And I have, and I have back to way a little bit from conspiracy theory
type stuff, you know. And now I'm just seeing, it's not a conspiracy. It's just structural.
Oh, boy, what world were my child grow up in? You really got to ask yourself. For those of you
using our pod show channels at podshow.com, I got to comment a couple of comments like this.
And I did what I respond to it. So check this out. I had a little steep from Boston. I wonder if
there's something called, Chad, that I'm going to call channel spam this morning. I've opened
up my iPod. I'm a way to work. And I found something called the best of Loita, which is not
showing up in any of my channels. And I'm sure I never asked for it to be in there. Anyway, it's
entirely in German. So let me go. And there was some other show that just appeared out of nowhere.
Strange thing that could happen. There are some other shows of mine that are completely not
showing up in my iTunes. But I have everything in my channel set to go to iTunes. There's the
presidential radio address. And I think I found that I want to view our channels. Have an
ever seen a show on my iPod or my iTunes. And the New York Times, Washington report. I've
never seen that one show up, even though they have some newer episodes of this opening. You
could help me understand that, maybe. So that's all I have for you, Red Till. I'd like to see
you get a haircut. I guess you just got one. And which racers are that you're hoping to win?
Any ready for that? Anyway. The arms rise.
Yeah, man. Thank you. Yeah. I got a pretty nifty haircut, by the way. I haven't touched my
hair for the past four days. I wake up and it's just perfect. I love it.
So we've been having some problems with our channels. And let me tell you what they are and what you
can expect. So there's three types of, actually, I guess four types of media currently that you
could have in a channel. It could be a single episode that is on the pod show network, a single
episode that is from anywhere else on the internet. So a single MP3 or MP4 or any other type of video file.
And then, of course, you can also subscribe to shows and then tell your channel how many
episodes to surface of that channel, which is and also the order in which they come out, which is
pretty cool. So there's two things you need to look at. If you put in your channel, if you
see a daily source code as the first show and then you would have the New York Times,
what is it? The Washington report as your second show and then you might have tech five as your third
show. That's the order in which they will show up on in iTunes and subsequently on your iPod.
So daily source code will be first regardless if it was released today or five weeks ago,
that the most recent episode for that show will be at the top of your list. So that you can always
play back the shows in the order that you'd like to play them back in, which is kind of cool.
We've been having a problem with the updates of external shows into the channel. It's been
sporadic and it appears that people who have older channels created a while ago on pod show
have more problems. Anyway, there's been heads down lots of work on this. I believe they've
actually decided to rewrite the entire 8,000 lines of code, which is not a lot that actually
create this functionality. So sit tight. Don't change anything with your channel. All of a sudden
it'll just start working on stuff. We'll start spouting through. Of course, I don't know where
what you call the channel spam is coming through because that's essentially anyone could drop anything
into a feed. So you might have been subscribed to a show in your channel that just decided to put a
German show in. That's possible, but I don't know for sure. So I'll keep you updated on that.
And of course, apologies that it's a little bit too large. Hey, this is a message for Adam Curry.
Adam, this is Sherry Miller. You played me today. Actually, I'm Tadwalk,
Pell just emailed me about it. And thank you so much. I really just want to thank you. I appreciate
it a lot. I have a new record coming out. So it really helps to really help a lot. So I just want
to extend that in person. Thank you. And hopefully we'll meet someday, really. All right,
have a wonderful day. Thanks again so much. Bye.
All of my life. I want it to be same day. Oh, but now I understand you got to play it all the way.
There's a child that hides a secret plane. I'm waiting in my eyes. We can see the plane.
And sometimes I just want to say you're not the only one in the world. Everyone hurts.
Everyone hurts. You're not the only one in the world. Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts.
You're not the only one in the world. I will come for you down and through the darkest times.
Oh, sometimes I will smile. I'll be right my secret scars.
Oh, sometimes I can't admit. I believe in God. I feel like I'm standing in the crowded room
with all eyes on me staring at the accused and I tell myself, hang on to the truth.
You're not the only one in the world. Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts.
You're not the only one in the world. Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts. You're not the only one in the world.
I will come for you down and through the darkest times.
Oh, even weary of this pain that's eating you alive.
Oh, you're solitary soul that needs a little light. You're not the only one in the world.
Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts. You're not the only one in the world. Everyone hurts.
Everyone hurts. You're not the only one in the world. Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts.
The only one in the world. Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts. Everyone hurts. I will come for you down and through the darkest times.
Oh, I'm going weary of my pain.
Sharing Miller on the Podsame Music Network, the Blade. See how easy it is to get your song played on
the daily source code. Just be a girl, be cute, send me a voice mail. That's how that's all it takes.
And by the way, have a pretty decent collection of songs, please. Before I get out of here,
one more thing because I've received at least 50 different emails about it. Forget all the other things
I talked about. If this law goes into effect, then I gotta leave. This is a green paper over here in the UK.
It's a draft law. It's the three strikes you're outlaw and here it comes under this proposal.
UK internet users will be monitored by their ISPs for illegal downloads.
Those caught will receive an email warning in the first instance.
Internet suspension the second time and then terminate their contract on the third strike.
Oh, man. What is the world coming to? Sure. Sure. And you're only going to be looking for illegal
files, right? Not the web page as I surf too and not the email I receive. Yeah, I believe that.
Hey, everybody. It's Adam and podshow.com and staleysourceco.com. Please live your life with
passion and for as long as it laughs. That was a Freudian slip. As long as it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.