Delta's here at Charlie's 718, Super Tuesday.
With $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm casting this battle curry.
I want to bet a line.
More than these four worlds.
I'm my loving wife.
I want to bet a line.
I want to be your man.
Cause you're pretty cool.
And you've got to tell that I want to be your man.
I want to bet a line.
Four worlds.
I got to bet a line.
I want to bet a line.
Oh, this is true, man.
I don't think it's true, man.
I want to bet a line.
Look down from on high, it's everyone better
I want to run the show
Oh, listen to me one
I want to be someone
Listen to me one
Haven't heard from me a while
Still loving, shakes
Better live kicking off
Daily source code episode number 718
Hey everybody how you doing
Back in the curry manner
It's nice and cold here in the UK
Reminds me a lot of like San Francisco
And it's Tuesday morning
I don't actually have time to do a show this morning
But I thought it was very, very important
Because of course today is super Tuesday
This is the day when in the United States
Almost all the other states
You like their favorite for representing their party
For the Democrats and Republicans
I think it's a 24th day to something like that
And I would feel wrong if I didn't get out there
One more time and ask everyone to vote for Dr. Ron Paul
Because I think he's the right guy for the job
And he's one of the few guys left
And you don't hear about him anymore now
And all of the public debate in the mainstream media
So please consider Dr. Ron Paul for your choice
Actually, I was just just looking at his
At his site and the $5 million boost
Going for gold achieved once again
Over five, see how much is it now
Here we go, going for the gold
We wanted to raise $5 million by February 5th
Today being the 5th, 5.225 million
It's that easy
You see the current government has to steal it from us
And Dr. Ron just asks for it
And we give them a wheel thing
Oh man
I had an interesting day
Yes, they can't tell you too much about it
But it did involve
It almost seemed like spiced off man
I had had a couple meetings at an airport restaurant
How cool is that
I'm a little from Virginia
They built a little democratic information
I don't
About five years old
White guy middle class
A middle age middle class
White guy
Just know the comment on Ron Paul
In Richmond, Virginia
And I have seen a number of Ron Paul banner
Ron Paul Revolution banners
Hang on, I hope that's also for
He is supporters are here also
And I consider myself one of them
So Dr. Later, love to show
All right man, thank you
Hope Ron Paul wins
Gladly
Step down from from that for him
A lot of people sent me a link to
Barack Obama
There's a mashup
See if the black eyed piece
And what is it
Will I am?
Someone told me this was
It was produced by Bob Dylan's son
Let me see you can find it at
DipDive.com
And I'm not going to play the
game from here can I
It's well done
It's a message of hope
It's a great mashup
You've got to take a look at it
Crap, I can't believe I didn't set that up
So I could play it for you
It's this new and there's a lot of
Reverb on my voice today
This is what happens when you
You set it all up for
You know a lot of seconds
Let me see if I can fix that a little bit
I just the sound a little bit
Crap, this new set up
I know if I just had
Two out of no three hours of time
I could actually concentrate
On setting all this stuff up right
Then I wouldn't have to do it again
Of course if I had two or three extra hours
I would have completed the
The pod finder episodes
That I'm behind on and
I have I think at least six
Optional tracks ready to go
This of course is the project that I embarked on
It seems to be working because I only put one out
And lots of people have responded
With songs that belong on their
On the soundtrack to their lives
So hopefully
I don't know a crap
I don't know it's it's a crazy week
We're meeting with all of the producers
In the UK this week
We're rolling out some new programs for them
I mean there's a lot going on
Certainly today tomorrow and Thursday
So hey, maybe I'm Friday
I can do some of that stuff
Or maybe just want to get home tonight
I don't have to work on it
More demographic info coming in
And uh and a French lesson that to boot
Hi I didn't Daniel from Toronto
Couple of comments about show
So entertaining but those are
And stands for in the constant form
You eat for the government
Trying to figure out what type of followers
Yeah middle age my revenge
I actually probably just need monitors
Okay, that sound level of your show
Sounds pretty good on me set up
Some colors were a little bit low
But that's fine, pretty good
And for the end
I will try to do it in French this time
So to be different
So bedclother
I'll just pack it for a guy needs
And I don't carry
It's almost a house he can't pass my end
And a cushion today
Someone else sent in
They thought the M would stand for marijuana
But then certainly not treating me that way
Just to go back to that Barack Obama
It's really it's beautifully done
I cannot believe that I didn't
So that up to play for me
It's beautifully done
They've mixed in
Classic Barack Obama speech
In with the words
There's a couple of celebrities who drop by
Who sing on it and it's a message of hope
And although extremely inspiring
And it really hits down to the core
I would have to say
When you see this of Americans
It's a really Yankee
This is the flag
Doodle Dandy type of vibe going on there
Just to vote for hope is not enough for me
I need some actual programs
It'll change something
And that's why I'm endorsing Dr. Ron Paul
For president
And of course, you know, right now we're still in the primary
So you could actually
I guess you can be for a
Barack and for Dr. Ron at the time
Being doesn't really matter
Ask a vote for your
For your nominee today if you're participating in the primaries and you should
But when it comes down to it
I just thinking about hope
It just doesn't do it for me
I need to see it. I need to understand what we're going to go do to make it happen
For instance
Doug Pilgrim
Doug got sends me the great stuff
This is fantastic
So somehow a video leaked out on to
I don't know if it was leaked out into YouTube or
And I've got the pictures here from
I guess this is the Daily Mail here in the UK
It was a French air sturdist
Which I guess can only be air France
Which of course these days is also KLM
It's shots inside the cockpit
And it was a video
It looks to me like the video was shot by the copilot
And
And the sturdist is in the cockpit
And she's basically stripping for the flight crew
Now in the picture she has her
She has her bra on
Which but you know
The pilots are holding on to her breasts
And they're all smiling
And she's cute
And now it's like you know even this article
It's like you know this is outrageous
What is going on at you know hundreds of passengers in peril
I like man
Please tell me which airline this is from
Because I'm going to be flying with them from now on
That's just hot just to just be sitting in the back
And no one that that could be going on
Of run
I knew there was a reason I became a pilot
You're listening to
The business cast
Hey Adam
And listeners of the shot shot is this robber called
Host of the business cast
Businesscast.potshow.com
Get together by co host Andrew Brown High Andrew
Good morning Robert and a
Babel host studio
Practical tips for business owners
Once a week at businesscast.potshow.com
Great three music by Jeff Smith
We'll see you on the flip side
Businesscast.potshow.com
Bye Adam
This is your business
Don't you sound
All the second best
Business take your business
Oh
Nothing like a little just Smith early in the morning for you
Big news over in the lowland in the Netherlands
Television records were broken yesterday
Actually, I should say Sunday evening
When investigative reporter
Pay to air to freeze
Got to the bottom of the
Natalie Holloway
You're on from the slow
Mystery you've probably seen something about this somewhere
I think it's a Nancy Grace who
Has been harping on this. This happened a couple of years ago
An American teenager disappeared from the island of Aruba
And they hadn't you know that been trying to get
Pin the rap on this on this Dutch guy
You're on from the slow to who is they who lives in Holland
And he's actually been locked up for a
I think a couple of weeks while they were
Questioning him and there's like no evidence the body is gone
You know, so they have no murder weapon, no motive
No body, you know lots of stuff missing
But from day one you look at this kid and you're like he's fucking slime ball
You know that he has something to do with it
So this investigative reporter spent several months and finally got
Some other guy and of course this is where the controversy starts because he paid him
To secretly tape they set up this range rover with three
Hidden cameras to tape this guy and to befriend him over the course of several weeks
or several months and
And basically getting him high on
On weed and the guy confessed
Although he didn't confess that he killed her
He said that they were hanging out on the beach and they were
You know fooling around and then all of a sudden she went into
Some kind of almost epileptic fit and then she couldn't wake up
And the guy panicked and instead of and this is the interesting thing
Instead and it's a 17 year old guy with a cell phone
Instead of calling someone to help him out
He decides to drag her in the bush is call a buddy of his
They more or less determine she's dead
And then this buddy of his takes her out into the ocean and dumps the body
And
What is going to be interesting to me is this has apparently been sold around the world
I think ABC news
Purchased this special
And of course the authorities have not gotten anywhere near this type of this type of information
I need the Dutch authorities or the authorities on the island
And
I can't wait to see how this is
Particularly the nuances of what this guy is saying in the car on tape is translated
To ABC that's one of the most interested in
Of course you can find it on YouTube
I'll post a link but it's a I don't have the I don't have a version with American or English subtitles
But it's so
Nothing really still
Still solved as far as I'm concerned because I believe this kid killed her
And has just lied so much about what happened
And to himself that he absolutely believes that he didn't kill her that she just kind of died
Right there or he's not sure
But if you haven't seen it if you if
If you've heard about it you may want to check that out
Hopefully it brings some kind of closure at least to the family
But wow this kid what a monster
Regardless of even just the story he's telling now and a monster is
Dick
Oh
Anyway, that's uh that's just but it's been big news that they had
Viewership of 7 or 8 million in the country of only 17 million
That's pretty damn good if you take away old people and babies
I don't have his jingle
But let's just pretend I played it
Polific programmer from San Francisco checking in with y'all
Buddy
I don't know if it's a program from San Francisco
It's in DS-671-4
When you ask for a destination of a decision
A recession is defined as two consecutive quarters of the night
To the next time the growth
While we are not very at either England or the US
We are hanging that direction
Cheers
Yeah, thanks that prolific programmer
Yeah, lots people sent that in
Some actually said it was two months worth of negative GDP growth
But I think it is two quarters we have not even hit one in the US
A granted it's under one percent
It's going to be 0.40.6 percent
So we haven't actually hit the first quarter of negative GDP growth
But already it sounds like everyone is in
You know they're they're in the middle of it
And there's no question we're going into a recession
I don't know
Actually, I do know that if we all stand around and say
Oh man, we're going into a recession
Yes, we will go into a recession
Because that's kind of how financial markets work
It's all about what the sentiment is
And then there are some official indicators
Like this one like two two quarters of
Negative growth and GDP
And there's something weird going over on here in the UK as well, man
I'm not quite sure what it is
I can't put my finger on it yet
But I
I already I think I already have reversed my entire stance on Gordon Brown the prime minister over here
I thought he was going to be great for the country
But I think he's just a member of the club, man
He's he's he almost looks like he's working on orders
And the orders are take as much money as you can
From the people
They came out with this new
This new law
Trucks going into London
Which apparently only are really responsible for about 4% of the carbon emissions and pollution in the city
They all had to convert their trucks with these
Fifteen to twenty thousand dollar conversion kits
And if they don't have it on by yesterday, I guess
Then every single day you're in in the city
And you don't have an approved conversion kit
You're going to get find 200 pounds, that's about 400 bucks
How do they know by the way?
They've got a very sophisticated system
Which you know for a guy like me
It's actually kind of nutty that that I live here because they have cameras everywhere
Every single move you make here in the UK is taped
On what they call CCTV
If you drive into the city
You're supposed to pay a congestion charge
Just take it money left and right from people in cars
And it's not like the congestion has gotten
Better it's gotten worse if anything
So they're taking money from people left and right
I know I talked about it on Noah Gendo over the weekend with John C. Dvorak
And I don't like repeating the conversations in either program
But there was a big article in the financial time saying that
Because of the new tax changes
Which will affect
Well it will affect everybody
Anybody who has any type of capital gain
So either selling your house or selling stocks if you trade
And stocks and bonds or if you
Have a company and you would sell that
It's almost doubling going from 10% to 18%
But there's all kinds of advantages for people
Living here and who have their wealth
Outside the country and only pay for a certain bit
If they bring it into the country
The bottom line is according to the financial times and
What they're reporting is that half of the wealthiest people are ready to leave
If this law actually goes through and it's supposed to be
Going to affect in April
I have already alerted my wife and I'm on happy with the situation
And if we've got to take a look at it
But it's crazy
I don't know what's going on
I think it has a lot to do with it
You know these bank bailouts
Which are just huge
So we've got this this bank northern rock which was about to go belly up because of the credit crunch by the way
The US credit crunch. It's absolutely spreading all over the world and
It's not just the 24 billion pounds that's 50 billion dollars that the government
You know dropped in there immediately to keep it from going under there's another
amount about that size so in total I think the
The government i.e. the money of the people is on the hook for over 50 billion pounds
Yes, I have it for at least the next five years. It's it's theft I'm telling you
No one asked that anyone if that was going to be okay and by the way you could have fixed education and health care in this country
Instead of bailing out this one fucking bank
It's nuts
It's really really nuts, but there's no outrage over it. There's a lot of talk and
You know you read articles, but you know we're being kept stupid here
You know what's the what's on the front page?
Let me see George Michael's auto autobiography his second one
Madeleine McCain still dominating the headlines
And we really got to start looking through all this crap and getting better information out there because people just being kept stupid while they're being
burglarized on the back end while no one's looking
Crap I need some of the cheer me up
Hey Adam Curry
Yeah, yeah, okay. I know what this is nothing like a like a guy from Jersey the cheer you up on a Tuesday more
You did from Jersey. Oh, Jersey. I hope I can make this clear and concise of the listening to all the demographics
I figured I'd finally call in and take care of business
Do it first. I want to thank you for having shows on a daily basis this past week
That was clearly last week
I've been listening since August of 05 nice and
It pains me when I plug my iPod in the morning from my commute to Brooklyn
That's you're not there
Anyway, so about me
Morning bread in New Jersey. We are walking. We are walking. I
I love we Hawking it's the last exit before you hit the Lincoln tunnel into the city
We Hawken Hoboken in the house right here the Lincoln tunnel
Now live in Central Jersey you front work with my wife right on kids gonna be married 25 years this June gonna be
47 oh my god bless you my July
Remember my first second here in high school we use they we time shared
We sat in the tell all tell a type with the yellow tape and the eight holes
And mechanical buttons pretty wild where we come got into listening to podcast when I got my third generation
15 gig I caught a couple years back and loaded all my music
Come on and I was like well really something more I can do it this thing and don't you know you came about and
With a few other people came up with this awesome thing called podcasting
Keep me entertained during the day can't listen to mainstream radio. It actually hurts me and I put it on
As painful my iPod love my technology
Just bought the way to spot car. Hopefully it'll come soon
You know, we got these big gas go with it. They finally finally and next motorcycle right now
You are currently riding motorcycles. Yeah, and that's what I do for fun
Great day love your immediate day care hope you win and as you say on the motorcycle
They look roads be stashed and twisted
What kind of what kind of scooter you got man? Did you forgot to tell us what you're riding there?
Yeah, I used to ride I had three Harley's I had a sportsster. I had a soft tail on a fat boy
And I didn't last very long my wife didn't not like it and she turned him into a couch
I mean literally sold him. Is it my wife's been good at selling my toys. I've noticed by the way
Now while that was going on I was thinking about
I'm sure it was something important
Lots of emails that came in about the FBI now wanting to set up a massive computer database of our physical characteristics
This doesn't remind me actually when I came back from San Francisco on Sunday
Actually so I you of course you leave on Saturday because you fly through the night
I was in the in the lounge the virgin upper class lounge and for the second time
And they these people only travel once every six or eight weeks Jan and John from Magnetoon which is
They've been they've been doing that for a long time. It's it's kind of like a record label slash licensing company you should check them out. They're really into
Into podcasting and promoting music through alternative means and and as far as I know they're they're doing great business
They're flying virgin upper class something they must be doing something right somewhere
And so Jan comes over and I don't know how you doing and you know, I had I had seen her maybe two or three month
Men was three months ago and I'm like on Jan are you doing she says I have two words for you like yeah
Curse De Hockshaw
Like no you're kidding me. She says yes. It's like one of my best friends
And you know, I'm trying to get her to do another another album over stuff and I just love her to death and then she had
hurt all of the conversation going back and forth and and I'm like yeah, you know, that's fantastic
And she says and she's so beautiful. I've seen her naked in the spa on like Jan
What why are you telling me this if you're not
Supplying me with pictures. I don't have to know
Anyway, she told me that the curse it started up the blowcast
Which of course I didn't write on top of that
Anyway, the reason why I bring them up in this context is when we arrived in the UK, you know, I was going through my regular
Getting in line to get back get back into the into the country and I saw them hang a left at the iris scan
And she actually had dropped me an email later said, you know, we we always take the iris scan because there's
You know, there's no no lines no waiting and if the thing works of course
I'm like you know, I am so against that
I am not voluntarily going to give the government or anyone for that matter my biometric data because you know that it's going to be misused
Somewhere or worse in this country discarded by the side of the road or lost in the mail
And you really should fight against this do not under any conditions do not let the government
Tag you in because it's tagging is what it is
So the bureau the FBI is expected to announce in the coming days a
$1 billion 10-year contract to help create this database
That will compile an array of biometric information from palm prints to i scans that would be the retinal scans
And here you go Kimberly Del Greco the FBI's biometric services section chief what a title that is
Said adding to the database is important to protect the borders to keep the terrorists out protect our citizens
Our neighbors are children so they can have good jobs and have a safe country to live in
cheese
This is wrong
No national ID cards fight against this crap
Vote for Ron Paul today, please it's a desperate situation
In your case if you look at hold on hold on a second. Let me get it
Okay, I have it here now by the way. It still turns on but as you know the
The touch screen is broken, so I can't actually use it. Okay, I've got it here. What am I looking at?
Three points for the headset where you put the microphone you know the
ear plugs
The bottom of that hole there's supposedly
Something there that acts as a sensor that they'll that attack and tell us the device has been dropped in water really and when you look down inside the headphone jack
It will be white if it's never been dropped in water if it turns dark or either a yellow or a black
It's proved that the device has seen water and therefore that voids the warranty here and
I'm blown whatever
So hey look down in the whole atom and tell us what the deal is if it's rumored fact
I'm looking in the hole now my friends. This is kind of hard to see. I got to catch the light just at the right angle
Hmm
I can see the well, I don't think it's a sensor. I think it's just the connector at the bottom
I can't really say is to if it's
No, you know what if I'm looking at it. It kind of looks
Silvery white. It doesn't look discolored at all. I
Don't think it's true
How can I tell I mean I have no comparison. I need a good one next to it to be able to
Oh, that's complicated. No, I don't think it's true. That seems to be
David and Sophie. That's sorry, David. I think that's an urban myth there
Doesn't matter. I've got my Nokia 810. It's a vice is just fine. Thank you very much. It does
All of my Gmail all of my Google Docs and it plays flash videos
Which means it's it's
completely compatible with
With podshow.com which I'm digging
And if you want one of those nifty devices for yourself go to podshowoffers.com
Which is just the easiest way to get it because that's where you can get it for any country now
I'm not any country, but
I've expanded the list. I don't even remember what it is. So you can get a 15% discount. It's the best
Deal anywhere
For the Nokia 810
Internet tablet 15% discount if you use my code daily source code
If you go to daily source code.com you can find the information in the show notes and a link to podshowoffers.com slash and
So it being a super Tuesday today and that's again really the reason why I just popped in for this rather short show today
I tried finding a song from the
From the soundtrack of my life that might help us think about to get now there and voting today if you're on your way to work
You make a little detour passed by the schoolhouse or
Wherever it is that that you vote and of course I'd like you to vote for Dr. Ron Paul if you're a Republican or if you're
Going to vote for a Republican candidate
Please do that and
Well, there's no song called super Tuesday, but this one comes pretty close
Sun is bright
Or in the darkest night no one knows
She comes and goes
Goodbye
Ruby Tuesday who could hang a name on you
When you change with every new day still I'm on a new seal
Don't question why she needs to be so free
She'll tell you if the only way to be
She would never say where she came from
Yesterday don't matter if it's gone
While the sun is bright
Or in the darkest night
No one knows
She comes and goes
Goodbye
Ruby Tuesday who could hang a name on you
When you change with every new day still I'm on a new seal
Don't question why she needs to be so free
She'll tell you if the only way to be
She just can't be changed to a life where nothing's gained
And the things lost
But such a cost
Goodbye
Ruby Tuesday who could hang a name on you
When you change with every new day
While there's still a round thing God for sheep bought.com
They still get tunes like this
Stons Ruby Tuesday on a super Tuesday on the daily source code episode 718
I'm off. I got to get my answer
London on the back tomorrow sneak in a show some way somehow or another and of course
Promise out to mainly p-dub and Brian
I am I am getting my production worked on this week as well
All right, everybody
Adam at podshow.com daily source code dot com
Please live your life with passion just a little bit today. You know when you come home and and your partners there
Give him or her or it a big a big snog for me. Well, yeah
And enjoy your freedom my friends
Because it's fleeing quickly
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
You