Delta Shira Charley, $7.31.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
The next generation radio contenting my ears.
We don't need not seeking treatment.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm testing his ad agree.
I don't want to run through.
I gotta go to the sea.
I don't need to run through.
Get me in the mirror now.
I don't want to run through.
Let me away.
Rise and look down around.
Rock his face.
Go to the ground.
Burn it up.
Go to the road.
What's the matter?
Go up your phone.
I call you.
I don't want to run through.
I make way the air.
No serenade.
No fabricates.
The platform in the air.
Come home.
What do you want?
I don't want to run through.
It's new.
No mirror.
Go to the direction.
I don't want to run through.
Now listen to me.
Burn it up.
Get me in the mirror.
I don't want to run through.
There ain't no cure.
For free.
Little fire.
Go in the mirror.
Get me in the mirror.
Go on the road.
What do you want?
I don't want to run through.
It's new.
No mirror.
Go.
You bitch.
I don't want to run through.
I'll be here, she's still lonely
Give me a moment, I'll be here
I'll be lonely, we got the power
Got the power, just lay on me
And if you need it, say yeah
Say yeah
I'll be here, she's still lonely
Say yeah, she's still lonely
I'll be lonely, she's still lonely
I'll be lonely, we got the power
Got the power, just lay on me
I'll be here, she's still lonely
Give me a moment, I'll be here
I'll be lonely, we got the power, just lay on me
I'll be here, she's still lonely
Give me a moment, I'll be here
I'll grow one kick self-dellysor's code episode 7
34 coming to you from the offline summer
I've already known as girlfriend run the west side of G-town
and the curry manner
It's deaf-lapped rock of agents
We come all the match stuff bits in there as we expect from a go on
You know actually I love the intro you couldn't hear everything that that happened that mashup
But they start with the infamous you can't glogan blue when I look at hold on
Let me let me just you got to hear that man
I love that's my favorite part of any deaf leopard rucker listen to it here comes
Somewhere around here
Love that I
Hope you had a pretty good weekend
We have a bit of a sick bag going on here
Both the lady Patricia and I are suffering just a little bit from uh, well, she's suffering much more than I am from a cough
Oh crap man, I can see I can figure my machine right if you hear a little bit of popping and clicking
Pay no attention to it. It's a known artifact
Yeah, um, so cough cough cough cough actually just uh Patricia went to the doctor this morning
It's one day morning here in the UK actually Monday afternoon. Wow. I'm gonna talk about three 41 in the afternoon
at a couple of uh
couple of phone calls conference calls stuff to do and a administrative work
Yeah, that's my uh once uh in the 60 day time to pay some bills
So um yeah, now poor poor Patricia and it really hits her heart
Because she's had pneumonia twice. I don't know if you know how severe pneumonia actually is
But it's really you got to watch out for that stuff
You know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna just stop this recording ever so briefly
I'm gonna reconfigure the buffer size so we don't have that clicking. I'll be right back in two seconds before you can even blink
I'll be back
Perfect. Okay. I knew it would only take a second. There we go
Okay, the reason why is because we said the reason why I had actually go back and reconfigure my uh my setup here is
We had a nice uh until we started to come down with this cough
We had a really nice nice weekend full of music
Remember um Patricia was talking uh actually
Well, I can't remember exactly how I came up with it. Oh, yeah
So I was thinking about doing a mashup between
Martha Reeves and the Van Delas heatwave and George Michaels
Or wham rather
Wham's waking me up before you go go. Hey, I got pretty far with that
But I'm not gonna play it for you because
I'm not quite sure if I can actually make it work out
But it did kind of fit together and I was amazed at the capabilities of able to live
The ability to you know pull stuff into the groove without changing the pitch or changing the pitch without actually
Changing the beats per minute
The beats per minute, you know what I mean right and then uh Patricia said you know, I really I need to have a song
Dutch song then I'm gonna she's gonna do with uh with the host of this
The Holland's got talent that she's in so somewhere in May
I guess when I do the do the live version of the show
They want to do a show together and so she said you I want to kind of base it a little bit on a combination of heatwave and wake me up before you go go
And I say well, that's fantastic. I've got a whole studio upstairs and I have no musical talent
Turns out I do and I was quite amazed at this actually
I was able with MIDI
Because you know, I'm not a musician. I can't really play anything but I do understand
When you're working with Patricia together, I you know, I know how to put together a baseline and then figure out drums and
It uh I'll play a little bit of it for you home on a second
It's instrumental because we still haven't done this singing obviously since she was hooking up a long half the time
This this just gives an idea
Oh, listen to me play damn horns baby
As soon as we've done some some of the vocal tracks. I'm sure I'll play some of that for you
Hey a lot of ground to go over to cover today tons of stuff going on
tons of voicemail which I just haven't gotten to because well, I wanted what we do we did at a full proper
Food bar Friday the only show last week. So I had to shift what didn't have to I was more than happy to shift through a week's worth of audio feedback
And it looks like as an interesting stuff is coming in
Exciting of the evil Adam Curry for those of you who don't know
I remain on a secondary watch list with the US customs and border patrol part of the department of
Home Security home land security
Because there apparently is an Adam Curry
As far as I know he's from Nebraska and they aren't looking for him
And looks like someone's found him
Hey Adam this is Johnny K call it from Kansas City and I'm calling regards to the evil Adam Curry that is terrorized in Midwest
It wasn't in Nebraska. It was in Kansas City. I called several months ago
And I was in one that found him on he's driving a red Chevy pickup truck with
Customized Todd Fobber Kansas license plates
And so the reason I'm calling is I'm challenging the evil Adam Curry to call him the Charlie and
Man up at a mid to his activities
So
Now or if anybody in Kansas City sees him take a picture of the truck and send it to you. So
Anyway, let your show been a long time
Love you no homo
In it great here help you win
Like thank you. Thank you. I love that expression. I want him to man up. That's right evil Adam Curry from Kansas City man up
Driving around a red pickup truck with pod father license plates
We need to go get this guy for sure
I'm not gonna do any
Any articles because I have so many phone calls that came in just kind of blow through him also a two weeks ago
I was informed through podcaster.de that the daily source code can now be heard
Through a German phone line
And so
Basically I have a dedicated phone number you can call it off anytime you want and you can hear the show and the quality was really good
I played it on the show and my question was of course, you know, is this like a premium rate phone line
Does it cost extra money?
How was this working and the comments started rolling in luckily?
To say it's plus no extra money. So if you go down the phone flat rate
I can call this number which I get from phone cards before my favorite plug-ass and I can use it. I can call my
Podcasts and yeah, what is the business model behind this though? That that's what I need to know because we've had
Systems similar to this where they would roll out at like a pre roll advertisement and I'm against that because you know
Unless unless I give you permission to do it you just can't do that
And so I think most of those initiatives just died just kind of fell by the wayside
So how are they making money is it really on the interchange the interconnect fees which is you know
It's like pennies on the hour or something like that is that how they're financing this thing, please someone let me know
I can also leave a comment by putting the stop button on the telephone and I really do like the service and
If you want to listen to my podcast
Wait before you get into the promo. That's pretty cool
So while you're listening you can
You can add a comment I guess you can record a comment through your phone by pressing the star button. I'll have to do that
I read somewhere else. I think maybe isn't there online documentation
That you can then subscribe to an RSS feed of the comments. That system. I like the best
I don't know how many people actually
We'll listen to their favorite shows on a telephone
I guess with you know with unlimited calling plans
It doesn't really hurt right so it doesn't make that much difference
The sound of course is still gonna be kind of limited to the was it the seven kilohertz band with
range that that audio that tell that the telephone uses
All right then plug you show
Also the way the language
There's a new English podcast who is called who the fuck got me to do this?
You can go to
Brought to us
Parts.com and my
German podcast is available at
Dadypot.com. So have a listen and keep up the good work
I'm 21 years old
Great air hope you win
No, no no no no no no no no no no no sorry and
Bye bye. I got to listen that Brad worse show
That sounds pretty good
You know with a new version 2.5 I'm really liking it because when I go to my channels page
I don't have to pop open a mashboard
It starts playing my channel immediately so I've actually rearranged the shows and my
Top channel which is the one that starts playing by default
You can find that at adam.podshow.com
We're at them.btpodshow.com as you wish and
I put the New York Times
Front page show in there
So now when I hit it it just like boom it goes
It starts playing that one immediately no secondary actions to pull up the mashboard and it's and everything's working again
It's like they blew out the system like just
You know it's stuck a big vacuum cleaner and pod shows Volopi and tubes
I don't know why I said that
Just made sure everything was clean ready for the birth of V3
I'm even getting the meet the press show now which is I think they delivered on quick time
I love watching that
Hey, so it turns out that there's also a US version of of this phonecaster thing check this out for second
Adam
Dave here from Williamsport, Pennsylvania
You talked a little bit
I believe on 732 and we go to the phone casting
In German you are set up a sound casting in the states
The number is I've one zero two four eight zero three one four
I've one zero two four eight zero three
One four we I check this out a little while ago
If I have unlimited calling on myself home and if I'm caught with my MP free player
I can't go without my Charlie so I'd dial it up
See you later
Have a good day. I have him cool. Hold on second. Let me try that right now
Was it five one zero two four eight zero three one four
Let's see what
By
role
Hello
Yeah, that's the that's the Friday food bar show
cool
I mean it's I guess it's okay for them to plug their service
But even that's kind of borderline without asking me
So if you actually listen to the show that way if you're interested to listen to the show that way
Let me know that's yeah, that's kind of cool
Of course the UK phone line is also not been still man. I got so many different voice males to go through here check this one out
Hey Adam it's Kevin from sweatshirt North Carolina
It's not really from from the UK now is he okay North Carolina. I don't know which episode
Anyway, I'm doing the flash mob thing over the UK
Sounds like great idea, but it always sounds like you want everybody else to do it
I want to know are you gonna actually go out there and do it too?
Well, let us know
Take part just hold strings
All right, well of course I was intending on only pulling the strings
But you know when I'm waiting for is someone to take the initiative
You know you work for us dot uh was it dot peanut butter dot com now you work for us dot
Man, I can't remember what the hell of the name that we I did a thug a week and a half ago
But I'm waiting for the for the bridge to stand up, you know
I'll be like the silly American fool running around
I'll do anything you need me to do but someone's got to start this and that's where I'm pulling the strings absolutely
I'm just amazed I'm amazed that that no one is as outrages as I am and by the way
There's a lot of crap going on in the US as well. It's just I happened to live here a momentarily
Hi Adam this is Justin I heard James Friday saying that we need not worry about all the video cameras in the nanny state
As long as I obey conform and report I have nothing to worry about right yeah, I'll that's what TV tells me
But then through the power of stumble upon what a great tool
I find our friends over at DARPA have a new project called vulture
A plane that stays up for five years at 16 and 90 thousand feet
That's what I call a constant surveillance
I sometimes feel like I'm living in the poem first they came
All right, man peace. Okay. I got to look that poem up now
Yeah
Boy can you imagine that a plane that can stay in the air for five years
What kind of bathroom facility do you need for one of them puppies, huh?
Oh
Hi Adam it's Matt from games. We's the longest week show we hang out with the survivors of oceanic flight
18 in the last the video game we go to war again with frontlines fuel of war and you can win one of five copies of
Saker superstars tennis for the 360 that's all a games result calm
Oh
Only as good as efficient
You
Kind of like an opera ski bang your head against the wall. Let's get drunk through our panic party panics on the stage kind of thing
If you don't what I mean
If following up on some news that we had a couple weeks ago that the government suggested that
Internet service providers
Probably would have to start helping out
Primarily the entertainment industry and software industries tracking down people downloading illegal stuff
And they in fact even when further than that and spoke about a three strikes your out rule
Were the first time you'd get a warning note second time they would
Disconnect your service in the third time terminate forever and go to jail and cut your balls off
Well turns out this is a practice not just reserve for the eye out of the United Kingdom my friends. Oh no
I did call about absolutely about a topic about 10 episodes bill. You were talking about
A three strikes your rule out for downloading illegal material in the UK
Well my friend I have to let you know that's actually alive and well here in the state
Just to give you the short story for me is a I have a video game as a
Four discs in it sick
By the way a lot of you complain about the the voice calls being soft. I don't have this nothing left to crank up
I have everything wide open on this one. It's allowed us that can get it. I'm sorry and that was installing my game
I know so one of my guess was damaged and didn't want to work
Well I'd be email the company that made the game as if I could get a replacement disk and they told me no
That's about a new set. You know that that pisses me off right there. I mean that just that's like an apple iTunes kind of deal
You know you bought it. It's yours, right? It's just the you know the
disks do get corrupt believe it or not it happens after a couple of years
I think they should have replaced it free if not you know for the
For the cost of shipping and handling tell me about that game company right off the bat first, you know
It's not like you know you're buying a whole new set. You just want one of the one of the disks
You know, I think you have a case right there forget about what it's about to say. Well I didn't like that idea
In order for me to buy a whole new set for a game that I already owned
So I went to one of the torn sites
Found
The torn download it's just the one disk that I made it with that be just four
And I went to sleep while downloading the morning when I woke up
On that that my internet connection had been suspended with a note saying for my internet provider
That I had been reported by a third party source
me downloading vitally go material
That my account isn't suspended until I delete set item and
Contact my internet company
Now hold on a second
If you wake up in the morning and by the way you didn't tell us if the torn completed successfully or not
How did you get your email if they if they turned off your your account?
How did you get the the notice curious about that?
But you still get to their site or still get your email from their servers
But you couldn't go outside the network. I'd love to know
I contacted them and they told me that
There's a company called
yesterday which is the
entertainment software
Association. Oh, yeah
The ESA sounds a lot like the BSA which is the business software alliance I believe
If you call their main number they'll pick up and they'll say Microsoft could afternoon not kidding
You can try it. So I wonder if the ESA has anything to do with that with Microsoft as well was there an
Xbox that you were running?
Which apparently monitors these illegal downloads of games and excretion torn sites and that when they connect to you
And you seem to be uploading part of that game or if he's a software music video or whatever
They report you to your ISP trying to get your
Private information that way I'll probably do a bring up on charges or some sort
But the ISP they're only required to do one of two things
Either one they can give over your personal information
Which in my ISP provider did not or they can suspend your service until you deleted the item and
You notify them now the ISP did tell me that you actually have two shots if you've been reported twice
On your third time your service will be terminated without the ability to open up a new account
So in most areas that's three strikes in your house. Yeah, if you only have one ISP
Fortunately, I have two I haven't until he terminates
So just want to let you know about that go check them up. See you just look home on the weather ESA
That's much information then
But that's it
Thank you very much. Yeah, I mean it
Wow, that's outrageous
That's absolutely outrageous. So there's an organization out there who is connecting to torrent uploaders
and
Sloo thing around getting IP addresses tracking them down getting the
ever basically reporting you threatening the ISP
Wow
That's pretty outrageous
Man, oh man
So it's gonna be I guess I still have the ongoing argument with a lady Patricia about the cameras
I keep telling her it's no good
Um, also I got a nice email from Libby Libby who is working here in the UK and is a consultant and I think she writes reports about
Alcohol abuse in the United Kingdom particularly amongst the
The younger demographic oops yeah
Sorry about that and
After it come on the show she didn't reply in time for today's recording
But you know, it's it's all that's all the stuff that's bugging me. It's all coming to a head
We're talking about everything and meanwhile you guys want something completely different from me
I don't this is
Flotskig in Oxford in the United Kingdom and just wondering
What are we gonna get in the Samsung tool?
Mm-hmm, something else on the pages and
I think it was for me best efforts
So yeah, I don't know the one
Oh, thank you. That's reverse of you. Oh, oh
Yeah, you're absolutely right. I got to do another sound seeing tour. You know what I'll do
Next time. Oh, you know what if if if I decide to do that game show pilot
I'll do a sound seeing tour something there something fun
Yeah, I'm out of ideas really and
Yeah, yeah, I've done just about everything I wanted to do
Give me some thoughts give me some ideas. Where would you like me to do a sound seeing tour be happy to do it?
It's it's actually a lot easier than doing a regular show
It's just you get backed up on voice males and stuff like that and other other
other pieces of the world to save
For instance, northern rock now I bring this up because of course that's the
The huge mortgage lender and and retail bank and the United Kingdom that got bailed out by the government
To the two to one hundred billion dollars with a B
And of course the same thing and just happened in the States
Bear Stearns you probably heard about it and it's funny because I know a lot of people of Bear Stearns
a lot of them from
Solomon Smith Barney
Who worked with us when
Ron Bloom and I had our public company think new ideas they went to Bear Stearns
I think they were acquired by Bear Stearns and now Bear Stearns looks to be purchased by JP Morgan
It's like their stock dropped 90% almost down to a couple bucks
And their bankrupt essentially
Bankrupt there you go
What is the entomology of bankruptcy?
Hmm
The word bank is certainly in there
So lots of people talking about that coming up again in the voice male comments
Hey good morning Adam is just seeing me answer
Did you see I was listening to the news this morning and heard that
Bear Stearns got bailed out blew up and um
And I just heard a quick story about it
So I don't think I really know the whole whole story but I can't couldn't help but
Think and draw a connection to your your northern rock
Story about how that needs to be bailed out because apparently Bear Stearns was bailed out
And with some taxpayer guarantee if not assistance I'm not sure how that works
So I'd be interested in getting educated and seeing if there aren't back parallels and why
Still a handle the same and or differently and north and north and rock was given the
The issues you had with that situation
How catch up eventually and still
And not listening to the day of day because my laptop got stolen and hasn't
Still deck around with the KSA on that and kind of pick it up, but I'll catch up. Thanks, man
I'm at just call
5102480314 get your fix on the phone no problem
Yes, or essentially this bail out
Is it is kind of the same thing but then it isn't exactly the same thing and let me see if I can explain it to you
The Bank of England is controlled by the government
The federal reserve is about as governmental as federal express
It's a private organization commercial organization who as the only organization have the right to print money
That's right go look it up when they were established in when I'm going to say 19 was at 1912
I'm gonna say
May was 1931 actually
Yeah, it's a bunch of banks
Go look at the federal reserve go go see what they do they get to print the money
With almost no checks and balances, so when they created this fund and jumped of the seat of war
I can I talked about it over the weekend on no agenda number 21
Which you can find at curie.com or no agenda dot pot show dot com
You know we came to the same conclusion that essentially it's a tax
You know, it's a tax on the
American citizen or anyone who uses dollars really, but really on the American people because they just printed up 200 billion dollars
You know, there's no gold or anything to back that out. They just made some more papers
So of course that devalues our money with that was reflected in the recent lowest
dollar versus euro price ever
And
So whoa
Damn so in that regards it is it is indeed a
You know similar to the northern rock bail out except northern rock
Came directly from the government and they failed
They failed to sell it so they had to nationalize it
Which I would say probably means we can kiss most of that money goodbye for a long long time now I could sit here
For another hour and talk about this
But since we have an experts advanced standing by shall we just bring him in
He's back to talk about northern rock bear turns and more it is the New Yorker in London
The next 35,000 so that was the oh
No, no, no, no, I can't talk to you right now. I'm doing my show. Well, what kind of put this cell phone so I want to do that
rap
This is about the bank guarantees about
25 billion of
The money going to northern rock to basically protect money that's in the accounts
But they're going above and beyond they're going way beyond the the first 2000 or you're the first
What is it
50,000 no a 35,000 I guess in total 90% whatever
They go away further than that
So that you know whatever they say whatever the law states doesn't matter because they did more than that
Still wasn't fully covered and still doesn't compare to the US so yes right now it's the 435
As in northern rock say it was only 2000 and the 90% the next 35,000
Next thing to just put into this navigation issue. There's two things you need to go look at
And then come back to us one is continental insurance bank
1984 and the US the US
Nationalized eight bank yes the US
Nationalized continental insurance and 1984 and held about
70 to 80% of the stock until 94 and so bank of America
To go over it so go back in history
1984 continental insurance northern rock is nothing new the US has nationalized the bank
Finally the savings alone twice is of the 80 the US pumped in who knows
under 50, 160, 170 billion dollars
To bail out and support the failed saving the loans crisis so
Northern rock is small peanuts given
Constantly insurance and the savings alone again two countries separated by a common language
We don't call it maximization
US calls it bail out and
Pumping up and pumping up and all those other things all right hold on a second let me just say some about that
I'm not saying that the UK is better or worse than the states. I'm just saying okay
You know there was no bail out when northern rock happened
So I'm just saying you know and people should know of course the savings in a loan
What a scandal that was I didn't know about the spank you mentioned continental bank whatever
I didn't know about that and yes of course the regulatory
bodies are put in place to make sure that trade continues and
You know that that banks continue to to do business with each other because that of course
It was really happening here. It's way way beyond the so called subprime mortgage crisis
Now no one trusts anyone's fucking deals that's what's going on the banks don't trust each other
Right now I think it's the last time I look bare-sterns had a four dollar stock price JP Morgan's offering two bucks
That's less than what the building is worth and that they're in over there on that was it's six avenue I guess
So they just don't trust each other anymore. That's what's happening here and I'm not saying that you know the US is
Better or worse than the UK
I'm just saying
Finally on the snooping
I'm a little concerned and bothered by your perception of snooping
Stop and search if you're a Muslim or
Ethnic minority use in the UK since 2000
The terrorism act of 2000 has allowed the UK police to stop and search you for no
Reasonable cause. Oh, I hate it. Absolutely. The same is happening in Amsterdam by the way
No probable cause no reasonable cause just stop and search. Oh, yeah, and they profile
Oh, man, do they even customs? I've not I've in all the times I've come into Heathrow not once have I been asked to stop
At customs and the only people the only people I ever see and I come through Heathrow a lot
our Asian
You know I'm saying so yeah. Oh, please
massive massive profiling going on here and
I totally agree stop and search no right to protest three strikes you're out
So I don't care about these cameras following you and and you're the guys with suitcases and ties or jackets on
You know if you're a minority you can sit in the UK or
Necessity the cops and stop and search you. That's more insidious than any use dropping
Finally e-spotting grid is telecom your blood partner
What do you think supports the GC HQ which is a snooper in the UK
CT in Cheltenham
They supply the cabling they supply the infrastructure
You embed with the snoopers
So think about that a little bit
I won flying
Yeah, oh, nylon. What are you doing to me now, man?
Get me in trouble with my partner
Yeah, well listen first of all British telecom of course
You know they had they for years they had the monopoly on the wire
I think they still have the monopoly on the wires in the ground so that's just the fact
You know and it was it used to be a part of the government it got nationalized
Right and
In fact, I think that
It's probably more on paper than anything. I was talking to Ben for Ryan. He's the CEO and this is before the the new chairman came in
And I was talking to him. I said you know
Would you be interested in the chairman job you already want to be CEO when you want to go on to another gig and I and you know of course the rumor now is that he is looking for
Or usually what happens when a new chairman comes in he brings in a new CEO so that's kind of like the other shoe ready to drop
But I asked him about it and he said you know, I'm not allowed to become a chairman
I said when he's talking about said now you can only be a British national
British origin born and raised because there's all these secrets
The one you mentioned I'm sure as a part of it that that no one else but a a
A Brit
According to whatever law this is adhering to
It has to be a full-blown Englishman
So
I don't feel
I don't take offense to what you said
Put it that way someone's got a man as the wires. I'm sure they're doing something good
All right well we're on that of course the campaign now against a terror
Still rains in the UK radio commercials outdoor spots
Telling you three main things if someone is it's taking too many pictures of public buildings you should report them
If someone has too many cell phones with them you should report them that's a nice one or if there's any
suspicious activity around or near a particular dwelling or house you should report them
At
That doesn't sit so well with me
Because of course I'm doing all kinds of suspicious shit with cell phones and taking pictures and with with my home
But there is a difference apparently between this campaign against terror and the one of the 80s when the IRA were bombing
Looking to Neil's comments and and also thinking back on what James was saying also a brick and
You know what you don't want about please stay to make it talk about
The way the climate has changed and so on but the real point I want to make is about the 80s
About the bombings that happened in the 80s
The major differences that we were given a warning
Usually about five minutes this memory serves. I would round about this scene. I think now that's interesting
I do kind of recall that I was pretty young myself
But I do recall that the IRA bombers would typically
Call in a bomb threat that say a bomb is about to go off and the fucker actually would explode
But it was usually five to ten minutes after that
I remember that thanks for bringing that out when it all starts it's anything
Amazing
But the point is the IRA actually had something to lose and that was that there was so close to it
They were looking for territory. I mean that we're looking for independence
I believe
So they they actually had something to lose or if he's like they don't have anything to gain at all
The terrorism that's happening now is the terrorism of the mines
There isn't in fact anything for them to win a global with it
The end of the day people don't just flip flop all faith and they certainly don't fit
Faith and territory
By blowing them up
So you know it's a completely inanimate it's not it's a I think it's a I think it's a the actual
What they goals are with a move point it's territory safe
I believe I mean
Pulling out of
But you know
With the whole body it's because we want that anyway so
It's not as if they should be for me anyway you know what I'm bloody round on you
I'm
You know
Yeah, I've overstayed you welcome Charles the drunkard London everybody
Yeah Charles I disagree with you
You know, so what we're talking about here is prevention of so-and-blowing something up
But it's not really the root cause it's kind of like the drinking
You know you don't in my mind you don't fix a teenage drinking by raising the price
You know that that's ridiculous why are they drinking what is the root cause of the problem?
And I think there's a lot to be discussed over there which I think a lot of it has to do with pure boredom probably
And lack of heroes and people to look up to
When it comes to the terrace why why do they want not because they don't have anything to live for
Or something has happened that has made their lives so horrible that they don't have anything to live for
Let's just go back for second. I do not believe
That there are people who for religious convictions have just decided they have to come and kill us
I just can't buy that and I don't also don't believe it's true. I think that's
That's something has been created by
government media people who shape opinions
But that it's you know, it's I don't think that that's the way really what's going on here
There's a lot of pissed off people pissed off primarily the United States and the more I look at the military
Industrial complex the more I start to understand it
You've been raping countries. What's the book?
Confessions of an economic hitman you must read this book listen to it on audible.com
Well, you can get it off iTunes. I think that comes from audible as well. It's where I bought it really easy you can buy it right now
Listen to that book
Listen to what the United States has been doing for the better part of 60 years
What's the other one legacy of ashes read about the CIA
I think we've been pissing people off
So maybe if we stop pissing people off we won't have to be racially profiling people to stop him from blowing shit up
And they'll have no reason to blow shit up
All right, I want to don't want to end on a downer note today. Thanks Charles by the way for calling in
Charles a drunk a Londoner. I'd like it when he's drunk better
Don't I am the root of all evil. I am the root of your drinking. There you go
Because he just funny of that way
I love it when I get calls like this one our buddy from Germany who I believe is from the Netherlands has
Made a career change and he seems to be very happy about it sales guy you've come on buddy
It changed keep in me slave
To my employer man
I let my girl and job, you know your podcast really made me think
About you know my life what am I doing is it's really where I want to take my life
I want to make the most out of it
I made a list for myself
Companies that I would like to work for
I applied I got in I quit my normal job. I'm moving into a new job for June 1st
Absolutely happy about it working on my blog right now
Even though I'm gonna make the last money, you know, it's not such a high position as I had before
It's all fine. I feel free. I'm enjoying life and enjoying my family and enjoying my kids
Starting my own blog
This summer shining again
Thanks man. You definitely definitely been a motivation for me and
Yeah, you changed my view. I'm a lot of things
Thank you keep up the good work
No home. I love you all the time
Take care when
Doesn't
No, it does
You've congratulations, dude. There's nothing more powerful than quitting a job. Don't you love that feeling?
I'd for St. Patty's Day. I didn't forget the I greatly assassination
When I reshized a burning on your daily source
I
Have a long-to-stagger leave leave have a long-toe slushy night
A long-toe girl that's leaving
Well, you want them to fight tonight
Listen to my arish eyes
Give these for the lattice chies
When you ever want to realize
All gonna do fight tonight
It doesn't matter
It doesn't matter if you're probably one
It doesn't matter if you're still
Believe it, it just is what I'm done
I want to see you the violent films with my friends yawning this girl friend
But we're gonna follow the show together
You can mix it up with a girl main tank
All the weeps and let's be
Somebody crack smoke, let's be friends
She sounds too musical
I'm trying to control
She's the first part who was a mess
Now she had a close head of the bed
Why did you see that six foot sound
Got a show doesn't watch the sounds
When the shots are burning bright
Dream to a women for your life
You'll get the shots
You'll run the night
When I reshized a burning on your daily source
I do go and I'll win through a show
We'll serve you in girl that I still know
It's a Friday night and it's a show that I'll
Rollin' and roll around on the ground
Under the lights of the mark each
The women feet are still scaling my knees
I was breaking my nose on the fear of the girl
It's special balls on the food
I want to listen my feet
But I didn't really know it
I was bleeding on someone and dreaming of you
Just this entire week, we're giving it to ourselves
Face and Kevin, we are ready
My jacket and bed and you jean glam
Frame, when I'm running out of shame
Just me and John and Frigney
We'll clean our soul, but we're goddamn lean
We're just the filing James Ford Murphy
We're making me laugh when I look for my teeth
When I misshized a burning cry
To your winning arms for your life
And then I misshized a world of nights
When I reshized a burning
In your feelings and seeing
It doesn't make you try and walk
It doesn't make you feel it's easy
For giving it to us one time
titanium
Sounds as pumper
Quite cast as jumping
Yes, belongs to the stag alone
Mement, belongs
for gross leaving
from around you
Vaseline
And humans are my size
Coop for making you stay
Incredible
We're a real
You're the only one to swell three nights.
Yo, the iGrily assassination with Irish eyes are burning.
You'll also find another positive music network.
Thank you to Sir Jersey Todd with a name like that.
Of course, he could be the chairman of British telecom.
Jersey Todd passed that on to me, especially for St. Patty's day.
All right, everybody.
The week is kind of weird, but I am planning on doing as many shows as possible.
I'd love to do five.
Wouldn't that be amazing to have a full week of the Charlie's?
Although I did get a lot of email from people saying,
Thanks, man, finally I could catch up.
All right.
Hey, whatever you do today, specifically,
as you walk through the normal habits of what you do every single day,
pay attention to stuff, pay attention to people.
Talk to someone you haven't talked to, live your life with passion
and enjoy your freedom while it lasts.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Thank you.