It was $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You know, back in my day, full-barred mid-really, really bad things.
Then this Adam Curry comes along and he makes a good thing.
Everything's happy, lots of music people have in fun.
It's on the DSC 743.
I hope you have fun with your full bar Friday.
I'm gonna sit here and eat my oatmeal.
Wait for Jeopardy to come on.
Maybe the rehearsal dropped her pen today, and then over to pick it up.
I'm gonna sit here and eat my oatmeal.
I'm gonna sit in the bathroom.
From the 25th anniversary edition
of Michael Jackson's Thrill.
I was just dropped to my mailbox the other day.
participation at the michaeljax.com slash podcast project.
The 2008 remix of Beat It featuring Fergi and it sounded like a whole new
Eddie Van Halen. Super power solo on guitar and it's even cooler when artists
do their own mashups. I'm saying this is the Fubar Friday maximum music big
time hangover edition of the Charlie episode number 743 man. I am hurting today.
I'll tell you all about it when I'm late with the boys and you know me is a
non drinker. I should have stuck to my guns and not drunk. Well I did drink
drunk and I'm feeling the pain today my friends. Sorry.
When I wake up in the morning I pull on my jeans and I'm feeling alright.
I pull my boots on. I pull my boots on. I pull my boots on. I pull my boots on.
I pull my boots on.
I pull my boots on. I pull my boots on. I pull my boots. I pull my boots...
All of these are all of these. I fell down at the airport. I knew they armed it here in eternity so
she'd keeprayed. I settled down like UT is a snack for a half a year. I would walk all day
I would be around the middle for three months. I just did get the idea and now this is just
a day with nothing了解 with these three backing sounds. I only need you to switch up and
And in the summer, the wind and the rain
And in the summer, the wind and rain
But in the summer, the wind and the rain
And in the summer, the wind and the rain
I'm gonna roll again
When I wake up in the morning light
I pull on my jeans and I'm feeling alright
I roll my boots on, I roll my boots on
When I wake up in the morning light
I pull on my jeans and I'm feeling alright
I roll my boots on, I roll my boots on
David Dunn has guessed it's ready for the weekend
Working his old blue jeans on
All the songs that are not from the concert music that work for this
For this footballer Friday are at least 30 years old
So just bear that in mind when you're saying, well man
I don't think I've ever heard that song before
Besides the usual for a footballer Friday
Which includes a young police hate test
And of course Sir Jersey Todd will be stopping by with his pick of the week
We've also got some financial talk today
Lots of people interested in what's going on with the credit crunch
With financial markets and all
We're going to that a little bit later on
Just kick back relax and get ready
Now do you remember this song?
Also 30 years old
Fox
Look at the phone
And come and sound
What they expected
You know tonight
Just choose
Shake them off
And while I go and turn
But there's a downside
I've got a lot to say
Don't think
I ain't no one
My way you're shaking
The mist of last train
Cause I've got a lot to say
Don't think
Shake them off
And they don't say
And they don't know
I can't sleep here
Shake them off
And they don't say
I don't think
But they don't want such a tear
Wanna solve such a whole thing
Ooh
Don't worry
I don't worry
But we're going to explore
Each of those minds
It's my turn to time, to hit flying
All the pleasures of life, all the choice of life
All the all I got is a single day
Ain't no hope, you're sleeping, wow ain't no shame
All I got is a single day
I could use some cowbells.
Probably the second most functional stuttering song I've ever heard of, of course,
there was my generation and when I was a small wee lad, it was fox and single bed.
Hey everybody, how are you doing? Coming to you from the Courier Manor on the west side of
G-town, it is the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Ge offered.
It's daily source code episode number 7, 4, 3, it's the Fubar Friday maximum music
edition. Really we want the sponsors today. Today is in part brought to you by
G-town and you can get 35 free songs that you can download all DRM free and you
have no obligation. So if you cancel out before 14 days you get to keep all those 35 tracks
for free but I'm pretty sure you're actually going to want to stick around because a lot
of people are using e-music, a lot of pod save artists are using e-music these days.
So have a look at e-music.com slash daily source code e-music.com slash daily source code
35 free songs can be yours.
So yesterday I actually tweeted this, believe it or not.
I had a dinner lined up with super agent Keith.
There's a lot of business for BT Pod Show here in the UK.
And the meeting with the Rod Taylor, a couple guys actually from a two-way traffic
company that I think actually was just acquired by Sony Entertainment.
And they distribute who wants to be a millionaire.
So they're a pretty big in the television world.
And we've been working on a couple ideas and talking about some things.
And so we went to this club and super agent Keith.
I think it does the PR for this club as well.
It's called the five Cavendish Square.
It's obviously a very posh address if you know London at all.
And it's not a gentleman's club. It's a private club.
There's all kinds of benefits if you remember.
You can pretty much book a table in the restaurant or room for a function if you have.
I think they have a nightclub and maybe 15 hotel rooms.
It's all real.
I mean, it's done up well.
It's really, really classy.
And the owner is this lovely guy, Jay, who's Sicilian.
But I think he's been in the UK for 20 years or so.
But boy is he Sicilian.
Italian from Sicily. Let me put it that way.
And we had a great time.
He said, man, these guys were hitting the bottles.
You know, and I'd love to drink a little bit of wine if I'm out and you know, have something with dinner.
You all know that.
And they had some excellent, excellent wine that was coming up from the dark depths of the dungeon there.
And then after dinner it was time for a smoke, a coheba cigar, which I haven't smoked the cigar.
And man, I'm going to say,
at least nine years, maybe ten years, certainly not a Cuban cigar like a coheba.
But of course, that kind of added, you know, to the whole mix of the great wine.
But then the mojitos came out.
And all I know is I was home at two o'clock this morning.
And when I woke up this morning, I felt like utter, utter shite.
I haven't felt this bad in a long time.
Because as you know, I literally, I just don't drink.
I just, you know, as I said, a glass of wine, maybe.
And now I remember why.
Holy moly, and these guys were packing it away, just unbelievable.
So the good news made some good friends.
Bad news.
Feel like shite.
Great news.
The foobars inform a thick foyer, everybody.
Hi, it's Matt from Games Weasel here on this week's show.
We play around with probably about 2000 and eight on the Wii.
Kick people in the face with condemned to on the 360.
Nice.
I visit theplay.com live event at when we stay.
You can let you know how that went.
And you can win the new game of worms for the Wii.
That's all at Gamesweasel.com.
And I break all the holidays.
Time to put the sign out.
Don't make a fool.
And we'll want it so far.
They can say so but not.
That began with a rush.
Look how far we have come.
You embrace.
Bring in the game name.
Show them that you slow her.
Why you haunt my love.
So I can't let it on my breath.
That's why you told me you made.
This is our home.
And tomorrow's home.
I'm taking such a lot of watch.
That began with a rush.
Look how far we have come.
You embrace.
Come from my red lips, who are you talking to me?
This is our home, This is our home, This is our home
This is our home, This is our home
Grandpa
decided
Santa
Grandpa
Recommended by the
Incredibly desirable yet parlar
Unreachable
reachable, and G.B. Beth Hersh from the Potset Music Network and our song.
We routed that request by the way through Sir Jersey Todd, it can be crazy the way things work.
You know, I was speaking of which that article about the Potset Music Revolution is apparently
showing up in Billboard.
I think either this week or this coming week or the week after.
I have not read it, but I hope just considering the amount of people that the journalist
even interviewed, I hope it's going to be a great story because man, this stuff really
is just a great story.
By the way, you hear the birds tweeting in the background there, it's because it's another
beautiful day, the sun is out, it's nice and warm, and still they expect snow on Sunday.
I'm not quite sure what's going on with that.
And I'm really looking forward to a restful weekend, finally with the girls, I'm going to go,
I think we're actually going to go look at a car for Christina, who of course will be taking
your driver's test pretty soon.
And then Monday is the Lady Patricia's birthday Tuesday, I'm off to the states for a couple
days.
I know New York is definitely in play, but maybe even the quicksand friend trips.
So what I should be back by the next footballer Friday.
And of course on a footballer, what can you do?
What do we all look forward to from sea to shining sea from Europe down to down under to
the west coast of the United States, everybody plays along with Yarnpol.
Let's hit test.
Oh, you're fantastic.
I'm very pissed, this is the test.
Hit it test.
Yarnpol!
Hey Adam, it's time for our hit test again.
Right on.
So here we go with intro number one.
Um, uh, it's, uh, oh man, where's she from Saturday night fever or the girl?
You've got a vine element.
Love it too.
You lost in music.
Oh, Yarnpol.
Mom.
And just a sledge of cry for it.
I grew up with that stuff, Yarn.
They get too easy on me.
Hit me number three.
And this is number three.
It's, uh, almost sounds like a, like a prince.
Little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little.
Did it.
And time for our hit on the answer.
So grab it.
Yes.
And so number one is from 1982.
This is the kind element.
I want you as your sweet thing.
My face.
The world pays
Honey, you know the blue
Come with me in love, too
All we love and all we free from these love
Rains, Danny, all the world
So I wanna be a woman
If I'm element in love, things just answer number one
And this is answer number two from Night Channel, this is Sister Slag
Honey, you know the blue
Some people who's everything
First and go with the mind
Oh, I'll check music
Holding a trap
So I'll get on music
No turn it back
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Lost in music, I guess answer number two
Two, two, this maximum music
Full of Friday, Friday, Friday, Sunday, edition of
Yeah, yeah, yeah
And this is answer number three from 1986
This is Nicole, don't you want my love
Oh man, I never listened to that kind of crap
Yeah, I remember it now, thank you
Nicole is answer number three
In this disco version of the hit test number 116
Just proves I'm not a disco guy
You do this way
Two out of two, Yana, I didn't get the last disco tracks, sorry
The answers to this hit test together with the iTunes link
You can buy these tricks online or to be found at hittest.photshow.com
I don't think you're for playing
Thanks for making us
Thank you for listening, next week I'll be back for hit test number 117
So until then, have a very nice week and try to think with your heart
Bye bye
As a nice sign off, y'all think with your hearts, I like that
Think with your hearts and smell like fart
It's the daily source code to food bar Friday edition
We have a new friend of the Charlie
Chucklehead who is as many of you just a little bit extra special
And well, I can feel a Jeff Smith jingle coming on pretty soon
Hey there Adam, this is Steve Saler from Ontario Canada again
The official albino of the Charlie
Apparently
So I guess that means I should try to get myself a jingle
Really?
Yeah, I don't know
Thank you very much that
I mean, it's a lot actually that you kind of think that's cool about me being an albino
I mean, I've been living as an albino for 24 years
And you know, the novelty kind of starts to wear off
But
Dude, let me tell you something
I love people who are different
Because you're not boring, man
It's like, it's like the same thing my love for comic strip blogger
And Roger Smalls, wherever he may be
Yes, no, you're special, man
You're a massive chucklehead
The stairs somehow remain
I don't know
Actually, it's kind of funny
You actually
The DSC listeners, you guys rock
And I also hate you all as well
Because since I mentioned my website in the last comment
I didn't think that
Well, there actually is a DSC Charlie effect
Which trounces the dig effect apparently
Because after I mentioned my website
Yeah, my website crashed
Yeah, too many, too many hits to the website
And yeah, it was down for a long time
It took me at least about 20 hours
Just to really get it back up again
It's okay, I'm totally prepared for it now
So if you all had to Steve Sailor.net
It's cool, it's going to work this time
So anyway, I just wanted to say thank you
And also send a song your way for the footballer Friday
Actually, a little bit of backstory
Being a part of the radio broadcasting program
That's a pill to put on
Especially show on the college radio station
Which is 90.1 FM
The heat tonight or a new rock
Actually, you show that we do call this week in geek
And it's also a podcast that's found at this week in geek.net
And it's a show that we do the cover
All things geek-oriented topics
From video games to movies, TV shows, you name it
We talk about it
And one of the segments we started on there
Was called The Rantings of a Double D
And it's done by my friend Dave Dennis
Or always known as Double D
And he does these weird kind of geeky random two to five minutes segments each week
And they've become so popular that he decided to go into the musical route
And with the help of our producer Pierre Sturks
Who composed in the music for the Double D Rants
They came up with a very interesting song
And I'm going to preface this by saying
If you know the short circuit movies
Back in the 80s with that little cute robot
John, you found it?
Yeah
Well, this is a little romantic techno-ditty
That deals with those movies
So Adam, I bring to you and the Charlie listeners
You can find the song now on the pot-save music network
The Rantings of a Double D
Short circuit, my heart
Hope you enjoy it, bye
John, bye
Came alive
It's all my heart away
Now we're new together
Getting better and every day
All I'm in for a little more friends
Like I'm the luckyest girl in town
It feels like I'm lucky and hooked around
When the heart is in your hand
Short circuit, my heart
We were together
We came and tried to take my love away
Oh, my little Johnny
You will always say the day
And looking for something but
And you know I can't survive
I just want you
When you want something I know
You know I can't deny
Short circuit, my heart
Hope you enjoy it, bye
Now we're new together
Getting better and every day
All I'm in for a little more friends
Like I'm the luckyest girl in town
Short circuit, my heart
Maybe I'd have such a red tone
Alright, it's coming from an unofficial albino
A Sherman, my heart
I've discarded people
The ranting of Double D
Short circuit, my heart
Wasn't there a
Was it like a debarge song or something that was about Johnny five who's Johnny?
Something like that?
I recall.
You've done it all.
When you pulled your memory cold.
I pulled the memory through the door.
You're supposed to gain no matter what you say.
The only better way.
What's the ball?
Right, right, right.
How can you tell us so many lies?
Come on, let me see me in this world.
I'll do what you want.
There's nothing left.
Oh, God, this runs away.
Maybe you carry far away.
It's just a test.
Again, for us to play.
We know this, it's hard to smile.
This is what it says.
It's true itself.
You have to hide.
Come on, let me see me in this world.
I'll do what you want.
The only one.
There ain't no more.
It'll take you to everything.
But believe it's my love.
Can you ignore my big, mean everything?
Because I know what big means and what it's worth.
I'll wait the way.
I don't say, maybe you carry far away.
Come on, let me see me in this world.
I'll do what you want.
Definitely songs from the soundtrack to our lives.
Steve Harley.
I'm pretty sure I mentioned this before, but the...
Those vocals?
That you hear now?
That's actually the Lady Patricia's sister, Lady Yvonne, back in the day.
When it was her turn to live in London, hanging out with Steve Harley and that whole gang.
I love it.
Oh, what a great way to get out of the weekend, man.
This is fantastic.
Nothing but songs you love.
And we're filled with savants today as well.
We had, of course, our official Obino of the show.
We had a young play with a hit test.
Of course, you got this new dude on the scene.
New chucklehead.
The lemonade man from the Netherlands.
Hello Adam and DC's listeners.
It's the lemonade man here.
Now that I catch up with the DC,
I'm also catching up with the podcast of a Dutch news show called
Method Al-Goborra.
A radio show of the NOS by Rick Broadcaster in the Netherlands.
There I hear this fragment, which I will translate afterwards.
At FD's, we have that psychotiroparter,
that since January, on the Zorfer's day,
Karam would have melded.
It was a kind of behandling.
That's why this is a misunderstanding of the privacy.
This is a bang that he gave us.
By the other half of the news comes,
so that iemandie depressivis starts before it.
He will take me to sleep.
So, it's a psychotiroparter,
which is the kind of regulation of health insurance companies
to supply the reason, of course, sort of a patient,
which is in their opinion,
a violation of privacy.
For example, if an insurance company has a death case,
it could be that this information lands on the wrong desk,
and someone who wants to refer to depression
is refuse a landing.
So, next time, if you meet someone who claims to have enough to hide,
you can use this as example,
how you suddenly can become someone with something to hide,
or make a point that you don't necessarily have to be a bad guy
to be in need of some privacy.
Yeah, no kidding, man.
And I think you're doing exactly the right thing,
what will happen with increasing frequency in our lives?
We'll see these types of connections being made,
databases linked up, information flowing through agencies
from one agency to the next,
with that information being tagged and added onto,
and before you know it,
well, that movie you may have seen on curry.com,
a couple weeks back about the pizza ordering.
It could actually come true,
but I'm glad to hear that this is now coming to the forefront.
So, the fact that it was on the news,
and that the doctors are unhappy with it,
that that's good, the fact that you're sharing it with us,
is fantastic.
And that's what we'll stop all the lunacy.
Just got to stay awake, stay alert,
and stay on top of our game, my friends.
That's the trick.
You've got her.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
You're on her.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's don't give a nod.
To the hardest working lawyers,
your turns in time, and then it's Jersey tight,
oh yeah.
You're on her.
What do you say?
You might even win this case.
Jersey.
Yeah.
Oh, how's it going?
Adam and Jersey tied the official musicologist of the Chacha.
Have I got a man for you this week?
old school, at least an old school feel. The band is animate objects. I like these guys. They've
got that cool kind of old school feel to them and they've got some amazing amazing lyrics.
I just dig them a lot. Check it out. It's animate objects with clot on your football Friday.
Yeah, I'm right back a lot, absolutely. It has been in the hopper. We'll ask to be in a race and ride a track, y'all
back to me, 20 things, y'all know when they're back to me. Actually, that's why you're hatein' me.
What's now sitting around the deal at the major T-8? The freshman in this game, none hazein' me.
Hip-hop, kid-hop, cold place of scene. But it ends of the beach, I'll be praising me.
We know we're up and down like a race of season patiently. As the world says, keep turning, wax me, burn in props.
We earned in France, we earned it, it's for 13. We fuckers in your clothes, the curses. So we ain't shuckin' it, y'all be joking.
This guy's been rocking with the bra of it, they ain't shit. That's from the city you're coming.
The DJ is not evil on him, we don't provoke you. That's the rest of my joke here.
We're guilty, they're gonna smoke you. You can ask me, though, when he press an enrollment.
They get the same impression in Poland, just be a case. You're a people forget, we ain't y'all win the shot.
And we make it a hop, too. Make it hot, get whatever you got from the set for the river.
And then it goes right up, and then I get whatever you got from the set for the river.
And then it goes right, make it hot, get whatever you got from the set for the river.
And then it goes like, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot.
And then it goes right, make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we
make it hot, we make it cold, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot cold, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot, we make it hot,
Yeah, when we said full of real hip hop and then it goes right
Make it hard, give way, never you got
When we said full of real hip hop and then it goes right
Would you take to the T?
If that's John fulfilled me in a long time
Jersey thought the master of ceremonies
What comes to musicology sends us anomade
like that, a lot of men definitely cool
a check-in mod the podcast music network links
In the show, a notice of course
At dailysourcecode.com
Told you the sponsors were able to control
Today
I want to kind of tune their own horn for a moment here
But our Nokia N110
Campaign that we've been running where you can kinds of
You can buy these
Do you can buy them through a number of
Potio programs
And you can't get this device cheaper anywhere else online.
We have absolutely the best deals,
like a 15% discount in the prices.
I mean, it's all sub 400 bucks now, and this thing is,
and by the way, folks, once in a while,
I get another email or a voice mail about the flash players,
or about the flash plugin not working on the player.
Just go to your settings for your browser,
which of course is completely web 2.0 compliant,
understands Ajax and Flash.
The iPhone doesn't do that in case you didn't know.
So you couldn't watch all the YouTube videos on this thing.
And the two-ing our own horn thing is,
we're actually responsible for like a large percentage
of all sales in Canada, you know?
It's like crazy.
It's really working out.
So go to my show notes, you'll see a link there.
And of course, you wanna use the daily source code promo code
to get your massive discount
and get this awesome device, which I'm just having a good time
with still.
It really is my computer, when I don't wanna computer,
when I just wanna sit down on the couch,
chill out and still have my Skype,
and my YouTube capabilities,
right near their flash stuff, just loving it.
Promise you a couple of svons,
or not just svons, but some questions about
to the credit crunch and about finance.
I do wanna delve into that before we hit the weekend.
So here's the first of those two.
Oh, sorry about that.
Here we go.
Hello Adam Poledogless Boyer of the MadModemachene.com.
Oh, wait a minute.
I need to have this show on our network.
MadModemachene podcast, like it.
Custom blog here.
You and I are arriving at the same fascination
at the same time, and that is,
what is going on behind the scenes with our money?
Man, love the reverb.
Now, on a previous no agenda,
you talked with John C to work about the meaning of gold.
You ask, why is gold so viable?
And John said, well, it's because they make jewelry out of it
and they use an electronics.
Gold is viable because it's rare.
And you know, for most of the previous 6,000 years gold,
itself was used as money.
And so when produced in the shape of a coin
and standardized, we now have a fixed value for that money.
Now, throughout all those 6,000 previous years of history,
there's been this struggle between real money
and government-controlled money.
And right now, the pendulum has swung completely
to government-controlled money.
But I encourage you to take a look at a book called The Creature
from Jekyll Island, subtitled a second look
at the Federal Reserve.
You know, I've had this ongoing conversation all week
with John ever since I really start broaching this topic.
And I think that there's a lot of conspiracy theory stuff
going on about the Federal Reserve.
Stuff that actually doesn't really matter anymore.
How it was created, or why it was created,
the fact that it is, is really the problem at hand.
And this whole Jekyll Island thing, that is a major conspiracy theory.
But I think it's almost distraction because it doesn't matter.
You know, it's something happened, whether it took place
in Jekyll Island, whether it was cloak and dagger stuff or not.
But yes, I'm very familiar with that.
And it is a very interesting theory, of course,
if you're into your conspiracy things.
But again, I'm just more interested in how it works
and how the money flows and what the Fed does
and who calls the shots, really, and who says,
let's make some more money and where can that go?
And do we realize that that is actually a hidden tax
because our dollar becomes less valuable?
Well, that's where I'm at my friend.
But please do continue.
By G. Edward Griffin, there is a one hour long talk he gave
about this subject.
You can find this one hour talk at Spielbauer.com slash
Jekyll download.htm.
Spielbauer is SPIL, B-A-U-E-R.
.com slash Jekyll, J-E-K-Y-L-L download.
It's got HTM and it's a fascinating talk
about the behind the scenes working of money.
I would love to see us have real money again.
Beautiful coins made out of precious metals.
You know, the UK, I just saw on the paper yesterday,
they're coming out with new coins.
So they were placing the pound, the five pens,
the 10 pens, the 20 pens, the 50 pens.
I don't think they were placing the two pound coin,
at least I didn't see it.
Actually, I was thinking, yeah, it's just coins.
But if you're putting new coins in a circulation,
and of course, what's interesting to me
is the timing of this new coin bringing into the new circulation
of money, even though it's just coins.
I mean, still, you can easily put several hundred million
into circulation in new coin, and of course,
you're supposed to take the old coins out of circulation.
But it's not interesting that that would happen
at this very moment when it seems like money needs
to be injected into the system.
I wonder if that actually has anything to do
with the timing of this, and they clearly can't take coins
out of circulation, the old ones out,
and then put new ones in.
I presume there's some kind of sliding scale,
but just interesting to me.
And then, of course, paper certificates
that are redeemable in precious metal coins.
And then, ultimately, the elimination of the federal reserve
and control government control over money.
In why is government control money so bad?
Well, it's because by printing more of it,
they create inflation.
Did you know that in Roman times, an ounce of gold
could buy a nice suit of clothes in the 1700s,
an ounce of gold could buy a nice suit of clothes.
And today, an ounce of gold can buy a nice suit of clothes.
That is a fantastic observation.
Indeed, with gold about, what is it, $1,000 a Troy ounce?
You could indeed buy a really nice suit.
That's a fascinating thought that that value has stayed
the same throughout centuries.
So with gold as money, there is no inflation.
Well, maybe a little bit as they dig more of it out of the ground.
And did you know Adam that a penny from 1982 or earlier
is made out of pure copper and it's worth two and a half cents?
You can find out more details at coinflation.com.
I'm going to be talking about the behind-the-scenes
looking money on my show at madmanemachine.com.
Thanks, Adam, insert standard closing here.
I love you, Nina, man.
Interesting.
Of course, all that's 2020 hindsight, I guess.
But it's fun to see how many people are responding
to this conversation about money, speaking of which,
if you die and you want your spouse or your other dependence
to get tons of dough,
have I got a deal for you?
I can sell you some life insurance, my friends,
up to 70% discount at acu-quote.com.
Here's what you want to do if you're interested.
And anyone should have some form of life insurance.
And there's other insurances you can get from acu-quote as well.
But please check out acu-quote.com slash DSC.
Or if you put this into your phone right now,
you don't have to call it now, but just put this in plus one.
In the stage, you might do 001, but just hit the plus sign.
Plus one, 800, 410, 7214.
If you missed it, just rewind a couple of seconds
and put that in your phone.
That's also a, these guys are pretty cool the way they set it up.
That's also a special custom DSC phone line,
so they'll know that you came through the, through the Charlie.
Make sure you get some life insurance.
You can always name me as the beneficiary.
I got no problem with that whatsoever.
So we stick with one more, and then we'll do two songs.
We'll get out of here, get ready for the weekend.
I think so.
Good one.
This is the last bit of feedback on finance,
but I think you'll like it.
Hi there, Mr. Curry.
My name is Lee Brown, and I find your conversation
about the current credit crunch and everything else
that's happening at the moment, very interesting.
Now, I've got a question, and it's probably very stupid,
and I apologize, and it's fun.
No, no, no, no, hold on a second.
You do realize, of course, that there's no such thing
as a stupid question on the Charlie.
I'm sorry for that, but what I don't understand
is that if the same amount of money is still in circulation
in the sense where people who've been making money
have waxed into bank accounts, and then those banks,
and now reinvesting that money into other things,
then surely the circulation of money is still about.
So why have we suddenly turned up into a credit crunch?
Obviously, people who've had mortgages
are being paying those mortgage debts into mortgage providers,
and those mortgage providers, obviously,
wacking that into the bank, and also learning it out
further into other people, which are then obviously paying it back.
So if the circulation is still about,
why have we then turned up into a credit crunch,
if that makes sense?
I'd like to hear your thoughts.
I don't know, I've searched around a bit,
and I don't really really found out any information like that.
So I love the show.
Hope you can answer that stupid question,
and I hope to hear from you soon.
Thanks a lot.
Oh man, I think it's the crux of the question right there,
that it's really good because indeed,
the money is still in circulation,
but what's happening is banks are lending out more money
than they actually have.
So that's where a second, let me just put that on silence there.
So the banks are lending out more money than they have,
there go lending out more than it's in circulation.
And all of this is built on trust,
because they trusted their mortgage brokers,
that the brokers were finding appropriate people
to lend out this money to this phantom money.
And of course, the banks in turn were basing that phantom,
the phantom payments, because they stopped occurring
when rate went up or when situations changed.
They in turn were using that to guarantee
their own lending and borrowing business with other banks.
And the real problem is, is just no one trusts
what anyone else says.
And it comes from the trust between the mortgage broker
and the borrower, which in many cases was,
oh, just pure stupidity and greedy on the borrower side.
And I have to say, I'm really sorry.
Yes, you got scammed.
Yes, it was part of a large overall scam,
but it should happen, you know?
And sometimes you just got to learn the hard way.
And I know that sounds unsympathetic,
but you have to learn if you want to play this game.
And, you know, this should also make you think twice
about eulas and software licenses,
and all kinds of terms of service and things
that you just take for granted and just say,
okay, I'll do it and sign off on.
And if these things are too complicated and overbearing,
then hey, look, where the customer,
we're king, we should say stop, this is dumb.
We're all gonna lose, because we learn that this is not
the way to do it.
So it's something, I hope that gives you some form of answer.
It's somewhere in the middle there
as I think what you're looking for,
but it is all about this idea of fractional reserve lending,
which is lending out more money than you actually have
to cover that and then turning around
and taking that phantom money that you think
you'll one day get back and lending that out,
or borrowing against that from other banking institutions.
It's really, it's just been whipping this money around
or these figures, because it's not really money,
it's just data in computer systems.
1s and 0s been whipping around
and people have been, of course,
been taking those 1s and 0s and commissions
and in bonuses and pumping that parts of that back
into the economy, the luxury markets, I would say.
But at the end of the day, yeah,
it's something was bound to go wrong.
And I think, well, today what I've done,
I've popped my 401k,
I've taken all the money out,
because of course, that was invested in US based funds.
I've transferred all that money into euros,
I'm keeping as much money as possible in euros,
I believe the United States is headed for,
definitely headed for a recession.
It could actually be a pretty shitty one,
when I think about it.
And was that movie I talked about
or that documentary I talked about the other day?
I was on the BBC, George Soros also agrees.
He says there's gonna be a US recession,
but the extent of it, even he doesn't know exactly
what that's gonna be.
That's all right, my friends,
so just stick with me, I've got all the answers.
We'll be fine, won't we?
Huh?
Oh, man, we will if we got some good tunes.
Here's one that is over 40 years old,
but a song that is definitely a sound part
of the soundtrack to my life.
I know all the words by heart,
I have no idea where I picked him up
other than my parents playing this at home.
I love you.
He wanted to give her everything.
Flower, present,
and most of all, a wedding ring.
He saw a sign for a stock car race.
$1,000 right, it ran.
He couldn't get Laura on the phone.
So to her mother, Tommy said,
tell her I love her.
Tell her I hate her.
Tell her I may be late.
I've something to do that cannot wait.
He drove his car to the racing ground.
He was the youngest driver there.
The crowd roar as they started the race.
From the track they drove at a deadly pace.
No one knows what happened that day.
How his car overturned in flames,
but as they pulled him from the twisted wreck
with his dying grin, they heard him say.
Tell her I love her.
Tell her I need her.
Tell her I'm not to cry.
My love for her will let her die.
Now in the chapel, one more great.
For her, Tommy, who passed away.
It was just for Laura.
He lived and died alone.
In the chapel, he can hear him cry.
Tell her I love her.
Tell her I need her.
Tell her I'm not to cry.
My love for her will let her die.
Don't you just love that story?
Isn't it just beautiful?
You probably noticed I haven't mentioned live 365 today.
I'm not streaming this live because there's something weird with the internet.
I have an idea.
Although I'm not quite sure I've been trying to do some troubleshooting here and there.
But is there something wrong with one of the big backhaul carriers?
Maybe level three is having some issues.
Because I'm just seeing broken connections to certain certain sites who I don't know.
Like Google has been really difficult.
Gmail has been tough.
But other sites, you know, blazingly fast connectivity and live 365.
It kind of started yesterday.
And it's like packets were getting dropped and I just really don't understand why.
Now I have two networks in the house and it's happening on both of them.
So I don't think it's it's the local ISPs necessarily.
Although they may all be connected to the same peering provider or backhaul or whatever.
But I just I didn't want to give anyone a bad experience because I think that that kind of sucked when we do the show on Wednesday.
People just it really wasn't worth it.
And I don't think it's live 365's fault.
But if you know anything about that, please let me know.
Because just drive them me now.
So otherwise I'm going to start troubleshooting my own connection.
And I'll hell, who wants to do that over the weekend.
Particularly since this weekend.
I'm looking forward to my big rebuttal to John C. Dvorak regarding reality television.
So I got better fish to fry.
Much bigger ones my friends.
We came in with Mike less leave with Mike.
He's rocking Robin from a long time ago.
Can I sit with each other hard in love?
I've been in a bottle since I had some.
I've been in a bottle since I have some.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Jackson 5, rock and robin' with Michael Jackson on lead vocals, rapping up the max
music full bar Friday, fright, train for you this week on daily source code episode 743.
Well, I'm just really knackered. I'm really tired. So I have no big philosophy for you this Friday
other than I hope you have a really good weekend. I hope you live your entire weekend as you
should the rest of your life with lots of passion. Ain't no what? Throw off all the shackles. Enjoy your
freedom. Another pot show pot cast. Stick it in your ear.