Uhhh...Fubile...
Ho Chi! Ho Chi! Get the camera quick, here comes Adam Curry in the DSC 732!
It was $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
On testing, this madam Curry!?
1K1…
Bat on your face!
Tonight I....I'll be with you tonight tonight
Tonight...I'll be with you tonight
Tonight
It's for everybody
You've got to burn it, burn it with the time
You've got to burn it with the time
You've got to think and think you want to do
No matter how many we do
No, no, no, no, no, no
Just don't be my hand, my hands, my arms
Don't come closer, come dear
Tonight you'll be the first light
Then I'll be the little do
You can't be so silent
I'm not showed alone, no, no
Tonight you'll be here
And I'll tell you it's thanks to
Tonight is all the rain
I'll be with you tonight
Tonight, I'll be with you tonight
I want to throw them all around the world together
Tonight they'll be the first night that I've been in love with you
You're getting me so excited
I'm not sure what I'm going to do
Tomorrow you won't be here
And I don't expect too
Tonight is all I remember
I'm here for you, for you
I'm from you
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Tonight tonight
I'll be with you tonight
Tonight is all I remember
Oh man, nothing kicks off a full bar quite like Chief Trig, nor I'm saying tonight.
It is Denny Source code episode number 732 coming to you from the affluent suburb of
Surrey known as Gilford, West Side of G-town up in Adams attic in the curry manner.
Boy, the description just gets longer and longer, doesn't it?
Ah, it's a beautiful day blue skies, couple of clouds, windows wide open, and the microphone
throttle pedal to the metal because the full bar is on and full effect that means maximum
music, minimum BS, and all the tunes that fit into the soundtrack of your lives, proudly
presented by the organization for the preservation to the soundtrack of your lives.
So from Chief Trig we head on over to Jersey, that's where the next track comes from.
I had in Jersey Joe here, please check out this artist to grow it up to the positive news
network.
My name is Marin, it's Morris, he's 17 years old, it looks like a lot of talent.
Thanks, and we'll see you on the jury side in the fight.
Today, you want it to go with it, be over at about this stage, just what you want
to know.
And I know what sets it to that, you stay, but I can't stay, because I know how to say to
reverse, yeah, I've been once you walk on the wild side before, but you're just
you must for me, must for me, yeah, I say it's gonna be okay, but yeah, I trust you,
and I'll give you one more day, get out of here, be over at about this stage, just what
you want to know, and I know what sets it to that, you stay, but I can't stay, because I know
you're saying, you're偷.
You wanted to know this would be alright
Right, yeah, yeah
I got to make today a celebration of sorts just a private little celebration because man so much has happened in the past couple of months
I think starting in November we went on a whole new reinvention tour
Of the pod show, I'm sorry Martin, let me show you a second
Let the youth take over
There we go
Martin Morris, you can find out the pod save music network links in the show notes of course at dailysourcecode.com
And thanks to Jersey Joe for calling that one
And also Jersey Todd, tip that one as well
Todd, the official musicologist always sends in a couple of choices from me to select from
For the Jersey Todd contribution and of course, Jersey Todd will be up in a little bit later on in the show
As I was saying, it feels like kind of a celebration man, there's so much has been happening
We figured out really two real rock solid ways of, oh gee, making money
So that's kind of good because that's kicking into gear
We've got new designs on the way of course v3 on the heels of that
There's just so much going on new show being produced as we speak the legends of rock
We've been able to license some awesome live performances from true legends
So that's being worked on as we speak in fact
I did the, I did the voiceovers earlier this morning
That's why the voice is so low
The legends of rock
Oh man, so maximum music football Friday
It's been a while since we don't one of these and I feel in perfect shape
A couple of calls that I do want to share with you
The first one from James who of course has been calling to the program for a number of years now
Pretty much ever since I hit the UK
The island, the island, the island of the United Kingdom
And James has got a gripe
Not just about to close circuit television cameras in the UK
And the way I view those or the way they view me
But also about his comments and general James
I don't James
So don't feel like you're sometimes not all the time
But sometimes his body is the media
I'll set you in a meal and I know you read my emails because you respond to them
And sometimes just sometimes you don't play in my comments
Sometimes you don't read my emails
That James James James, I just want to say one thing
Do you know how many comments I receive
And the biggest problem is the length
You know when you're calling in a two minute comment or three minutes
It's just too long
It just takes up too much time
And sometimes your topics are very specific
So it's not that I don't love you man
And it's not that I don't care
It's not that I'm the filter
Well I am filtering
Sometimes I just don't feel like talking about what you're talking about
No I'm saying
But I do save them all
And I look at them every single day
On the podcast
Which is fair enough
I've got no problems with that verse
As general rule
Because yes you sometimes think my comments are interesting
That's fair enough
I've got no problem with that
But sometimes I have to be involved with this here
And you still don't play it
And that is your filtering
Sometimes you're calling from the car
And it's hard to understand your James
Your filtering what you want to hear
And sometimes I think that's because you think it might sway
People's judgment on your way of thinking
The one I'm talking about is this 16 thing thing
So I reiterated for the podcast verbally
So it may get clear
We've got 3...
6 billion cameras in the UK
Something like that
I was a 10
Or you'd buy to buy anyway
So then we've got those cameras on
And 24 hours a day
365 days a year
So somebody else can do the maths
Basically that's a lot of hours
Let's say 188 cameras
Adam, nobody's fucking watching you
Stop being such a paranoid fuckman
Nobody is sitting watching
This many billions of hours in CCTV
It isn't fucking happening
It's used reactively
It's used when a little girl goes missing
They go and look at the CCTV cameras and go
Right, we saw past this problem
We saw going to this shop
It happens when somebody holds a bank
It's very bad quality
But we get the picture of the girl
That's got the bonus place
Played into the casiers
Nobody is watching Adam
Cool content
Ask me how do I feel
As we know that we're cozy and cleaning
Well all I can say is if I were a bell I'd be ringing
From the moment we kissed tonight
That's the way I've just got to be
Hey girl if I were a lamp I'd light
And if I were about a right way
Ask me how do I feel
Little me with my quiet upbringing
Well all I can say is if I were a game
I'd be swinging
And if I were a watch I'd start
Popping my spray
Or if I were a bell I'd go
Tim, dong, ding, dong, ding
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Triless, and I'm learning.
Well, all I can say is if I were a bridge I'd be learning.
Yes, I knew my morale would crack
From the wonderful way that you look.
Girl, if I were a duck I'd quack
Or if I were a goose I'd be caught
How do I feel?
Now that we're finally crescent
Well, if I were a solid I'd know
I'd be splashing my dressing
Asked me how to describe this whole beautiful thing
Well, if I were a bell I'd go ding-dong ding-dong ding
Justin Marcus, if I were a bell
Also from the pod save music network
What a diversity we have there, huh?
And it's all for free enjoy
Put it in your show, promote the music
And may all your Fridays be football
Is a woman from a Billboard magazine who's doing the rounds
She's she's contacted several prominent podcasters
Also myself
Although she contacts him some other prominent ones before me
I found out
And it looks like she's doing an article on the promotion
Valpromotional value of podcast
Boy, do we have a story to tell?
I can't wait, I'm very excited about that
That should really reset the bar for the music industry
Because Billboard people do read it
But it's really an industry magazine
I remember people used to go and buy it
You know, to find out was on the charts and to read the stories
But now it's really become
They might be in pretty much an industry type magazine
So that should be pretty exciting
Get some more promotion out there for the pod save music
Now work in the artists and producers who participate in the revolution
So you can tell the high-pitched wine has gone
I figured that one out
We are yet one step closer to having the perfect set of
Not only that, but I've also improved my
Headphone amplifier
So I need this shit loud man, the older I get
The louder it has to be
I've got an email, which is clearly an automatic email
It's in German, so I won't bore you with my attempt at reading it and pronouncing it
Apparently what it seems to have done is gone out
There's a system called PhoneCaster.de
They automatically go out and are parsing XML feeds
And are making those available on their own telephone numbers
So you can call in to a German, actually here
Let me do it on my cell phone for a second
Let me see if I can find it
I know I called it earlier, here we go
Those of you who want to play along at home
You would do in your cell phone plus four nine
nine three one six six three nine three three one eight
Let me pop that up right now
I'm just going to hold the phone up to the microphone
So you can hear what happens. This is pretty interesting
And I just have one question about it, so there's ringing
Hold on
I'll watch it now work now, right?
Let's see
Hello
Hello, is DailyStores called home
The hell is that?
It sounds like
Now it sounds like I hit the middle of the show somehow
Is that when's they show or Thursday show?
Yeah, interesting. I thought it would start at the beginning
Okay
Anyway, so my main question was this 0931 number
Is that a, it says it's a regular network cost
At least that's what I can translate from what I'm reading here in the email
From phonecaster.de
But I'm interested, I'm interested who's behind it how it works
And if it costs anything super extra
Because I have to say the quality was surprisingly good
Coming through the phone
And I'm not a big fan of these things usually
But this, you know having a, you don't have to enter a pin number
Have your own dedicated phone number
Interesting, so German friends, let me know
Hey, it is a football Friday
And tomorrow I've got an interesting day ahead
Christina has an audition
I can't tell you what the project is for
But it's an existing television series
And she has to go to Europe to continental Europe
In order to do the audition
Now the part is, I would say almost written for the way it looks
I mean, it's unbelievably perfect
So I'm sure she'll be, she'll be great at it
Now of course the question is, are we going to fly tomorrow
Together on easy jet
Or will the weather be nice enough
That I take her in the Delta Share
And we go over back and forth
I obviously know what my preference is
But I've kind of got to get a good hand along the weather
Because if it's going to be bumpy
I don't want to put her through that
Particularly not once she's already
A little bit nervous for the audition
And of course, it's being football Friday
There's one highlight of everybody's week
It's got to be the hit test here's young pole light
One challenging casting with Adam Curry
Adam, are you ready to be stumps?
Hell yeah
Because he is the hit test with young pole light
Yeah Adam, hit test number 112
Okay
And we're going to start right away with intro number one
It's a easy easy peasy
Pointing in part
Fahanaanaana
Michael Jackson rock with you
Of course it is the 25th anniversary of the thriller album
So it doesn't surprise me
Number two
It's either Kim Wild Cambodian
Or it's a visage fade degree
I'm going to go with Kim Wild actually
And this is intro number three
Whenever I hear that kind of like
Going to do it
I always think of the SOS band
But I'm sure I'm wrong
All right
I think I got two out of three this week
And it's done
I think it's done
For a try
Two
Three
Four
Two
Six
Four
Two
And this is answer number 1.
Yes, Kim Wild.
Yeah, it's from 1982.
I was just clubbing.
Wild and Kim Boja.
But he was tired of this.
She wasn't ever as well.
He had jobs to do.
Yeah, he did.
Kim Boja by Kim Wild is answer number 2.
And this is answer number 3.
From 1989, Sydney Youngblood.
They've only I could.
It's a shame we're only allowed to play about 30 seconds of each track.
Most of the time I really want to play every little detail of every track.
Okay, well, we just can't.
Sydney Youngblood, if only I could have answered number 3.
In today's, this week's hit-ish time is same.
All right, Adam, how did you do?
Two out of three on.
I knew I'd do okay.
If I had time to update the website, hit test.
That part show dot com.
That is the place to find the answers to this hit-ish,
and also the links to iTunes.
So that you can play or sorry by these tracks and flying.
Alrighty, thank you for playing, Adam.
Next week, I'll be back for hit-ish number 113.
So until then, have a great time and take care.
Bye-bye.
We back, hit test at gmail.com!
In four young pull-up dots com...
7 N P O E O Y O E D C C C C C C C!
Oh man!
Here in that Kim Wildtrak really took me back for a second.
I was just doing my first television gig in the Netherlands
and Kim was on the show and she was much younger
at the time as well.
I think she's maybe two or three years older than I am.
And I was,
I was in 1920s, something like that.
Oh man, I was, I was in love with her.
God, she was the perfect woman.
I met her again a couple years later, I knew York, she did a showcase when I was at MTV.
And it was kind of weird because Patricia was there.
And somehow I didn't feel the love coming back.
Hi, Adam, it's Matt from Game To Evil.
On this week's show, we've got a review of a beautiful catamari on the Xbox 360.
You can also win yourself a copy of that game.
I also play Res HD on the Xbox Live Marketplace.
And we get a little chat with the guys from Sega about their new game, Viking, Battle
for Asgard.
That's all at gamesweasel.com.
Still the snow keeps falling, till we can't keep out the cold, but they don't know that my
back was broken back.
I'm so no, I can hardly move until dawn now.
And so you get the love to win the league.
Some people say...
Man, I dream of silence lying, and I left you so far below where I can't say,
where the world is from the land.
It's so hard to just watch you play, but you can't say.
Some people say...
And some people say...
And some...
Neil Burr sent me this one.
David Asher soon to be released on the Pods 8 Music Network.
And some people say...