Atom warned you about the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the DSC 788.
Atom warned you about the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole.
It's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get sucked into the black hole, now it's time to get
Oh man, this whole Freddie Mac, Fanny May, better known as Fraudian Fony, this whole bailout situation, it's, first of all, completely un-American, although I understand where the coming from, but bailing out enterprise, even though it's a so-called GSE, it was never really made clear if this government sponsored enterprise, if it really hasn't implicit or explicit backing from the federal government, well now of course we know they do,
the treasury wrote a $200 billion check to both of these companies, and it's open-ended because a lot more can happen, and a lot more needs to take place, how you feel in today?
You feel in good after this exercise, the treasury and the federal reserve went through this past weekend, I don't know about you, but I'm having trouble sitting down from this flaming hot poker that's up my ass, because I am one of the many Americans, millions who will be paying for this, for the bailout of these two companies, and you're right, my friend of there in Seattle,
sorry, Portland, yeah, they talk about cronyism, I read another name, one of the guys who's going to be taken over as intra-manager, he's from the Carlisle group, right, that's the Bush hedge fund empire, Carlisle group, it's like, there's so open about it, so blatant, it's not, and then, you know, how do the world leaders feel about what's going on, well they feel great because they're, you know, those the guys that get basically got bailed out,
I see leaders from Japan, word from China, oh yes, this is great, we love it, this is exactly what needed to happen, well, you know you're getting screwed with those guys are happy about it, you just know you are, meanwhile, as your mortgage gotten any cheaper, I mean, significantly, is anyone still willing to lend you money?
G, did your house price go up? No, of course it didn't, this is, this is just an atrocity, is what I call this, and I don't even understand how far all of this can go, but some good links on the drop from Bloomberg, certainly a credible source, investors, maybe, and I've been talking about this one for a long time, investors, it says maybe forced to settle contracts,
protecting more than $1.4 trillion of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac bonds against the default, after the USC's control of the companies and a bid to bolster the housing market.
So this is these, these derivatives, which, you know, the word already says it, it's a derivative of the actual security, so it's little bits and bobs and pieces, and the entire derivatives market is just so huge, it doesn't just deal with, it deals with currencies, not just mortgage back assets,
but we're talking hundreds of trillions of dollars in total, so now, what I understand from this is that the international swaps and derivatives association, because this stuff is really fuzzy, these derivatives, okay, it's a guy's college up on the phone and hey, I got 8 billion of these, yeah, I got he billion of those, well, let's just do a swap, I'll say the facts later, but because, because of the fact,
this conservatorship, basically, these companies being more or less nationalized, but certainly bail out sounds too light, you know, it sounds like your, your skiff is filling up with water.
Ooh, let's bail it out, no, this is stealing hundreds of billions of dollars from the American taxpayers, let's just call it theft.
But anyway, this theft apparently does trigger what they call a credit event, which means that they have to settle all of these, all of these trades, these swaps,
at least that's what the international swaps and derivatives association is calling for, and nothing of this size has ever been settled ever before, so, and I'm sure there's not going to be a hell of a lot of news about it until it all goes horribly wrong.
September 30th, I think, is when the U.S. closes its financial books for the year, and that's probably when we'll see that we're just bankrupt.
I think, you know, as far as I'm concerned, the federal, you know, the deficit rose by five trillion dollars.
I mean, these these companies, these phony and fraud.
They are, they're bankrupt, so all that debt just being passed right on to us, yes, sure.
There's all kinds of fuzzy words about, we get first money out and investors, they got to take some pain, but, you know, when I saw the premier of Japan Prime Minister, when I saw him yesterday, I didn't have to understand what he was saying.
I knew he was happy. All these guys are happy, because they saved their own asses.
Let's see, lots of links about this event, and it's just fascinating to follow, because this is purposely, I think, being held away from us.
Please, don't look at Wall Street, don't look at the markets, go look at the hurricane or anything else.
Hey, we'll invade a little country there next to Russia, just so you don't have to look at what's actually going on.
Now, this is spreading.
Now, this is a great link, and of course, all of these links can be found in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com or curie.com.
This is, this is actually sourced from two Dutch newspapers as the President of the Dutch Central Bank, now Dvelling,
said what we've talked about before here on the Charlie, so this pertains to Europe pay attention.
He said, in the financial times, the Dutch financial times, you know, jailed dogblood.
Here's the quote, it's translated, of course.
The European Central Bank cannot continue forever to provide liquidity to banks with money market problems.
It says not Bill, like President of the Bank of the Netherlands, and board member of the ECB in an interview with a newspaper.
If we see that banks have become very dependent on central banks, then we must encourage them to tap other sources of funding.
This means that shareholders in extreme cases must come up with money.
So, just echoing that the system is not, it's broken, but not just at the fraughty and phony level.
It's broken all across the board, because these banks have been able to just go to their central banks and get money.
It awesome loans, cheap, and who's going to be paying for all of the bailouts?
You know it, luckily I pay taxes in the United States, and in the United Kingdom, part of Europe.
So, groovy.
I get two flaming hot poker, and this is the thing that really, this really blew me away.
Because, of course, I was watching to see what would happen when the markets opened yesterday, Monday.
And as predicted, financial stocks went soaring.
But what happened in London was outrageous, and you've got to think that there's definitely something very fishy with this.
The London Stock Exchange broke.
Okay, there was a computer error, which, or they call it, computer failure, left them unable to trade for seven hours.
Now, this can only be a couple of things. First of all, I think it sabotage right off the bat.
It had to be something where either the US markets wanted to, it could just be greed, which is very likely.
Hey, let's not let those fuckers do anything.
It could have been, perhaps, to stop the possibility of even settling swaps.
That's, you know, the story we just talked about.
Those swaps typically are done between New York and London.
So that could have been it.
It could have been just an honest computer mistake.
But somehow, you know, the timing of it, just after markets opened, it was for seven hours,
meaning the traders could only get in on some action at the very end of the trading day.
No, this sounded like this sounded to me like massive sabotage.
I hope someone has some more information on it, or some more info comes out.
Let's be on the look on that.
For any kind of news about what happened with the London Stock Exchange.
Because that just feels to me like not only was it was the whole financial industry,
shoving it up our butts, but they were also fucking with each other.
That's what I think.
Adam, Eric and Portland.
Ah, shit. Sorry, Eric, we already got you.
Now I was going to go to our, one of our financial savons from run to gold dot com.
Here we go.
Hi, Adam is the monetary scientist from run to gold dot com.
I'm Adam.
In DSE,
787, you mentioned some gold bars.
And it's good to see a little bit of the peer coming back.
Anyways, we should keep in mind that sound money is what protects against despotic
inroads by government.
And we really all need to run to the gold to reclaim a lot of our liberties.
And it's good to see the transformation in the show since the awakening has happened.
Well, I'll tell you, I've been coming very interested in gold ever since I found out that
it's actually quite hard to get your hands on it.
And you can get all kinds of pieces of paper that say that you own some gold,
but actually getting the gold in your hands.
Hey, very interesting.
Not that easy to do, which means other people are onto this strategy,
probably people with a lot more money than you and I.
Anyways, some really big things are happening in the financial markets.
And pretty much being taken over by the government.
They're going to be pumping in tons and new treasures to buy all that garbage dead,
and whatnot, which is just, oh, it's such a mess.
Anyways, a lot of those, as much as I hope they're financial assets and whatnot, are safe.
It's important to keep in mind that there's about 140 ounces of paper gold,
or everyone ounces of physical gold.
So it's getting a little difficult to actually get.
Anyway, let me just, let me just get that.
So this is the same fucking game those guys are playing.
So there's about 140 ounces of paper gold, which means, you know, just like for,
for every dollar, the bank holds, they can lend out.
Well, it used to be 10, but it's probably more like 30 dollars now.
Who knows what those limits really are.
But for every bar of gold that you buy in paper, 140 ounces,
there's only really one ounce to back it up.
That's what I mean.
But the real deal, you know, just want to get the pieces of paper,
if you're really into this strategy.
It's a good physical position and metal.
I talk about it a lot of my site, Renicle.com,
how to properly purchase your metal and whatnot.
Anyways, I've got a quick, I want to play from McElene,
speak with commentary about this.
We have an interesting market, Danny, I'm like,
wouldn't be obvious to really anyone on the street today.
But with all of our primary dealers, the market makers,
for the physical metals, we're looking at four to six week delayed deliveries
on almost every product.
And we're looking at something as generic as a cruiser and had its wholesale market premium.
Generally, on the wholesale market, I can invite that for half a percent
to 1 percent above the spot price.
It's now 4 percent.
It's moving to the extra 300 basis points higher.
And it's still on a four to six week delayed delivery.
What we're watching happening very curiously,
whereas this in the commodities realm,
you end up having a bifurcation where the paper asset world
that the paper side of the trade, well, that's futures or options,
there is a run towards liquidity.
But there's no liquidation in the physical markets.
In fact, there's more supply going off the market than the market.
You can really even handle.
There are no secondary market quotas.
And this is what I mean.
So it's getting really hardy at physical metal.
Anyway, it's great here.
We're keep it up, run to gold, and they work for us.
Hell yeah.
Keep reminding them.
They work for us, whether you got a pen, a microphone, a camera,
keep reminding them of that.
So there you go.
This is the game that's been played around us for decades,
that I never knew about it until the past,
really the past year that I started fighting you.
I guess you kind of know where you think about it.
And once you understand how truly evil some of these people are
that are just evil due to greed, by the way.
And that's the whole financial industries.
Evil due to greed.
They make their money up front when you give it to them.
That's what a great scam.
But then this whole business of being able to lend out
a multiple of what you actually have.
Do you see it?
Do you see how that's wrong?
It's like me, I can't even do it.
I don't have the right to print paper, but I guess you could print
IOUs for the same services over and over and over again.
It's like a lot of businesses.
It's almost like a fractional jet ownership in a way.
And here's how that works.
You have a couple of planes and you have many more passengers
and fractional owners than you have planes.
This is how net jet works.
And so the whole idea is to set up the right computer system
so that you can manage everyone's flying.
And it's about positioning.
But at the end of the day, it's like the sewage system.
You don't expect everybody to flush the toilet at the same time.
If everybody flush the toilet at the same time,
there would be shit flowing through the streets.
Now there's all kinds of models for that.
And that's well understood.
And this has been working for quite a while in the financial markets.
But at a certain point, you just flush one time too many.
And then the shit comes up anyway.
It was just too much of it.
Too much flush and going on.
Hi.
Well anyway.
We'll see where it all lands.
Right now we're sitting on the flaming poker.
And our destiny is literally at the hands of Paulson and Bernanke.
And let's see how well they do.
But remember those names because your grandkids certainly will.
Gives me some.
Put back.
Hi Adam.
It's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show.
We review Final Fantasy IV on the DS.
Also Tiger with PGA 209 on the Xbox 360.
You can win copies of the brand new wrestling game, TNA impact.
And then Judy Dench tells us about the new James Bond video game.
That's all it gamesweasel.com.
Alright.
Matt Cuddle.
Of course, a new sport out as well.
I think he's got some on that next week.
I'm not a gamer at all.
Don't own a game console.
But once in a while I see a trailer and like wow.
There's no wonder that shit's bigger than the movie industry.
That's just amazing.
What the stuff is being made.
Hey, let's talk about the MTV video musical words for a second.
I had a chance to see them last night because they were delayed by a day due to time zone differences
with the United States.
Of course, I spent seven and a half years at MTV in the formative years.
Mine and MTV's in the mid-80s to early 90s.
And a couple of things that I just wanted to mention first of all.
When you know, you have to understand that the VJs were never really invited to the video
musical words.
You know, I usually got in, but only with a ticket to sit in the crowd.
And I had to, you know, beg borrow steal to get a ticket for Patricia because you usually, of course,
you'd fly out with me if we were in Los Angeles.
And I would usually be out there because we'd do the countdown to the, you know, order the top 20 videos
to the countdown to the video musical words.
We do all kinds of location-based shows with some of the people who were performing.
You know, there was a lot of programming surrounding the video musical words.
Musical programming, by the way.
One thing that is just so interesting to me personally is that everyone's calling it the VMAs.
Because when we were at MTV, you were for, it was for Bowton.
You were not allowed to call it the VMAs.
I have no idea why, but you had to say video musical words.
And in the hallways at MTV, in Memos, we all call it the VMAs.
And even the artists were instructed, you may not call it the VMAs.
I think there might have been some kind of copyright thing.
There must have been some other something that was called maybe there was a,
that didn't want to confuse it with AMAs for the American musical words or whatever it was.
But it's just interesting to see that everyone's not calling it the VMAs,
which I thought was a stronger brand anyway.
Because it just kind of rolls off the tongue.
MTV's VMAs.
The VMAs.
It sounds good.
About the show itself, I have no idea how it did in the ratings.
Actually, I should have looked that up.
It just kind of happened because there was so much going on with the,
the Democratic National Convention, the Republican National Convention,
hurricanes, war.
You know, it's like, oh yeah, and then there's the VMAs.
First of all, it was directed by Joe De Mayo,
who was, I think Joe was an associate producer when I was at MTV.
So I was very proud to see his name on the credit list as the director.
By the way, an associate producer pretty much gets the scripts from the printer and gets coffee.
That's about what you do as an AP at MTV.
And so I have to say the whole vibe of the show was it looked great.
Now, the part of that I think was Joe because I know Joe's been around.
He really gets it.
He's got music and is coursing throughout his veins.
Also, of course, it was a perfect set.
It's being the paramount lot.
So they had, you know, all in fact, all kinds of great sets.
Well, that stuff's made for being lit well.
And the lighting was also, probably most cases pretty spectacular.
Some of the performances I didn't think were lit that, you know, really that well.
But what the hell was this show?
I mean, I really, it baffled me.
Patricia and I were just sitting there.
I mean, the best thing about this show had to be Russell Brand.
Russell Brand, who I know quite well from what it is work over here.
I think he really took that bull by the horns.
He went full steam ahead.
It was, first of all, his opening monologue where he started riffing on Bush.
And, well, praising Obama.
But it doesn't really matter what he, you know, who he stands for.
But basically what was kind of interesting is he was an English guy saying,
Please, on behalf of the rest of the world, get this Republican dickhead out.
Get someone in whose different.
And what was funny was the apathy of the crowd.
Now, maybe this is just the way it was shot.
But the apathy of the people sitting there in the audience who are mainly industry
Insiders, advertisers and their kids, you know, it's like those are the people that come
to these award shows.
And they were like, huh.
Uh, he's talking politics.
This is a music show.
He didn't be talking.
And the awards used to be at all, all awards shows used to be a perfect opportunity
for someone to grab the stage and say something about the state of the world.
So good on your Russell brand.
I mean, unfortunately, you lay a lot of trust in Obama.
But good on you for coming out and saying, hey, this is messed up.
You guys are messed up.
We wouldn't trust Bush with a pair of scissors.
That was pretty funny.
Uh, so I thought Russell was good.
Really, really good.
Not too pretentious, just wacky, rock and roll.
And he was the most dangerous thing of the show.
This show was once again completely safe.
Safe, safe, safe.
There was no danger whatsoever.
And really it was, you know, half the show was Disney Channel.
Everything from the Jonas Brothers to Britney Spears, Christina Aguilera.
That's all Disney kids to hip hop.
You know, and we're so noticeable.
How MTV has changed in a such a bling culture channel.
When you get kid rock, who, who pop in a kid rock has been touring around the world.
So he's got his band.
They're tied.
He's, you know, his vocals are special.
He was the best singer of the whole evening.
Now Leonuluus was actually pretty good too.
But in general, I mean, you know, he was a kick-and-tune.
The audience was dead.
Completely dead.
He should've been grabbing his crotch like a little will or whatever his name is.
I'm just, and that to me said it right there.
You know, rock don't write.
That's what we say in the music business.
It doesn't rock and roll, doesn't get ratings.
And so that's why MTV moved away from it completely.
That was pretty much the only rock performance that I can recall in the entire show.
And then you have that pretentious Christina Aguilera elevator thing, you know, whatever.
She's got to watch it because the Disney police will come and get her.
She's had her baby and now her hips are big.
And she's masking it.
Not that I give a shit.
But, you know, the Disney police, they're going to come for her if she doesn't slim down.
That's, that's a huge machine, man.
That machine put Britney Spears back on the map by giving her three awards, including best
video of the year.
What a scam.
That's the same people who brought to you by the same people who brought you the, the phony and
fraughty bailout.
Here's the MTV video music awards and Britney Spears completely mind controlled at this
point.
I don't know if she's on drugs or if they put a chip in her head.
But any normal person would have said, hey, you know, I've had a really challenging
year.
Thank you for standing by me, you know, all the people who are around me, who love me, who
really, you know, had my best interest at heart.
I mean, all of that stuff.
None of it.
The same rehears speech.
Thank you.
I want to first of all, I want to thank God and I want to thank my record company.
And I want to thank the fans.
Three times in a row, the exact same thing.
The girl is sad.
She's mind controlled.
And who the hell gives out these awards at MTV?
Where's that blue ribbon panel?
The disgusting.
And just because they still have this pretentious attitude that they're the shit when
it comes to music.
Bull.
Now, not to say that they didn't make the right choices from a business perspective to go
to, you know, a longer form programming.
Half hour shows my sweet 16 in my ride, cribs.
It all started with a remote control.
Remember that Ken Ober.
Harry War.
And, uh, uh, was, uh, was my guy's nice Steve, Steve Trickus, and the band.
That's when they started getting 1.0 ratings.
They don't get those anymore, by the way.
They do get some, like, tea or tequila.
That's a big show for them.
So, from a business standpoint, makes total sense.
But please, fuck off with your music awards.
That's bullshit.
I found this on the podcast.
I'd say the music now work, which I thought would be a proper po for this particular moment
in today's Charlie.
This is for all you people sick of hearing about Britney.
Oh, baby, baby.
My sisters have been babies.
And driving my Mercedes.
Oh, baby, baby.
What's it till when I awake?
Should I stay with Kimberly?
What was I doing?
And getting with Lindsay, the one.
Let's watch it have the best.
Why need some help?
Some medicine or a pill?
I don't want no time to feel.
Dr. Phil.
When I get no attention, I'll teach my mind.
It's such a sin for them to be none, to be live.
I'm not a girl.
I get a woman give me a sigh.
Help their baby one more time.
Oh, baby, baby.
I'm new.
I was losing my mind.
Mary Kevin Federaline.
Drinking and smoking.
Oh, my two favorite joys.
That's why I lost my two boys.
What was I doing?
Hard in and the rock scene.
Now I take a paparazzi.
I need some help.
Some medicine or a pill?
I call my friend.
A pair is hell too.
When I get no attention, I'll teach my spouse.
I even blew a Mickey Mouse.
And the Disney crew.
I'm not a girl.
I get a woman give me a sigh.
Help their baby one more time.
Oh, baby, baby.
I used to be so melodic.
Then I filmed Cayalex.
Oh, baby, baby.
I never used that to drugs.
Now I listen to bone thugs.
What was I doing?
Shopping and buying earrings.
Should've been at court hearings.
I need some help.
Some medicine or a pill?
Before I jump.
Of the winter's sale.
Winter's sale.
When I get no attention, I'll go to bed.
Do something like, share my hair, share my hair.
I'm not a girl.
I got a woman give me a sigh.
Help their baby one more time.
Little skank.
Oh, man.
Matt Sterman, the Britney Spears song.
Oh, boy.
Hey, you two can be like Britney just joined the MK Ultra program.
They're firing that up here in the United Kingdom.
I came across that you're going to love this.
Listen to what they've developed now.
Remember now, we, of course, are all supposed to be very, very afraid of the,
depending doom of the avian bird flu, the H5N1, which, of course,
you need the actual virus to create the anti virus.
And now, in the United Kingdom, they're coming out with the universal one hit
wonder.
One flu vaccine is good enough for life.
You never get sick again.
Uh-huh.
I'm at the Jenna Institute at the University of Oxford.
Now, researches here are working on vaccines.
Talk a bit about the way.
This is BBC.
BBC News links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com and at curie.com.
It's HIV, TB, malaria, and influenza.
Now, there's already a very good flu jab and millions of people in the UK around
the world have one each winter.
But in effect, that's part of the problem.
Okay.
So, flu jab, obviously, for those of you not familiar with the Queen's English,
is a hypodermic needle in your arm.
A flu jab sounds much kinder that way, doesn't it?
We need to have the jab every year because the strain of flu shifts a little bit.
But researches here are now trying to create a universal flu vaccine, which
wouldn't need to be repeated every year.
Now, with me is Professor Adrian Hill,
the director of the General Institute, Professor Hill,
how much of a breakthrough would it be to have a universal flu jab?
Well, it could change things dramatically in two ways.
Nice biking, by the way, BBC.
He sounds like shit.
It's funny.
You see this video, which is a part of the link I'll put in the show notes.
The guys sitting there pretending to look through a microscope and then the presenter
does a little walk about.
He walks from one side to the other side and he ends up.
Oh, and here he is, Professor Hill.
And the guy, go, oh, oh, you're filming?
You wanted to ask me something. Oh, yes.
Well, let me tell you about this mystical flu jab we have in the works for you.
My prettis.
Asking, we would be able to vaccinate people and have some confidence that if a new pandemic
comes along, even a pandemic of birth, which is what people are really worried about.
We would have an accident that would work again.
Okay, there you go.
So, what are you saying?
And what this article is setting us up for is,
we're going to get vaccinations against the bird flu.
This is the flu that has killed no more than 150 people worldwide.
And we don't actually have a sample of the virus.
And it's supposed to be, you know, the virus being the kind that goes from human to human,
not just bird to human.
If that's even true.
So it sounds like these guys have it in this lab where he's working.
He must, if he's going to create the universal jab.
That new strain.
Hopefully, but that's something we're missing today.
And in terms of convenience, as well, it would mean you wouldn't have to have your jab every
autumn.
Yeah, something flu is extraordinary in that it's one of the very few vaccines
where we have to keep giving it because the virus shifts and changes.
Over the years, so it's recommended you have a different flu vaccine every year.
We could get away with giving one vaccination and then it might last a life.
And in terms of how it works compared to normal vaccines, tell me about that.
And scientifically, that's what's really so important here.
For years, we have used vaccines that work through antibodies.
And most of the vaccines on the market today were designed to do exactly that,
like the existing flu vaccine.
What we're trying to do here is develop a fundamentally different sort of
vaccine that works through cellular immunity.
So we induce lots of white blood cells that will kill early infected cells.
And if that technology works for flu, it could be really important for other globally
diseases like malaria, HIV, like tuberculosis.
And it's even being used to try and treat cancer to those.
Yeah, okay.
So I don't believe one bit of this.
And I think we need to be very, very careful when the government says,
Oh, we've got this fantastic wonderful new system.
And it's just one little jab.
You won't feel a thing.
You know, there's nanotechnology that experimenting with and checking that into people.
You know, this could easily be some kind of RFID dust.
Yeah, you think I'm coming up with all kinds of wacky cookie stories, maybe.
But I think you need to be very awake.
And by the way, flu is not bad.
Get the flu.
Okay.
Just get it.
I had it took me 36 hours.
Patricia got it.
Christina got it.
You know, makes you stronger.
My in laws both 82.
They didn't get it.
Why?
Because their immune system is strong.
They've had probably every, every freaking flu flu known to man.
And they're from the old days.
Be very, very careful when the government suggests they want to inject you with something.
Choco heads, please be very, very careful.
Moving on.
This is just nice contrast to the.
The bailout.
The skiff is filling up with water.
To the phony and fraughty bailout.
This is not getting a lot of coverage.
Although I've seen it mentioned here and there.
But the US transportation secretary, Mary Peters,
that said, you know, we, we, hello.
While you guys are bailing out your buddies there for 200 billion,
just as a starting point, we are, we need $8 billion to fix our roads.
We need 2.7 billion immediately.
Immediately.
We need money desperately because they can't.
The projects are going to stop in the United States.
Bixing of roads, building of roads.
You know, this is, I think Ron Paul has said this a couple of times.
You know, we spend billions overseas to build bridges in countries we don't live in.
Meanwhile, our bridges and roads are falling down here at home.
Perfect example.
No one's talking about it.
Billions are needed.
Last night, Patricia and I were, um,
Blaine and bed watching the news.
Yeah, we still trying to go to bed at a reasonable hour around midnight, I'd say.
And I don't know if you caught this.
Um, it may be in the, in the papers in the U.S., it should be.
Uh, they sentenced three, uh, and I haven't sentenced the, um,
found three of the, I think was eight men conspiring, uh,
to, uh, blow up airplanes that you probably remember the story.
This is from, I think 2006, all of a sudden there was big news.
They'd, uh, foil this terrorist cell who were planning on blowing up airplanes, uh,
in trans Atlantic flight, mainly American airplanes.
Um, and they were going to do that with liquids.
This is the whole reason why you can't take more than, uh,
a hundred milliliters of anything on board an airplane because of these guys.
And here's what's really interesting.
They were indeed convicted of a three of them only, by the way,
not the ring leader and not all of them.
They had to let three of them go.
Three of these guys were convicted, uh, of conspiracy to murder.
This was the five-month trial they had plenty of time.
And what the jury would not convict them of, what they could not convict them of,
is that they intended to target transatlantic jets.
Uh, now these, you know, there's some circumstantial evidence.
I'll clear the guy, the guys, these guys were up to no good.
They were making, uh, bombs.
Well, they had the ingredients at least to make bombs.
I don't even know if they actually made anything that, uh,
wasn't in an, uh, explosive state.
They did have the ingredients.
Um, but, you know, the, you know, from the circumstances talking about that,
they want to blow up a power station.
And, uh, maybe an oil refinery or storage tank.
No proof whatsoever about transatlantic jets.
Can we please now go back to normalcy where we don't have to do this idiotic shit of, of,
of carrying on little, little, little plastic baggies of crap.
And can we just admit that that was bullshit and wrong?
That's the proof is here, right?
Even the sun, uh, links in the show notes.
Even the sun can't get around it.
So what was interesting last night is we're watching television.
The same day that they convict these guys.
The news media had amazing footage.
They had, you know, they're inside the house where these guys were.
They had undercover footage because the cops had been in and, uh,
the terrorist anti-terrorist brigade.
And they planted, uh, cameras and they had that footage.
And they had, uh, just amazing amounts of information, uh, beautiful scans.
High quality video that these guys had laying around.
And this was a full on beautifully edited piece.
I don't even think it was BBC.
I think it might have been, uh, Channel 4 ITV.
I have to go back and look.
But everyone had great footage, great pieces.
I'm thinking, how do you get access to all that material?
How do you get the access?
I think it's only because there's, it's an embarrassment.
You know, that all the rigmarole we're going through.
Yeah.
So these guys definitely were up to no good.
I'm glad they got them.
And they were onto the system working that regard.
But then this whole fucking security, the airport's being so idiotic.
Which you can't stop anyway.
It's just terrorizing the passengers.
You know, maybe they just needed to make a lot of noise.
Because, you know, this is almost like the Georgian thing.
Where Georgia snuck into south of city of first before Russia retaliated.
But the new story is pretty much Russia's the bad guy.
And here it is.
Oh, these are the guys that wanted to blow up the planes.
Um, they didn't, they can't actually prove they wanted to do that.
But they had, uh, they had, uh, fertilizer.
And, uh, hydrogen peroxide.
Anyway, it's, uh, it's a war for your mind, my friends.
That's what it is.
There are no secrets, only information you don't yet have.
Again, good on the guys for stopping, uh, for stopping these guys from continuing
whatever their plans were.
But if I have to hear one more time in a new story that they had,
links to Al Qaeda, it's just as bad as a bailout.
Oh, I've got some links.
There's a hyperlink, a space link, a telecommunications link.
And what kind of link is that?
What the hell is that all about?
Hi, this is PW Fencing.
Sometimes the truth is something you're just not ready to learn.
That's the subject of the latest digital flotsom.
Check it out at digitalflotsom.org.
Just don't bring the kids this time.
Uh, you'll understand when you get there.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
I love it when PW here's the call to action.
I told you I'd play any promo.
If you just throw it up on the drop drop.au slash daily source code.
Happy to do it.
Uh, different kind of music day in the Charlie.
It's kind of my, uh, 70s, uh, porn vibe that I'm in.
It's cast-handly easy to love on Charlie seven eight eight.
Yes, I do.
I'm so good.
So we say, so we say,
So we say,
You won't be there,
I'll miss this moment,
I'll string a test or two,
From fandom to life,
Is that a bug?
And then I'll head on my end,
Why does it seem too good to be true?
Because you also eat it,
So I'll be there,
I'll be there,
I can help me
If you can,
I'll be there,
Test Henley,
And it's from the pod state music network,
I gotta tell you,
I haven't heard the sex like that since 71.
Links in the show notes at that isourscope.com
and curie.com.
Of course, you can always check out
Music.edu.com for the complete offering of the pod state music network.
Completely free license to play in any audio or video independent production as long as you join up.
And you put a link in the show notes.
That's simple.
T-minus one told you at the top of the show,
Tomorrow, Big Bang Day is a BBC Radio 4 is calling it,
The Large Hadron Collider in Geneva.
Part of the big, certain project will start to fire up.
I don't know if they're,
I think they're not actually smashing any Adams starting tomorrow,
but they do crank it up in that thing.
Oh, I guess just keep spinning through October
when they really expect to do some massive stuff.
So the BBC is teeming up with Sern.
They've got the going to do a live webcast.
They've got Radio 4.
We'll be covering it all day, I guess.
Hey, this is interesting.
I just, I tell you,
I tell you, they have pictures of all the scientists.
Interesting, interesting.
Once this torch would.
Okay.
So that fires up tomorrow.
So we'll have to see, of course,
what that does.
I still find it very amazing.
So this thing is it's been years in the making.
$8 billion is what it's cost up to date.
At least that's the published figures.
And over 30 countries participating in the funding of it.
Now, I know a lot of countries, certainly Western Europe,
have strong Christian Democratic representation.
How can I never heard any debate about this?
Because this thing is supposedly what they're looking for
is the Higgs boson, which is some kind of particle that
or state, I guess a particle that existed milliseconds
or even less than milliseconds right after the big bang.
So this is, you know, creationist versus evolution.
And how can all these Christian Democrats have approved all the spending
without at least some debate about why they're spending money
and going after something they don't believe in?
That's the kind of stuff that just makes me so suspicious
of what this is really all about.
Anyway, we'll know tomorrow.
I'll get up right in early.
So I'll see any black holes.
I'll try and speak out or show before I think horrible happens.
Some other good alternative energy stuff.
And this is such a fantastic idea.
Unfortunately, the inventor of this, as it usually goes with,
with alternative energy solutions.
And this is something called wave partner.
Invented by Stefan Neistrum.
And it's a very ingenious idea.
And I encourage you to take a look at the links.
They actually, well, they don't have the whole system set out.
But apparently the guy was actually, I think it was killed in Ghana
where he was testing it out.
His idea is, you put a whole bunch of balloons in the ocean.
And this is a very simplistic version of it.
And the balloons are attached to a wire.
And the wire goes down to the bottom, where basically you have the kind of generator of unit.
And these balloons, of course, move with the motion of the ocean.
And with that, if you have the right gear, you, in a very simple way,
you can transform that into power generation.
And you know, he did it all a lot of the work.
And there were a lot of people very interested.
This is the way it always goes with alternative energy.
Because, you know, when you come up with such a great idea,
the first thing you got to forget is making money with it.
Because if you think you could make any money with it, you're definitely getting killed.
Then if you can actually promote it and market it.
So it catches on or someone builds it or it's easy enough for people to build themselves.
Yeah, you'll get threatened by industry.
And these are the thugs.
The same guys with that Ponzi scheme called Federal Reserve Banking.
But I did love this next idea.
And this is presuming that the carbon dioxide really is an issue.
Cloud seeding ships could combat climate change.
And this is a pretty interesting idea.
The National Center for Atmospheric Research and Boulder.
I've come up with this idea of spraying salt water into the air from unmanned sailing ships on the Atlantic.
And that that would essentially, you know, they've got their calculations.
And it would only take like a couple thousand, I think.
It didn't seem like the hand to have.
Yeah, 1500 ships.
And by having these 1500 ships, spouting salt water, which is pretty beautiful in the ocean, into the air,
which would cost about each one to two million pounds.
So between two and four million dollars, they could completely reverse the carbon emissions issue.
Which by itself is interesting if that's all it takes.
How big is this issue really?
But another thing this coolest is the sales that they have on these unmanned ships.
Just take a look at this thing.
It's kind of like futuristic sci-fi towers.
But as a sailing exercise, it looked interesting.
I wouldn't mind having a sailing ship without the sheets and a rope with one of these, you know, sticks on it.
It looks like it might kind of work differently and more cool.
But interesting from psychics world, oh, some sorry, psychics.
Physicsworld.com.
And then finally for today, just trying to give you a nice overview of the news, what's really taking place.
Because most people, of course, are paying attention to the news about Sarah Palin.
And this is the most audacious act I've ever seen in my life.
This is from the Financial Times, Georgia.
Our buddy, soccer is really the Ty Eaton Terrent from Georgia.
It's taking Russia to court.
So they're taking Russia to court for attacking them.
So the things that are interesting about this, first of all, they're taking them to the world court.
I mean, do you see Starfleet command?
Do you see how this now actually fits together?
I mean, this is, that's just going to be a joke.
So who are these guys?
And it's in the Hague, of course, in the Netherlands.
Pussy ass country when it comes to this kind of stuff.
Oh, yeah, I just bring them over here.
No one will pay attention to this little dinky ass pimple of a country.
Oh, just so we get everyone in black robes and white ties.
And we got ourselves a world court.
But the audacity of Russia to do, if they have a real hearing, then of course, what should come out is,
well, actually it was Georgia who attacked South the city of first and then Russia retaliated.
If that comes out of this, I'll say, all right, World Court, you've done something good.
But do you really think that's going to happen?
And what is the point?
What is the point?
One thing I know for sure, Putin has given NATO 21 days.
This is probably only about 16 of those left.
21 days to get out of the,
as the Caspian Sea, where they are, the Black Sea, to get out.
Because, of course, we've gotten, you know, our motto there at this point.
And all these things come in together.
So that'll be around the end of September.
The US closes its books around the end of September.
We got a couple weeks of very interesting financial markets.
Who knows what's going to happen with the US election?
But know that we are awake.
You're listening to this show.
You're awake.
We're getting more information.
We're sharing it.
We've got great tools for that.
It's drop.io slash daily source code.
Before I forget, it's a bookmarklet.
You can use, which is really handy.
You just drag that into your browser bar and then any page you're on.
If you want to submit that into the drop, you just click on that bookmark.
It'll give you a little, you know, the, it'll fill out the URL and the name of the page.
You can even add in some comments.
It's fantastic.
Please use that upload stuff.
And find some good pod safe stuff to upload there.
A little tired of all the licensed music going up, which I keep having to figure out and remove whatever possible.
But anyway, we are awake and we're making more and more people awake.
Tell them to listen to this show.
Tell them to listen to no agenda.
There's plenty other places where you can actually find out what's going on in the world.
You know, the real news.
Please tell people to turn off the televisions.
It's really not helping.
It's really, that really pulls the wool over your eyes even further.
So with that, we have one more track to play.
Yet again, something for my fishing expedition on the pod safe music network.
I just like the dynamics of the piano.
Don't Oxford.
He's my baby.
Somebody's got to tell me.
Where my baby lays his head.
Because it's the nas and weak spots for sure.
Since he's been sleeping in my bed.
He's got to know I got to know I got to know.
He's got to know.
If he's still in love with me.
I was in his with another woman.
And he's closing round the wrong tree.
He's my baby.
I love that man.
Oh, I got to call him on the telephone.
He's my baby.
Why?
I can't wait.
Now I moved over the mountain.
Across the river to the sea.
Just to be closer to my baby.
He moved his heart away from me.
I remember like it was yesterday.
He said that he loved me.
And now my heart is aching.
There's pain where his love used to be.
He's my baby.
Oh, I love that man.
Lord, he knows how to make my body full.
He's my baby.
Why?
I feel full.
If you see my baby.
Walk in round town on the arms of another girl.
Or you tell him how he hurt me.
And he destroyed my whole wide world.
He's my baby.
Oh, I love that man of mine.
Oh, I got to call him.
He knows how to make my body full.
He's my baby.
Why?
I feel so lonely.
He's my baby.
Oh, I love that man of mine.
Lord, I got to call him.
He's my baby.
Why?
I feel so lonely.
Sing it again.
Don't Oxford.
He's my baby.
So I just want to remind you, you really are free and you are.
All that captivism that's all in your mind is whatever the mind control is that they're sending to you.
So all you want is a white pick of fence and Britney Spears.
You don't need to buy the crap.
Absolutely.
Look out for the crap they're trying to sell you.
Go buy some fresh fruits and vegetables, will you?
And please enjoy your freedom because you really, really, really can.
And since the human residents of the earth is rising with fantastic rate, I just like to say,
keep the vibe alive and whatever you do live your life with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.