Hey, I'm the first one to say it's a great country, but it's a strange culture.
We've got a strange culture, this has got to be the only country in the world that could
ever come up with a disease like Bolivia.
Gotta be the only country in the world where some people have no food at all and other people
eat a nourishing meal and chew it up intentionally.
This is the country when tobacco kills 400,000 people a year so they ban artificial
sweeteners because a rat died.
This is a place where guns store owners are given a list of stolen credit cards, but not
a list of criminals and maniacs.
Now they're thinking about banning tyguns and they're going to keep the fucking real one.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped by us, to the next generation radio contenting my
years.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Come closer, I am the sky.
Come closer.
Hey, little rat, here's my home tonight.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
So hey, I'm a fighter ...
Digus, Molly, you are my hero!
Like you asshole, like you asshole, like you asshole, gayaire!
Fuck ya, oh ya!
Eh rider, don't look!
Electronic ass!
Digus, Molly mound shit after us, full bar friday!
Daily source code episode 7-7-2...
Hey everybody, how are you doin?'
How are you doing? This is the show that's been five days in the making. It has been a week
and you know right now it's Friday evening. It is quarter to nine and the first top opportunity
I've had has been going non-stop and you know I could even see some people getting worried
what's going on people calling me you are right man what's happening so first of all apologies and
really you know Twitter has become so unreliable that I don't even post updates or anything to it anymore
and the blog well yeah what am I going to say show coming I tried that at the beginning of the week
and I shouldn't do that because it was not coming it's not coming now the really wasn't much to
report on because there was a lot of family stuff I'd take care of on the continent in the Netherlands so
I went over oh was it Monday yeah Monday morning I flew over a beautiful flight by the way
had about 25 not tailwind oh yeah oh yeah doing 170 not so that was nice nice and fast
and I went up to flight level five five haven't been there in a while because of course the
the wind's got even stronger the higher you get and it was just oh it was beautiful and you know
me right I like to smoke a nice home home rolled tobacco at altitude there and use my
ass trays everything is on autopied at listening to the BBC World Service fantastic
anyway so I had some family stuff to do as I said it took up a couple days
and then I flew back on what was it uh oh when's day evening I think yeah and then I had meetings
in town this morning our yesterday morning and this morning and London how man the traffic it's
just gotten it's gotten so horrible I've progressively seen this traffic just go from bad to worse
even though the introduced the so-called congestion charge which was supposed to you know make it a
lot less congested well quite the opposite seems to be happening of course there's still lots of
construction going on in London they're renewing all of the sewer pipes the drainage
because they're all 100 years old that's just maintenance they should have performed 50 years ago
probably but whatever reason didn't it's just been a mess and then Nelson Nelson Mandela's in town
celebrating his 90th birthday so there's concerts which of course is great because if you're in town
oh man the city is fantastic as long as you don't have to go anywhere unless you can get there by foot
and so to be two hours to get home I took the train in this morning but you know you're coming
cross-tron across town from east from shortage where the HQ is back to the west side then out of
the city it took me two hours two freaking hours luckily I could utilize some of that time
on conference calls with San Francisco add to that of course I'm still doing this morning radio
show thing on aeroclassic rock but man the experiment is really gonna pay off for us today because
today I have a special for you and that is an interview I did this morning with commissioner
a European commissioner so you know you kind of have the the European Parliament where the laws are made
I guess with the ministers council so they they make the laws but these these commissioners
in the European commission they're like starfleet command okay they can they can reject stuff they
can't really they don't make the laws but there's only 27 of them of course for the
one free to the 27 member states of the United States of Europe as I'm going to start calling
it from now on one of them of course is Naley Cruz she's the the competition commissioner
and she's the one that find Microsoft you know two billion euros or whatever the hell the amount was
that something in the billion billion of something is a lot so that's the kind of power
and what this Vivian Redding has been working on she's trying to harmonize all of these
roaming rates now of course in the states we used to have this where you know if you went from one
state to the other or so often even one town to the next before these networks really rolled out
you'd have to pay extra roaming charges extra fees because these networks would then have to do
some kind of settlement amongst them and it turned out you know it really became a big scam
um and a lot of money was made on that so that of course still happens in Europe even though
you can have vote of phone in the UK and then you go to Germany and you get and you go by the way
you don't have to show your passport anymore to get from one country to the other but then you
arrive in Germany and all of a sudden you know if if someone calls you it's going to cost you 20
cents per minute if you call someone else it was costing up to like a full euro so you have a
buck a minute not to mention sending text messages half a euro or internet data 15 euros per megabyte
I mean just outrageous pricing even though it's the same company so she's been working on
fixing this and the calling price is she brought down by like 70% on roaming charges by enforcing
law and she said okay you guys really need to fix this shit and she's like she's no joke man
she's she's the she's the real deal um she said if you guys don't fix this by July 1st
and you don't bring these rates down significantly I'm going to propose law and look at what happened
last time so anyway um I specifically got a recording of the interview and it's an exclusive
here on the Charlie even though of course it has been broadcast in the Netherlands actually I got a
little bit of the air check so here's some just like a 15 minutes of the of me talking in Dutch
for those of you who care but of course the the roughest thing for me personally this week was
you know it's some other stuff that's been going on it's the passing of George Carlin which really
I I found out about this early in the morning and when I read the the email started coming and I was like
it really shocked me and and I have to say I I was really upset for a full day and like you know
just this guy this his awesome take on the on life and how he's able to turn that into words
uh it's just always amazed me it's been a huge inspiration just tremendous and uh I will really
really miss him I know a lot of Americans will well miss laughing about ourselves uh with him as the
catalyst so even though we got some cool music lined up for you today I just I have to play
some George Carlin so here's four minutes of George Carlin on voting I believe this is from his
his last special which was somewhere around January 2008 his last HBO special so indeed one of his
last words check it out George Carlin notice I don't complain about politicians everybody
can planes about politicians everybody says they suck yeah well where do people think these
politicians come from they don't fall out of the sky they don't pass through a membrane from another
reality they come from American parents and American families American homes, American schools,
American churches, American businesses and American universities and they're elected by American
citizens this is the best we can do folks this is what we have to offer it's what our system
produces Garbage in Garbage out if you have selfish ignorant citizens if you have selfish ignorant
citizens you're gonna get selfish ignorant leaders the term limits they're gonna be any good
you're just gonna wind up with a brand new bunch of selfish ignorant Americans so maybe maybe
maybe it's not the politicians who suck maybe something else sucks around here like the public
yeah the public sucks there's a nice campaign slogan for somebody the public sucks
fuck hole fuck hole because if it's really just the fault of these politicians then we're
all the other bright people of conscience we're all the bright honest intelligent Americans ready
to step in the same nation lead the way we don't have people like that this country everybody's
at the mall scratching his ass picking his nose taking his credit card out of his family pack
and buying a pair of sneakers with lights in them so I have solved this little political dilemma
for myself in a very simple way election day I stay home I don't vote fuck them fuck I don't vote
two reasons two reasons I don't vote first of all it's meaningless this country was bought
and sold and paid for a long time ago they shipped a shuffle around every four years
doesn't need a fucking thing I've certainly I don't vote because I believe if you vote you
have no right to complain people like to twist that around I know they say they say well
if you don't vote you have no right to complain but where's the logic in there if you vote
and you elect just honest incompetent people and they get into office and screw everything up
what you are responsible for what they have done you caused the problem you voted them in you
have no right to complain I on the other hand who did not vote who did not vote
who in fact did not even leave the house on election day and then no way responsible for
what these people have done it they've ever right to complain as loud as I want about the mess you
created that I had nothing to do with so I know that a little later on this year you're going to
have another one of those really swell presidential elections that you like so much you'll enjoy yourselves
it'll be a lot of fun I'm sure as soon as the election is over your country will improve immediately
as for me I'll be home on that day doing essentially the same thing as you the only difference is
when I get finished masturbating I'm going to have a little something to show for it folks
thank you very much
there are the great George Carlin his very last words on the public stage ever
I had a bit of a map from games weasel on this week's show we've got a review of Metal Gear Solid 4
and you can bag yourself a copy as well I've got a review of Final Fantasy 7 crisis core for the PSP
I want to chat for some very many spandex when we have a look at the TNA impact game
that's all the gamesweasel.com
someone you've never heard of don't cry about it
there's no use about it
everybody knows it's only ones and us that's the way it goes
today everyone repeats so you can just delete it's just another game just like yesterday
turn off the sound when the hate starts going around there's always someone
loves to say they're the right ones anyway they're the comments on
just turn off everybody knows only ones and us that's the way it goes
today everyone repeats so you can just delete it's just another game just like yesterday
oh yeah don't cry about there's no use
about everybody knows it's only ones and us that's the way it goes
today everyone repeats so you can just delete it's just another game
just like yesterday everybody knows it's only ones and us
it's been a while with finally new gemsmith on the show and on the pot say music
it's one's and us it's another I love it just admit that I love you
I'm so happy you stuck myself it's like yesterday
beautiful you know do you know Jeff how long we know each other man like two
three years and now he's got the ringtone business and it just met a working musician
and sticking it out in the new media and being successful it makes me feel so happy and also
proud just proud of what Jeff has accomplished check them out of the jefsmith.com and of course
up at a link in the show notes at dailysourceco.com yeah I may not have the same level of energy
that I normally have but man I'm so full barred so incredibly tired let's change topics here
for a second this is due to a conversation topic that Charlie Delta Lima started of course
you know Charlie Delta Lima's Charles the drunkard Londoner he was talking about touching his
I think it was his his his iPod when it was plugged in just touching the metal back and getting
this electric kind of charge like feel and I said I had had exactly the same thing on Patricia's
Mac is that a MacBook or power book I think it's a MacBook an old version MacBook which he
uses downstairs in the kitchen I had the exact same sensation and boy I'll tell you I got
comments just streaming in from everywhere. Adam it's Michael calling from Chicago Eleanor in the
U.S. responding to dailysourceco 770 Drunken Charlie I forget his code words Charlie Delta
Charlie Delta Lima you got it. Talking about the strange sensation on his iphone
I was just in London last week I was there for two weeks visiting lady friend
I had to have a MacBook pro brought it with me and I was recording a podcast while I was there
not even and I got some kind of weird harm while I was recording it but the point being that
I would graze my hand over the MacBook pro over the area just above the touch pad and I soaked
that my blation I thought maybe it was because I didn't have a
I had around the power converter but I was just running it it wasn't grounded I thought maybe
you know maybe it's because it's not grounded Adam and you know before you go any further
that man you know this is interesting because I came back from Holland I which is also
which also uses 220 volts so they have a different plug but it's the same voltage and I believe
the same cycles which would be 50 cycles per second versus 60 cycles in the U.S. there is a difference
there and I plugged my MacBook pro power adapter in and I literally heard a pop and it got warm
because it was in my hands and so you know I immediately unplugged it but it basically blew up
and I'm wondering if there's something related to these these these power book adapters or the
or the power supplies and I guess not because that would have nothing to do with Charlie Delta
Lima's iPod charger but anyway I had to do that too had to go to the Frick and Apple store to get
a new one oh yeah they England it's high voltage high voltage high voltage high voltage
I think it did be that was what it was
all right now I get the point
by the way so I did go to the max store and picked up a couple of things of course what I was there
also picked up an ITV which is kind of cool plugs into USB port and you get digital television
so that's pretty cool up here in the attic and what else I picked up a compact flash card reader
because I want to update the map so my my navigational equipment for the Delta Sierra
and what else I picked up there was something else I was going to tell you about oh
so by the way a lot of Americans work it in the in the Apple and the London Apple store
and so the guy who helped me you know he said he's American and I think they're there because they
train the staff and maybe the lot of the or management or whatever I mean the whole store is
it beautifully efficient and so I'm talking to the guy I said hey any chance that I could
sign up and pre-register for the 3G iPhone on July 11th and here's the guy's response
it's absolutely not I'm like okay yeah I figured as much you said but you know you just
stand in line because it could be really cool I said well what's the cool about standing in line you know
it's like you know I said you know it's it's pressed for you guys which is great I understand but
you know I don't want to stand in line she said well you never know who you're going to meet
on line it was kind of like patronizing which it it irks me a little bit you know you could meet
El McPherson she was in line last time like you know dude I'll see you on July 12 okay
I don't know what it was it was just a little bit it just irks me a little bit anyway back to
this this electricity problem here's another call Adam it's Chris lightning here like the
I was I'm calling about the problem that we're not not with you the problem more or less
some say some of these seem to get whenever you touch an aluminium MacBook or MacBook Pro or
a power book or the back of the iPhone the child is on command and there was referring to the other
day of yesterday um the reason why get that sensation is it's static electricity it's the fact
the the MacBooks the iPhone the power book is plugged into a power source and basically is then
vibrating along in your own body electricity then vibrates on that if it's like with those um
all those those plasma balls you know that the ones that generate do that just keep yeah I know
you you stick your hand on the on the glass and a little bit of ash there you stick your hand on the
glass and then the blue flame comes towards your fingers I know what you're talking about but you
hand on your hands stand up until an hour touches you it's all through a static so stupid
you're just running through the body you know we'll see what the old all through the
body but how come I have that only with the I mean with iPod and is it because of the metal
the aluminium is that what it is that's interesting so when you brush it you get a vibrating feeling
it's just there to stay moving between you um because I'm going through you down to the granule earth
in the artist's case just moving along you natural age you can get it with different metal objects as
well um something about their example back out how about a steely down sorry real obscure reference
for the older a chuckle head done amongst us yeah okay yeah all right Chris thanks one more of those
hello and go man here so run the being rude and just let's talk to you on my iPhone 2G
I don't know if I'm going to look at my iPhone or iPod touch you're not going to look at the
device you're going to look at the first speakers and it's on an Apple product I'm looking
to feel a buzz on them it's on a word is it's actually leakage in the power supply okay
here's another theory leakage in the power supply scene now we're back to the power adapters
in the mains 50 hertz 50 cycle mains on it please not and there was an Apple shop here the day
looking for MacBook when Apple MacBook started with with those arrogant fuckers there I know what you're
talking about like shell on it uh oh there's a MacBook Air actually and I've got the
the cell phone I felt it was actually the same feeling on it there was a Mac book flow right
and it's also it and that didn't have that like feeling on it and the Macbook Air and the Macbook
Pro have got these other things covering like that and like that and I've done a mini covering
yeah you know I think it's under leaky counselors the only thing that you're trying to
come to my day use they they're going to leak it you know I think it's for now it remains a
mystery is it's static electricity is it leakage and you're feeling 50 cycles hmm what is it one
things for sure it's all made in China um I'm laughing at myself here so the next call I have
lined up to really fits in with all this extremely extremely important talk about uh iPods
I had them this is Justin from back and it was podcast.com and you've been talking about lately
why people won't stand up for their liberties being stripped away well I figured out and it's like this
where's this okay all that was required of them was a primitive patriotism which could
be appealed to whenever it was necessary to make them accept longer working hours or start a
ration and even when they became discontented as they sometimes did they're discontent let's know
where because being without general ideas they can only focus on petty specific grievances
after my Georgia well 1984 all right man they were correct
say about crosses some of those that work for us is what I say about crosses some of those that
work for us is draw the same that for us it oh
now you do what they told you okay now you do what they told your молод
Now you do what they told you
Now you spell it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, I got turned on to that just recently.
I had wasn't really in the rage against the machine, but this really really does it for me.
Crikey.
All right.
Yeah, so talking about, I won't do what you told me and how they should be working for us.
Let's see how one of the most powerful political bodies in Europe is working on creating
a better Europe for its citizens, and this is the whole reason why I reached out to European
Commissioner, Vivian Redding, who is Commissioner on behalf of Luxembourg.
And she is the Commissioner of the Information Society and Media.
And so, of course, she understands the importance of ubiquitous internet and, you know,
traveling from a country to country here is like traveling from state to state in the U.S.
Hence, of course, the United States of Europe.
But the roaming fees are still in place.
And of course, you know, the telephone providers are all saying, well, you know, we
have to recoup our investment.
Well, yeah, in fact, as she's going to use a word, I'll tell you right now, because
when she used the word, I actually had to look it up while I was talking to her.
And the word is a necronism.
And a necronism, I'm just bringing up the dictionary.com page right here, is something
or someone that is not in its correct historical or chronological time.
So essentially, something that is really, really old-fashioned, that's what that means.
So I interviewed Vivian Rating this morning, you know, this is the thing that, on one
hand, really pisses me off, because, you know, if I'd called up High Madam Curry, I've
got a show, I've got a podcast or whatever.
And I said, I like you to like to interview, because, of course, you don't get to talk
to a Madam Commissioner immediately.
Oh, no.
No, you gotta go through a whole bunch of people.
Now, of course, on this radio show that I'm doing the morning, I have a producer and
she's damn good.
But still, the fact that it's live radio, national, that's why these politicians jump
on it.
I mean, they're calling me.
They're like, hey, man, I got something to talk about.
It's amazing how they're clamoring any way to get their message through to the people.
And I want to first main basis with a lot of these people now.
It's very, very interesting to me.
So now, of course, I'm taking all this knowledge, all the stuff that I've learned
together with you guys.
And I'm applying that, these conversations and listening and thinking about things.
I'm applying it to this, you know, very small country with its own language that really
doesn't go much beyond the borders, except somebody in South Africa may kind of understand
it.
So now it's time to start reversing that process.
So now finally, I have something that's in English and believe me, I'm going to be talking
to a lot more of these people at Starfleet, the Starfleet Command of Europe.
And go ahead, look it up.
I'll put a link in the show notes.
You'll see, this is no joke.
I mean, these commissioners, they got a huge amount of poll and power.
And they're out to prove something.
They're out to prove that what they're doing is good for Europe and good for the individual
member states in Europe.
So we're going to get a little bit of an education from Madam Reading and some specific
information on how she's approaching the situation and how we're going to benefit as consumers.
Now particularly these days, what oil just jumped above 140 bucks.
So that's a whole nother story.
By the way, I might want to point out that Russia is turning out to be the new Saudi Arabia.
These guys, you know, they're building gas prom.
It's going to be a company that will be worth a trillion dollars.
And the Russian CEO of gas prom said, well, look for $250 a barrel oil next year.
So anyway, amidst all of that crap, if you can save 50 bucks a month on your cellular
bill, or how about, you don't actually be able to work efficiently and use your internet
connection, your mobile internet connection, or you might say, Java card into your laptop,
to be able to use that cost effectively, will greatly enhance productivity, will greatly
benefit the economy and directly impact your pocket by not costing an arm in a leg.
So it's like a super win win, of course, the evil guys in this equation are the phone
companies.
But we have the kind of guy like a doopily thing going on.
So this is kind of in their business model to be a little bit evil.
But that's okay.
It's just that their time is up.
The gig is up.
It's 2008.
Now it's time to change.
Okay.
So I'm going to play this with a little, it's about eight minutes.
So if you get totally bored, which I don't think you will, because this is them working
for us in its finest form.
And remember, I'm, I'm pro European, I, you know, not dig in the Lisbon Treaty at
all.
So, yeah, I'm just moving beyond that and I'm going into, okay, how does this thing work?
Does it actually work?
Will the United States of Europe function?
Will it benefit us?
Will it benefit member states in smaller countries?
Well, apparently if you've got a microphone on a national radio show, yes.
But of course, I'm spreading that foreign wide now and a little secret, much further
and wider than the audience of the radio show into the, into the chucklehead community.
Okay.
So a little bit of the radio show is I'm just coming out of a record and then straight
into the interview.
It's all live.
No, it's enjoy the show.
Here we go.
Oh, it didn't fire.
It went better this morning.
Did you do it on the hall of team London calling your heart the clash and it's close
to you in the dance?
Well, I'm going to give you a little bit of pressure on what I've done, leave codes and
Starfleet command, no, but proud to for more from it, Vivian Redding, says Commissioner
for Information Society and Media, Madam Commissioner, good morning.
Good morning.
I appreciate you joining us this morning on the program and of course, yeah.
Oh, yeah, and I want to thank you for your service to the people of Europe in particular
with our current economic issues with increased fuel and food pricing, your initiatives
certainly with pricing for the international calling and SMS text messaging and data is highly
appreciated.
Thank you very much.
But you see the European politicians are there for the better of this continent and of
its citizens.
But it's very important to take in hand the pricing where pricing is projected to the
negative side of sea citizens.
And I could not agree with you more and this is also, this is actually it's quite new for
us to see something affect the citizens of the European member states so directly and with
this initiative coming from Europe.
So it's very important to, particularly in these days, as we look at issues surrounding the
Lisbon Treaty and what this Brussels actually mean to all of us in smaller countries around
Europe.
If I could ask you, what type of power do you actually have Madam Commissioner as a commissioner
in our European system to actually force companies like the mobile operators to lower their pricing?
Well, the European Commission, you know, has power of proposing regulation and laws.
The law makers are the council of ministers and the European Parliament.
So they need to agree on every proposal I do.
That means the commission proposes the disposition on this and the decision on this is done
by the elected law makers.
Okay, but clearly there is a lot of power and I think in this case it's a good thing
if we look at your colleague and of course, Dutch citizen Commissioner Naly Krus who
has done an amazing job of finding Microsoft billions of euros.
Could it come to that, could we actually force or see such a huge measure of force used
against the mobile operators if they don't comply with the wishes of, well, with your
wishes and eventually laws will be put into place to regulate them?
That has already happened.
You see, when we tackled the voice roaming costs, which were a poor and high and we
made European regulations and that is applicable directly in each member state.
So the operators had to comply with this new rules and the costs for roaming on voice
went down by 70%.
And for which we're very appreciative and actually I think the word roaming is almost
an insult in these days with the European Union because we don't need to show our
passports with movement between countries.
Shouldn't we even abolish the entire concept of roaming, certainly considering many of
these operators have networks in multiple countries and are actually running over their own
networks.
It seems to be like it's almost well, it seems very unfair towards the consumer and
maybe even anti-competitive.
It isn't an optimism actually, you are absolutely right and that's why we were fighting
it because you see we see a continent where people and I can move freely and here people
are punished when they cross the border, that is not fair and that is not the European
one but we have to go step by step because we still do have our national telecom markets.
The reforms which we put in place is to eliminate the barriers between these markets
and make it possible that more and more of a pan European players come into force because
that is also a question of surviving in a globalized world.
You see we cannot continue to do bits and pieces in Europe.
We have to unite forces also for our operators in order to be strong enough to sustain
the competition from operators, from outside Europe.
I could not agree with you more in particular for the generation which is now growing
up and is now crossing the borders who are very used to low-cost internet access, which
I think is probably even more important than the SMS pricing for the future.
Some of the some pricing across the borders, even 15 euros per megabyte of data received
which is multiple times more valuable than the price of gold.
It's absolutely, I would call it a scam madam commissioner would you agree?
And it has no relation to the real cost of the operators.
You see we do not want to punish operators that would be completely out of reason.
We want to have strong operators who can get in their cost and can get in a remineration
for the service they make.
But if this is going 100, 150, 500 percent over and above a normal commercial relation,
that it is not acceptable anymore.
And that is why we have asked from the operators and put a deadline for the first
of July to bring down their cost for SMS and for data roaming, bring them down to normal.
I wait until the first of July and see if things happen here, if things don't happen
here and I have announced that already very clearly, I will make the same proposal I have made
for voice roaming, that means I will propose a regulation in order to bring those prices down to normal.
I cannot tell you how much I love hearing a strong woman say words like that is very exciting to
be.
I want to tell you a quick report from the member state of the Netherlands, our Secretary
of State of Economic Affairs, Fronka Hameskettik, has really been doing good job, he's tried
to communicate to the local telecom operators here, and of course you probably are aware
that we had the highest roaming charges of all the member states that has been reduced
in just the last week.
In fact, however, indeed, if I look at your statement and you were very clear and I'll just
repeat it briefly, if the situation stays unchanged until the first of July you will see
from today's council that I will not be the only one to believe that our regulatory
intervention won't be necessary once again, so I'd love the CEOs of all mobile operators
do your job, respond to consumer concerns and lower your prices, you know exactly where
you have to go.
Those are very strong words, Madam Commissioner, at this moment not a single operator in the
member state of the Netherlands is even at the 28-year-old sense you're speaking of that has
to be lower, not a single one, they made a big deal about going from 50-year-old sense
down to 33 or 29, I have a very little hope that they will comply by your July 1st
deadline.
Well, let's wait and see, there might be a miracle, you never know.
Like Holland will win the European Cup, that would be a miracle.
Well, you see, I have said the first of July and I'm going to wait until the first
of July, because I have been very much criticised by the operators, they say, we
can get the market in a equilibrium, we do not need processors to do that.
So I told them in February, okay, I trust you, you were bringing the market in a equilibrium
until the first of July, but if you don't do it, then unfortunately I have to come in.
So I give them a chance until the third of July, but that's the beginning of the next
week.
Madam Commissioner, hopefully we couldn't speak with you again after the first of July after
you have a major assessment, we would love to contact you again and find out with the next
episode.
Of course, we're also hopeful and we're all positive here, but we do have hardouts,
so that would be possible, that would be fantastic.
Thank you, and we will certainly come back to this during the course of July.
Fantastic.
Vivian Reading Commissioner for Information Society in Media.
Thank you very much for your time this morning and again, thank you for your service
to Europe.
Good day.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
You're on her, please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out, let's don't give a nod.
To the harnessed work and lawyers, jerseys and tigers, man, yeah, it's jersey time.
Oh, how's it going, Adam?
It's jersey time.
Give the fish on musicologist of the shot shot shot.
So, this week in my football Friday segment, I wanted to give the listeners a little backstage
pass.
I want to give them a little bit of behind the scenes on how this football Friday thing
has been going down for a long time.
You see, I've been giving you some choices every week, I give you some choices of bands
that you might like for the football Friday segment.
And then you choose which band you think is appropriate for the show that you're doing
that week.
Not this week.
Not this week at all, because this week on football Friday, I've only got one band
free to play.
The band, of course, is from New Jersey.
That goes without saying the pot saved music capital, New Jersey.
But you got to check these guys out because they are going to officially break summer
2008.
They're going to officially start it all off.
The band's name is Woodfish.
They completely, completely rocked at the opportunity to talk to them.
They're great guys.
And I think you're just going to absolutely dig this.
Well, choices this week, big band.
You're going to like this.
It's band diddly.
By the band Woodfish, check it.
You know it.
You're going to love it.
What's all this?
Stop it, think about it.
Yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
But I can't make a foul
That's what you're doing
I wanna break you down
With the sun we know it
That's all the way
That I'll be as you can't hear
But what I'm all alone
I'm feeling good there
Who would say that I'm with you
It's all that I'm all to do
That I'll be as you can't hear
I'm just music
Surgy shirt was he tied, once again an excellent selection
Particularly for this full bar Friday
Oh man, I see that once again put too many eggs in my basket, have a whole new clear energy
thread that I want to share with you.
I'll say that for Monday, because Monday will be kind of back to normal or some semblance
of normal.
Let me see, you know what, I always find one of these comes in, it's a good buddy or a European
correspondent.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, so next week France is taking over the ship of European
Union.
Yes, long commands under the dwarf, Thakuzzi, you know, by the way, I think Thakuzzi has
got it together, man.
He got his model wife just in time for the presidency, yeah, the man, he's a player.
With married six Italian model Karabun, he will be there for even more, opening his
gobb.
And in unrelated story, you have just lifted sanctions against Cuba, with this piece of
you a say in that story.
I heard that.
And by the way, do you know that any Cuban who manages to escape Cuba and put his feet,
his feet on American solid, automatically gets US citizenship?
No, I didn't know that.
Is that true?
No, I don't know.
All the other stuff, I'm sure you're right, because you are the official EU correspondent
of the Charlie.
Thank you very much.
Comic strip blogger, willow, by the way, has a response to some of the stuff, of course,
going on an Italy, willow, my sister, she called it it in two parts.
I haven't even had time to put those two parts together, so that'll have to wait until
money as well.
But she gives that.
It paints a pretty bleak picture of things going on in the European member state of
Italia.
Oh, I'm proud of you casting with the credit.
It is crazy.
It's just just young balls.
Hey Adam, hi, doing.
I'm tired.
I'm going to suck today.
It's just again.
This is in trouble.
Number one.
I'm so fried, young.
I'm not going to get any of them right today.
I have no idea what that was.
Number two.
I don't know.
It could be total in Africa for all I know.
I really don't know.
And this is number three.
Dunn.
Hey.
Yeah, this one.
I know.
Oh.
Why, you gotta get at least one, right?
Dunn.
Oh, I gotta stop.
I gotta stop.
I'm just gonna stop it.
Dunn.
I'm too tired.
Don't know the end and that's it. The null of this week's answers are from
Answer number one
Christopher Cross
Sailing oh
This is answer number one and this is answer number two. It's the need to
It's really enough
Um
The answer number two, the niche William sits your conscience.
Oh, the hell with this one.
And this is answer number three.
High gloss.
You have gone down.
You have fooled.
The best one.
Get to come.
You don't know.
You better go.
One more chance.
And you fool me.
Question number three.
All right.
Glossing.
You'll never know.
Yeah.
This somewhat slower hit us than usual.
Number one hundred and twenty eight.
So Adam, how did you do this week?
Well, I suck monkey balls.
Yon, thank you for asking.
But I enjoyed singing along because I recognized all of them after the first time.
Around two out of three.
No.
So four out of six points.
The first one.
One hundred hit us.
So that's it.
Yeah.
The answer to this hit us.
And also the links to iTunes.
So you can buy the tricks.
Featured in the hit us.
Online up to be found to hit us on video.com.
Adam, thanks for playing again.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for another hit us.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And remember.
Think with your arch.
Bye-bye.
Hit us.
That's chie-mail.com.
In ho-yan-polet.com.
Jayden, P.O.L.T.T.
Go!
All right, Yon.
Thank you so much, my friend.
And I think that definitely was a signal that I need to wind down this through our Friday
to start the Charlie episode number seven hundred and seventy two because I...
Is a fried little boy.
Let's chill out.
Listen to some...
Come on, Edda.
Edda Lass.
My love has come along.
My lonely days are over.
Your life is like a phone.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, at last.
The skies above the blue.
My heart was wrapped up in clover.
The night I looked at you.
And I found a dream that I could speak to.
I found a dream that I can't go home.
I found a thrill to rest my cheek too.
Oh, yeah, you smile.
You smile.
Oh, and then the spell was guest.
And here we are.
Oh, you smile.
Edda Lass.
That song always gets me in the right mood for the weekend.
I hope it puts you in the right one as well.
And if you live in Australia, I hope it wrapped up your Sunday night just fine.
Edda James at last.
It's on then a source code episode 7772, the end of a footballer Friday.
They have a great but rather tiring and busy week.
I look forward to talking to all of you again on Monday.
And of course Sunday for no agenda.
Hey, live your life with passion and want to last.
Enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.