Delta share a Charlie seven nine or three is going to be a great show everybody because I can see them starting to sweat
One two three
Come on everybody from San Francisco
Are you ready?
Oh
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
It's a curry
You can't turn him into a company man
You can't turn him into a horn
And the boys upstairs just don't understand anymore
We're the top west don't lack a talking so much
Anyone feel a day set of play
And he don't want change
What don't need to change
There goes the last DJ
Who plays ready once we play
It says what he wants to say
And there goes the freedom of choice
There goes the last human voice
There goes the last DJ
Who's so close to the guy
And I'm so happy just can't do anything
There's something you just can't do
There goes the last DJ
Who plays ready once we play
It says what he wants to say
And there goes the last DJ
Who plays ready once we play
It says what he wants to say
And there goes the last DJ
As what he wants to say, hey, hey, hey
And cause you feed him a choice
And goes the last human voice
And goes the last teaching
and goes the last teaching
I'll be home, home, home, home
Well, you gonna be astation Donning Mexico
And sometimes you can't come here
And I'll be staying here
and remembering how it was best ever
And there goes the last teaching
Who plays when he wants to play
And says when he wants to say hey hey
And there goes your key to my choice
And there goes the last pure voice
And there goes the last teaching
Yep, there he goes. Here he is right here on your
Favorite show
The last DJ Tom Petty and the hardbreakers on daily source code
Episode number 7-9-3 is the Fubar Friday edition
Coming to you from San Francisco Northern California
I never had that on the video for some reason
That's right everybody
I'm back in the curry condo here for an extended stay
There's just so much to nice fade out
As there's so much to do so much going on
I'm very happy to be here of course on the one hand
Not so happy because I know I'm not going to be with my girls for a little bit
But they support me and everything I do
Even some of the wackier stuff
They're out now I told them you
You should get some stuff like pasta and rice and some canned stuff
Just in case right now
I don't know, weird shit could happen
We just might want to have some food for an extra week or two
I love them so dearly
And I love you chuckle heads because today's going to be a good show
Lots of information for you
Obviously it's going to be pretty much all about the big bailout
Or the rescue plan
As it's now been renamed
Because I sound so much more friendly
Now it's Thursday evening here in San Francisco
It's 10 30 PM
And a word is just coming on the mainstream media
That members of Congress are now back on Capitol Hill
And they will work at least throughout, I guess, part of the evening
Which just blows me away because that's East Coast
I don't know if they're working through the night or what's going on
But as of late this afternoon
A number of house Republicans
Walked out
They've walked out of the quote negotiations about this bailout
Now we've got a lot of data points on the bailout
And let me just give you my quick assessment
The number
This 700 billion or which many say
I'm pretty sure that's right
More than a trillion
Combined by the way
Almost 5,600 billion which has already been handed out
Not quite sure how that happened
While we weren't looking
Hundreds of billions have already started to flow into these banks
From, you know, it's our money
But it's not about the number
It's about the gangster mentality
Or I should say, Banksterm mentality
Of this bill where the Secretary of the Treasury
Hangpulse and wants complete super power
That's really what's going on here
And the numbers, of course, it's crazy
It's ridiculous, it's outrageous
We've dated it to support that
Lots of links, of course
Collected through the drop.io slash
Data Source code
But it's really about the powers
That are proposed to be given away
That's really where the secret lies
Because, hey, look
Even if the bank that holds your mortgage isn't in trouble
That control over that bank will fall under the government
Because that's exactly what Paulson is asking for
Is, you know, complete unchecked, no balanced blank check
In fact, power, pure power
To do whatever to, and you know, in a point banks
As helpers and deputies
And he'll be able to do anything
Just absolutely anything
Not just with our money as taxpayers
But our money in banks
Another bank went to belly up today
In mutual low and behold
Looks like that one's going to be purchased by
JP Morgan
So everything's complete
We've got these two major banks that are left
And now they're really our banks
Because they can also borrow money
Fundra Federal Reserve
That was a quick change
It was made early on in the week
Talking, of course, about Goldman Sachs
And Morgan Chase
And, you know, that's the real crime
That's being committed
Besides stealing the money
You know, even suggesting that you can do that
That you can have these full powers
That's really the travesty
And that's not being discussed right now
It's about the amount, how much
And there's a little bit of, okay, you know
After a hundred or two hundred billion
We should have some checks
And, you know, we have a vote
If you can use more money
But it'll still come down to, if this bill passes
It'll still come down to the complete secrecy
Of how Paulson, who is a billionaire by the way
I think when he left Goldman Sachs
He was the CEO of the, you know, one of the companies
That he's now deputized and wants to bail out
Now, I'm pretty sure his total holding
Exceed one billion dollars
Don't be fooled by the cheap wristwatch, okay
He is definitely one of them
But what is so cool
Is that unless I'm reading this entirely wrong
What is so cool is that we're making a difference
I'm hearing every single interview
I'm hearing with representatives
Are saying, hey man, I'm getting too many calls coming in
I'm getting 200 to one negative
That was a pap you can and said
200 negative
Anti this bill, phone calls and messages
To congressman coming in
And congresswoman, of course
Versus one that might be pro
This is because we are finally stepping up to the plate
And we're doing our job
And as I said, what you have to do
And I'll mention it a couple more times throughout the show
You must contact your congresswoman, congressman
You're representative
And tell them, you'll hold them accountable for
Treason
Because they know the truth is going to come out
And you know, you don't have to be still a sitting representative
To be tried for treason
You need to tell them that
And it's something's working
Because now unless I'm totally nuts
And I'm pretty sure that
The Democrats, they're all chipped
And they're just robots
Walking along with the plan
Because they're proceeds
The ones in congress at least
And of course, not all of them
But the majority proceeds
So now it's the Republicans who are standing up
And saying, hold on a second
This is for this is a big news in my book
Now unless of course it's a total set up
And I have to say the whole John McCain thing
Saying, well, I want to postpone
The campaigning, want to stop right now
That certainly smells a lot like
A leading to a postponement of the elections
So it could be
This is just a, and this is totally a theory
It could be that, you know, somehow
These Republicans are incahutes
And saying, look, we're going to blow up this bill
Make it not happen
So we can really go into financial turmoil
Crisis
And then of course you get into the whole
Postpone the elections, martial law
And we all get killed
But I, but it could also just really be
That a lot of these representatives
Out of pure, egotistical, selfish reasons
Are saying, screw this shit
I'm not going to put my name on that
People are going to hold me accountable
They're calling up
This is what we're doing right, Chuckleheads
This is what we're doing right
And I'm really, really happy about it
We're getting pissed off
Finally
Adam, here's the Portland
Just finished watching the George W Bush
Speech
And think it was a steaming pile of bush shit
Yeah
It was filled with lies of omission
This guy Bush should be in jail
Yeah, hell yeah
Paulson, jail
Bernaki, jail
Christopher Cox of the SEC
To be played in jail
We should throw away the key
And they can take their time
Awakening themselves there
To dream about it
You know what the nicest thing is
Dr. Ron Paul, congressman Paul
Is getting so much attention now
From everybody
Because knowing the media
And of course, you know the media
They're trained, they're controlled
But not really
You know what people are saying on air
There's a corporate DNA
We've been through this many times
And you know what to stay away from
But Ron Paul is now becoming accepted
Because he was the one that continuously predicted this
And the mainstream media loves it
When someone predicts something
And it comes true like a Nostradamus
Like it's some big mystery that this was going to happen
No, no
This is what Ron Paul has been professing
For years
He's been, you know, and he is
He's an award-winning
Economic scholar
And he's cited
His studies
And true and tried and accepted
The theories of economics and methodologies
And the answer has always been the same
And it's not that hard to understand
Even though I'm just basically a VJ
One of the last DJs
Even I can understand what it means
To flood markets and control the price
And not have a free market
And now when the market
The market being supply and demand
Is absolutely saying
Hey, you know
I got nowhere to go right now
But down
To manipulate the market
Even further by putting in money
And manipulating the interest rates
Yet, you know, even more
It's only going to prolong the inevitable
It has to happen
And the question is
Do we want this to be long and drawn out
Or do you want to take our pain
And I think we pretty much discussed that in the previous show
We just got to take our pain
And, you know, sure
There's going a lot of people are going to get hurt
But we have to learn from the mistakes
We certainly didn't learn what happened
From the Great Depression in the 20s
So maybe it's time now
But why don't we take the hit
We take the pain
So our kids can learn from this
And can see that, you know, the way forward
Is not the way the federal reserve
And the reserve banking system
Operates
The whole financial system
Is built around this concept
And it's not working
We need to get back to basics
And I think that if we let these guys
Let these fuckers go
Let them burn
Let their companies burn
Let their profits burn
Let their jets burn
Let their boats burn
Let them burn
We'll figure now
We're going to, you know,
We're a very resourceful people
All people of the world
Very resourceful
We'll figure out how to make money
We'll figure out what to do
We'll figure out how to create new companies
Maybe even
Growing food
Real food for real people who need real nutrition
Just a small idea
There's so many different things we can do
Same way different things we can make
And come up with very creative beings
So I came in
What I come in Wednesday
And I already felt that this was going to be a great trip
Because I did not get apprehended
I did not get stopped
There was no secondary
There was no match in the computer
On my name
Which means one of only a couple things
A
The computer was broken
Doubt that
B
The evil Adam Curry that I kept getting matched to
Has been caught or whatever
And has been taken off the list
It seems to me kind of amazing that
Within the span of five weeks
The sky could have been
If it really was true
Could have been picked up
And the name
Taken off the list
That just sounds way too fast for any government
Institution
Particularly Department of Homeland Security
Which the Border Protection Agency
Is a Department of
Or
Maybe
Maybe all the complaining
Bitching, moaning and exposing
Of the bullshit
Has gotten through to someone
I think the only person who could really
Effect the change like this
At a level that actually
Remove something out of computer
Is probably a team leader
Of Border Protection Agency
At probably at SFO
And I have a feeling that someone
Someone out there is listening
In fact, I know that all kinds of people
Listen to the show
And it is people within government
It is people within the just the system
It is people within the police departments
It is also people within the Department of Homeland Security
They are listening
They are not all evil
Just because they have a job
So I think that this, you know, we are definitely
The message is getting out there
Things are happening
And just by, unless this is a very, very good setup
I mean, an amazingly good one
I mean to me, it seems like
We are gaining ground
We are not winning by a long shot
But we are definitely
Definitely gaining ground
The Chinese are listening
Maybe not to the show
But the Chinese according to Reuters
Chinese regulators have told domestic banks to stop
Interbank lending to the United States financial institutions
Provent possible losses during the financial crisis
This is from the South China Morning Post
Translated by Reuters
So there is no more money to be gotten from China
Are they listening?
Are they in on it?
Yeah, they are not stupid
That is basically what it is
And we have got
People in Congress
Doing their job again
It could be out of your fear
For their own selfish reasons
But when I listen to
Representative capture
I think your name is
And I'm going to play this for you
It's about, well, it's five minutes
Because that's her time limit to speak
I listen to this
I'm saying, yeah
This is the kind of language that gets people's attention
Because now we're starting to simplify the message
And people are really understanding and responding very well
And people are watching YouTube clips
Even older people
Even people who are really, really, really old
Like 72 like John McCain
Which if I hear that one more time
That is as bad as a sexist comment
An ages comment
72 is not old
All right
72 is just not old anymore
And it's really bugs the shit out of me
When people say that
Stop doing that
You can come up with a lot of bad shit about John McCain
But just because he's 72 doesn't mean he's unfit for anything
I just disagree
I hang out with a lot of old people
It doesn't incapacitate them
In fact, in many cases they have a lot of experience
Anyway, so this is a really great wrap
It represents a chapter laid down on the floor of the house
And I got this from cspan junkie.org
Which you really, that's a great site
Because cspan there's so much boring shit
And the good stuff is always on during the day
When you're at work or at school
That's up melts to do
And so this is a fantastic aggregation
Or a really extrapolation of all the cool stuff
That is on this wonderful channel cspan
Listen to this, this is from the 17th
But now just really making the rounds
It only has 88,000 views
So please, this is the way to help get this message out
You've got to put those YouTube clips
Everywhere that you can
Of the one the example about the give you
But also lots of new ones from Ron Paul
By the way, another 70 year old
Okay?
So stop already with the 70s
Alright, let's listen to this for a second
Because I just love this
Here we go
Without objection
The lady is recognized for five minutes
You'll love this
I thank you Mr. Speaker and I thank you Mr. Weiner
Wall Street's big banking boys
Those self-proclaimed geniuses
Of high finance are bankrupting America
These plunders of our economy
Who have fought tooth and nail
Against financial regulation
Now are running home to Mama
Hey, this is very importantly opposed
Government oversight in the markets
Have come begging to the US government
Mama
To bail them out of their bad decisions
They want Mama
That's right
To make it all better
Mama
The federal reserve and the treasury
Now run by Wall Street's best friends
Have happily been showing out from our tax payers
More than 300 billion dollars already in counting
For those irresponsible Wall Street giants
And this was on the 17 so it's already more like 500 billion
And just a week's time
While homeowners in my district
Our suffering is a result of these high-flying bankers
Self-aggrandizing decisions
Yeah Marcy captor is from Toledo, Ohio
She's a Democrat
I've not seen Secretary Paulson or Chairman Bernanke
Running around Ohio over the weekend
Expressing concern about working people's houses
And helping them work out troubled loans
No, all they're doing is sending those folks
The bills
The first check they wrote
Excuse me
That Mama wrote
It was in March
The Fed's main role
In the Bear Stearns by out
By JP Morgan Chase
Was a $29 billion loan to a corporation
It created by $30 billion worth of assets
From Bear Stearns
If the assets gained value
The Fed would profit
If the assets lost value
The first billion will be lost by JP Morgan Chase
But the rest of the losses will be borne by Guess who?
The American taxpayer
Then Mama wrote a blank check a big one
To Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac
Now that bill is already $200 billion
And could rise to 2.4 trillion
Adds a little more about the cronies
And there I'm sure if you haven't heard already
There's plenty of news of
John McCain's advisor
Receiving a $15,000
Month checks up until last month
Even though he lied
And said that there was no involvement
And no connections
And you know what folks nothing to see here
Just keep on walking
Please look at the pretty bird on your way out
Miss Palin
A blank check
Last year
The head of Freddie Mac
Turned
Compensation of $18.3 million
And Fannie Mae's chief David Schmidt
Received 11.6 million
Directly, not counting all
Their other bonuses and stock options
And who knows what else?
Now Mama has written a third check
For the crisis on Wall Street
And effectively
Nationalized American international group
Today with an 85 billion dollar loan
I wonder why we just don't change the name of the US Treasury
To the sovereign wealth fund
Because we're borrowing money from other countries
In order to bail out these institutions
Now you understand why we have to put more money into the
Kitty is because there's no more money to borrow
So where does that come from?
It doesn't actually exist yet
It's just going to be made up
Electronic money my friends
More about that later in the show as well
By the way, from 1999 to 2004
The CEO of AIG
Maurice Hank Greenberg was named
Forbes magazine is among the world's richest people
With a net worth in 2004
A 3.6 billion
Dollars
What a cozy group they have up there
On Wall Street
The CEO named earlier this year
Robert Willemsted had been the president of city group since 2002
And his base salary was a million dollars
Plus up to 4 to 8 million
Internated annual bonuses
Plus 13 million
Internated annual incentive pay
And a 1 time
24.5 million restricted stock award
To vest
Let me just explain that for one second
Because all of this money
That they created
It wasn't real money
It was just money that they made up
Because if you
You get a dollar you can
You can lend out another nine
And because it's all electronic
There's no actual huge heaps of cash
But because it's all electronic
And it runs through this
Basically criminal banking system
You can use your credit card
To go buy a plane or a boat or a house or whatever
You know, and turn it into something real
And this is the way that it's worked
Since, well, in the United States
Certainly since the Federal Reserve Act
It's a boom and bust contract
Expand
Remember there's only so much money
That's put into the system
And if everyone's barring that money
You know, in order to pay back
That all that money with interest
Someone's got to fall off the edge
Or a lot of someone's
That's why
The reserve, the central banking system
Of course the main culprit being the Federal Reserve
Would mess with the interest rates
That is how you contract the economy
You take the money out
You raise the interest rates
You can put money in
You lower the interest rates
That's how you create real wealth
When people take this money and buy real stuff
Real stuff really houses
That's the most real kind of stuff you can have
And land, of course
And then when the squeeze comes
What's left over is the real stuff
And that's the stuff that right now
The banksters are also with this bailout
They want to get their hands on it
Anyway, I digress
Yeah, so to all that money is
They didn't, of course, they didn't actually work for it
It's just skimming off the top of the fake money
It's just, hey, just put some digits into my account
That's the deal that's why I'm here
That's why I'm here
I know this is so well
I was a part of the NASDAQ system
Gosh, I could do it
I should do a whole show on that
In the 90s
And we weren't a dot com company
Yeah, we were
But we started in 94
A little bit before all this bullshit
that really hyped up in 1998, 99, but man,
I saw some wealth creation and
bakery and trickery going on then.
It's just a small little precursor,
minor drop compared to this whole financial system.
So I did get a good insight into all of it.
And of course, the big problem now is all these derivatives
and these guys, you know, they're afraid to be each other,
because they're all each other billions of dollars.
That's the biggest problem right there.
All right, Marcie capture continues over four years,
where our homeowners to get a deal like that.
The American people are truly getting built.
They didn't get a fair share of the upside
and they're getting all of the downside in a huge IOU.
For closures are going up in Ohio and while Wall Street is made whole,
the folks back on Main Street are losing their homes
and getting the bill.
So while the banks get to run home to Mama and they are crying,
we really have to ask ourselves,
what has Mama given us here?
What does it say about our values when we pump hundreds of billions of dollars
into preserving Wall Street's bad boys
while ignoring the plight of the American people?
Across Main Street's from coast to coast,
people are losing their homes.
But our Mr. Paulson or Mr. Bernanke giving them any bet on the upside,
they're not even helping them on the downside.
All they're giving them is a bill for Wall Street's excesses.
When Roosevelt talked about malifactors of wealth,
boy was he right.
I feel sorry for our country.
I feel sorry for this Congress that we can't do a better job of standing up for the people
today who are losing their homes in Ohio.
38,000 more perched at the edge.
Our state needs $20 billion just to do workouts in our state.
Where's the federal reserve?
Where's the Treasury Department?
Why do they only help the rich people?
What about the rest of the people who have to work for a living?
Like, I can't think when I have been as upset as I am tonight about what is happening
by the big shocks and the people who are paying the bill are getting shoved off the edge.
Wake up America.
Wake up America pay attention to what is happening here.
Contact your member of Congress every citizen of this country that is a taxpayer.
And every citizen who owns that home mortgage has a right to a decent life.
Not just the big shots up at the end of Wall Street, up in New York City.
Mr. Speaker, I yield back my remaining time.
Right, thank you.
But you're right on this for a dictatorship.
Let me turn that off.
This of course is a YouTube clip.
You can find that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Then people ask me, lots of people are waking up.
They're listening to this show.
They're reading blogs.
They're looking at lots of YouTube videos.
And they're saying, okay, so what are we supposed to do?
You know, we can't do anything.
But this is exactly the right thing.
Spread this word.
Help people wake up and call your representatives.
That really will work.
There's no two ways around it.
It works.
If we can motivate enough people to block this bullshit,
then we'll block this bill.
And we've got to do it with eyes wide open and know that, of course,
you know, there's pain to be paid.
But we're going to get that anyway.
Whether it's now or down the road and probably down the road,
it'll be much, much, much, much worse.
So we've got to go through this.
But please, don't do it for yourself.
Do it for your fucking children.
Let them learn.
I have a conversation with Christina.
Christina, not Mike Christina, but Christina, who who cleans the condo.
Well, usually after I leave and she kind of freshens it up before I arrived
depending on how long I've been gone.
And since I kind of spun around on a dime and whip right out here,
she was still working on the place when I came in.
And we're chatting and said, you know,
and I said, who are you going to vote for?
And she said, well, you know, probably Obama.
And of course, I'm biting my tongue.
But I don't know what I want to lay into this whole thing with it.
But I say, well, you know, so I kind of start.
And then she said, you know, I lost my home.
I said, really?
She said, yeah, said about six months ago.
My mortgage tripled by the criminal bankster syndicate who did that.
And she said, couldn't sleep.
You know, my husband lost his job in this building alone.
She said, 10 of her clients, 10 have just moved out.
And within the course of like a month, they've moved out.
She said, oh, they, you know, they've been in more job.
Where they couldn't afford the mortgage or whatever it was.
This is new building.
I'm looking at the tower of doom right across the road here,
which as far as I know is completed.
And I can see, you know, of this, what is it?
60 stories or whatever, one of the largest buildings.
If not the largest west of the Mississippi.
I mean, have more than halfway up.
I don't see any lights on tonight.
And she said, she's got no work for you out.
She had one, one, um, you know, she works through an agency.
And they have these buildings, right?
And so that's how they dull out the work.
And she said, he has one client in that building in the tower of doom.
And I think it used to be once every, you know, twice a week.
And now it's once every two months.
I mean, people have no money.
And that's, you know, we fall through this plan.
We're really going to have no money.
Oh, we'll have money because the prices are going to go increased by 20%.
We'll get hyperinflation.
As a couple other links in the show notes that I do want you to check out,
from the market ticker, I will just fire this one up for just a second.
So you can just hear the beginning.
This is, um, titled the flat, uh, the, the fed is speaking out of both sides of the mouth.
Right now I watch the market ticker where I read it, um, not religiously.
But a lot of people posted this link to this particular episode.
Uh, what's this gentleman's name?
I forget his name, who, uh, who does all this analysis.
And he has, uh, an in-depth analysis of, uh, what, what is called slosh in the industry or liquidity
from the banking system, uh, of which a 125 billion has been drained, uh, which really means that,
you know, that, that shit was already underway.
Shit was already being undertaken, uh, this, this bailout, this, this crisis was really pre-planned,
uh, in fact, uh, a lot of people have, um, I've posted this, uh, where is it here?
Right, this is from, uh, roll call, which I really love this.
Now, this is from, uh, September 23rd.
And, um, here we go.
Uh, this is, uh, what's his name, Frato.
White House deputy press secretary Tony Frato, uh, talking about, uh, the bailout and, uh, to move rapidly.
And here it is.
Frato said, uh, sorry, I'm, uh, I just lost my, my place here.
So this was like, uh, here we go.
Frato insisted the plan, this is how stupid press secretaries are.
Because, you know, though, though, you got to watch these guys.
This is, this is almost as good as mainstream, uh, reporting by the way.
This has been reported in many different publications.
This is just, uh, the link that I happened to pull up.
Frato insisted that the plan was not slapped together.
This is the rescue 700 billion bailout and had been drawn up as a contingency over previous months
and weeks by administration officials.
He acknowledged lawmakers were only getting days to peruse it.
But he said that, oh, this should be enough.
Well, it was only, you know, three pages.
And, uh, even though McCain on Tuesday said he still hadn't read it.
I mean, we were reading this thing, what? Sunday night.
Crazy old cook.
Um, but that this thing has been, been drawn up over months and weeks.
Means that all this rhetoric and all this BS about all the fundamentals are fine.
They knew it wasn't fine.
They knew it was coming.
And I think it's pretty much been orchestrated.
You know, it's time to crunch everybody.
It's time to inflate the money.
It's time to take away your shit.
Take it away, fire sale, America for sale.
We're not standing for it.
We are not standing for it.
This is, uh, my own version of something and almost everyone has done, uh, trying to
help us understand how big 700 billion dollars actually is.
This came in through the drop, of course.
Hey, Adam, it's dean and poem desert.
I was listening to this weekend science and, uh, they started out every show with a disclaimer
that's written by one of the listeners and sent in.
Read off by one of the hosts and this particular one just plays into your conversation
with the bailouts that are currently going on.
So take a listen.
I hope this will give you a perspective of how much money this is.
This is, claim or disclaimer, this claim or disclaimer.
While particle physics awaits the large had wrong colliders returned from the disabled list,
the sign blind scientific community has time to ponder more tourist real matters.
Such as the $700 billion corporate donation given out by our very generous federal government,
which is scientifically speaking, approximately equivalent to $191 for every mile between the
planet formerly known as Pluto, $155 for every year the planet has existed, $140 for every year.
The sun is expected to continue shining, $233 for every American alive regardless of age,
$100 for every human being alive anywhere on the planet today.
A mere $7 for every human being that has ever lived on the planet at any time ever in history of
almost sapiens.
I didn't calculate back any further than that, more than $2 for every penny that has ever been
minted by the U.S. Treasury, 7 pennies for every cell in the average human body.
If carefully stacked in pennies, the pennies would reach a height of 69 million miles,
which would be enough to reach the planet Mars and continue for another 21 million miles into space.
In the other direction, the stack of pennies would pass both in her planets and reach more than
two-thirds of the distance to the sun. And while incomprehensibly massive mismanagement of finances,
much like the falling out of programming, does not necessarily represent the views or opinions
even in Russia, California, Davis, KTVS, or its spent responses. And while recklessly mismanaged
finance schemes of our modern economy has cost us more than $2 for every star in the Milky Way galaxy,
the most startling of all these somewhat silly contrasting comparisons is this.
It amounts to $1,015 to every dollar spent on the National Science Foundation.
If instead, we had invested that $700 billion in scientific research.
Well, price list doesn't even come close to describing the returns that we would get.
Speaking of price list, returns get ready for this week in science. Coming up next.
You know, and I got lots of links, thanks by the way for sending that in.
And I think we don't have to ever do that again. It's a lot of money.
But it's not about the money. It's about the powers that are associated with it.
But if, you know, here's a plan, okay?
For all you guys out there listening who are part of this financial scam.
What you should do, what you should do is you say, you know what? We're going to take the hit.
You know, and we all got money. And you know, having money, even if it dev dev dollars doesn't
matter to these guys because, you know, they've got real estate. They've got real things. They've got
stuff, okay? Having money is just not going to matter pretty soon. It's going to, it having stuff
is going to matter. You know, just having stuff ownership. They should say, you know what? We're
going to take the hit. We're going to take billions of dollars out of our pocket. We're going
to settle all this shit over time. And that will fix health care. Or we'll guarantee everyone's
pension. Go down as heroes, boys. Here's your chance. Go down as heroes. Not as freaking
cowards. Cowards. Go run into mama. It's exactly as the representative said. Run into mama.
Cowards. When you see these fuckards, tell them, you're a coward and you're treasonous.
So there's plenty of plenty of good links. One is that I put in the, in the show notes, of course,
is how to, it's like, although I think you should use your own words. There's a link here to
click to send a letter to Congress real simple. What happened? I don't tell me. I just clicked on
that and it's firing up an email program. Is it now? Okay. It's called vote no bailout.org. I,
just call, or email. Find out who your representative is. There's a couple of links to find out
who your representative is since many of you don't even know. Now is the time to learn. And call
them up. Pesteram. Send emails. Now say you want to written response. Keep it going. Keep it rolling.
And help us get back to real money. There's lots of plans. Dr. Ron Paul has a good plan.
pajamas media, which I think is that Michael Moore's site. He's got an alternative to a Wall Street
bailout. I put all these links in the show notes because we are being conditioned. Remember I was
talking about the money, right? The money is not real. It's electronic, which is the next scam.
You know, the next scam to get, you know, when the money's not real, then you can make as much
as you want. And you can just perpetuate this. And we're being trained. We're being conditioned
for this electronic money, which would remove real coinage, which is really the only thing
we're supposed to be using anyway, which is where we have to get back to real coinage back by
something. This is, this is, this is the, I don't know if this is the, I don't know if this is the,
I don't know, CBS, this was at CBS the early show. So there's, and you got to see this YouTube clip.
The monopoly has come out with a global monopoly game. It's the new international monopoly. They
got the, what is it, Mr. Penny money, Penny bags, whatever his name is, the guy with a hat and the
mustache. And he's out there with a huge blown version of the new game, right? And so you've got
to, it was at Harry Smith, and he's pretending that he gives a shit because, yeah, and I don't think
this is a paid commercial. To me, it seems like complete propaganda and indoctrination preparing
us for electronic money. And so right now, they've uncovered this thing. And what they have is
all the, the big properties are different places around the globe. But listen to the question
when they talk about money. Okay. What are we using for the new international game? Are we using
international money? Listen to this. Montreal and Riga, why got the most votes? What about the
game pieces? All the game pieces, those are all new, too. They represent artifacts and from all over the
world. And even the, yes, the houses and hotels are also in the reflecting the architectural
styles from all over the world. I know we have big fake money. No, you don't because we have
electronic banking now. No, no, it's all up in the fair and square. And it makes the game go faster,
of course. There you go. Okay, can I show it? And we also have, yes, sir, is you must
all show up? Of course. Don't you love that? It makes the game go faster. We're modern,
electronic money, of course. Are you crazy for even asking that question? Are you nuts?
It's electronic money, of course. That's conditioning. That's, and that, I think that's the whole
message right there. Because the rest of this piece is such fodder. Take a look at it. You know,
let me know what you, what you think about it. Anyway, it is, of course, the Fubar Friday coming to you
from the Curricondo here in Northern California, San Francisco. We're now at, what do we have?
The six past eleven. And of course, no Fubar Friday is complete without a test of your knowledge
of popular music. Well, it's not really yours. It's mine, because I'm the only one that gets points.
You win no prizes, but you might save the world with the hit test.
Hey, Adam, this is hit test number 140. And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
Oh, baby, I know that one. The one known as 100, and as wild romance Saturday night,
the dream, that's what's next. Number two.
Spend no belly, only when you leave. Only when you leave. And then things like that.
And the final one is number three.
Very appropriate. What a Fubalese would be your number three young with a Dooby Brothers.
Let's see how we did. And it's time for the answer.
And this is the first answer of hit test number 140. And it's from 1978.
This is Hermann Broth, Saturday night.
We'll be open all night. We'll just make every play by the magic of you, Saturday night.
We'll set it in night.
Set it in night is enter number one.
Yes. And this is answer number two.
So only when you leave. No belly.
Answer number two from 1984. Spend no belly, only when you leave.
This is answer number three.
From 1986. Dooby Brothers.
And so number three from 1986. The Dooby Brothers.
Fubalese. And that concludes hit test number 140.
So Adam. Yes. How did you do this week?
I'm so proud of myself, John. Easy though. It was not that hard.
I got six out of six for today's hit test one four zero.
Use your place to find the answer to this and any other hit test.
And also to find the least. I tuned so you can buy the tricks.
The feature on the hit test online is of course hit test.mevio.com.
This hit test was created using some bites.
But Adam, you should check out the better version.
That's version 361, better two.
Oh. Because I've been talking to Chris Malinsky from a Blackhead system.
And based on those conversations, he has implemented some changes.
And some new features. So check it out.
Alrighty, thanks for playing Adam. Thanks for listening.
Next week, I hope to be back for another hit test. So until then, have fun.
Take care. And remember to try to think with your hearts. Bye-bye.
John, thanks so much, my friend.
Yeah, I use sound bite. I use it for
I use Ableton Live as most of you know.
And what am I using on sound bite? Because I did buy it.
Yeah, licensed too. Adam, I'm curious. There you go. Sound bite.
Oh, I have three dots six dot zero. So I wonder what the improvements are.
What if they put MIDI controls into that? It would be just perfect.
That's really the only thing that's really missing for me at least.
But anyway.
Thank you, John.
Let me see one more bit about the US, the elections, the political system.
This is not only for people within the United States who, unfortunately, there's a lot of people,
probably don't really know how it works. And they think they can only vote for one of two people.
And it's a very unpopular idea to vote for anyone else. But there are more people on the ballot.
There's more people that you can vote for. Todd is outraged about the whole system as am I.
Hey, Adam, this is Todd here from Kentucky and I want to express some grief about the upcoming election.
Everyone is going back and forth with our voting for McCain or are you voting for Obama?
But I have chosen the roadless travel by selecting a third party candidate, namely Ralph Nader.
I'm tired of people telling me how I'm wasting my vote and how Nader isn't going to win.
That might be true. But when are people trying to vote for who they think will win?
It's not some popularity contest. This is our land.
By the way, Todd, that's because we're trained to go with winners. That's why
didn't know more losers anymore. Everyone's got to be a winner. Oh, I should play hot chocolate.
Everyone's a winner, baby. That's the truth.
But that's why it's because everyone thinks they got to go with the winner.
But there's plenty of people. You got to go with your heart people. Go with your brains.
That was who's supposed to win. Who's supposed to win? Give me a break. Give me a break.
Here in the hands. I mean, this is our land and the hands of the winner here.
I mean, the stakes are very high. Another gripe I have is, you know, why won't they open up the
debates to all third party candidates? People are running to lead our country. Shouldn't we be entitled
to hear every candidate's voice? We actually have that power in our hands as well because the
they who don't open up the debates is the media. The mainstream media, the only people who determine
that is the media. Now, of course, they're they're corporate overlords who are tied into
the political system. You know, they pass that on down the food chain. But there's no law.
There's no law that says you can't have Ralph Nader in debate with the Republican and the
Democratic nominee. There's no reason you can't do that. So yeah, you can vote with your
feet once again. You can call them up, call up CNN, call up the fair and bounds dudes and
tell them, I want Ralph Nader on the debate or I want this in the McKinney in the debate,
or I want Chuck Baldwin in the debate or Ron Barr or I want them all in the debate. And otherwise
I'm not going to watch you. I'm not going to watch you the debates. Not on your channel.
We have that power now. We're proving it. We are proving it. We can break these decks.
We can break them with this bill. Let's prove it. Let's prove it. I don't burn.
On national television, it's thickening to think how the two major parties are basically strong
army, the less the parties out of even being heard. I just want to know what are the
outrageous over this. People should be outraged and really upset that they're not hearing
all the possible candidates speak. They need to be informed to make an intelligent,
smart decision. But thanks Adam. I enjoy this show and keep up the good work.
Hi. Todd, thank you, man. I remember they do work for us. Okay, a couple of things from around the
world from the UK. Looks like I'm going to get my biometric data stored into the database
in the United Kingdom. Identity cards are on their way. Here it comes. The first identity cards
from the government's controversial national scheme have been unveiled according to the BBC.
And it will include all of my visa information. So the first people who are going to get this,
the first people who go on record, who's, to me it's privacy and thus part of my freedom being
taken away. First people are a students and we're where they call it marriage visa holders,
which is me. The reason why I am allowed to live and work in the United Kingdom is because I'm
married to an EU national. They are allowed to travel and work freely amongst EU nations.
Hello, don't try to just show up at E at Heathrow and say, hey, I'm from Poland. Let me in.
Don't think it's that easy. Okay. So we're the first ones. And let's see. I'll have my unique number.
I'll have my official photograph. I'll have entitlements, which is interesting.
So it'll say if I have right to public funds, if I have the right to work. And then of course,
my favorite is the biometric chip, which holds my fingerprints will be on this card. I'll be
on file, unbelievable. And of course, who's going to protest this, right? Who represents me?
And in fact, many Brits, you know, when they envision someone who got married to live in
the country and suck off the the teeth of the British mom, they don't think of me that way.
And of course, I'm not. I'm contributing IPA taxes in the United Kingdom. Income taxes.
Capital gains taxes. IPA counsel taxes. I pay road taxes. I pay my taxes over there.
As I do in the United States, as I do in the Netherlands, because I work and make money in
multiple countries. And I pay the taxes locally. In most cases, that's pretty much the rules.
Only in the United Kingdom, either way, do I get tax double according to the new rules?
Because yeah, sure, we want to go take from the really, really rich, but that starts at like
100,000 pounds a year. So I fit into the really, really, really rich bracket.
But I'm not one of the really, really, really rich. So this should go into effect by next April
at a cost of a 300 million pounds. So we'll keep our eye on this, but it's pretty sad.
Pretty damn sad as far as I'm concerned.
Good news. Again, the same thing happening. Another BBC story that school is now banning
girls from getting this HPV cancer and population, this vaccination. And there's a video that goes
along with it that you can get from the link that I put in the show notes. I'm not going to play
that for you right now. But essentially, there's a couple of good points. One is teacher saying,
hey man, you know, we don't want to, we don't want this shit happening at school because we don't
actually want to be like endorsing this stuff. And the teacher who said that was, uh,
I did it in a very diplomatic way, but the intent of the words was quite, quite clear.
But more importantly, there has been quite a number of cases of side effects and of girls getting
sick after they had this shot. We're talking nausea, joint pain, headaches, high fevers. Oh yeah,
it's all perfectly normal. It's all good for you. And it's a sexually transmitted disease, okay?
It's not, it's not like a virus that's flying through the air. You get it through having sex.
Because a lot to be said for giving this, uh, this is an accumulation of 12-year-old girls.
You know, it's been through this. It's a scam from the pharmaceutical industry. And who knows
what else is in this shit? Would someone please get this guardous pill and do an analysis
and tell me exactly what is in it? And with these snazzy commercials on television,
it's disgusting the way we're, we're hypnotizing these kids into wanting this, this, this vaccination
of a disease that, um, it's a sexually transmitted disease, okay? It's not quite the same as
polio. And it does cost about $500 per person receiving this. If anyone has a lab, please,
please let me know what's going on. I'm not quite sure what to make of this. You know, there's so
much news coming out continuously that needs its attention. I mean, even, did you even know that
washed in mutual, essentially, went bankrupt? Did you even know that amidst all of this, you know,
hype about the, about the rescue plan? No, of course you didn't.
You know, hold on a second. Did I lose it? It looks like I left. I lost my connection there for a
second. Hold on. Want to pull up this from the independent, uh, another mainstream publication
from the UK about this, uh, methane that is starting to bubble up, uh, from the Arctic ice.
And, uh, of course, what else methane is, uh, is going to kill us because it releases 20 times
more carbon dioxide into the atmosphere than anything else we can do. It's a, it's a, it's a greenhouse
gas. That's, I'm sorry. I'm saying that wrong. It's 20 times more powerful than carbon dioxide.
And, uh, people are worried about this. I don't know enough about it, but I did want to bring it
to your attention so we can study it. Remember, we got to aggregate as much information as possible
on the drop. Drop.io slash daily source code, um, because, um, these methane chimneys, uh, usually
mean bad stuff. And, isn't, uh, a methane, uh, flammable? So, let's, uh, let's figure out what's
going on with that. It's, uh, it's certainly worth, uh, worth mentioning. Uh, also, uh, uh, just something
I just haven't had time to really look into, uh, this, uh, Marriott attack in Islamabad. There's a
lot of theories about why that took place who did it. And I put one of the links, um, into the, uh,
show notes, uh, called the real story behind the Marriott attack. We can't overlook that. A lot of
people died. A lot of shit going down that we have to really look at. And then, uh, on top of all of this,
beginning in October, the army plunge to station an active unit inside the United States
for the first time to serve as an uncalled federal response in times of emergency. The third
Infantry Division's first brigade combat team has spent 35 of last 60 months in Iraq, but now the
units training for domestic operations. The unit will soon be under the day-to-day control of
U.S. Army North. The Army Service component of Northern Command. The Army Times reports this new
mission marks the first time an active unit has been given a dedicated assignment to Northern Command.
The paper says the army unit may be called upon to help with civil unrest and crowd control.
The soldiers are learning to use so-called non-lethal weapons designed to subdue unruly or dangerous
individuals and crowds. That would be me. That would be me. You're unruly, sir. I'm going to
taste your ass. Ha. So, uh, we did talk about this, uh, on this, what the last show 792.
Uh, this is from democracy now. And it's for real, you know. Now, for many Europeans, it may not be
that weird to have the military walking around patrolling streets. It's, uh, it's standard practice now
in many cities in Italy. Uh, it, uh, it happens. But in the United States, it's, um, pretty much
pretty much it's illegal. You know, uh, you can't turn the army on the people of America. It's, it's
written. It's a law. You know, it's, it's, it's a, it's a, it's a no-can do. And the fact that they're
gearing this up tells me that they're ready for some kind of shit because just like they already
had this bailout plan all written months, weeks, whatever it is before, it actually came to a head.
They're prepared. They know what's going to happen. They know what's coming down because we're going
to get our pitchforks and our torches when and go, we're going to go, uh, we're going to go
cost them shit unless they go peacefully. And as I said, I'm feeling really, really good because
it looks like they actually might go peacefully because we are making a difference, my friends.
Call your representatives. Tell them you're going to hold them accountable for
treason for everything they do. Let's wrap it up. I'm happy to know today, shall we?
We're the cool stuff.
We're gonna go up, up, up, up, up. Straight to the moon we too.
Hi in the starry blue. I'll be out of this a world with you. So away we'll steal in my space
mobile, a supersonic, a honeymoon. Leave your cares below, pull the switch, let's go,
a destination moon. I just want to thank sponsors for this week, uh, budget rent of cars,
get $30 off, uh, any weekly rental 10% off any amount, 10% off at brookstone.com, 30% off at
godaddy.com and 35 free songs at ebusic.com check the show notes for the code you need,
to get all these great discounts on sponsors who believe in free speech and kick-ass programming.
And now back to Dino Washington, take the ebusic, you're right.
We'll go up, up, up, up. Straight to the moon we too. We'll be high in the starry blue.
I'll be out of this world with you. So away we'll steal in my jet mobile,
a supersonic, a honeymoon. Leave your cares below, pull the switch, let's go,
a destination, a destination, a destination. We fly high, let's go,
destination, destination, destination moon.
Dino Washington, wrap it up, jungle, favorite show, seven, nine or three, with destination
moon. One of these days, I'm just going to do another music show, you know, it's just, but whenever I
sit down, whenever I'm getting ready to do it, something happens that I just can't leave alone.
So anyway, everybody, thank you so much for listening. Welcome to the awakening, um,
of course, during the weekend tomorrow, uh, sorry, yeah, for you tomorrow in Australia three days ago,
do a show with Johnson of O'Rack, no agenda, which you can find at noagenda.mevio.com.
And, um, we'll talk to you then, of course, and we'll have lots of discussions inside into what's
going on. And I really will try to put together just a pure music show this week. If we can get away with it,
if things settle down, yeah, you're right. I don't think we'll get to it either. So until then,
enjoy your freedom, you deserve it, and we hold that power and live your life with passion.