Now the man willing to ask the questions that lead to the answers that spark more questions.
It's Adam Curry and the Daily Source Code 731.
We don't have to debate for me.
Going to go to the cinema and TV.
Down in the bass, we got to be family.
Going to plug it into another thing saying,
Can't say not so we know it won't be true.
Hold him, we'll have him ready to go.
I want a kill top radio.
I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again
I'm going to do it again, I'm going
to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to build a video, a video going on, smart
time with 15 million dollars and then that will go into its library panels, so I'm going to do
it again.
Now, I'm just going to do it again.
Motherfucker, the下次 window is cleaned up here.
Now, there's a cover track that will be карlichted up.
There's so much flex and thanks for watching it, I'm going to turn the pedal in front of
the back of the car, it may be already wider and I'm just going to finish it yourself,
then it will protect the balanced pound compressor from the electric vehicle.
All day here in the United Kingdom, more and more home I'm just getting everything set
up here.
I've gotten rid of most of that annoying sound that I had on Monday, it turns out it
is indeed a ground loop and I haven't quite found it yet, but I'm pretty much in the
process of getting rid of every other piece of hard board, hard board, hard board,
outboard gear that I've been using for the show.
I just don't need anymore.
It's all pretty much contained in the Mac, gotten my MIDI controller for the faders
from my tactile feedback.
And of course, on the way my father-in-law is building my new mic preamp, so getting
everything together very excited about that.
It is the 5th of March, 2008, which reminds me that I have to say happy birthday to
Willow, my sister who was born, what is she today, I'm not supposed to give out
ages, huh?
She's younger than I am.
That's the good news for her.
She's celebrating an Italy today, had a nice quick catch-up call, a little chat with her.
I got to tell you, I stayed home today, the thinking was that I actually, I was supposed
to have a lunch in the city, which I canceled, and let me tell you why yesterday, of course,
I didn't do a show yesterday.
I was up very, very early for me, getting up 6.37 o'clock, that's early.
I actually saw my daughter walk out the door off to school, so just to give you some kind
of idea, I had to do the trash, Patricia hadn't taken the trash out for the two weeks
I was gone, so I knew I had a little extra work to do, and the trash guys come to us
for pretty much first on the route, so you got to get you shit out early, and you know,
there have been going back, they only collect once a week where we are, and I hear there's
talk of them not only scaling that back to once every two weeks, but also charging you
extra for more than like, you know, three and a half bags or something, the, anyway,
that's the UK's trash problem, don't have to deal with that right now.
So then I went to the dentist, I was able to get slaughtered in early at an 8 a.m. appointment,
I got a couple things, you know, and my head's fallen apart, what can I tell you, and
it comes with age, I guess, back home, had a quick bite to eat, gathered on my things,
and then rushed off to the station to take the train to Waterloo Station where I usually
pick up a cab, and then from the cab, I'll go off to the office. Now, I'm in the, I'm in
the train, and by the way, usually when I get to the station to Guildford Station, which is
just like a five minute cab ride from the house, I'll buy myself a nice cup of Chino, you know,
I'll have, I've got day, HDS, PDA, FM, and LMA, no PABC thing that gives me, you know, high
speed, like a megabit per second broadband access on the train in my laptop, so I've got that
in my bag, got my mac and my bag, but usually I'll choose to just listen to a couple of podcasts
on my way in, because I'm a commuter, and that's what you do is you chill out, and you sit back,
you listen to some shows, and I was thoroughly enjoying this week's no agenda, yo agenda, I should
say, yo agenda is is a program that discusses no agenda that I do with the John C. to Vorac,
so the candy man and comic strip blogger do the show about our show, which is kind of a throwback
to the old answer records of the 50s, and even more recently, of course, we've had some of those,
and it was entertaining, I was laughing my ass off, and then, you know, they were talking
and talking and they were kind of droning on, and it was, it was nice and warm, I didn't have
my cup of Chino because the train, you know, there was an earlier train that just arrived,
as I walked on to the, onto the platform, and so, you know, kind of their words were
mashing into, you know, the announcements, the train was making, I fall asleep, which is okay,
because I know the Waterloo station is the end of the line, and when I'm there, I'll have to get
up and get out, you know, not a big deal, so I won't miss any stops. I was a woken,
the some time later, I'm not quite sure how long I was asleep, it couldn't have been more than
15, 20 minutes, and there's a crowd of like four people standing around me, and I can feel that
my neck is like cockback, you know, I really have passed out essentially, and then people like
say, so are you all right, night, okay, they thought I was dead, I was in so much of a coma
that they actually feared for my, for my well-being, oh man, so, um, there you go,
and I was groggy. There were people, there were new people coming onto the train to go
back down south, like, oh, right, this is a signal from God, and I could feel it, you know,
how you kind, you know, they talk about narcolepsy, or even if you go into our courses, I guess,
if you've been given anesthesia, you can feel it, you can feel it in your head, you know, this is kind
of, it's almost like a chemical, and you know that is trying to put your body down and put
you to sleep, and it's just exceeded clearly in, in the situation I was in at the time,
and I was like, this is not good, and I grabbed a cup of chino at the station, got in a cab,
and I was groggy for the rest of the day, and I was like, okay, I know I got some late night calls
to do, so I'm gonna sleep in a little bit, and I think that was a pretty good idea, so I'm feeling
much, much better, and much, much more awake, and with you guys, so there you go, life on the road,
I guess. I've been talking about this, it's kind of a minor discovery, and I didn't know it until
I dropped my iPhone in the toilet several months ago, but there is indeed an indicator inside the
iPhone and the iPod Touch that will turn fully or partially pink, which allows the, if you
take it back under warranty, and you know, you just want to say it doesn't work anymore, for instance,
my phone, everything works as far as I can tell, except the touchscreen is broken, so now I'd love
to take it back and say, hey man, the touchscreen broke, but you gotta, you know, I don't know what happened,
but of course I know, fully well what happened, and indeed, on the inside, I guess you could say,
maybe there's a little bit of pinkishness, it's kind of hard to see, so I'm not sure if they use a
microscope or some other optical device to actually look and see if you've, if you've played by the rules,
well, of course, someone came up with a great idea on how to hack around that little minor
nuisance. Hey Adam, okay, so you drop yourself on at the toilet, my solution to that,
maybe it'll work, maybe it won't, it dropped a wide out, and just put it over the little indicator,
and voila, literally, I don't know, it might be worth giving it a try, thank you very much, I'm
remarkable, and I won't be able to carry. No, I love you too, man, thank you very much.
Hey, that's a good idea. I just mind try it, just see if I can get away with it, although I need
to know how they look into that little hole to see if it indeed, if the indicator has turned color,
I just mind try it, it's not that I really, I think that I'm sure there's going to be another
version of the iPhone coming, and I may be interested in that, but for now, everything satisfied
with my Nokia 80010, which, of course, you can buy at a 15% discount and cheaper nowhere else online,
go to patchowoffers.com, enter my code, daily source code, and you'll be with the way and soon on your
way to having fun with the internet tablet, full web 2.0 browser. That's really what does it,
from the end Skype, which, of course, is our instant messaging system of choice for pod show.
Primary still taking place in the U.S., following it here in the U.K., I got to tell you,
man, they showed Ohio last night on, I think, was a channel for news here, and it was just,
they make it look like the whole state of Ohio is a fucking slum. Boy, what a slanted report those
guys were bringing. This place is in demise, job losses. I'm sure it's not great, but it's not
like all of Ohio, I mean, it was really, really, really slanted. A little bit annoying, I'd have to say.
Of course, their primary is taking place in other states as well. Some of them, not quite as large
as Ohio, in fact, here's a call from the smallest state in the Union, where my mother was born,
Rhode Island. Hey, I'm a shrine in Rhode Island. I haven't called in a long time, a bunch of bullshit
going on in my end and all that jazz, but I get back into the DSC. This is one of the common great
because, like I said, I live in Rhode Island, and today's primary day. And I know what I haven't
voted yet in my life. I'm 28, never voted in my life. And you know what, I always said, it was
Kennedy inspired me. I would vote. So, you know what, I found a candidate to this part. And I said,
in my voter registration card, and I went through all the steps like a good little dovy and
good, all my shit done. And guess why? Here comes because my registration card was postmarked
three weeks and two days and not exactly one month from the primary day, I can't vote.
I don't know if this is a law everywhere, but you know what, it was nowhere on the registration
card, and it was nowhere on the time of the website, and it wasn't anywhere. So, for the first time,
I'm like, I want to vote and the state does talk to you, you can't vote. I've been living in the
goddamn state for 28 years. It's not like, they don't know me here. What the hell? You know,
so I'm just kind of missed, you know, I mean, I finally got the gumption up to do it, and the man's
telling me now. So, you know, here we go with all system thing again, and man, I just don't know if
I want to vote again. No, that's just, just pisses me off. It's just pisses me off. I won't,
hey, hope you have a great day. Let's see, going back for a long ways, 28 canal technicians,
folder, not a scratcher. I love you. No, I'm almost great here. I hope you win all that jazz.
See you later.
All right, man. Thank you. And I apologize. The system clearly is screwed up.
I presume you were going to vote Republican. I think the Republicans have all those really harsh
measures that make it very complicated. Yes, sucks.
And the more I, I think actually this primary has been fantastic. It's been a learning experience
from myself personally. I've been, of course, very involved with the Ron Paul campaign who,
although no longer listed still is in the running. You know, they only show McCain and how
could be these days on the Republican side. And I am not a card carrying Republican member,
which makes it a little more complicated being an expat and not registered as a Republican
for the primaries. But, of course, for the presidential elections, should Dr. Ron get on the
ticket somehow. I'm going to vote regardless. And I'm not going to vote from McCain. I can tell you
that. But I'm not too sure about about Obama and Clinton. You know, it's to me is there's some
pros and cons on both sides. I listen very closely to Obama and it sounds like a lot of promise
for change. He's very charismatic. I like that a lot. I think it's a lot to be said for a
charismatic leader that people are almost in love with. That's fantastic. But, of course,
there's also a lot to be said for someone who knows how works in Washington. And they're both
pretty much, excuse me, fueled by Wall Street. So I'm not too high in either of them. I think
I'll agree with my friend, John C. Devorac on this. That Obama would make a great
president for the next election in 2012. What in every 100 Americans now in jail? This has been
going around going around the blogosphere, unbelievable. How many of those are in jail for marijuana?
I'd like to know. That's a lot of people. That's like three, three and a half million people in jail.
And when they come out of jail, you know, what kind of chances do they have? A lot of them
are going to come out in the next year or so. Like 700,750,000, so they pay their dues. They spent their
time. What's the program when they come back out? I mean, this is, of course, we've got these
commercial jails in America. We've been through this on the Charlie before. And of course, they get paid
extra for each inmate they have. So there's a lot of really weird incentives going on. And it's
quite concerning to me. You probably also heard that all the athletes who are attending the
2008 Olympics will be allowed to keep personal journals, i.e. a weblog. But those may not include
any other types of media, no pictures and no podcasts, no audio, no video, no pictures. And this
just kind of summons for me that these Olympic gains are one big political money making
crap scheme. And it's unfortunate because of course, I don't think they were intended that way in
the early days and Greece. But I have had a couple meetings in the past 20, 30 years with
members of the IOC, the International Olympic Committee, and it's all about the money. It's all
about the sponsorships. It really doesn't feel when you're talking to those guys and man, they're
arrogant. It doesn't feel at all like it's about sport anymore. And now they're not, you know,
and the reason why they're not allowed to distribute any type of digital media is because
well, they've already sold all those licenses to mainstream comic strip comic strip comic strip
comic strip comic strip. Our favorite EU correspondent ends up on to the Charlie comic strip
blogger checks it. Yeah, Adam and they get pictures carry. So the best actresses,
Bruce the best for in film in Oscar's 2008, came from European Union countries who were
it was from Spain, France, England, Ireland and Austria. It's funny, you know, we have these conversations
about shows and formats and programs. And we're doing a lot of shows here in the UK. And initially,
you know, I was getting some pushback from programming on the US side. It's like, well, you know,
another guy with a British accent. I'm saying, excuse me, would you please go look at the Oscars?
Would you please look at the number one, two, and three television shows in the United States?
I mean, the American Idol Simon Cowl dancing with the stars. You've got Len and the other guy
English accents. I mean, it appears to be kind of what's working. And maybe it's, I don't think it
has anything to do with the quality of the acting. It's maybe just a shift. It's, well, no, it is a
shift. It seems that that's what consumers of entertainment, like right now, I guess.
So, you is not that yet, huh? Anyways, I wanted to say that in UK, liberal, Democrats, party,
calls for a friend, I'm about UK membership in EU, which, of course, would result in UK living
EU. And so, Adam, better get yourself dual, American British citizenship, or you may be
expect from UK, but clearly because you are now calling people to demonstrate in UK,
but it's also could be considered a kind of reason to experience from UK. Ladies and gentlemen,
and Oscar goes to Adam Kerry. Yeah. I don't think I'll be expelled, CSB. In fact, tomorrow
I have my interview with the council for my national insurance card. Now that I've moved my
employment over to the UK, I'm being a really good citizen, paying all the taxes, I can, except for
capital gains here in the UK. I have the right to live here because I'm married to an EU national.
So, I'm contributing, I'm working, and I still believe there is a, there is a freedom of speech
here in the UK, CSB. So, I think that even though I'm suggesting, and in fact, I am recommending
a protest, and this is all about the flash mob, and still to this date, no one stepped forward,
no one has said they're going to organize it. I'm still calling out to my UK listeners. I think
it's time we do something, don't get caught, you know, tidying away or hiding in a bottle. Let's
do something about this. But the dual nationality show me where that's easy. It is not easy by any,
means whatsoever. The United States does not like people having dual nationality. And right now
with the UK and the tax laws, I don't think I have a shot at all, and it won't change that much.
And by the way, they can kick anyone out of the country they want, where the other passport that
belongs that country or not. No, man, no, I'm doing everything right, and I'm speaking my mind,
which I'm pretty sure is still allowed in this country. I'm high shelves, I'm here in London.
Hey, Charles, I'm talking to you. I'm going to go in 19, beautiful day, Blue Sky.
I just caught one of your episodes. I tend to listen to the latest one of the work backwards when I've
made the film. Okay. So, I've just heard some op-soul. Elky Brooks pulled this is op-soul stands for
organization for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives. It is a nonprofit organization
that encourages people to remember songs based upon the soundtrack to their lives
and relate those to where they were when they heard the song or the first time or whatever comes to mind.
And it really does work. And we've been doing a lot of that. In fact, this time for another
op-soul episode, which I'll put together this week. It's op-soul, Oscar Papas here, Oscar Lima.
.podshow.com. So, yeah, Elky Brooks, I played that one on a recent Saturday show.
The singer. Oh, man. And you said, do you remember where you were when you heard that?
And I tell you what, my older sister, Pippa. So, my older sister.
Doesn't get more British than that, having an older sister named Pippa. Yes, what about Pippa?
Uh, you used to sing it. And that's why I first heard it. I'd never heard it first.
I hadn't actually heard the song. I don't even heard her singing it for years. And then you just
played that. It's really very neat thinking about my lovely beautiful sister, who has just had a
beautiful 9 pound baby boy, has 3rd time around. Good baby. Have you babies? And uh, so my point is,
I'm now going to go and buy that song. Stick it on a speedy and send it to her.
Because she's a real special person. And you just made me smile. I'm saying that song.
You have enriched my life. And you have also encouraged a sale.
Okay, sure. I'm going to buy it. Wait. But, yeah. That's not the point. I'm going to buy it.
Oh, I take it by. All right, Charles, thank you. Well, this is the point. And if only the
record companies would understand this. That people, I mean, there's a lot of music being made.
And allowing people to share it, to promote it, invokes this. There you go. Not just a great
memory, a great experience shared amongst the friends, but it induced a sale as well.
All right. Let me share one from the soundtrack to my life since you were talking about your
sister, Pippa, who just had a Pippa, who just had a child. When Patricia and I on August 27, 1990,
went into the hospital, St. Barnabas Hospital in Livingston, New Jersey.
Our daughter was to be born that day. It was a very laid-back situation.
New Christina was breached, so it was a cesarean section. So it was a little more planning,
a little more organized than most people might have the opportunity for.
We were in the operating room. I knew all the doctors. It was a very comfortable surrounding.
Patricia was feeling great. I was feeling great. And they had the radio on at the time. And it was
light FM 105.5 WLTW in New York. And just as Christina was being lifted from my wife's
abdomen, as she was brought into the world, this song was played.
Don't forever not far better. Some have gone and some remain. All these places have
a moment. Full of us and friends. As you can recall, some are dead and some are living.
I love them all. But of all these friends and lovers, there is no one
compares with you. And these memories lose their meaning. When I think of love as something
you, don't I know I'll never lose affection. But people and friends, when people
I know I love something about them. In my life, I love you more.
I know I'll never lose affection. But people and friends, when people
I know I'll often stop the thing about them. In my life, I love you more.
In my life, I love you more.
Presented by the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives, the Beatles in my
life. Boy, does that bring back memories? Daily source code episode number 731 helping people
nationwide, getting them jobs. Hello, Adam. This is Torsten Collin from Germany.
I'm listening to your show for about three years now and about two years ago. I got involved
with making podcasts and created some podcasts because I'm a assistant professor at the University
of Mines. And so I created some episodes related to my lessons that I'm a teaching in class
for my students to download them and get their hands on this educational stuff wherever they want.
So I realized that E-learning podcasts are in general, are a little boring and got very noisy,
audio quality and all this stuff like ask questions which you can't really hear on the
recording because the students ask questions. Don't have microphones and so on. So my approach
to this E-learning podcast was pre-recording all that and getting online with all these entertainment
aspects because I think the entertainment factor is totally missing in A-learning right now.
So I created my website called jocophory.com, the free space for geography and my students love that
so much that right now. The folks at the University decided to give me a job or at least half a
job 20 hours a week from this month on to create go on creating episodes for the better and
master degree in geography at the University in Mines. Isn't that great and you know why in the
first place I started recording podcasts. It was because of you because of the daily source code
and all this coolness and this cool stuff happened in there and this entertainment and lifestyle and
I found that so entertaining that I wanted to put it into this E-learning podcasts. So I did that
and you are the reason I did it and so I felt like sending this voice message to you to say thank you
so much for inspiring me and all the other listeners of the DC. So I'm 32, my assistant professor
at the University, still got all my hair on a strong way to the middle class right now with the first
thousand bucks in my pocket. I love you. I really mean it straight. Great hair and I hope you win.
Do. Oh dude, Torsten, thank you very much. You humble me with that man. Absolutely. And anyone who's
out there teaching kids anything is a hero in my book, a big ass major F and hero. We should get back
to that. In the States, it's still like that. Teachers are still revered as some form of hero,
though I think it's diminishing as well. And it's a little bothersome. I'm getting old.
I'm sounding just like my parents used to sound. Oh, cranky. Oh man, awesome.
Let me see what else do we have. Oh yes, still lots of conversation going on about the
Airbus A320 that landed in Hamburg, Germany. I posted the video which was from lively.com on
it's still up on the homepage if you want to go take a look at it. And what's really interesting is
the comments thread Kent and. Oh boy, Robin, of course, Robin from the InsightWorks. Both Boeing
pilots, both checked in, both have confirmed a lot of what I said. And it's some real good insight
is into how you perform across wind landing with a huge machinery like that. Of course, it is
actually exactly the same as a smaller aircraft, although there are differences in limits,
et cetera. But a really good read. And I think you should take a look at it. And there's another
other call about this. Hello Adam, Marcus from Germany. Um, just your comment today in
the I think episode 730 about the Airbus that well had this somewhat strange landing in Hamburg,
Germany. Um, it was actually a little bit more, well, a little bit stranger or world than you
reported because the left wing actually hit the runway. I have seen furrows from from Airbus,
well, I have close ups off the damaged winglet. So it was a little bit more almost a crash than
then you made it sound. Also, to the another in Germany, the accident into the investigation guys
are investigating because the question is why the pilot took the runway where he had this
high amount of crosswind. So anyway, just wanted to let you know. Well, thanks. Bye.
Yeah, indeed. I saw the pictures too. And if those are authentic, then the winglet did indeed
touch the ground. Still, the whole situation was right for a go around and I think it comes
down to decisions. And when the report comes out, I think you'll see that the pilot's probably
should not have even attempted that landing. So, you know, to say, boy, they're heroes, they saved
everyone's life. I don't think everyone was in that much danger. I think that just when it
comes down to good airmanship, they probably should have found an alternate airport with a runway
more situated for the wind situation. And we'll see. But again, you know, scraping a winglet is
not the end of the world. And the go around was performed perfectly. So, check that to thread out.
I put a link today at the top of curry.com to the comments as you can read along. And if you
are an airman or pilot, feel free to join in on the conversation. Hi, Adam, it's Brennan Jones,
Brennan Jones.com. Hey, Brennan. To the latest, they say, well, the nylon on the latest,
they say this morning. And he said on deposit protection with British banks and depositors,
and he protected for the first 2,000. Okay, this is from Monday's show where the nylon came
back to life and into our lives. Thank goodness, the New Yorker in London. And he explained with some
degree of authority that in the United States, the FDIC ensures your deposits at a bank up to $100,000.
But according to the nylon, in the UK, and of course, we just had a bailout of a big bank northern
rock for 50 billion pounds. That's a hundred billion dollars. Apparently, the insurance here in the
UK is, well, according to nylon, it was only up to the first 2,000 pounds of what's on deposit,
which, of course, makes a big difference for the, for my perception of the bailout. First of all,
although I would say regardless of the amount, if there's a cap on the amount, then that cap is
there for a reason. You should be ensuring up to that amount. And if it's above that amount,
well, tough cookies. But no, they bailed it out, bailed everyone out. And I understand their reasoning
behind it, still not agreeing with the amounts that have been put up as guarantees. But let
listen to what Brennan says about these insurance amounts in the UK. I'm quoting from FFSAA.gov.uk,
which is a financial services authority. And the quote is, with the UK bank, the first £35,000
worth of deposit is covered. It's not £100,000 or sorry, $100,000 is in the US, but it certainly
has a lot more than £200, just not laid out. Thanks, man. Oh, that's a big difference. So nylon,
if you're listening, I know you are. When you're done with the performance reviews,
let's hear back from you. Thank you very much, but I'd call in any time, man, when you've got
more info, you're very close to savonstatus, my friend. That was a good catch.
And now for something that hasn't happened at a long time, some sexy talk from NGB.
A crap. Let's try that again. Some sexy talk from NGB.
Hey Adam, it's NGB. How the hell are you? I decided to get caught up on daily source code today,
and I checked out your link to the demographic survey, and I was totally stoked to see the number
of your listeners listed the chill cat. It's indeed awesome. You know, I still get emails from
various men who said that they discovered me through the daily source code, and they still remember
the old days when you and I used to flirt. Oh, they missed those. But I had to feel like I'm
knowing things to tell you, um, well, one, I've got a gigantic collab of cats going on on the chill
cast this week, uh, 16 different podcasters pitched in with songs and audio in support of one of my
listeners who actually attends Northern Illinois University. And, uh, came out great, 90 minutes.
You should check it out. And, uh, the remix contest for Love Spiral Song, this truth is ongoing.
I've been getting some great tracks, including one that's already upon the Pots of Music Network
by the groove blaster, and, uh, I hope that you will like it. I'm going to play it for you,
and I hope you'll play it for the listeners. You bet your baby. So don't be a stranger. Love you,
mean it, and I don't have to say no home now. That's right. I do miss those days, Angie. Next time
don't mix the song in with your feedback, and I'll talk sexy back to you, baby.
Only thing, I wonder is what I hear. We didn't begin our lives, but still not. From the foot time we met.
Yeah, well, I have it all my wishes, it's precious. That's nothing but a side of it, no.
You'll never take away from that song, but it's nothing, so you can say no to.
Say go away, this truth. You belong to me, as I feel, I'll tell you.
Yeah, yeah!
The spirit will be a decade. With rubbing general hands of hell.
You tell any trouble, and I'll be free
Trust in me, yeah, but we're wrong, doesn't it?
We have never been there in the street
I don't think we're ever away
You, that doesn't seem to be my neighbor
I think love can't fulfill
She will never take away
From back to all that's nothing she can say
I'll do, they go away, this truth
That you belong to me, that still belongs to you
Yeah, you belong to me, that still belongs to you
Oh yeah
And you mean love spirals, wrapping up the Charlie 73-1
I, on today I'd like to send a special shout out to all the developers
The software engineers who created Ableton Live
The hardware and software engineers who created the FaderFox MIDIController
FaderFox.de
To the people who worked on the open-source program JackPilot
Which started over in the Linux world to the folks who make MIDIPipe
And of course to the engineers at Apple who've done such an awesome job of a core audio
The aggregate devices you guys rock my world
Wait until I put all this crap together and show you how I've
Strap everything you're going to love it
You're going to be amazed what's possible with all the technology you guys are putting out
And thank you to you for listening once again
I'm pretty sure I'll do another show tomorrow and on Friday
Looking forward to a football Friday
I still have a jersey Todd lined up
So he has the day off but I have one from last week
I'd love to hear your tracks send them in
Adam at podshow.com
DailySourceco.com
Is of course where you can find all the programs
Show notes on my weblog curry.com
Until tomorrow my friends live your life with passion
And as long as it lasts
Enjoy your freedom
Please
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
You