It is my desire if not my duty to try to talk to your journeymen with some candor about
what is happening to radio and television.
Our history will be what we make of it.
And if there are any historians about 50 or 100 years from now, and there should be preserved
the kinoscopes of one week of all three networks, they will find recorded in black and
white and in color.
Evidence of decadence, escapism, and insulation from the realities of the world in which
we live.
We are currently wealthy, fat, comfortable, and complacent.
We have a built-in allergy to unpleasant or disturbing information.
Our mass media reflect this, but unless we get up off our fats or pluses and recognize
that television in the main is being used to distract, delude, amuse, and insulators.
Then television and those who finance it, those who look at it, and those who work
at it.
I see a totally different picture to light.
I can't stand it, I know you're bleeding, I'm a sin of strength, this one I can't stand
working with, I've been here, because the crystal ball ain't so crisp and clear, so
warm and simple, and one the one, I've got this fucking boy in my side, oh my God, it's
all right, I'm telling you all the same, it's all right, you're new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new
new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new small, new, new, new year, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new,è£ for our
You know, I think it's exactly what the Beastie boys need, you know, a little more
ability in there, sabotaging the cooks, the cooks match with the Beastie boys, steady source
code episode number 755 coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gulford, we're
here in the curry manner up in the attic everybody how you doing another beauty full day, not
a cloud, it's all the nines cavo k, for those of you just turning into the show, that means
that all the nines is super visibility 10 kilometers and cavo k ceiling and visibility
okay.
Hey, I've got most of the, most of the hum out of the, out of the signal, out of the processing,
you know, yesterday I discovered by some chance that the DVI connector to my monitor is,
is the cause actually of a whole bunch of troubles, giving enormous static and I'm trying
to figure out how to get away from that, and a couple of different suggestions came in,
I really like this one that I got from Mike Ackels, just try clipping a ferrite ring to
the lead, these can be most bought at most radio-shack type stores, maplens in the UK ferrite
ring.
I've seen those, it's one of those kind of like the, you know, the big plastic bump that
kind of clamps over the wire, that's crazy man, it's not even touching the wires, it's
just around it and that should reduce it, so I'll go out later, if I don't go out
today, I'm going to go out early tomorrow morning, go to the, to the music store, see if
they have that there, otherwise I'll have to find myself a maplens pretty quickly, really
pissed off about this, I cannot believe that this is happening in our country, that would
be the United States that in this case, in an announcement, check this out, that puts troops
in their families in the middle of a political dispute, a Pentagon spokesman said yesterday,
this was Tuesday, the army will not be able to pay soldiers after June 15th unless Congress
approves an emergency war funding bill, they, they're not going to be able to make payroll
to our boys and girls, our men and women sitting in the freaking desert, and now the, and
you look, first of all, of course they're going to be able to make payroll because the money
will come from somewhere, we just print some up, but to turn them into such a political
tool, it's just about the worst thing I can imagine, and I am, I'm personally just outraged
by this, and so now, the Bush administration is using this, as I said, as a political
tool, oh, please, hold on, so go away, don't call me now, I can't deal with you, sorry,
I didn't have the phone near me, so I had to get up and silence it. Anyway, back to this,
so army payroll accounts are running dry faster than expected, if Congress does not act
by May 26, quote, will have to come back to them and ask them for permission to reprogram
money, check this out, reprogram money, so that we can take money from some of the other services,
Navy, Air Force, and use those payroll dollars to pay the army, does anyone else see how
fucked up this is and how incredibly wrong this is, I mean, how could we ever get to this spot?
All right, Congress, it's really down to you, as far as I'm concerned, you're the guys
they're going to have to show some backbone and come up with a solution, what's it going to
come down to? What is it going to be at the end of the day? I'm, I'm flabbergasted, absolutely
flabbergasted by this, flabbergasted, gobsmacked, that's the one. Oh, there's some other horrible
stuff I gotta tell you about, but, but everything that came in yesterday, email, voicemail, comments,
it's about the news, actually I'm going to, why don't I just roll this comment you'll hear about it,
because I love it when I'm right. Hey, I don't this is Richard and Claygate,
and that you'd like to be proved right of now and again, so here's another chance, and also time
for me to eat a slice of humble pie. The report I had today from Detective Chief Inspector,
meet Neville, the net police officer in charge of, I didn't let me help one of these,
the visual images, identifications, and detections office, that's called Unyard,
because rather disappointing that perhaps unsurprising verdict is that massive investment in CCTV cameras
to prevent crime in the UK has failed to have a significant impact despite billions of pounds
spent on the new technology. Ah, oh my goodness, you don't say. So wait a minute, you're going
to tell me that all of those cameras are actually not solving crime, millions of cameras,
billions of pounds invested, not actually solving crime. Uncobsmacked again. I need 3% of
street rubber President London was sold, using CCTV images, despite the fact that Britain has
more security cameras than any other country in Europe. And can you guess what a DCI naval
plans to do about this? Oh yes, I had more control over us to try and justify the massive spending.
He wants to build a new database of images, which is expected to be a technology developed
by the sports advertising industry to track them out into face offenders, put images of suspects
in muttings, rape, and robbery cases out on the internet for the next month, that's suspects.
And above the national CCTV database, incorporating pictures of computer defenders as well as unidentified
suspects. The plans for this have been drawn up, but on hold, well, that technology required to
carry out automators searches is refined. As much more on the card games website, but I thought
you'd appreciate this. Yeah, for now. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, ain't that interesting.
Of course, I know exactly what they're going to do now. So now they're saying,
we're going to build a database, which I believe is built on sports database technology,
where you want to find a certain player, so it'll be by characteristics, such as what he's
wearing. I think actually, I think those image recognition technologies are helped tremendously by
the fact that the players have numbers on their chest and on their back. But they're going to use
this to be able to track people doing bad things. That could be you. That could be me as well.
And I guess build up. I just, it sounds like shit. It sounds like an incredible pie in this guy.
Good luck building that. In the meantime, you've wasted billions of pounds of our money of
taxpayers money. And it's not doing anything. I believe the actual number is that all this money
has resulted in solving 3% of all of Britain's crimes. 3% think of all the money. Why
should put some more cops on the street, dude? And now I'm reading all these stories about this. This
is a big thing. Everyone's talking about this and everyone's really laughing about it because
it's just not doing anything. So you have choices here. You can, yeah, you can store it all in a
database. That's another billion-dollar billion-pound project to bring in Oracle and Microsoft and
other consultancies. And they'll all rip you off. It'll never result in anything. You could, of
course, alternatively open it up. Connect all these cameras to the internet. That will be an
interesting experiment. It would certainly be something novel. So we all could watch each other.
And thirdly, I don't think there is third option, actually. We sell the entire kitten
caboodle to Mark Burnett and turn Britain into a worldwide reality show. Something like that.
I'm sure it's going to be used to track down abusers of cannabis. Actually, for some reason,
I lost the page. I had it all cut up. I told you that here in the UK, Gordon Brown has said,
well, or at least the administration of the Labor Parliament has said,
well, you know, we're going to reclassify cannabis. We're going to turn it back into a
class B drug. Here it is. I've got it. BBC News. I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Jackie Smith, who is the home secretary, says, because of increased strength of some types of cannabis,
she wanted to reverse 20 blares 2004 downgrading of the drug to class C. It has to go back to class B.
And there's lies in here. Lies lies lies lies lies. Let's see. Miss Smith said
that the new skunk varieties, skunk varieties, which has been around for 30 years,
accounted for 80% of the cannabis seized on the streets and here this comes. And the drug was nearly
three times stronger than in 1995. Oh, could you please quantify that for me, Miss Smith,
qualify? And if so, tell me where to get some. Hell is wrong with you.
A little side box here on the BBC web page. Skunk. So called because it has a very strong smell.
I think cannabis is always smelled pretty strong. Oh, another factoid from your BBC three times
stronger than other types of cannabis. It's a lie. Quantify it. Come on. How do you can't even
measure it? Oh, contains much higher levels of the active ingredient, touch a hydro cannabinol
THC. Now accounts for between 70 and 80% of samples seized by police and six years ago,
it only accounted for 15% of the samples. Yeah, it's good herb, man. So anyway, let me just
tell you about these classes. That is a nice little box they put here. So class C,
which includes currently cannabis, tranquilizers, some painkillers, Gamahydroxybutyrate,
which is known as GHB or the date rape drug, the date rape drug is in class C. That's the thing
that you need to put in class A and ketamine, which I've never tried either, but I think that's
what they call special K essentially. It's a horse tranquilizer too. I've seen people K it out.
That's not okay. Cannabis has no business in that with these other, I think horrible drugs.
Possession of class C drugs can get you up to two years in prison or an unlimited fine or both.
Oops, an unlimited fine. And dealing can get you up to 14 years in prison or an unlimited fine
or both. Now class B, which is where cannabis is moving towards, that's where we find end
fedemins, things like riddle in and full codine, I have no idea what that is.
Seems like that seems more like class C stuff to me. If you want to go shoot up with
you know, steroids and shit, that can get you up to five years in prison or an unlimited
fine or both. Dealing is the same 14 years class A is where we find X to C, LSD, heroin, cocaine,
crack, magic, rub mush, mushrooms, and injected end fedemins. Possession up to seven years in prison
or an unlimited fine or both. Dealing up to life. Hey, hey, hey, hey. Well, I agree there.
But I don't know. And this doesn't seem like they've classified this properly. And of course,
the travesty is let me see if I can find it. The reports as a report that came out that was
actually commissioned by Gordon Brown, the evidence suggested a probable but weak casual link
between psychotic illness, including schizophrenia and cannabis use. However, in the population
as a whole, it played only a modest role in the development of these conditions. Council
chairman sir Michael Rawlings told BBC Radio's for World One, the strength of things like
scunk hasn't really changed very much over the last few years, but it's now more widely used.
The question of potency is a very complex area. Absolutely. This is just, just pisses me off.
Well, we'll just have to go with the flow, I guess. Let me see Jack calls in
some about the iPhones. Hey, Adam, it's Jack. I thought I'd update you with some area,
something within my area of savant expertise. And that being the iPhone, I heard you mentioned,
and I don't know, DSC, 1051 or two or something like that. You know, you're waiting for the
3G iPhone. And I can't report that at least in the area that I live on the beautiful sunny
West Side of Florida, the Apple Store that's nearby is completely out of iPhones.
Yeah, I've heard these reports. I've been reading them around that, and that's of course,
everyone, you know, that's fueling the speculation that the 3G iPhone is on the way. I think
Apple actually said that the 3G iPhone is on the way. And there's been some pictures that
popped up here and there. But of course, the first thing you want to do is get rid of all the
old stocks. So I think Jack has an inside line to probably an AT&T store, and that's what
it's basing is knowledge on, which is a telling thing. Here at the great Death Star Wireless
Communications Store where I work, we're kind of running low. We still have some, but they seem
to be being replenished. Hey, man, you run a low. You got some supply, baby. At a slower pace.
Yeah, I, I, when I was in Los Angeles, I had a couple hours to kill on Saturday before I had
to take my flight home. And I walked to an AT&T store, and I looked at the iPhones and I held
them in my hand. And I'm like, you know, I wouldn't mind just having one just until the next one
comes out. And it was really difficult. And that, you know, of course, they're already a hundred bucks
cheaper than they were initially worth to several hundred dollars cheaper. I resisted the urge, though.
And so it's probably gonna be Harrison. And, um, but you, man, seven and a half hours not being
a lot enough continuous usage time. Well, let me just quantify that because, um, I don't believe
cell phone manufacturers really are honest about how long their devices last on a single battery
charge. I've never, and actually the Nokia E61, I really gets me two full days of full blast,
whatever I need to do. And of course, I'm not sitting there doing seven hours worth of phone calls,
but yeah, I have phone calls that last an hour or two hours. Absolutely, conference calls all the time.
And I want to do it on a mobile so I can walk around. And that will pretty much just start to
delete the iPhone to add to that, um, that I have the Wi-Fi on and it's either searching or connected.
It, uh, it just, it can't hack it, dude. And, you know, of course, the minute you use the browser,
the backlight comes on, all the stuff that drains the battery. So, I really need a much longer
charge. I need something like the E61 eye. That really completes my day. On the phone, you're free,
can I? I mean, yeah, four hours. I was just getting used to talk time as a bad as long as
most cell phones last seven hours on the internet, getting email, making phone calls,
watching video is a long time. And, uh, by a car charger, you know? That's exactly what I
don't want by a car charge. That's what I see. Everyone with an iPhone has got a freaking car
charger. Oh, let me just plug in my iPhone because, you know, it's running all empty again.
By a battery pack. Yeah. Oh, by a battery pack. Let me see, uh, non exchangeable,
can't put a new one in the iPhone. The 3G one isn't going to last any longer, I wouldn't think.
Well, that would be a huge mistake. That would be a big mistake if the 3G phone was not going
to last any longer than the current iPhone. Um, but hey, that's just my little point of view.
And I had something else that I was going to mention, but now I can't really recall what it is.
It's the skunk man. Oh, yeah. You set up awesome. Yeah, up with the little blanky light
controllers, uh, and everything, but doesn't that with the MacBook Pro and the two controllers
and the software, cause in the microphone, cause like three grand? Just asking.
Have your mean great hair. Yeah, man. Well, what did, no, actually no, the most expensive piece
is able to live, which I'm using. That is about a $400 package. But damn is that good. From
Germany, I might add, then I have a sound bite, which I think is like, um, 30 bucks.
And I think I got an, uh, you can get more racks. I use that for kind of like a cartridge
jingle rack thingy, um, maybe 70 bucks. And then, uh, a couple hundred bucks for the fader
fox fader. Another fine German invention, couple hundred bucks for the winky blinky light. So what
are we at? Yeah. Yeah, you're right. It's expensive. Hey, cast blaster. Go check that out. 50 bucks
for your windows machine. It does everything you need right in right out of the box cast blaster.com.
As speaking of people wanting to get into, uh, into this audio stuff on the internet,
he's a radio guy who's trying it in. Hey, Adam, this is Brian Seabers from Appleton,
Wisconsin, listening to Daily Source code, uh, the iPod made in China. Yo, it's okay. Um,
I'm actually doing something a little bit different. Trying to go off top of a little bit. I'm, uh,
I've been following you since your MTV days, I'm 30. So, you know, I was, I was a young and
when you started, but I knew, I knew a bunch of other jack and the long here, but good, um,
love your hair. Um, and, uh, you know, I actually have a radio background. I went to school for radio.
Uh, tell me you went to the Connecticut School of Broadcasting. I love it. And I worked in radio
outside of college and all throughout college. And until recently, actually, I was doing a program
director morning show that afternoon show at an AM station, uh, which was interesting to say
the least, and I'm out of radio now, um, because hey, guess what, they don't pay shit. Did you know
that? Yeah. Oh, yes, I've heard. That's a big, uh, that's the thing a lot of people don't know about
radio. Yeah, particularly United States. It is, without a doubt, the lowest wrong of the show
is latter. Um, yeah, yet some of the biggest egos on the show is latter. And it's, it's corporate,
just like everything else in America is becoming, but besides the point, I'm wondering about this
whole podcasting thing. Do you think this is really the way of the future? Do you think that
radio will go away and everyone will just get podcasts? And do you think I can get in on it before
it's too late? Well, first of all, dude, there's always time to get in on it. Just start. That's what
I always tell everybody. Um, and, um, and, you know, and John C. to work, and I proved it just
just, you know, well, actually it's been almost, uh, it's been almost six months now. We do a
weekly show. We started from zero. Uh, didn't really even promote it that much in the beginning,
and it just took off like wildfire, you know, in that case, it's all about the content.
Well, I think we're referring to as the infrastructure. Well, there's two parts to it. One is the,
the actual physical infrastructure distribution of transmitters. Primarily, two people who have
radios in their cars. That's still a pretty big market. Yes, it's changing. Yes, we're
getting seeing more cars, particularly in the United States that include, uh, satellite radio receivers,
like Sirius or XM, or soon to be, of course, the same thing. Um, I, uh, I don't see that changing
very, very quickly. That's still going to take another 10 years, I think, before we really see a
big proliferation of that in cars. And by then, who knows if we're still driving, if we can actually
move anywhere in our cars. So that's part one. Of course, this, uh, a synchronous distribution
through podcasts, uh, really downloading and taking it with you is, uh, is a whole new market,
a market that was not being fulfilled, you know, a market that, uh, would not listen to radio
necessarily in the train in the bus, uh, in the subway on their way to work, uh, or on their
bicycle, etc. Um, so I think where it's going is, well, wait, there's one other piece of the
infrastructure that mainstream radio has, which is the advertising infrastructure. Okay, so their
ad units are known to the advertising industry, uh, their measurements are known. Hey, by the way,
what's up with the association of downloadable media? You know, they came out with this report that
we were all waiting for that was going to be perfect to explain to advertisers how downloadable
media works and how it's counted. What a piece, what a crock that was, huh? Well, a big disappointment.
I'm like, well, where's, where's something new? You know, they, all the, well, there's
server logs and a shut up. So that's the biggest problem is how do we get the money flowing?
That's the biggest challenge in general with, with content on the internet is how is it measured?
What ad units do you have? How do I measure my return on the investment as an advertiser?
Because that's pretty much the only business model that's there right now is advertising. Yeah,
sure. Um, if you have something specialist, I am sure you can get lots of people to pay you for.
I'm in fact going to play something from the kid from Brooklyn a little bit. I pay, I pay for
for his videos 20, uh, 20 bucks a year or some or $2 a month. I don't know what it doesn't matter.
I love him. I think he's funny and I can afford it so that that kind of works. I don't know if he's
making a living off of it. So yes, the answer is yes, start starting now, start quick, get in the game.
I heard you talking about mixing boards and things like that and the hundreds of thousand dollars
you must be spending. I'm just going to get a for that. But what are you, if that's something
that's at all feasible? If it's something that I should really look into because, you know, I got the
gift. I'm selling insurance now, which I'm sure will make a lot of your audience members cringe,
but um, and it's better money and for a lot less trust. You know, I get that gift here.
Here are my radio voice. Everyone's in a while. What are your thoughts on that work?
Um, I, I guess I love your hair. I'm, I'm newer to the show. So I don't know all these things
mean and I don't know at no home on me. And when I'm, I'm hoping that's not a whole
public. You know, starting as a home of public kind of dude, but I do hope you win. And I'm a,
I'm at least five times a week. I used to spend when the lady is working. You know what I'm saying?
No. All right. Well, we'll talk with you soon, man. Love you, bye. All right. So I should explain
a couple things here. For those of you just turning in tuning into this show. First of all,
um, this is a whole legacy thing. It's, say, the phrase is actually, I love you, man, no
home. That is the whole phrase has nothing to do with homeophobia. It's something I picked up
from Tony Price, Costas World, uh, Black America, uh, men say this to each other. And it's just kind of
stock. I love you, man. No home. It doesn't mean anything more anything less. It's, uh, it's a
typical American male macho thing. Which is just stock and hasn't gone away. Regarding the five times
a week, uh, I just got to bring this up again. I'm now posting it in the show notes. This is the, uh,
from the news report that, uh, purported that, uh, men who masturbated at least five times a week
have a much lower risk of, um, developing prostate cancer. So, uh, we track our prostate cancer
prevention quotient here on the show. I'm currently at two for the week. I am behind because I've
got to hit my, my number of five. So, uh, I'll keep you up the date. Don't worry. And hope to hear
you soon. I was some kind of show buddy. Thanks. Call it in. Hi Adam. Uh, this is Janet from New York
calling to explain what the problem with nuclear fission is. Um, we made a mistake with fossil fuels
by burning them and not worrying about what the waste product was CO2. We just kept dumping
CO2 and air without worrying about the effect. And we'll only hold now we have to worry about
global warming. Okay. This is, uh, about my curiosity towards nuclear energy. Uh, of course, we know
that it burns clean, uh, but it does leave a waste product. And, uh, that is the main problem.
I think it's something that is solvable. Uh, but I'm very interested in it. You know, and by the
way, let's just agree not to say global warming. Can we just say climate change? Okay. Uh, because
even though I'm skeptical if CO2 emissions actually as reported by the IPPC, which is also
disputable. If, um, if these carbon emissions actually do cause global climate change, I will say that
the reports now are, oh, as a part of the global climate change, temperatures are actually going to go
down for the next 10 years. And then, of course, we're all going to fry to death. Um, that problem
plus obviously is the 10 in front of our oil. So now we'll, uh, depend on nuclear power and just because
the product's fission are not green ooze doesn't mean that, um, we don't have to worry about them.
Um, when you split atoms, um, in fission, you're making way more radioactivity than it's just
before. Uh, and the, and the products may be attract the blocks of metal, but they're mixtures
of highly radioactive materials that we don't have a fucking clue what to do with. Okay. So we've established
a couple of things. It's very important that you understand that nuclear waste is not green ooze
that, uh, you know, like you might find in doom or, uh, or some other, uh, uh, you know, game where
you have nuclear vats hanging around. That is, that is, of course, the image that you're supposed
to have, but it's not that way. They are stackable blocks kind of like, uh, kind of like Lincoln logs,
you know. Now, um, I do not believe they by themselves are dangerous. I'd have to get, uh, uh,
nuclear rod in on the game here. But anyway, uh, it is stackable, uh, and disposable. Uh, but of course,
we don't actually know what the long-term effects of that are. And, uh, but we can measure radiation.
So if it's a meeting radiation, we will know that. And obviously, no one wants to be near that. So
um, what I'm kind of pleased to hear is that no one is saying it's dangerous.
And of course, there's a whole argument for that, you know, a terrorist attack on a nuclear
plant. And let's et cetera, et cetera, slamming a plane into a nuclear plant. Well, we have a
couple of them already. It hasn't happened yet. And, uh, you got to do something. Can't live in constant
fear. Um, but the waste is an issue. I agree. We've got to figure that one out. Um, the American
plan to storm a nuclear mountain is not working because a nuclear mountain doesn't want it. So
I would say that maybe a decision is a great choice of energy, but until we figure out what to do
with the waste products, we shouldn't be making any more of those attractive metal boxes.
Okay. I got an idea. I, uh, it just came to me. Let's put that on the moon.
And this also solves the other problem of giving a nuclear power, a new name. We'll call it moon juice,
moon juice, moon power powered by the moon. I love it. That should be totally possible. We should be
able to, uh, you know, we'll look at these shuttles are going up all the time, deploying a
billions of dollars worth of satellite equipment. You know, it takes some shit up that we were on the
moon, right? We were actually landed there, right? We actually know how to get back there, right?
And that's not going on there, but that's shit on the moon. That's out of our way.
Make it make that the Death Star and call it moon juice. Nice, friendly moon juice, powering your
life. Your life powered by moon juice. Uh, the other problem is the source. And I, I actually
know less about this, but my understanding is that much of the uranium in the world comes from
places like South Africa. So, to trade dependence on the Middle East for dependence on South Africa,
it's not exactly great trade. I think that's a fantastic trade. Are you kidding me?
Go look at the Middle East. Are they loaded? Do they have tons of money? Yeah. Boy, that could
finally give Africa its props. You're right, the yellow cake or whatever. I guess it does
mainly come from from Africa. You don't, you need a lot less than the other natural resources.
And by the way, thank you, Mother Earth, for giving us the basic building blocks of our moon
juice. That's nice to know. So, um, until we figure out what we can do with nuclear waste,
I don't think we should be performing any more fusion. Anyway, love is show Adam, love you,
I'll say it twice a week. That's not enough for your prostate cancer prevention quotient. Of course,
this is not really an issue you might run into. However, with you calling back in from time to time,
giving me your quotient, that will raise mine for sure, because that's hot just thinking about it.
Hello Adam Curry, you from the Netherlands, South Guy Ups. Hey, listen, we have an echo today.
Everything going great. This is when I first heard this. I'm like, what is you talking about
an echo? He's referring to his wife, South Guy Ups wife, they're pregnant, they're having a kid,
they had an echo, it lives. It's a little mini-sills guy or it's a sales bill. We don't know yet.
Everything, very healthy, everything, looking very good. We made it the following decision. You know,
once you get a baby, everybody brings along gifts. And most of the time, it's like
teddy bears or stupid Chinese created gifts. All these gifts, all the doors,
most of the time are created in China. So my wife and I today made the decision
instead of having people bring a gift from China, make a donation,
to a charity that will try to find out right now. So we don't buy $3 or $3 a year
of gifts produced in China. No, we use the money and we do some good with it. That's all.
See you later. All right, sales guy, you, everybody. Yeah, man. I don't know. I don't know.
Now, make sure you kid get some toys. I mean, you don't want to totally
deprive the little sales, sales weasel. I got more sales weasel stuff coming up for you.
I really, oh, man, there's something weird today. I don't know if it's just, is it my ears or
fuck, and let me play a song and I'll figure this out. Be right back with you.
I don't know. People are all around you. We're just in my eyes. I don't want it to be
leave you. The lies that I could see through, but I never got between you. I'm ghosting
your mind. The other ghosts in your mind. It's that you're right, that you're
always. You're always. You're always. You're always. Let it go. Now you're
way. You're always. You're always. You're always. On a day like today, I don't remember.
How beautiful of you could be to me. The colors that surround you, the
friends that come and found you, fits you up and crown you, the land of mine.
And I wanted to believe you. The lies that I could see through, but I never got between you.
I'm ghosting your mind. The other ghosts in your mind. It's that you're right, that you're
always. You're always. You're always. Let it go. Now you're always. You're always.
You're always. You're always. You're always. You're always. You're always.
You're always. You're always. You're always. You're always.
Like glam ghosting your mind brand new from the boys. So on the outside music network,
of course, Black Lab also featured in that billboard magazine article talking about this
obsessed. We did bum rush the charts here right here on the Charlie 755.
And we got something that is very typical American that I want to share with you. This is
the LA sales weasel. Hear that? They're coming in to get me. And you know, when we talk about
the differences between countries and you want to listen to something typical American,
this next voice comment is so 100% Yankee Doodle Dandy. It really defines, in fact,
you can really hear pieces of the DNA that do not exist in any other country, or I should perhaps
say any other country's culture. It is very American. And I love it. I just do it.
Hey Adam, hey, this is the sales weasel from LA. I'm on actually a little bit of vacation.
I'm going to visit my mom in Virginia. I'm traveling and pretty about me. Dude, I'm going to tell
you something. I talk. I talk a lot. I talk to everybody in anything. And every everyone and they are
wonderful dude. Our country is going to be okay. Our country is going to be just fine. We have
we have the best. And maybe we're going through some rocky times right now and pardon me,
because I haven't listened to DSC. I've been on some hotels with some crappy internet access.
So I just want to tell you, I consider your friend. I've been listening to hours of DSC.
And I love freedom. I love this country. I love every part of it. And there are so many
good people in this country that are doing right and doing good. And they are going to be the best.
And our kids, there is a 15 year old right now. There is a 14, 15, 16 year old right now
who is going to be take us to the level where we should be. And we've been eating a lot of
shit lately, a lot of shit, probably 20 years worth of crap. But America, you can count on it.
You can count on it because we are in us. It is in us to be Americans and to love this country and
to love freedom and to love all the good stuff and to have common sense. And I think once we start
agreeing on the things we can talk about, just, you know, what do we agree on? Forget about the
bullshit. Whether you're right or left, just agree. Just what do we talk about? Do we agree
on? Let's just get to the next level. And we are going to be okay. This country is wonderful.
I have been traveling and I needed this vacation just to realize again, realize again,
the goodness of families and people and all the great things that we have. This is the greatest
country God has ever put in any place. We are Americans, we will do okay. Regardless of who
the next president is, regardless of what we should try. What happens to us? This is a fantastic,
fantastic country. And I just want to tell you because I know you're a patriot. I know you care.
I know that all this stuff with internet is going to help us get to the next level. And when we get there,
we'll be thankful. We'll be thankful. Just as much as we're thankful for the people 100 years ago
and 200 years ago for making freedom alive. Freedom is the best. It is freedom. It is freedom that
I'll die for. It is freedom that this country was founded on. It is freedom. And we are there.
We will be okay. We will be fine. And I just want to tell you as a friend who hasn't listened to
your for a while. I just have been a great road trip for me. I just want to say, please add them,
so that I won't sleep at it.
about the high gas prices, the full prices and supermarkets,
but nobody does nothing today.
Nobody does nothing, a my time is Brooklyn.
If they raise the gas prices like they raise today,
100 cars would pull into that gas station
and we all start blowing the horn.
And we keep my hands on it on until a cops game.
And then we put our hands up
and tell the cops they're sticking us up.
Come on, fight for your rights for God's sake.
The politicians are watching,
they ain't gonna fight for you.
We gotta stick together.
Pull them fucking gas stations and keep your hand down.
And that fucking horn and wait for the fucking cops to go
and put your hands up and say we're getting stuck up here.
The same thing and then goddamn supermarkets.
Will they raise some prices over 200 fucking busset?
Get on it, K-C-E-L-I-N-S-N.
How are they fucking screaming?
And when the cops come in, just hold your hands up
and say they stick to me up.
These fucking red bastards, come on,
we gotta stick together.
We gotta fight together.
Show watching him, we're not afraid.
Anyway, they gone but it this is the big man.
The boys, the boys,
tell them people fight back America
and the big man's always happy to see it.
America, America, America, America,
America, America,
America, America, America,
America, America, America
America, America, OK,
Fris..
America, America, America,
violent gun,
immation of America,
what you got to do when we come on you now.
you're scared
the whole horse might own
VO switch to your
Øºelos, walk
from home, walk
get more
walk gaining
walk air
air
through
and walk
yeah
legally walk
oh, get out
Stop on fuck yeah, didn't work on yeah, for no fuck yeah, value, fuck yeah, we burn fuck yeah, fake did fuck yeah, sushi fuck yeah, fuck yeah, bro you fuck yeah, better be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah,
never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never been on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck. Yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fucking fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah. never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck yeah, never be on fuck
comes to global gasoline prices according to fellow
chucklehead Sergio Gasparini in Venezuela you can fill up your entire
car's tank for about three bucks the price for leader of gasoline
in Venezuela before the changing currency was 95 bullet of ours
one US dollars worth two thousand one hundred and fifty bullet of ours
so that's pretty damn cheap but i got an email from
Alexander Omoth and uh here's the ranking uh by cost of
gallon of gasoline okay the most expensive anywhere in the world
is Bosnia Herzegovina oh Herzegovina oh some might say $10.86
cents per gallon then uh let me see uh number three Norway 873 the UK
number four eight dollars and thirty eight cents per gallon
right underneath that the Netherlands eight thirty seven the
Netherlands of course has shell oil it just made five billion uh i'm
sorry it was nine billion dollars like seven or eight billion a
lot of billions i think of seven billion dollars in profit in this
past quarter alone not for the year in this quarter um
now at number one hundred and eleven
that's where the United States comes in currently listed on this chart at
three dollars and forty five cents so the cheapest in the world is Venezuela
twelve cents a gallon did the conversion there Iran forty cents a gallon
Saudi Arabia forty five cents a gallon and uh uh uh United States
amongst the number forty five on the cheapest list so uh i think we got a
way to go actually it's probably not a bad theory that uh we won't
really start seeing people freak out until it doubles in price and of course
my prediction has come true that uh the price of a barrel per oil is
going to be two hundred dollars before the end of this year of course that
all depends on who becomes president because things can go kind of
wacky once that happens and that'll depend upon what our new president
does in the middle least hey i'm tired i gotta go uh i'm gonna sit in the
garden with my wife enjoy a little bit of the sunshine the last few
rays here of the day as it is now four o'clock in the afternoon i'll
speak to you tomorrow we'll do another source code give me your comments give me
your suggestions for songs rants rays whatever love to hear it
until then please live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom another
fine medium presentation stick it in your ear
you