This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Delta's Yeracharly.
$7.16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I guess it's Adam Curry.
Tonight there's the only one thing to do.
Everybody are you ready?
Sing along now.
We're going to party like a rock star in a bunch of stiff bars.
Wake up naked in a hotel room.
So my TV at the window, smoke a bunch of endo.
And I've been to get my mind over you.
I didn't tell a phone for the wrap around my car.
And party like rock star.
After all the nights we spent
We could ring all the cows.
And all the parties I passed up because you didn't feel like going out.
I can't see you sleeping Tyler.
Didn't put up with crap like this.
But tonight I'm making up for what I missed.
I got a body like the rock star.
I hit a bunch of stiff bars.
Wake up naked in a hotel room.
So my TV at the window, smoke a bunch of endo.
And I've been to get my mind over you.
I didn't tell a phone for the wrap around my car.
And party like a rock star.
And all the parties I passed up because you didn't feel like going out.
Now everybody's excited to see me floating in the house.
And I have a realSAAr Jeep home.
All theRakes are in my wall, open all of them here.
Oh, a man who's watching me being killed.
And I got my nose open.
You know my dream kind of came true I was wishing for this song to go pot safe
wanted to happen as soon as possible I'm low in the hole it's an anthem
Oh my god that's a lot of it's daily source code episode number 716 coming to
once again from the curry condo in San Francisco California I'll be here I'll
be here all week y'all everybody before I head on home back to a blighty and
quite honestly I'm missing the girls pretty mighty major mega so I do one of
my favorite things this evening at six o'clock we pretty much done with all
of the meetings we had a nice day very focused kind of skated through lunch
there just a little bit because I knew tonight I was going to be having dinner
with John C. Devoreck I look forward to these evenings because we basically
focus on the food we talk a lot about the food and about you know John of
course is a major foodie we talk about the wine we go into great depth and
become real assholes about having to taste every single one before we decide
and what we're gonna have and then we have all kinds of talk just like no
agenda and of course if you haven't heard no agenda you can find it in no
agenda that I'll pot showed hot comp and there will be an excellent show which
I'm sure we'll contain information about our meal this evening and we'll try and
get that out on Friday otherwise over the weekend so straight into it today
this is it's this is a pretty amazing actually what's going on you know being
here in San Francisco I wasn't able to do my usual monitoring that I do of
the air waves you know as you know interested in what Chris Moiles has to say
particularly when he's talking about me and you know people always think that
a million people have sent me the link and luckily I've said many times
please don't assume that because eventually what happens is no one no one winds
up sending me the link I did get a link today and it was the only one actually
let me just see who it was from quick Gmail scan hold on it was from I
think David yeah David Graham and he even emailed me I'm sure someone has already
told you but you had a mention on Chris Moiles show this morning and even
gave me the time code fantastic and a link to the to the show now let me
set this up the right way please understand that disc jockies are a very
certain breed very typical type of person mainly very very insecure don't
forget that as a disc jockie now not talking about a DJ like DJ T. S. though
when I'm talking in the UK we would say presenter right a radio presenter a
host or just a plain old disc jockie some column Chris Moiles a shock jock but
doesn't matter you're a disc jockie you also play records very insecure
bunch mainly because we have to hop from radio station radio station you know
no gig really last longer than 18 months in the states we always joke about
disc jockies having a owning a you haul trailer because they're always driving
across the country to the next market in fact one of these days out football
Friday please remind me send me an email I've got to play WOLD for you by a
Harry Chapin because that is the quintessential disc jockie song so we're inherently
insecure because you know stations change format you're not the hottest guy there's a new
young kid coming in and you move around you try to kind of climb up the lowest
wrong of the show business ladder that's just the life of the disc jockie call me
crazy but it's kind of romantic and I love it and that's where I come from so no
different in the UK I'm sure I can definitely feel that and Chris Moiles of course
is he's a smart guy and he knows that his audience is not necessarily going to
continue listening to the wireless as they still tend to call it in the United Kingdom
because they're all listening to iPods and stuff on their on their cell phones and it's a
very you know it's a radio one man this is the cutting edge the most modern completely
in tune with the youth it's that's what the station is all about so Chris also is you know
he has his eye on this stuff in fact they do I think was a 270,000 downloads a day of the
podcast of the Chris Moiles show so they're into it and he knows where the future may be and
you know he's looking for his next run check so anyway so he had talked about me you know
actually you guys I guess I talked about him you guys called in and gave your opinions and then
he responded to that and then I responded and this morning he came back and he talked about
me so more and I wanted to share this with you because another thing about disc jockies
we're always communicating through our show the good ones I feel we're always sending messages
when we're in love with someone or when we're just horny for someone we'll play certain songs
and in fact at one point I had a jingle and the jingle and then I'm talking like 20 years ago
and the jingle in Dutch at the time would go and Daisy is for y'all in other words this one
is for you baby and of course there was no name mentioned so I could tell five or six women or
girls hey man I'll play a song for you on Friday and I'll let you know that it's just for you
and I play that jingle so anyway that type of communication so it's often and it doesn't
have to go with an announcement it can just go on set it's a song that's played and the message
just come through it's little things and there has been that this some stuff has been going on
on the background ever since you know Chris Moiles kind of came on to my radar I started thinking
wouldn't it be interesting if he left radio one and just it is podcast full time
and I'm purely thinking from a marketing I'm coming from a marketing place when I'm thinking
about this and that would be a lot of news it could really get a lot of things going I truly
believe what does he have six seven million people listening to him in the morning he could convert
at least a million people over to a podcast version of his show because listening to what he doesn't
necessarily have to be live and I think a lot of people well clearly already 270,000 people
are interested I think we could up that by three quarters of a million get it to a million
really pretty sturdy audience think about what it would do for independent media so you know I've
been in contact with his producers I tried to get him on the phone of course that's not done or
whatever show business bullshit so or maybe just you know I don't know I excuse me he's not picking
up the phone for me so I know I have to talk to his agent so I get super agent Keith to call
over and start opening some conversations and I'm thinking I'm just going to make it really easy
just just tell him and I've actually I did this before when I was interviewed
did I talk about that the other day with John I think Peter Day from in business
and he was contemplating leaving the BBC or taking the early retirement package and I tried
to hire him and I said the same thing that I you know I passed on to Moiles' agent like whatever he's
making double it just double the money whatever perks you know tally it all up just double it it'll
be worth it it'll be well worth it anyway so although I've not spoken to the man himself I think
he sent a me some mess so this is from the morning show now listen to the first thing he says
pretty interesting so the song is relevant I could have queued that up a little bit better I'm sorry
all right here you go
I like this record you can simple plan when I'm gone uh-huh did you hear that when I'm gone
now listen to this I want to play that for Adam Clarine uh-huh he's immediately honoring me
kissing the ring at the beginning of the conversation you totally guess I was talking about on the
show a few times before but I'm not going to get into it but uh he talked about me on a podcast
he did and then I talked about it on the air and then he talked about it again and it's it's this
bizarre thing right and I'm not even going to go into it but um I know for fact that somebody will
now send this link to him and then there's a good chance that he might play this again on his podcast
this is why I was chuckling earlier because of course that's exactly what's happening but of course
it could just answer the phone I'm talking about it so if we're gonna if we're just gonna do this now
he's gonna talk about me I'm gonna talk about him he's gonna play me to about him on his podcast
and talk about it then I'm gonna go on my show and talk about him playing me on his show
we may as well have a conversation so hi Adam how are you yes I'm very good Chris thank you and I'm glad
that we finally have this opportunity to speak because I want to make sure you hear the offer just
in case the message didn't come through loud and clear so if this is the way you choose to do it
no problem now he can answer that and then someone will send me the link but they did yesterday
of me and I was and then I'll we can have a conversation it's part 10 this isn't it just call it
yeah yeah yeah sure right I was really funny by the way Chris I know the BBC is really weird with
regulations and stuff but feel free to use any of any of this audio you know that's uh it's
under creative comments attribution non-commercial so you're good to go and talk about it but I
will now he so I thought about this due to the week I don't feel like I'm saying he was he was
slagging me off from blah blah so someone sends me a link of of him talking about me right
and so I'm a sensor and he's going he's playing the clip he keeps pausing it and jumping in
laying out like we do with clips and stuff and he's gone oh he's obviously been ego surfing
surfing himself and I'm like oh no I wasn't now I'll put my hands up if I you know if I was
he certainly knows what the concept is it's okay Chris it's all right we all do it
it's like whanking you know of course we all ego surf are you kidding I've got bookmarks
that's the only way I stay in tune with myself I'll I'll search myself everyone's the blame
I didn't see what's on the internet of course you were bothered but on this particular
occasion I wasn't so I'm listening to this yesterday in my flat and I'm putting it on a washing
up doing what I was doing and he's talking about me and there's a really funny bit where I'm
I said on our show I'm listening to this guy on his podcast I said I'm Korean he's calling me a
banker and all this stuff like that and he pausing goes I never called him a banker a banker and I'm
like right okay so let me correct he didn't call me a banker he called me the W word which
but I can't say it I've never said that I never said that that's really interesting
of all the things you can't say on the on the BBC you can't say wanker I mean I hear a lot worse
oh my goodness I know this is whole thing it has to be as the watershed and after nine o'clock
and that's when you can really open up and that's why big brother live is such a problem
and divina always has to say please don't swear you're on ITV live but uh wanker
come on that that seems pretty tame I'm actually shocked by that I think that's a perfectly
valid word and does not offend anyone because you know we all do it and I'm like
just the weirdest well like two children who have never met anyway he's American guy but turns out
he lives here which I didn't realize so he's based here all the time he lives here now
not just here I live in the affluent suburb of seri known as gilford so hi Adam all right
well go ahead yeah you should hook up for pod then yeah well let's do that now
I just play the sound effects of beer pour it and then class check it and then we when he plays
the back on his show and go cheers like a virtual night out hi Adam how are you me I'm not so bad
thanks for asking have a great show all right anyway so I just want to make sure Chris that you
understand and this is an official offer and I speak on authority we will double your salary actually
I I googled that the other day I thought that there was a isn't like 630,000 let me just see
Chris Moile salary that always works here we go okay so according to Wikipedia and we all know
Wikipedia is absolute gospel Chris makes 630,000 pounds per year I mean it's still obviously
an obscene amount but Chris I'll double the salary okay so that's what is that 1.26 million
and we'll build it if you don't have a studio at home we'll build a studio at home so that you know
you don't have to go you know you don't have to get up early in the morning you can do the show
kind of like if you want in the afternoon or in the evening or whenever you fancy whenever you
feel like it and well and in fact what is the term of your contract will double that and guarantee it
because dude you would be you're already major you would be legendary and and by the way it's got to
be hurting you that guys like Jonathan Ross and Terry Wogan for Chris takes how much money they're
making they're making so much more money than you and Terry Wogan shows up at 730 and leaves at 9
if he's there at all of course his audience still listens to the wireless and your audience Chris
is listening to their iPod so once again double and if that's not the right amount just bring
your pay stub and we'll double it and if you don't think we're not good for it first of all we're
making money second of all look at who's who our partner is in the UK British telecom look at who the
CEO is Ben for Vine he's a Dutch guy you know I know him you know I've done and do business with
them these guys are complete marketers they understand they'll back it it would be a cool Chris I'm
telling you it would be awesome and since you were so nice to play a song for me I'd like a
play a song for you the kind of song that you will enjoy playing that you cannot play now at least if
you can't say a whanker I'm sure you couldn't play this song you'll have one too
I take a look at my enormous penis and my troubles start a melt away
I take a look at my enormous penis and the happy times are coming to stay
I got a saying and I dance when I glancing my pants I end up feeling like a sunshine day
I take a look at my enormous penis and everything is going my way
I don't go in
Okay, that was just about the dumbest thing I've ever did sorry about that
Here I am throwing around big wads of cash and I can't even get the microphone to turn up
Were you reaching for the iPod were you thinking oh my god something broke something's not right
Well we all had that experience
Hundreds of thousands of just simultaneously did exactly the same thing all over the globe just consider that for a second
Let me see
Actually what I was doing as I was over in a Google notebook seen what else you guys have sent in
a little bit of political stuff. This is from Kentson Foster
Actually the email caught my eye of course because of the subject line often underused the subject line boy
Will you get my attention if you have the right subject line?
Subject thank you for supporting John McCain for president
That got my attention seeing as I'm not supporting him that's right
Kentson says that hypocritical scumbag who was always bitching about campaign finance reform
has decided to get matching funds so that we the taxpayers can fund his campaign
and then he also
Posted a link to a YouTube video of a John McCain at one of the caucuses saying he thinks we should stay in Iraq for a hundred years
Yeah, take that one
Interesting
See this is actually
Is this something I wrote down myself? I wanted to talk about
Davo and the or Davos I guess
How are you pronounce it in the world economic forum?
But I'm actually going to save that. I know people don't like it when I talk about stuff on on the daily source code and then repeat the same
Topic or get into it with with with John C Devorek on Noah gender
I want to keep this one for for Noah gender because I I really got something to say about that
Okay, some more demographic date actually that's kind of fun you've been a lot of human sending in
information on about yourselves
And Catherine says hi there Adam just for your demographic research. I'm 20 German and I'm working at a freight forwarder nothing fancy just work talking with truckers and lying to the telly man
Telly band no telly man when our containers are late again. Oh, okay
Listen to your shows since I moved to Hamburg last summer. Love your show great hair
Hope you win hope I recalled it correctly anyway. Have a great day. Dunkishon and Avita Zayn from Anca Anca
Anca
I want pictures
I got to get home to my wife. It's clear
See actually have a label for this. I saved a couple of them
Run through with a couple more just so you guys are introduced to each other sergio. However. I am 33 years
It's starting to sound like a like a porn site. I'm 33 years old and male
Says sergio. However, I might not be your typical listeners since I got to listen to the chuck through your relationship with Devorek
There you go as you can see from my email signature. I'm quite a bias listener
Born and raised in a Latin American country, but have an Italian background. Oh, he's a contributing editor at Devorek.org
Okay, make sense. Hugo. Hey, man
I'm listening to DSC 715. I'm 31 years old. I was wrong. I thought I was only 20 or 40 year olds. I guess we have the whole gamut
So here's the complete profile for statistical use only
31 year old straight male from Portugal married one daughter folder don't take any pills
Wouldn't vote for any of those U.S. candidates each and every one of them will fuck this world for the rest of us
Fuck this world for the rest of us do do do do do do do do do keep up the great show right here
Yeah, love it. Adam Rockstar John from North Charlotte North Carolina here been listening to your show almost since it started
Just wanted to send him my demographic profile after hearing DSC 715 34 self-employed graphic designer
Living in Charlotte North Carolina college educated income in the media and I guess not sure where I stand
enough to take care of myself and that's fine
Excellent. I just got a band on now. Oh, I got a lindi lindi dobbins.com. Okay. I got to check out his band
Maybe for the food bar Friday
And so there's uncle and that one Adam 30s. I was so wrong now. So the 30 year olds are coming out of the closet. So to speak
Even if I'm only from 1977. I often beat you at the hit test. Hope your dad's all right. Love you man
Meant it great hair. Hope you win even on the hit test. Tino excellent
No one in between another 30 year old Stefano
Italian and Ozzy national hometown Milan single ethyro ethyro ethyro
What's that ethyro
Hmm
Please let me know work in an advertising agency
Windows tolerating Mac user
Canon versus Nikon photographer red-pilled conservative politically. I'm living. I'm living oxymoron folder. Love you. I mean it
All right
Excellent and then of course amongst all of these people in the daily source code demographic
We've got our savants
Comedy strip
Hiya Adam cookery carry
So you caught just this week
Enhanced that you countries
Don't have to reveal names of people who are doing fire sharing on the internet
Because it is civil and not criminal case
So personal data is indeed protected in you
By the way, please pass my best wishes to jay carry jay carry your American dad who is now living in your hopefully
I hope he will get some well
Stay healthy you all
You
Dude CSB the TV in the background is not working for me. That's it was not helpful
I
Have been over served on good wine and good food
I'm overjoyed
In fact, it's really true. I came back to the condo really excited about talking to you guys and I can't wait to do it again tomorrow
And I'm really looking forward to the fubar friday because fubar friday for us here in San Francisco is going to be a special day as
V3 that's our our codename for the new stuff we're coming out with is going into alpha
So that means we can really start playing around with stuff for real internally at least and next of course is closed beta
So yeah, that's exciting
I want to leave you with with a song that I have played many times before on this program
That wasn't the one that stopped
This is the one I was talking about I think I've been playing this for the past two years and whenever you feel good
Even a way you don't feel good. This is the song that can bring you up
It's the latest of the new dawn
And it's a good day
We don't talk about the bad days
Every day is a good day
We are
We've got the summarized and shine just an other day in this life for mine
I take up the prep alone still took capacity. It's got to be a good day because it has to be
Touch out my arms I take a lot my worries that you've been aided no end of the possibility
For mine it feels my blood like I am I still becomes cold as I swing from the bottom of the store with time
I finally feel five days as you should be of my own design
No belong like needed when I rest sleep and dream I
Circadian rhythms are all that I need and I choose a bad day
And I don't choose the creep because you can't have a good day unless you believe
Every day good and bad are both here round to those focus on nothing but the positive snow
I don't want to talk about the bad days
We're my friend all the fact that we are here
And that makes the day a good day
And that makes the sun find the horizon long shadows reduce.
We're Britney beach and bосьers snow
We're sparkling with blue paint in the room
Is like this we come destroying the room
We're going to see the process
We're going to save the 300
And the lights are dark, it's our secret to dumbness
And they can keep the smartest
I learned about perspective between the close and the pharmacy
I've been the partner in the season of the harvest
They've just learned you still the seeds and I
Leave it the hardest
Every day couldn't bear it both
Be around what's in it was focused on
Nothing's up the positive so the good day
I don't want to talk about the bad day
Oh my friend, all the fact that we are here
To the naive city of Georgia
Oh yeah, I ain't alone go away
We don't want to talk about the bad day
Oh my friend, all the fact that we are here
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
a هي hasta la Band with me, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, yeah, yeah,
And I hope your day is going to be even better tomorrow if you're, uh, you know, Australia.
I hope your Friday is fine.
Thank you very much for listening.
Adam at podshow.com is my email address daily source code.com.
As we can find information about music played in the show.
And of course, links show notes can be pretty short today though.
I'm sure.
And, uh, well, I'll be back tomorrow, uh, bring you another one.
I hope you'll join me until then live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.