Delta Sierra Charlie 7-7-8
There's nothing more romantic than fantasy
And we can make the war on terror distract
And like videos and TV shows with scanily cloud winning
Covering with oil, rub it in like lotion
But at 16s and the skies and the battleships in the ocean
The voters won't notice
Tell them to eat or with this
Are you against us in the same breath over vaccinated
Our soldiers they'll want to believe these lies are true
To the point that even Cynthia McKinney with proof
We'll be able to convince them that there's a connection between the war on terror
And the Carl Hub will be able to believe these lies are true
As I said, all the vaccinate our soldiers
And hold their ammunition with radio active to you
Fear is the final frontier for defenseless
If it's logical, tell them it's senseless
She either with us or you're against us
It's all about confusion
Name it the Patriot Act
If it acts against the constitution
One man, one vote is a joke
You should be more concerned about your family being broke
Poof
Mirror
Smoke
Now watch me raise, spending and lower taxes
The answer to any question at the 911 Commission I'd ask is
We believe that stem cell researchers in the world
North Korea has WMD's translation
Time for Operation Iraqi Freedom
Sacrifice American laws on Baghdad, soil
Unmore from our investments in defense
And increase our supply of oil
The question is, how can we have it done anything about the genocide and the four
The answer is
We believe in protecting the same entity of marriage
Just give them a slogan, let's roll
We're gonna smoke them out of their holes
Watch the hands, watch the hands
And this hand, oh son of Bin Laden
And this hand, the world traits and are exposed now
I know you want me to get them for you
But the 200 billion dollar question is
How much is it worth to you
For me to allow my colonies and investments
And defense to work for you
Don't worry about what we knew prior to the fact
About the attacks
That's a distraction
Careland, look away from the oil fields
The important thing to remember is that voting for my opponent will get you killed
There's a connection between his election and your family's demise
That's why African-American voters have to be disenfranchised
Neon democracy means the electronic voting machine companies
Get to help us decide that way you can win the election and still lose
That's the new world order
Global economy, no borders, no sovereignty
With those cries, corporate democracy, true lies
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
And the next generation radio contenting my ears
We don't need not to dinging, dinging, dinging
I like to think I'm flying, dinging, dinging, dinging
On gas, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding
That'll carry
The children on the street, using guns and knives
We're taking drugs, and each other's lives
Kill any child or with knives and folks
We're calling each other names like drugs
There's people on the street
Get to see us from my kids
Yeah, that's what I said
Now there's junkies with monkeys, there's these
Who's such a new monkey's police
These leave these pauses, monkeys alone
They got problems and obviously ill
Man, there's a line on the streets
On punks, chopped up his head
I'm the only one who starts
She's his day health
Truths out he's dead
And that's why I'm singing why
Why is wrong with the world today
You got to think about it
You got to go think about it
Go think about it
That you got to think about it
You got to think about it
Afteriu
Obviously
Okay
And then if you ask about it
You got to think about it
You got out of it
My mom's second husband, who of course is now part of the family.
And I stayed overnight, hung out with him, where I learned something incredible.
I've never been into Pink Floyd and certainly not Roger Waters, and he's built a huge
wide-screen DVD system in the house now with the 5.1 Dolby Surround System and speakers
hidden everywhere and bass woofers.
He put on a live concert of Roger Waters and I was blown away because they have the subtitle
feature and I'm looking at these lyrics and reading a lot, I had no idea how political
these were.
I can't believe that it's been 20 years for me to get turned on to Roger Waters.
Definitely check, I should play that song.
I'll see if I can find it and I'll play it tomorrow.
I'm used to death, oh man, it fits so perfectly in our days today.
So I went off on Saturday then up to the Northeast corner.
That was another couple hundred kilometers and it's really fantastic.
It's not easy to find a spot to put anything into a Jaguar underneath the bonnet as it's
officially called.
Now this hydroxy booster we've talked about on the source code before if you're new to
the show.
It's essentially a pot of water that has electrodes in it, the pieces of rust-free steel.
Is that what it's called?
Stainless steel, I'm sorry, rust-free, stainless steel and you put a current on that, which
is the process of basically separating the water, which gives you hydrogen.
This is like a high school experiment, so nothing, no big there, right?
Except then you take a tube and you route that through a safety device called the
bubbler, which basically makes sure that hopefully this main device doesn't implode should
some kind of fire get shot back from the engine, but you basically hook it up to the air intake
of your engine.
And then the theory is, is because this is now being mixed with the air and gasoline mixture
that it's going to replace this highly explosive gas, which burns very cleanly, by the way,
a very low- if any emissions.
I don't think any.
It's like water comes out of it after explosion, after ignition, and I'm no physicist, I'm
just talking when I learned previously and on the day itself.
The theory is that it then will basically use less gasoline, less petrol, because that's
being replaced by this hydrogen.
And I know a couple of guys have installed it and they say it works and I've read all of the
negative comments about it, and of course there's people out there with MLM schemes for
selling these things.
You can make this yourself, like Guy, I got it from basically made it himself, florist
as his name, with some PVC tubing and some stuff he had laying around the house.
Now, of course, we couldn't fit it underneath the bonnet, so he wound up fitting it in the
wheel well, right behind what would typically be the mist lamp, which we remove.
Now, of course, that is extra special cooling onto the unit, so I very low probability
of anything happening.
But of course, more exciting is what it actually do.
And of course, it was great for me to, you know, to have to drive the 600 kilometers
back on Sunday to really get some measurements.
And I had already, and the way I measured was very simple, filled up the tank as far as it
will go.
Of course, that's where there's a fudge factor.
I'm going to say at least one liter, it's a 60 liter tank, but, you know, one at one gas station,
the pump may switch off sooner, you know, and I tried to really get it as full as possible,
so I could actually see some gas coming up in the tank mouth there.
Then you just drive for a set of amount of kilometers, I did 100, and let's just presume
the, the, what would that be, the tuck on, not the tuck on, or the speedometer is correct,
and it's a digital system, so it actually measured 100 kilometers, and then, or whatever
it was, doesn't really matter if as long as it's close to 100 just to make it easy,
and then I'd stop another gas station, fill it up and see how many liters I had to put in.
Presuming what the tank, what the pump is reading out to me is accurate as well.
Without the booster, I'm getting a 10.5 kilometers to one liter of gasoline.
Now this is an overall, which is pretty consistent regardless of what speed.
Now I haven't done any city driving, this has just been on the highway, and I've tested
two speeds, 130 kilometers per hour, and 110 kilometers per hour.
Now at 100, so when I switch this, the booster on, I do have a switch in the glove compartment.
At 130 kilometers per hour, there was an improvement, and actually about a 10% improvement,
as I went from 10.5 kilometers per liter to 11.6.
So a little bit better than 10%, I kid you not.
Now there's all kinds of stuff going on.
This is the first, the guys that I hooked up with, who have ever done it on an injection engine,
which of course also has a chip built into it.
I'm sure if we just messed around with a computer chip that we could get it to run
more efficiently, anyway, but just as a test, I then tried out at 110 kilometers per hour.
You're not going to believe this, 100, and I'm sorry, 13 kilometers to the liter.
13, do you realize how significant this is when you're paying a couple of bucks for, you
know, like four or five bucks for a, for gas, even if you're paying one buck, it's just
amazing.
Now, I haven't done any other tests other than the two I mentioned, because I did
actually have to get on the boat on time, but hopefully later this week, I'll have an
opportunity to try some town driving and see how it does.
Also, weather conditions can, of course, make all the difference.
It was very hot during these trials, so about 27 degrees centigrade.
Now it's much cooler.
I mean, it could give me better efficiency or worse efficiency.
I really don't know.
All I know is that according to this very simple test, which is the same way, I calculate
how much time I can fly, so I kind of trust the method of seeing, well, in this case,
I do hours for air planes, but now I did kilometers.
It actually works.
This thing actually works.
It's not even really surprised, you know, it makes so much sense.
Now, there's a lot of tweaking that can be done, and I'm going to keep you up the speed
as I progress with the trials, but I'm very, very excited that we've got something that
actually works.
So many people have said that you're crazy.
It can't, but I think these people are confusing efficiency with power efficiency,
which I'm sure it's not, because it's like pulling 30 amp pairs, amps off of the battery.
Just what seems to me, like a pretty simple physics exercise, you're just displacing
parts of the fuel flow with the different type of gas.
So obviously it's using a hydrogen, but the hydrogen, you can go for, you know, I don't
know, you can keep the thing on for probably 20 hours nonstop, and you won't have to refill
any water.
It's not actually condensating it out anywhere.
It's just producing hydrogen, fascinating shit.
But there's been, you know, today's show is going to be a little bit of a free wheel, because
it's just so much that it's come in, and I haven't even gotten through all the voicemail
comments that have come in, and I know that after when they show you guys definitely
have some stuff to talk about.
So I'll be doing that later on this week, a couple of things that did pop up on the radar.
This one was just phenomenal, and you see if I can, why can't I open this up for a second?
This is a, I was actually a boiling boiling story, and this just shows how crazy we've
gotten when it comes to, to terrorism, and well, you know, my favorite is security airport
security.
But now apparently the New York Yankees in case you hadn't read it, banned Sunblock at Yankees
Stadium to prevent terrorism on one of the hottest days of the year as well.
And then, of course, once you get into the stadium, a, a crappy Sunblock, SPF 15, a little,
you know, a little crappy bottle sold for, was it like five bucks, so you had to buy their
crappy Sunblock while yours was being taken away because, well, of terrorists, of course,
is this going too far or what, and that's, that's just nuts, and that's only the beginning.
Here's something that's circulating around the net that is quite disturbing.
Actually, I first got to it through, let me see.
There was someone pointed out to me, it was, uh, hold on.
Oh, I'm sure you've heard of this one.
If you're into some of the theory's project, Camelot.net.
And there was a link there to an interview that, uh, out there TV did with Lindsey Williams.
Now, when, uh, Lindsey Williams is the, uh, is the pastor we talked about.
There's a great video out there called the non-energy, the energy non-crisis.
He also wrote the book, and this is the guy who, um, two years ago, predicted that around
this time, we'd have four to five, um, dollars a gallon of gasoline, and he really went through
all the reasons why, and, and it was mainly because he says, look, the only people who really
control the oil price are, um, the, the world bank and, uh, other, uh, organization, similar
organizations, but primarily the world bank and the international monetary fund, and they do that
through a number of constructions, which he didn't really explain very well.
But when it came down to predicting stuff that was going to happen, that's why I love watching
stuff that is, you know, months or years old, he was spot on the money, and a lot of it had to
do with oil that we would have found that Alaska supposedly found that Alaska, uh, but we couldn't
go ahead and, and use that oil for ourselves, because that would break down the whole system of
Arab states, uh, selling oil to us and trading that in dollars, which of course is the deal that
Kissinger set up in the 70s, and which is, and enabled the United States to build up such a high
national debt, because that's all being purchased by, uh, by the Arabs as well. So, um,
May 29th, this interview on out there TV, uh, Lindsey Williams, first of all, his website
closed by the way. He says, uh, that, that happened under some specific threats, so he just, uh,
you know, he needs to protect himself and his family. But here's what he says, and I'm, uh,
a paraphrasing obviously, and this is on May 29th where he says this, the price of a barrel of oil
rise a little more. He said, $150 is what it would, what it should hit. Now, we came very close to $150,
about $14647. Then an announcement will be made of the discovery of huge oil reserves,
North, uh, Russia. Well, isn't that interesting? Didn't that just actually happen?
Didn't they just actually announce oil in the Arctic, which, of course, Russia is going to claim
part of and no one really owns it, but it's North of Russia? Yes. He also says that'll happen in
Indonesia, haven't had heard anything about that yet in the news. Now, um, here's his prediction,
these will flood the market with oil and the price of oil per barrel will drop down to $50.
Well, we're not there yet, but it has dropped down at least $20 more than 15% so we're close, uh,
you know, we're on our way down. Now, here's what Lindsey, and this, I mean, this guy's a minister,
a pastor. Yeah, he's not an economist. He's just a guy telling his story as he learned it and
is apparently he's totally clued into. He says that this $50 barrel oil will then bankrupt the
Arab nations who will be forced to dump their dollar reserves. Of course, I would have been the
same thing that would have happened if they opened up the oil in Alaska. Here it comes. That will
turn effectively bankrupt the US and America will see a financial collapse from which it will
take years to recover. Already on his way, I'd say the euro today is, uh, it's 63, it's 6.
Yeah, 63.5 cents to the euro. So we're moving up on $2. Am I saying that, right?
That gets out from confused. Anyway, it's almost at his low point. Let's put it that way. Yeah,
I guess we're going to be at the $2 euro if we keep going like this.
Then that will in turn effectively bankrupt. We are did that one following that will come.
I love this. The North American Union and of course, we'll need new money since the dollar
will collapse the Amaro. So if you followed along with a show or any area, you've probably heard about
the North American Union. I mean, mainstream has reported on this as well, which would contain
of Canada, North America and Mexico. And this, you know, this currency the Amaro has been mentioned
before. Additionally, Williams said that he was told something will happen shortly before the
election, which will ensure that McCain becomes president. So that's pretty interesting. And I
actually registered and I paid some money to be able to see this out there TV. Wasn't a video
into it was a phone interview. But then I got word of something that was not very widely reported,
which relates to the Pfizer bill, the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act and how that was handled
in the Senate. Now, I'm looking for a home on a second because this is drove me nuts when
all this stuff started to come together. Here we go. So Dennis Cassinać actually, he's the Democrat.
I think he's one of the only Democrats that Dr. Ron Paul likes. He made a big stink in a big
objection on March 13th because there were calls for a secret meeting of the house.
A closed door meeting. Let me just see if I have some details on that. As I said, I'm kind of doing
everything on the fly here. So I've got my links all lined up, but still got to get it all set up. Here we go.
This is where's this from? How think and post? Okay, that'll do. The house on Friday and this is
from this is March 14th. Okay. So this was about the Pfizer bill. And of course, this was about
as far as we know about granting immunity to the phone companies for essentially
conspiring with the government to place illegal phone taps all in the name of the war against
terror right after 9.11. And this is the thing that Obama said he was opposed to and then later
went back and voted for the for the new Pfizer bill, which as far as I understand,
gives the telecommunications for immunity. But the crazy thing was, is that there was a call for
this closed door meeting, which was secret. And so Dennis Cassinać objected, which gave him the
opportunity to get all kinds of information on record. And you can just go to YouTube and find all these
different different pieces. I mean, this was about 20 minutes of him talking and objecting and
really some good Donald info, which I have not seen anywhere on mainstream news pretty much the same as
the as what's going on right now with the impeachment trials. You know, just not seeing that anywhere.
So I guess we might as well expose that as much as possible. Now back to the 13th. So a lot of
senators said, you know, I'm not going to participate in this Cassinać said, I'm not going to be a part
of that meeting because of course you're held a secrecy and it's an undemocratic process.
This, by the way, is only half of this would be the fourth time in over 100 years that a secret
session like this has been called. So of course, everyone would kind of like to know what the secret
session was all about. Now coming out of Australia is interesting. A lot of news like this seems to be
coming out of Australia just recently and I'm not quite sure why and I don't know if I should be
suspicious or not, but I have read this in several different places. So you're going to love this.
So on March 13th, 2008, according to sources, so not saying that I buy into this and it's all the way,
you know, the way this has written just, you know, it's placed too much into all kinds of conspiracy
theorist plans, but it actually was not just information they were given. It was a scheduled plan
of events. Here's what apparently was discussed in the closed door session. The imminent collapse
of the U.S. economy to occur sometime in late 2008. So that does kind of corroborate there with
what Lindsay Williams is saying. Then the imminent collapse of the U.S. government finances sometime
in mid 2009. Quite honestly, that one I think we can pretty much see coming. I mean, we've
opened up the door for Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac and, you know, banks are going out,
literally, even though they've raised new money, their losses are bigger than the new money,
they've raised. I'm not making this up. This is in the financial times today. There's a huge issue
with banking. And now we're going from the subprime market to the prime market, which by
admission of the bankers themselves is, quote, terrible again, sourced from the financial times today.
So what else was discussed? What else, what other information was given in this closed
door meeting? The possibility of civil war inside the United States as a result of the collapse.
Because, of course, our money would be valueless in the rest of the world. I don't really know what
happens when the one currency collapses, but it's a can't be good. Then the advanced
round-ups of insurgent U.S. citizens, as you know, anyone could be called an enemy combatant
under the Patriot Act. George Bush and still that. So no, anyone can be locked up. So anyone who
was, quote, likely to move against the government will be locked up in here, comes the detention
of those rounded up at the Rex 84 camps, which have been constructed throughout the United States.
I've heard a lot about these Rex 84 camps. Never really seen any good pictures.
Talked about this with Johnson Devorak on Noah Gendo over the weekend, and he said,
you know, he was skeptical about that. So I don't know too much about him, but of course,
I've heard the conspiracies about these camps, internment camps that are just ready to take.
I guess, insurgent U.S. citizens board likely to move against the government. That would be
probably yours truly, my friends. Then the possibility of public retaliation against members of
Congress, because of the collapses, so they discussed the location of safe facilities,
from members of Congress, and their families to reside during massive civil unrest. And then
the necessary and unavoidable merger of the U.S. with Canada and Mexico establishing the North
American Union and the final point, the issuance of new currency called the Amaro for all three
nations as a final economic solution. So here's two different sources, pretty much saying the same
thing coming from totally different vantage points. Of course, I have no idea how this stuff
in Australia has been sourced, but you know what, I'd be no Australia. I like those guys down there.
And the gals too. So I'm sure that they're not just bullshit and around. It looks like some pretty
serious reporting is going on, and the someone is doing some pretty serious leakage to the press.
And maybe only the Australian press or the ones that will actually have the guts to print this
stuff. Who knows? We probably going to a hell of a hand basket. I mean, we seem like we're
going to credit cards and spend the rest of their lives paying 18%. Oh, I'm sorry. I hit that kind
of without an intro. This reminded me that I wanted to play a piece from a guy who I unfortunately
never met, but of course, passed away just recently. George Carlin on what I just called George
Carlin on the New World Order. It's just on something because 1250. And they didn't like it
when they got at home anyway. Not too bright folks, not too fucking bright. But if you talk to one
on about this, if you isolate one, I'm just sitting down rationally. You talk to him about the low IQs
and the dumb behavior and the bad decisions. Right away, they start talking about education.
That's the big answer to every day. Education. There's to be more money for education. We need more
more books, more teachers, more classroom, more schools. But we need more testing for the kids.
He said, oh well, you know, we've tried all of that and the kids still can't pass the test.
So I don't sure about that. We're going to lower the passing grades. That's what they're doing.
A lot of these schools, now they lower the passing grades, some more kids can pass.
More kids pass, the school will look good. Everybody's happy. The IQ of the country slips
another two or three points. I'm pretty soon. All you'll need to get into college is a fucking
pencil. Got a pencil. Get the fucking there. It's physics. Then everyone wonders why 17
other countries graduate more scientists than we do. Education. Politicians know that word
they use it on you. Politicians have traditionally hidden behind three things. The flag,
the Bible, and children. No child left behind. No child left behind. Oh really? Well, it wasn't
long ago. You were talking about giving kids a head start. Head start left behind. Someone's losing
fucking ground here. But there's a reason. There's a reason for this. There's a reason
education sucks. It's the same reason that it will never, ever, ever be fixed. It's never going
to get any better. Don't look for it. Be happy with what you got. Because the owners of this
country don't want that. I'm talking about the real owners now. The big wealthy, the real owners,
the big wealthy business interests, the control things and make all the important decisions.
They get the politicians. They're they're in irrelevant. The politicians are put there to give
you the idea that you have freedom of choice. You don't. You have no choice. You have owners.
They own you. They own everything. They own all the important land. They own and control the
corporations. They've long since bought and paid for the senate, the congress, the state
houses, the city halls. They've got the judges in their back pockets. And they own all the big
media, media, all the big media companies where they control just about all of the news and
information you get to hear. They got you by the balls. They spend billions of dollars every
year lobbying. Lobbing. So get what they want. Well, we know what they want. They want more
for themselves unless for everybody else. But I'll tell you what they don't want. They don't want
a population of citizens capable of critical thinking. They don't want well-informed, well-educated
people capable of critical thinking. That doesn't help them. That's against their interest. That's right.
You know something? They don't want people who are smart enough to sit around a kitchen table
to figure out how badly they're getting fucked by a system that threw them overboard 30
fucking years ago. They don't want that. You know what they want? They want obedient workers,
obedient workers. People who are just smart enough to run their machines and do the paperwork
and just dumb enough to passively accept all these increasingly shitty jobs with the lower pay,
the longer hours, the reduced benefits, the end of overtime and the vanishing passion that disappears
the minute you go to collect it. And now they're coming for your social security money. They
want your fucking retirement money. They want it back. So they can give it to their criminal
friends on Wall Street. And you know something? They'll get it. They'll get it all from you.
Sooner or later, because they own this fucking place. It's a big club. And you ain't in it.
You and I are not in the big club. By the way, it's the same big club. They used to be
chover the head with all day long when they tell you what to believe. All day long being
over the head of their media. It's only what to believe, what to think and what to buy.
The table is tilted, folks. The game is rigged. And nobody seems to notice.
Nobody seems to care. Good on us. Hard working people. White collar blue collar doesn't matter.
What color shirts you have on? Good on us. Hard working people. Continue. These are people
of modest means. Continue to elect these rich cock suckers. They don't give a fucking about
them. They don't give a fucking about you. They don't give a fucking about you. They don't care
about you at all. At all. At all. No. Nobody seems to notice. Nobody seems to care.
That's what the owner's count on. The fact that America's will
will probably remain willfully ignorant of the big red-white and blue
dick that's being jammed up their assholes every day. Because the owners of this country
know the truth, it's called the American dream because you have to be asleep to believe it.
Dead men don't lie. Okay. By the way, sorry for the erroneous sound effects there. That was
uh, something I couldn't change while I was running. Yeah, George Carla Man, he knew what was going
on. Boy, do we miss him? We could use him right now, although he's left us up quite a legacy that
we need to delve into continuously and not forget what he stood for. Did you see that YouTube
video? By the way, I'm sure it's been on the news everywhere of Bush, a recording at some private
fundraiser and he actually says, could everyone turn off the T.K. TV cameras? The audio
is shitty, so I don't even want to play it for you. But he sits there and he says, you know,
this problem in Wall Street is Wall Street got drunk and now they got a hangover and they got
us sober up. But housing crisis, there's no housing crisis. Loris is looking for a house in
was it either Houston or Austin? All right. So if you haven't seen it, go to YouTube,
visit the top of the list. This really pissed me off. That's the first of all, you got to,
you got to wonder, is the guy really so stupid to think that when he says, turn off the cameras,
turn off the TV cameras that people won't recording with cell phone cameras. Does he really think
that? Or is that or is he smart? Is he so smart that he thinks, hey, now someone's definitely
going to record it. Then I don't know. But if that is his explanation of what's happening right now
in the financial world, bring back the nylon Christ. It's not a case of Wall Street got drunk.
Usually he even said using those fancy financial instruments. My god, man, this is not what happened.
That's a vet. I mean, how the people who were sitting there in that room who were giving him
thousands, if not hundreds of thousands of dollars, do you think they're that stupid?
Which actually kind of brings me back to my thinking that maybe maybe he said this on purpose.
So that he could get this message out to the people that this is, this is the real, this is what's
really going on. Folks, here's George Bush explaining it to his buddies jokingly, that is not what
happened. This has been systematic and structural. And people have been warning against it for 20
years. How about Dr. Ron Paul? 20 years, the man's been warning against this crap. And here we are.
Someone's got to pay for it now. And you know what? It's going to be us. And then the comment
about the housing situation. Hold on a second. So he talks about Laura getting a house
for after they leave the White House. What happened to the Crawford Ranch? Which by the way,
he bought just before he moved into the White House. So this is a ranch where I've never seen
cattle or they're supposed to be a working ranch. What does he do? Move brush around.
Whenever whenever some dignitarious hanging out with him, wherever there's a photo up,
clearly this thing is just a prop in the whole game. It's not really his house.
Pop! So now he's going to go live in some huge house.
Well, hundreds of thousands of people around him are losing their homes. And his joke and about it,
just makes me want to be sick. Really does.
Hi, Adam and Matt from Gamesweasel. On this week's show, we review Sifra Smash Bros. Ball on the
week. We also take a look at the new Prince Casper game on the 360. We've got the brand new
Tomb Raider Underworld trailer and footage from E3 a Gaze of War 2. That's all at Gamesweasel.com.
Alright, Matt, thank you. That shows really taken off. By the way, if you haven't seen it yet,
check out the video version of Gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
So I have a trip to San Francisco coming up. And of course it's interesting. I'm going to be there
just as all of this stuff is predicted to happen. I could be picked up as an enemy combatant.
And honestly, there is a little twinge of anxiety in the back of my mind about being in the
states in August of September with all of these predictions going on. But okay, you know, so be it.
But I do want to try something new. Because of course, as you know, for the past 10 times that have entered
the United States, I've been stopped for secondary and tertiary search and discovery and questioning.
It's very unfriendly and unwelcome to have this when I'm going back to my own country.
Particularly because the Freedom of Information Act requests I'm supposed to ask. As per the
form, I was handed. Has resulted in nothing. I'm still on the database. No one can change it. It's a mess.
And now this didn't start until I got my new passport. Because the old one's basically filled
up to the brim, even got extra pages put in. And the new passport has an RFID chip in it,
which they always slide the minute they slide that thing into the reader man. It's like, whoa,
hold on. It's big stripe across your landing card. Please go to secondary.
So I'm wondering, is there a way to disable the chip that would at least be plausible just to see what
happens? Of course, you know, they'll have my passport. So they have to enter the number manually.
I'm just wondering if it's a separate system, if we'll make any difference.
But I have to have the chip not working. I know the easiest way probably is to throw it in the
microwave for 5 or 10 seconds. But that may actually burn a hole in it. And I don't want to do that.
So can I do this with a magnet? Is there any way that I assure fire away that I can disable the chip?
Just to see what's going to happen. And I'm going to have to get a new passport. I don't know who knows
what will happen. But something that at least is plausible. And let's test the system. Let's see,
yeah, let's see what comes of it. 10 foil hat wears out there. Let me know, drop me in a line.
Adam at www.mevio.com.
Hey Adam, how are you doing? I'm doing great. I'm sorry about Friday's number 131. Yes.
And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
Hey mate, I'm so excited to see what happens.
Creusy. Chris. Isaac. wag lid game.
Fight off the bat. Yeah, we didn't do a football Friday so we got to roll this out today.
Alright y'all number two. Number two.
Little crazy seal.
And this is number three.
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, see you see me as a factor, you're gonna make me sweat.
YAH!
What is this a 90's vibe today?
89, 90?
Probably?
Let's see how we did.
I'm going for six out of six.
And times seven, these are the answers.
Just...
Yeah, yes.
Answer number one is by Chris Isaac.
Game the hit test, though, which all the answers are from.
91.
14, 1, 2, 1 and 10,
saying what I have got to say floating in a bird.
What a falling in love!
Where do you all like that?
I'm sorry.
Chris Isaac can wicked game as answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
Yes.
This is seal.
Crazy.
Four out of six.
One number goes to life.
On.
We are a little crazy.
No, no, no, no.
On the left, we're a little old man.
Seal is answer number two.
Oh, I got six out of this.
This is answer number three.
Oh, that's out.
The CNC music factory.
Here is the goal.
That's worth the face for jammas life in a best.
And I don't waste time.
Or the mic will drop.
Dancing the rhythm.
Dance.
We're the music factory.
The CNC music factory is answering number three.
I'm going to make you sweat.
And that's it for hit test number 131.
So how did you do this week?
6 out of a possible six.
Rock in today in the 90s.
Alrighty.
The answer should just hit this.
And also the links to iTunes.
You can buy all of the tracks features in it.
The online have to be found at hittest.mefio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I'll be back for another hittest.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And remember to try to think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
Hittest at gmail.com.
info.
Unpolled.com.
BNBOLCT.com.
Yo.
All right, young.
Thank you.
I love it when I get them all right.
Hey, let's go back to the real world.
Shall we?
By the way, you know, people actually do buy those tracks.
It's all presented on the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
Upsal.org.
And people actually do go to hittest.mefio.com and and purchase the tracks.
It's g. It's a great system.
Instead of mucking around trying to track people illegally sharing your shit record companies.
Look at some new models, dudes.
All right.
I got some more cool stuff from the world of the used to be free.
Uh, this is great.
Headline as it's loading here.
This is from the telegraph in the UK.
Passengers at British airports to be fingerprinted.
Oh, yes.
The home offices border and immigration agency is confirmed that it's considering forcing airport operators to introduce the measures to increase security.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
So if you're traveling internationally, you'll have to be fingerprint fingerprinted at, uh, I guess he throw a
gateway, or even stance it.
And I wonder if international also includes the European Union.
Who cares?
It's another step.
It's just another step on the way to, well, whatever the plan is.
And this one was very interesting.
Um, if you like conspiracies,
um,
there is now thinking coming from the search and rescue team as well as the insurance company
who did an eight month probe into the mystery of Steve Fossett's death.
Steve Fossett, of course.
Uh, the aviator, um, who has flown around the world nonstop.
Uh, he took off from, uh,
the, uh,
Hilton, uh,
Baron Hilton's flying and ranch and Reno on the action.
My birthday.
That's why I remember it.
Uh, September third, uh,
what are we coming up on a full year now, I guess?
Or is it now two years?
God, I don't even know how long ago it was.
Uh, took off and, uh,
and was never found again.
And, uh, you know,
read some of the quotes here,
despite a massive search for Fossett and his
Velancas hitabria super to cathlan,
which is, uh,
uh, an airplane.
It's funny.
They mentioned something about this.
No trace of either has been ever been final tenant.
Colonel Cynthia Rhine of the US Civil Air Patrol,
who was involved in the operation from the start said,
quote,
I've been doing this search and rescue stuff for 14 years.
Fossett should have been found.
It's not like we didn't have our eyes open.
We found six other planes while we were looking for him.
We're pretty good at what we do.
Rhine believes Fossett, quote,
may have faked his own death due to personal problems
or fears about his business dealings,
explains the telegraph.
Uh, and then Lloyds of London goes on to say that,
uh, you know, they're stomped and, uh,
well, there's a 25 million,
fifty dollar,
fifty million dollar payout.
Uh, but he finds it, uh,
baffling and, uh,
that, uh, they haven't found either Fossett or the aircraft.
And he noted,
the superdicathlon aircraft is constructed from a steel and wood frame
and actually covered in fabric,
making it easy to dismantle.
Wow, there's a conspiracy for you, huh?
Just thought it'd throw that one out for you.
And, uh,
a good friend Ray is, uh,
is back in the fold.
And, uh,
it looks like he's got an item that he wants to produce,
I guess every week or whenever he feels like it for,
uh, for all you chuckle heads.
It's, uh,
it's kind of an ego thing for me.
I like it very much and,
and I really appreciate the work that's
Ray putting it in,
that Ray is putting into it.
And also gives me, you know,
a chance to play,
indeed a song that is the soundtrack to my life.
So here it is,
episode number two
in the soundtrack to my life.
1986,
here's Ray on the Charlie.
soundtrack to my life.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The soundtrack to my life.
Let's take a look at the landscape.
On a road trip through your life.
In his first decade in the Netherlands,
and after a time working in Dutch barric radio
under the A.S. John Holden,
and cut his big bragging broadcasting
as the host of the witty pop music television program
Countdown.
He also started several other radio and television programs
for the Dutch broadcast station for Raleigha.
In 1986,
Adam Scourier in the Netherlands moved
with two years from being a local kid
from nest on the host old
to an original celebrity in Holland.
And he parts of Europe.
He was living in the apartment in the south of Amsterdam.
The expensive area of our Dutch capital city
and Adam was breeding media and entertainment.
It was the year in which Adam started
a secret affair with the Lady Patricia
had to deal with the changes in his life
from being a nobody into a European
celebrity.
He performed on stage with his lifefox
and a meatball and co-miconjection
to give him some human advice.
Michael, could you tell us
you're in your accent?
You're in your accent?
I will.
I just need to go.
I will do my thing.
Do you have all your Disney characters
there with you in the tank?
I don't know.
I don't know when I before I go to sleep.
I put on my Mickey Mouse suit.
I'll come along, Adam.
This is no Michael Jackson.
This is what it was.
It sounds like my life.
And it was also the waterboss.
It was very productive and refined
the new sounding bridge rock and roll
the whole of the bridge is number 26.
The way you want me to touch up for you
and curse.
I'll dress you my body.
I'll dress you down and make you happy.
The way you kiss me.
I'll picture the rainbow.
You held it in your hands.
I had a flashes.
You saw the land.
I wandered out in the world for years.
But you just stayed in your room.
I saw the present.
You saw the whole of the moon.
You held out in your hands.
I wandered out in your hands.
You saw the whole of the stars.
And you know how it feels to reach too high.
Too far.
Too soon.
You saw the whole of the moon.
I was granted.
When you fill the skies, I want some boundaries back to you.
You cut too late, I saw a ring dirty valley.
Yes, I'll bring it to you. I saw the presents.
You saw a hole.
I spoke about wings.
You just flew.
I wonder that I guess that I tried.
You just knew I saw.
When you saw that I saw a ring dirty valley.
Yes, I'll bring it to you.
I saw a ring dirty valley.
You cut too late, I saw a ring dirty valley.
Yes, I'll bring it to you.
I'll bring it to you.
You try to find the stars, play the options for tears.
It's like a place, a rainbow, a city of the world's stars.
Every stranger's dream and vision, I'm gonna need the stars.
You can find all that I want.
When did yourselves leave you like it for me?
Lazing your chance, I am too far, too soon.
You saw a hole.
I'll bring it to you.
Thanks man, great way to put some more licensed music in the show under the fair use
doctrine.
Yeah, water boys, I don't know.
It's funny because that is definitely one that I'd like to put on the soundtrack to my
life.
I think it was kind of because we're in the middle of the synth pop, the Durand Durand
era of 1986 and all of a sudden here was this very melodic piano based.
It was a real radio record.
It sounded so good.
I love the lyric.
You saw the hole of the moon.
It's romantic.
It can be put in different contexts.
I don't really have a direct memory associated with it.
I have to say, except it was just a great time in my life and I was feeling great
and I wasn't loved.
Yes, with a lady Patricia even at the time.
Yeah, thank you.
Anything you guys put together.
I love to play that.
You're kidding me.
If you put anything you want and I'll use it.
Just try and keep it within reasonable length.
With the song is fantastic.
Really liked it.
Okay.
Just a couple more things before I get out of here.
Edgar Mitchell is an astronaut who was the sixth man to walk on the moon.
And guess what?
Again, another article from down under.
This is from news.com.au.
Not quite sure who runs this.
That's even a Murdoch thing.
I don't know.
Yeah, it makes sense, wouldn't it?
Well, anyway, on a radio show,
correct radio show of all types of programs.
How cool is that?
Dr. Edgar Mitchell who's now 77.
And you'll see a lot of these guys, if you look at the disclosure project.
A lot of these guys were getting up there in their 70s and 80s.
They're, you know, the now they're starting to just say anything they want to
because I believe probably their non-disclosures have expired.
But also they're nearly into their life and they want to get information out.
So he's part of the Apollo 14 mission says aliens exist.
He says extraterrestrials have visited Earth on several occasions.
But the alien contact has been repeatedly covered up by governments for six decades.
He says the real life ET's were similar to the traditional image of a small frame large eyes
and head or the grays, as they're known.
He went on to claim that our technology is not nearly as sophisticated as theirs.
But had they been hostile he warned we would have been gone by now.
It's just great.
So we've got all these people coming out.
We've got, I mean, is it just all the conspiracy theories are coming together at the same time?
I'm not, I'm not the only one talking about this.
I, you know, it's out there.
My daughter came home.
She said, you know, is it this party dad?
And there's this really, really cute guy who was a male model and thought he would be pretty
vapid and empty.
And also he starts talking about David Iken about the new world order.
And so, you know, kids are talking about it too.
I guess that's good.
I mean, certainly something's going on.
You can't deny that.
So now to have these guys come out and just one in a slew of many to say, hey, damn.
You know, there's something going on here that we should be knowing about.
And I'm like when it, the start on some of the stories that I've been hearing.
It's kind of confusing time from me, honestly, because I do think about these things.
And as I said, you know, I'm getting ready to travel and I'm thinking about could it really be true?
Could, could the dollar really collapse or will it be some kind of UFO visit?
Could that be staged by the government?
I mean, you know, you've got to be careful not going down the rabbit hole too far.
But just staying with the stuff that I kind of understand the financials, we're in deep deep trouble.
Deep Kim Shea is what I'd call it.
And then one other thing, which a chuckle had pointed out to me, and I'm still researching this.
You know, in this, for this is for the folks who live in the European Union,
but those of you in the States may be interested to listen how this works.
So we have this Lisbon Treaty, which was basically a rewrite of the European Constitution,
which was voted down by France and the Netherlands, who both had referenda on the topic.
So neither of those countries were able to vote on the re-worked version.
Basically, their representatives voted it in, ratified it.
This has already happened in 21 of the 27 countries, as you know, Ireland said no.
So this thing is off the table, but man, these guys are really trying to drive it home and make it happen.
And particularly Sarcosi, who is now the president for the next six months of the European Union.
And of course, President of France is really taking the seriously.
And he's trying to figure out how to make this go into effect next year.
Anyway, even if it means leaving Ireland behind in a so-called, you know, slow speed Europe.
So along with this document, our number of protocols.
And they're kind of like a denda.
You know, it's a contract.
This thing is unreadable.
I've struggled through it.
I've spoken to politicians who I can just tell by their answers.
Haven't read it at all or certainly haven't given it the attention they should have.
And particularly when you look at all these extra documents you got to bring in like the protocols.
And one of these protocols refers to another European Union, namely the European Atomic Energy Union.
Now there's only a handful of countries that are member of this.
But even if you go to the Wikipedia page and you look at all of the, all the treaties, you'll see that the European or your Atomic as in your European Atomic Union.
It kind of sits on top of all the other treaties, which means it's in effect for a long, long time and will be for a long time.
It was written in 1965.
So there's a couple of countries, you know, some of the big ones, including the Netherlands.
And I don't even, I think either France or Germany was not a part of it.
But it had like six or seven countries.
And the protocol in the Lisbon Treaty, which if it goes into effect, if it's ratified and whatever they figure out,
let's just say it goes into effect or once kind of acting as if it is anyway.
And this protocol will also become law.
And the protocol states that the members of the European Atomic Energy Union will have the following specific.
And it's specifically states that not only will the governments or the people working for the governments, the invaluable.
You understand what I'm saying?
So you can't do, you can't serve a warrant to search the government premises.
You can't look in the archives of government documents.
The people working for the government have many of this, including their spouses have many of the same privileges.
It's protocol number number 36, by the way.
I was just looking for a link during Ray on the Charlie couldn't find it that quickly.
But I know it by heart because I've read it so many times.
The really scary thing is that these same privileges now will be extended to the European Central Bank and something called the European Investment Bank.
Both which, well, the kind of like federal reserves.
So I mean, does this have anything to do with a democratic process where you are not allowed to look in the archives of your federal reserve bank, the European Central Bank?
Is that democratic?
If the people who work for the European Central Bank, like, you know, Trishay, which is kind of our version of Bernanke, if he can't be held accountable, how does that work?
Why does the European Investment Bank not have to pay any taxes on anything?
The someone's making money off of that because they're raising money in the capital markets, charging interest, somewhere someone's getting paid something.
So that's let's call that homework, my fellow chucklehead. So let's look into that a little bit more.
I got a quick upload to do so I'll search around for at least that link so I can get the show out before I have to hurry on off to London because I got another meeting.
Yeah, remember Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, living in two worlds. Yep, that's me. So I have something for my British friends who are losing more liberties every day.
Now, according to the Terrorism Act section 44, you can be forbidden from filming in a public place.
It's true section 44 and all the constables at their own discretion may invoke it. And so if you're filming something on the street, which could be a protest or could be just some cute girls walking by.
A police officer, a constable may come up to you and force you to stop that under section 44, the Terrorism Act. How do you like them apples?
So there's something else that happened very recently, which I think eventually will affect all of us in the European Union.
What you are and are not allowed to say to certain people, thank goodness we have Victoria Wood who made up a little song about what's going on.
Now, I'm going to finish with a couple of songs and I wrote this first one because I read this thing in a paper that said there was going to be an EEC ruling that we're not going to be allowed to use the word specky for eyes.
Like at work, you won't be allowed to call somebody specky for eyes.
Now, I don't know if it's going to be like being in a non-smoking building. I don't know if you can take them around the back or into the car park and call them specky for eyes.
But within a, within a work situation, you know, it won't be correct and it had a whole list of things we're not going to be allowed to say. There was specky for eyes, fatty, spotty, lardos.
And right to the bottom, I had this little word that I use all the time out of Africa. I can't use that word, how can I describe that sort of a person.
So I've written the song, sort of, gets me out of the difficulty, which just use the word in question. So I hope it doesn't offend anybody.
I don't mind if I offend somebody.
I never wanted to say nigg. No, I was never keen on pecky.
Or capital is lackey. I thought was rather tacky. It was never on my lips.
But there's a term I'm rather fond of, and to use it, I do hanker.
It's not hurting, cast a blanket. A little word is wanker.
As a term it's attitude. They say it's not correct. It's got to go. They say it's too dark.
Well, I don't know if it is never heard, then how convey. That very special word, another way.
He is a little self-abusive. His mits are always in his nicks.
He prefers to jiggle solo. He prefers his unlast roll-o-o.
To a bad of began micks. He writes for masturbation weakly, when opportunity occurs.
If you're buying him a present, his and hers things can be pleasant, but don't bother rapping hers.
I never wanted to say fault, face. I don't find our soul to appealing.
He depends with whom you're dealing, and it's just a personal feeling, but I don't like how it sounds.
But political correctness has taken hold, just like a kanker.
I don't like to nick a tanker and run down the stupid wanker who was put it out of bounds.
All right, it's not correct. I'm out of touch, but please reflect. It's so much.
Are there some other ways? It's such a shame.
Is there another phrase that means the same? His scrotum isn't used to strangers.
There are no condoms on his shelf.
When his tones caress and soften, when he asks you come here often, he's talking to himself.
He'll never need a bigger dress, book, because all his friends are in his flies.
I think may sometimes disappear, but it won't drag you around, Ikea, or by your polyester tie.
And if it's not correct, it's awfully cute.
I feel I'm afraid yet, a substitute, though it may make you squirm.
You find it strong, to use another tone, just take soul.
His favorite film is Brief and Counter. He has the tissue standing by.
He thought, get short, he was just silly. He was mad about free Willy.
And it's easy to see why. His wrists keep very fit and act too.
They'll never need to join a gym. He has no need of friend or neighbor.
He can toss without a cave.
Oh, together, lucky him.
There will be this full of different people.
Some are moral, some are hinnuses.
Some are ugly, some are like Venus. Some take photos of their penis.
We all have our different acts.
And as the world turns through a new day,
we know that bankers will be banking.
But this will be spiking.
No doubt, bankers will be thinking you and people basic facts.
Yeah, that's true.
The Victoria Wood and Wankers wrap up episode number 778 of the Daily Source Code.
Thank you very much for listening my friends.
I'm off to the wonderful city of London, where, unfortunately, our liberties are diminishing every single day.
But people are awakening. There's a big awakening taken place.
People are figuring out that, hey, wait a minute.
Just like George Carlin said, someone seems to own my ass and seems to be making me do stuff.
I don't necessarily like doing.
So please, my friends, live your life with passion.
And while it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.