Hey, happy, watch you do one.
Pearl, I'm listening to the brand new Pod Show Press audiobook from Bedtime Stories My Kids Love The Adventures Of The Men In The Can.
And these put all the adventures of the men in the can into a book.
And it's going to be published on Pod Show Press.
But don't worry, you can hear the first chapter of the book is a podcast.
We're going to find it.
Just go to bedtimestoriesmykidslove.podshow.com each week to listen to a brand new chapter of the book.
Wow, hey, happy, that's great news.
Hey, aren't you supposed to introduce the show?
Oh yeah, big hair, big show, big time.
Love ya, but no homo, Delta's here at Charlie.
Seven, two, one.
With 15 bags of squanders stuck in our pants.
Sugar!
And 15 bags of toilet paper hanging from our cracks.
We don't need no stinkin' sugar.
I like a thing I'm right.
For the future.
We're gonna hold on to his day.
He's very, very.
Sugar!
Hot summer, beating down.
Burnin' my feet just warming around.
Hot summer, making a sweat.
Gators never close, fuzzin' dark in the air.
I can dance, I can talk.
All the things about me, you're the way I want.
I can dance, I can dance, I can sing.
I'm just standing here, set up everything.
Set up, set up, you're telling me, you're driving love.
I've been sniffed at me.
Time to run, you're telling me, telling me, telling me.
We do sit on the beach.
But don't talk to me, but she's at the beach.
I can dance, I can talk.
All the things about me, you're the way I want.
I can dance, I can sing.
I'm just standing here, set up everything.
Set up, set up everything.
You're telling me, you're driving love.
I've been sniffed at me.
Time to run, you're telling me, telling me, telling me.
We do sit on the beach.
I can sing, I can sing.
I can dance, I can talk.
All the things about me, you're the way I want.
I'm just standing here, set up everything.
Set up, set up everything.
You're telling me, you're driving love.
I've been sniffed at me.
Time to run, you're telling me, telling me, telling me.
We do sit on the beach.
You're driving love.
All the things about me, you're the way I want.
Got to tell ya. I built up quite a rapport with DJ Schmolley over the past couple of weeks.
Of course, played his match me on Medeo, so on the Fubar Friday.
And start checking out some more of this stuff. Awesome. I love this.
I can't drop upside down.
DJ Schmolley kicking off episode number 721 of the daily source code.
It is Monday, February 11th, 2008.
Another beautiful day outside of the United Kingdom.
Blue skies, no clouds, almost no wind.
Again, what the hell am I doing here instead of flying around?
That's a very good question.
You know, actually I was very excited over the weekend.
Finally, everything came together on this quest that I've been on for.
I got to say at least four and a half years probably or four.
Yeah, about four years.
I've literally been trying to find the all in one, one box solution for recording
everything I need to on one computer.
And all I really want is I want to be able to just put a microphone in,
put headphones on and everything else should just work, all the routing, all the,
you know, all this external gear that I normally carry around.
Of course, the biggest problem was latency.
The minute you start processing your voice with electronic or software,
essentially, it then it builds in an automatic delay.
And this delay can make you talk funny.
So it looks like a combination of a couple things.
Well, the guys over at Apple, I got to give them big ass props.
No, let me back up.
I have tried everything to do this.
I've tried it with previous power books.
I've tried it with Windows machines.
I've tried it with external recording devices and audio hijack pro.
And of course, all of that eventually led when we started off in like 2004 before we
would encounter numbers on the show.
That eventually led to the collaboration with Mike for state that turned into cast
plaster on Windows.
That's the whole reason I moved to the Windows platform.
It looks like the guys in Cupertino have really gotten together with with the latest OS.
And with the, I guess the dual core horsepower that these new MacBooks have.
Because finally everything is there.
This whole concept of this, I guess it's the core audio team at Mac who put all this together.
The concept of aggregate devices being able to route through virtual devices.
Add onto that the smartness of the guys over at Ableton who make Ableton live.
Who have essentially concentrated 100% on speed and processing and ease of use.
And not a lot on the interface to very flat interface.
No spiffy knobs, no high end renderings of something.
It looks like a 24 track mixer or anything like that.
Lots of flexibility to build up the interface the way you want it.
Why the fuck is the dog barking while I'm talking?
It rotates me.
Oh, I know why it's the window washer guys here.
He's warning us.
He's not actually barking.
So everything now works inside the Mac.
I can route to Skype and back again.
External applications have to be fair.
I'm also using another program called SoundBiteBiteSpelt as BYTE as in a computer bite.
Which essentially lets me load up a whole bunch of anything.
Well, anything I guess, you know, MP3s, wave, AFFs, GS3 files that come off of cell phones.
You can just drop it into essentially it looks like a cartridge rack.
You can fire stuff up and you can pause it.
And that's it's a good program.
It's not quite the way I'd like it.
But it's certainly fulfills the main need.
And now I've hooked up the Yamaha workstation.
The Alpha Whiskey's 16 golf older listeners remember that one.
And I'm using it basically as a MIDI controller.
So now when I move the microphone fader up and down like that,
I actually, I'm not actually controlling the output of the microphone into the computer.
I'm controlling the live software.
And I actually see the faders move on the screen,
or at least the indicators that are indicating the fader.
So anyway, now I've found, I forget the name of it.
I found this beautiful little portable battery operated MIDI driven.
And by the way, is MIDI undervalued or what?
This MIDI driven six port fader bay.
So I can take that on the road.
And then all I basically need is that as an external device,
very lightweight, not a whole another computer to carry around.
My microphone, my headphones, and I'm done.
And it's expandable so I can add on another one of those panels
where I can just, I can map button so I could fire up songs
and little bits and openings and jingles, et cetera.
It's really come together.
So far, in fact, now I'm ready.
I think I'm ready, or just about after this kind of stabilizes.
I'm sure that it all works.
I'm going to go for one of these live situations.
I think that there's some good services out there
that offer you a phone bridge and you can mute and unmute people
and it's a chat room.
And I really wanted to give it a try.
Especially after hearing this comment from J-Mac over at hood hype.
I'm just wanted to check in and drop you a message.
You know, we did our first live show through Eustream.
We just did audio only in over the year.
And I tell you what, and there's something to be said about doing a live chat
and inviting people to call in live when you're interviewing somebody
right there.
And when you're spending music and you get live comments
of what people think, based on the people coming out
and dropping off, you can see real time what people like and dislike.
Because a lot of people are really too lazy to post a message on the blog
or to email, or you can call for that matter when you give them a free phone number.
Yeah, this is essentially the real difference between podcasting and live radio.
It's about the time driven nature of it.
When you have to tune in, there's certain time to get something
and I think J-Mac is going to talk about how that happens when you miss stuff.
You know, having people respond in real time, but also a finite starting and ending point.
You know, like this morning, it's like I spent at least an hour
ticking around after I got my perfect setup.
It actually wouldn't start up.
And I was so ready to pontificate too.
But this of course was because my Mac needed it's weekly reboot.
Very different from Windows, where it's a couple times a day
because something with the MIDI court server was all messed up.
And by the way, I still got to give props to the core audio team
because I've been messing with this thing for at least a week
and amaze that I hadn't had to reboot before then.
Anyway, let's check in with J-Mac again.
Let's see what he has on his experiences with doing who'd hype live.
Anyway, so which brings me to my next question.
I listen to Howard Stern religiously every single damn day during the week.
I get 30 minutes to listen to the show on serious satellite.
Luckily for me, they looped the show all day.
If I'm lucky, I won't catch it in the same segment.
I was listening to it on and I get 230 minute pieces of the 4-5 hour show.
My problem is, you know, I want to hear the whole damn thing.
I just don't have the ability to.
Well, you know, that's interesting because I think if you listen to Howard Stern,
sometimes he goes on very long rants.
And that will carry out a thread throughout those three or four hours.
But very often they regurgitate or repeat stuff.
Certainly every other morning show that I know over the United States does this
because the audience flips over every 15 minutes.
And honestly, I don't think it's necessary.
And you don't have to, I think you can get everything out in under an hour.
But of course, it's a little different because it's a live situation.
They're just passing the time.
They've got to do something.
So it is very interesting.
Sorry about that.
And I'm not quite sure.
Well, I got to think about it actually.
I got to think about if the Howard Stern show has changed dramatically
since they're on serious or not.
I'm sure that they were thinking a lot more about repeating certain items
and certain news bits when they were still on free to air broadcast.
So if I can put it on my iPod, you know,
via podcasts, subscription to iTunes or whatever,
that would be optimal.
But I'm sure there's advertising issues with that.
Copyright issues with that.
Yeah, obviously they can't be tracked and all that shit.
So my thing is,
it's all about the music.
That's the only reason why you can't,
and how much music do they play?
The Howard Stern show doesn't play very much music.
That's just the control issue then.
I think it's just because they don't want their shit out on the internet.
And it's probably a part of the contracts
so that it remains exclusive to serious.
Did you see the price?
You know, why can't we create something
that there's a happy medium between all of it?
You know,
I guess satellite radio would have to be free
in order for podcasting to be a legitimate medium
married with the satellite radio
because it doesn't work if the podcast is out there for free.
Yeah, there's an interesting article
on the financial times I read over the weekend about.
There's some shifts going on here
when it comes to infrastructure
because you mentioned serious satellite would have to be for free.
Well, unfortunately,
they don't really know how to sell advertising on serious.
The sponsorships, yes,
but real advertising spot advertising,
no, because they don't,
I don't think they qualify for the arbitron ratings.
That's what you need.
You have to appear in the ratings book
which makes it very, very complicated.
And on top of that,
keeping two satellites in orbit continuously is an extremely expensive business.
Same thing going on here with digital audio broadcast,
better known as DAB,
where this company has invested very heavily
in all this architecture and infrastructure
so that they can actually deliver
multi channels of digital pristine clear quality audio.
But the bottom line is
only 1% of all people have digital audio broadcast capabilities
in their car.
So unless the government says,
we're going to stop all regular FM
and AM broadcast which they will never do.
That's just not going to be the same type of
silo-driven pipe business model
that people have to have to listen to
one particular type of architecture in order to
be able to listen to it all.
Now there's just so much choice.
So when you look at the percentage of people who have an iPod
or other MP3 device,
I think it's pretty clear where the future
is going to be.
But it's open.
There's no restrictions.
There's no one who has the lock on the frequencies.
Or people are pirating.
They'll show out there for free.
Damn it.
There's got to be a way to do this.
So I don't know, man.
I think that's the battle with serious satellite
trying to get them to accept a free medium.
Now it's about money.
If somebody's going to be paying money,
why would they fucking pay if they're
can download it on the internet?
But the fact is that.
Exactly.
So anyway, my question is,
or my idea is,
we need to come up with something that
allows people to do it all.
Complete 100% freedom.
Podcasting offers that,
but man, if the live feed
that just has so many cool
extra things to it, man,
I love it.
I wish we could do it all, man.
I really do.
What are your thoughts on it?
I would really like to hear it.
I know it's all about sucked a man,
fuck bro.
Podcast media.
It's all about violence.
Sure.
I was bringing a whole hell of a lot
to a show.
So we'll look at what you're doing.
I'll be curious to hear your thoughts.
Thank you.
Okay.
Jay Mag, look at what you're doing, man.
You're doing essentially.
Although it's not quite streaming live
onto portable devices,
but it will.
I mean, it can only take five or ten years
and we'll be there and then the internet
will be ubiquitous.
You'll be able to pick it up
on almost any portable device.
And then you can do a live show.
The question is,
what is the audience really want at that point?
It seems that, you know,
live broadcast is still works on radio.
How many listeners did you have?
That's what I'd like to know.
So I think it can work both ways.
One is the way I do it,
which is essentially you call in
with your phone comments.
And we have a quasi interaction,
which of course is intellectually
not quite very stimulating for either party,
but I think it does work
and doing it for a while.
And then, of course,
the other way is to do a live show
that people who can participate
and I think you'll find that a
group will be able to tune in
and if you have some,
you know,
if you can set up a schedule for yourself,
we can do it at the same time every day.
Of course, for me,
that's a double whammy,
because you know,
I'd love to do it in the morning
or in the afternoon,
or the evening,
and one particular time zone
is going to be different
all over the world.
And the Charlie listeners,
just looking at that survey,
man,
we're from all over the place.
Anyway,
to be continued,
and right into something
I've been saving up a whole bunch of comments
about this is the
metered bandwidth trial
in Beaumont, Texas,
time Warner is doing.
And of course,
lots of people have opinions on it,
and let's listen to a couple of them.
Hey,
what's going on?
Hey, I'm your Beaumont.
This is David,
your friend,
and Bobbi, Texas.
Hey, David,
call you every once in a while.
You know,
the big thing is that we got
compounds now for eyelids,
and time Warner was through.
I didn't know they were still in the time
and the Beaumont market.
Yeah, see,
I've been looking for someone who lives in Beaumont, Texas,
so I can actually find out
what the metered trial is all about,
and how they're thinking of charging,
and is there a limit you get,
and then you pay over,
I mean,
all the questions that are just completely unanswered.
That's interesting news to hear.
It's metered stuff,
garbage.
I just read a pay for the highway,
and you know,
just get where I need to go.
Not a mean.
Uh-huh.
In fact,
we talked about that,
that very topic about paying more on the highway,
if you have a bigger rig,
if you're using up more of the road,
I eat,
if you're using up more bandwidth
or the only guy who can answer that
is our very own trucker time.
You know, Adam,
Tom Wiles here,
aka Trucker Tom,
trucks do indeed pay a lot more
to use the roads than cars or motorcycles.
Now, I'm a company driver.
I'm making wages just to drive a company truck,
so I'm not paying out of my pocket,
but I do know that the average truck,
and this is kind of an estimate,
is paying probably 15 to 20,000 dollars
a year.
Rolling drive.
Various fuel taxes,
road use taxes,
registration fees,
so on and so forth.
It's very expensive to operate truck.
One of the problems I see is that
it's inconsistent from state to state.
California, for example,
if you own a car in California,
it's going to be more expensive
than if you own a car in Arkansas
for where I live, for example.
You know,
if they could make it consistent
for the immediate bandwidth,
all across the country,
it might be a good system,
but what I'm afraid of is you
end up with different prices for different regions.
Something's going to have to be done.
It's going to be interesting to see
what the results are of the
experiment that they're conducting in Beaumont.
You can find my podcast at Trucker Tom podcast.com.
You can find my HD video podcast at Trucker Tom HD.com.
I'm talking also find my video podcast
as of February 1st on Tivo.
You can find me on the Tivo Guide.
You can check that out at TivoCast. podshow.com.
All right Tom. Yo.
You love you, me and it.
Sorry about the crackling there.
I've said my latency filter.
But I can't change it while I'm recording.
So if you hear a crackle once in a while,
do not be alarmed.
It's not the wire on your earbud.
So we heard last week from Belgium listener
who talked about his bandwidth constantly in the cost
and his situation.
Of course, I would venture to say that the infrastructure in Europe
and in the east and the far east is a lot better in the United States.
Of course, this is only US-centric conversation.
I am here during a long time listener since Episode 1.
I'm calling with some info about the meter bandwidth
discussion you were talking about.
Here in Holland, I pay 20 euros each month for a full limited data pack.
And usually I'm around about 60 to 60 gigs a month.
Wow.
20 euros for unlimited bandwidth.
Are you sure there's not little asterix there?
That says that there is a limit.
Check on your bill or your contract
and get back to me, man.
Because that sounds almost too good to be true.
And you've got 20 megabits down one megabit up.
Oh, I've got wood for your situation.
It's 20 down and one up.
So it's a bit cheaper than the Belgian guys.
A little democratic for me.
On the bus driver, a city bus driver here in Holland.
I'm 30 years wife two kids.
Yeah, just a normal guy.
I'm also trying to start my podcast called talking about being a bus driver.
Yeah.
I'm searching for info.
If you can help me do this.
And yeah.
Fuller rep deal.
I love you no homo.
I wish you a good day.
Hi, boy.
Thank you.
Yeah, let me know about your contract.
If it's really true that there's no, no cap on what you can use on a monthly basis.
Usually there's a little, a little fine print there that you got to take a look at.
But, you know, it's Europe.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Interesting.
The idea of a bus driver doing a podcast.
That what I would do is I would rig my, my, my set up there.
And yeah, I'm sure you have lots of interesting conversations with people.
That's what I would be doing.
I'd be recording that.
But then again, I'm not a bus driver.
Not everyone's happy with this.
All right.
I'm curious.
Officially lost your freaking mind.
About meter bandwidth.
Come on.
There's a big, big hole in your theory.
And the big hole is this.
The cell phone industry, which you keep using as an example.
Lowering rates and how it's much cheaper now.
Is suffering from competition.
There are four or five, maybe even seven major carriers of cell phones in the United States.
Yeah, but my friend, it didn't start out that way.
Now, did it?
It took quite a while for there to be some real competition in cell phones.
There were competing systems today.
There is still competing systems.
Well, you can't use one phone on another network.
And there's all kinds of downsides and competitive measures that it just took time.
You know, it takes time.
And I believe that anyone should at least have a DSL option, a cable mode of option.
And then why not even a dedicated line?
You know, like a local unbundled local loop.
It does take some effort, you know, depending on where you are.
Companies aren't going to set up unless it's going to pay off.
So you've got to create, you know, groups of people that say, hey, we're willing to look at an alternative.
That's how it works.
Competition doesn't just show up.
You've kind of got to work for it.
That competition drives down prices.
The problem is even in major metropolitan areas like where I live in Seattle.
I still cannot get anything but contest for my provider.
They will never drop my rate.
So you can't get a DSL connection through the phone line.
I had to find that hard to believe simply because they don't have any competition.
And as long as the, you know, infrastructure built on a wired system.
There's no incentive for competition because the output in order to run more wire is so expensive.
That unless you're 18T on East Coast and already have an infrastructure there, which they don't have here.
And there's no competition.
There's no reason for competition.
There's no incentive for someone to stream a new wire because it would be too expensive.
So therefore, meter bandwidth is only going to host people like me who have no other options.
I can't get DSL.
I guess I could get a cable or a satellite modem.
I had a choice in that, but it's not really competition.
Competition is what's going to drive down cost.
That's what drove down cost to the philanthropy.
Love you.
I mean it.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Love you.
No home.
Emma.
You know what?
It's very interesting.
You can't get DSL.
It seems to me like someone technically it should be possible.
There may not be another offering there, but technically it should be possible.
And I think that's where you have to go.
So in the meantime, I'm still trying to find someone who lives in Beaumont, Texas, to find out what's going on.
So if you remember, consider that maybe the reason why you're not hearing from anyone in Beaumont is because
the internet service is so expensive that they can't afford to download podcasts.
No, I hadn't considered it, but it's a good point.
I had a list of Paul and Littleton Colorado.
A long time listener called in a couple of times, I think.
I can remember anyways.
But anyways, I was driving home listening.
Episode 719.
We started talking about the bandwidth issues.
It was a limited or meter bandwidth.
And I had a question.
I believe that color from Belgium was saying is like a year old per gig over on that meter.
When I started thinking, if they started doing like a dollar here, for every gig over the, a lot of,
most consumers will think that's pretty fair deals, not knowing that they're making in the moment 90 cents.
On the dollar of profit per gig that you go over.
So just wondering if you think that's fair, if, if, I don't know if any, if anything can be done about that,
that's just my thought that they'd probably price it right around the dollar on an overage charge.
But I also was thinking, have you tried or thought of contacting someone directly from a well time Warner about the pilot in Beaumont since no one
from Beaumont has called or contacted you.
You know, that's such a good point.
And honestly, I don't think there's a reporter out there that has taken the effort that has made the effort to actually call time Warner and ask exactly that.
I know I certainly haven't.
We do seem, you know, this is a culturally very interesting.
We seem very, very much at ease to copy paste news reports and then add our own opinion and yell and rant,
actually do the work that it probably should should be put into something to affect any kind of change or getting information.
We're just a bunch of lazy bastards.
Man, you're so right.
Okay.
Does anyone know if anyone has actually asked time Warner about this G would a novel question?
Just be kind of interested to see if maybe someone from their PR department will be even willing to talk about this on your show.
There's a couple of thoughts.
See if I can get this sign off to incorrect.
Here you go.
31 Italian American losing hair.
Hope I win too.
And, uh, Guillermo Adam.
Yeah.
No, almost.
Guillermo.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate a good point.
How stupid am I not even think of that?
I'm going to hunt around on Google News and see if anyone actually spoke to a time Warner representative.
All right.
I'm sick and tired of this.
Oh, you know, I've always heard that Carmen Tyler has such a beautiful voice that she could read the phone book and make it sound good.
So I think that makes me a karma haul like I'm not sure.
With anger at the thought that Adam Curry wanted naked pictures of this beautiful perfect angelic pure Carmen that we love listening to so much.
It just angers me.
I got thinking, you know, you're real gift to all of us via these little podcast isn't just a cute half hour or so sweet fun chatter.
No.
No, the real appeal of Carmen Tyler is the positive spirit that you have, Carmen.
Even though you've never sent me the naked picture.
Make pictures.
I assure you.
You have the fuck.
Well, he keeps them to himself.
Because I know I would.
If I had naked pictures of Carmen.
That's K-R-M-Y-N-K-A-S-T dot pot show dot com.
Oh, indeed.
You know, I'm going out to LA.
I think in the next couple of weeks from maybe a day or two and I can't wait.
If I'm lucky, I can hook up with Carmen Tyler who's out there.
Sir, ladies from the pod safe music network, think you'll like it.
For it in love.
Oh, I think she's sending me messages again.
In a day, she don't know what to do.
She's late.
How he just moved my throat.
She loved and then he went away.
For then now she don't know what to say.
And don't go away.
And don't leave me stay.
I need you here beside me.
For then now to go away.
Night's my pass.
Without a word from here.
Walking down from this, the perfect scene.
This love was tainted from me.
For then now to go away.
She didn't stay.
And now you're here.
I wonder how she records that.
I wonder if it was recorded with the musicians in the room or she did this in her.
I have this visual of her creating this in her apartment on like garage band.
It says it's a demo, but damn it's straight up for me, man.
Carmen Tyler for bitten love from the pod safe music network.
And of course, you will find a link to that.
And everything else discussed in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Okay, Adam.
In the Jewish religion, there are two crimes that are considered unforgivable.
Murder and adultery because they can never be taken back.
I think the Carpander's mashup that you played in daily source code number 720.
Could qualify as a third.
Dude, that thing was fucking awful.
Okay, just plain fucking awful.
That thing, it's a musical abortion that needs to be a code hanger before you can play it again.
Now, I understand that some guy called in and he wanted to hear yesterday once more by the Carpander's,
which in itself is about as lame as Stephen Hawking on a stairmaster.
But you, you proceed to play this thing.
Now, I love the mashups on mashup.com.
I love the mashups you play. They're very clever. They're cool.
They kind of, they tickle various spots in my cerebral cortex that I find to be satisfying.
But this Carpander's mashup, you know what it's like?
It's like getting a blowjob from somebody's grandma.
I mean, it may feel good for like the first one or two seconds,
but then after that you're filled with more loathing than ten years of therapy can cure.
This, of course, is hypothetical. I've never been blown by anybody's grandma,
but I'd like to think I keep an open mind.
Anyway, please, just, Adam, repeat after me.
Okay, I hear you.
Please say this.
Okay.
I will never play the Carpander's mashup again.
I promise.
Oh, man, I got like 15 minutes and we got a sales conference call,
so I got to hurry to long today.
Hey, good response from the Brits over here about the Snoop Dogg Nation better known
as the British Surveillance State.
Although on the, when it comes to close circuit TV cameras,
this is very interesting when I'm getting back.
So, you know, this, this country, for those of you just listening into this thread
for the first time, is filled with wire taps and over four million cameras.
If the most watched nation in the world barn on everybody knows it,
Stephen East meets, says Adam,
generally speaking, I'm with you on your argument for the most part.
I'm concerned about the amount of bugging and lack of accountability there appears to be,
but I'm not quite with you regarding public CCTVs.
I was a magistrate, which is, is that a judge?
I think it's a, well, we'll find out.
I'm magistrate for many years, which encompassed both pre and post widespread CCTV use,
while I consider that there ought to be more regulation of CCTV.
I only ever found them very helpful form of evidence in a magistrate's court.
And this is exactly what my wife says.
You know, she says, hey, this is really good because, you know,
bad people will are on the watch out because they know that they can be identified by cameras.
And yes, that is a benefit.
The question is, it's, you know, it's not the cameras.
It's who's operating them.
And what powers are they given?
And what can they watch you do?
And it's, it's never ending discussion.
This is why in the United States, it's such a big deal that this is being,
being done.
This is the whole, the hell is the name of that act, the Fina or whatever.
You know, it's, it's nuts.
Because, yeah, today they're catching bad guys tomorrow.
Well, actually, today they're also catching you speeding by three miles an hour.
Yeah, now the CCTV cameras are starting to talk back to you,
telling you, hey, calm down over there.
I mean, this is big brother, no matter how you, how you look at it.
So, yes, well, sometimes it may be handy.
I just don't buy the argument.
If you have nothing to hide, what are you afraid of?
I like the argument.
I'm doing nothing wrong.
Why do you have to be looking at me?
I don't know.
We've told you.
We're probably going to be drunk this evening.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I am just walking past the practice.
It's a, I like getting it in recognition of it.
You need contribution to British cinema.
I'm on Monmouth Street, WC2 in London's West End.
Just having a little looking to 719, I think.
Talk about the CCTV or closed circuit television.
You know, this shit really does piss me off, but it is unfortunately necessary
when you have this many people squeezing to such a small space.
All absolutely stuck and jacked to the eyeballs on booze.
They tend to fight in the streets.
And it's just, it's not common to these galley to run around.
You know, Charles, and by the way, I love it when you're drunk.
I think we should be looking at the cause of all the people boozed up to their eyeballs running around
drunk in the streets.
Why is that happening?
This doesn't happen in every single city.
It doesn't happen in New York.
It doesn't happen in Amsterdam.
It doesn't happen in San Francisco.
This is consistently happening in London specifically, but I believe in every city around the UK.
Maybe we should be looking at the reason behind that and why that is happening instead of just trying to put a bandaid on it
by stopping drunk people from running around.
Shouldn't we look at the root of the cause?
Unfortunately, it is a bit of a necessary evil.
But I have to say, when those cameras started talking,
we're right here.
That was that it's spooky.
I mean, if anyone is interested in a red film moment,
they really want to get themselves a copy of brave new world by all this luxury or even better.
The word that I think you really should have been looking for was all well,
and you should read the George Orwell book 1984.
Yeah, good point.
Go reread that.
Go reread it.
And then go look at that Tom Cruise movie.
What was it?
I can't remember the name of it.
Something, something report.
You know, basically where they know you're going to commit a crime before you actually commit it,
and then they arrest you.
Okay, that may be a bit far fetched.
But go reread it.
Go reread 1984.
Go to the library.
Go to Amazon.
I'll put a link on Amazon on the show notes.
I'll put a link to the Amazon store so you can buy it.
Purchase it, reread it.
You'll see where the dangers are.
This is not new.
Okay, so I mean, the book you've been in the station to appear to use 1984 as a manual,
to keep you at all in a state of constant fear.
The very, very beautiful book, but really excellent reading.
I am myself having read them all in fact a bit of a blue book.
Although, yeah, you know what, this, the ID cards.
Don't get me started on that piece.
I'm snatched the chip inside my password.
Because I don't want to story all that shit about me.
So just have a number.
That's why I'm not actually on me.
Now.
Anyway.
Bye.
All right, Charles.
Thank you.
Richard and Clay Gates as a flash mob to protest our service surveillance society.
Which is what I suggested.
He said, when you've been the victim of a knife point mugging and seen the bastard convicted
on the strength of CCTV evidence, you might want to think again.
Ah, we really need some more red pills here, my friends.
Yes, that is a great benefit.
But maybe we go after stopping people before they mug you.
There's reasons behind that, too.
This is just a bandaid on top, which is trying to make you feel good while the same
time you're being frightened to death.
So you think that this is the right remedy.
Can't you see that?
Some of you luckily can.
Hey, Adam, I just want to say thanks very much for your show 720.
Brilliant.
Do you actually hit the nail well and truly on the head about the totalitarian state
that the UK has now become based on fear?
I reckon based on fear after seven, after 9, 11 with Bush and Blair screwing
us all completely out of fear.
Keep your scared.
Keep us under control and we'll accept anything.
And we certainly have in the UK.
One thing I suggest, you do, if you haven't seen it, is see a video called taking
it by Chris Atkins.
It's a brilliant video and it really explains Michael Moore fashion exactly what's happened
to us under the guy's of the Labour government.
Oh man, you've got to watch that.
I posted the first episode that's broken up in the ten parts on YouTube.
I posted that on Curry.com over the weekend as required homework for all British
daily source code listeners.
That is a fantastic piece of work.
In fact, I saw last night that it was nominated for a British film and television award
at the BAFTAs, a very boring show otherwise, but I was surprised and delighted to see that.
You've got to watch this thing because you'll see that protesting actually is kind of outlawed
in the United Kingdom.
It was surprising to me.
Certainly within one kilometer of parliament, you are not allowed to protest.
Want to protest somewhere else?
You've got to go watch this documentary.
You'll be surprised if you're living in the United Kingdom.
It is your duty as a Brit to watch that.
I'm not kidding.
And what they've done for us, they have completely removed our right to protest.
And that's the reason that nobody sees any protest anymore.
Because you have to apply to protest.
And of course they'll say no.
And if you go ahead, they'll of course crush it.
So yes, I think that the Labour government have done a lot of wonderful things for us.
But I can't think of one at this moment in time.
So many things you talked about.
You're absolutely right on about their heroes.
We've got the wrong heroes.
Football is being paid to ridiculous amounts of money.
They could actually pay for a hospital wing.
I think that's outrageous.
Dude, you are now officially my UK Savand.
You've got to call in more often, man.
First of all, I love the fact that you recorded this.
It sounds awesome.
I don't know what you're recording on.
You've got to send in more comments.
The media is stuffed full of footballers, wives, and trashy.
We call those distractions.
One of the three necessary tools of the three necessary legs of the stool of fascism.
Yep.
Keep them distracted.
In consequential news, what's wrong with the independent news?
Now, through I think podcasting is such an important part of the world information service.
We should be telling people exactly what is going on.
And certainly things like, are you aware that British citizens can now be taken to America?
By bounty hunters.
If you have a look at times online, the US and there's now clearly stated in a UK court of law,
that it has the right to kick them out of British citizens, accused of a crime in the US.
Horrific things are going on.
Of course, the government haven't protested against that.
Education, well, you touch a sore point there.
My wife was a teacher, and certainly there's a lot of things going on in education.
What people don't realise is just that the teachers are completely crushed by the amount of paperwork.
And they meant lists and targets that have been put onto them.
Oh, it doesn't surprise me at all.
I've seen the complete apathy of teachers in the public schooling system here.
Complete apathy.
I totally agree 100% that the Department of Education has removed all of their power.
And they can't discipline.
And they just have to hit too many targets.
And there's tons of paperwork.
Oh, I buy that for sure.
That's taken from the American Department of Education Playable.
I once again buy the government.
They don't get extra time.
And they've also taken away all their rights as regards discipline children and so on.
And of course, nobody will take responsibility.
These days, nobody takes responsibility for anything.
It's always somebody else's fault.
And if that's the case, that means they can sue.
So it's not surprising that kids don't protest.
They haven't actually seen a protest.
And when you consider you've got, that's a great point, man.
The only protest kids today in the UK of seniors.
When footballers walk off the field because the crowd is throwing too much shit into the pitch.
Three generations in this country now that have probably never worked in a family.
And they've lived off the state.
And then the state opens its doors to these Europeans.
They come in their cheap labor.
They're earning money.
They're sending them any back home and they're using our facilities.
Maybe that's why we're all drinking over here.
That sounds like a pretty good, nucleus core of issues.
And blocking up the hospital as they're currently doing at the moment with the Polish people, apparently,
filling it all in maternity wards.
It's a dreadful state of affairs.
I couldn't agree with you more.
I just want to thank you very much for flagging it up.
I think we should be protesting an awful lot more.
And the best protest I could think of is actually everybody by a t-shirt that says,
you work for us and then surrounding parliament on a busy day and stopping the traffic and just saying,
just a silent protest.
Just to remind them exactly where they got their power from.
But they've certainly abused that power.
And you're absolutely right.
There are what 20 or 30 cameras for every person in the UK at the moment.
It's outrageous.
So that's me, Sonny.
Thanks very much.
Late 40s.
Good looking.
No.
Still married.
King podcaster.
And that's Bob from the Idol Station.
Bye.
Thank you, man.
I love you.
No, homo.
Send him more, dude.
This is a great idea.
You work for us.
So we need t-shirts and we need to coordinate.
I think multiple flashmob since it is illegal to protest within one mile of parliament.
But this wouldn't be a protest.
It would be a quick flash mob and all of a sudden we'd have hundreds of people appeared with these t-shirts.
And then within five minutes, boom, we all disperse before the cops can do anything.
How cool does that sound?
Bob, you want to coordinate?
You want to rock and roll, man?
You want to have some fun?
I'm certainly ready for it.
Steven Lowe says, Adam, I have had my N-810.
This is a Nokia internet tablet.
Since they were launched in the UK, I love it.
Found all sorts of cool apps.
But apart from the video center app,
I haven't found a decent podcasting out the downloads directly.
Any ideas?
Muller?
What is it?
How much?
$4.47.
Wage slave, Birmingham, UK, White Mail.
Boston Air, Hope you Win, Kippertai.
Love you, and a Brotherly, Love, Hippie Way.
XXX.
You know what?
I posted a link on Curry.com,
just this morning to the candy men's Weblog.
You should take a look at that because he shows Canola,
which I think you'll like a lot.
Canola, I think version 2 is now odd.
I haven't had time to load it myself,
but it's a very nice interface for big thumb type usage.
and uh... i know that uh... previous versions of uh...
of canola have done podcast and quite well see might want to have uh...
have a check of that a wait a minute
what is this
what day is it
it's not friday this is weird
come motion to rock this mother out
your honor please don't bang that gavel
you can try this cowbell out let's all give a nod
to the hardest work and law here it's jersey time
yeah it's jersey time oh yeah
you're out of what do you say
you know how's going at i'm it is jersey time the official musicologist of the
chacha
hey dude i know what you're saying
of course you know it's not food bar friday
but over the time that i've been your official musicologist i do think that i've
built up some certain credibility some certain ability to come to you and say
dude dude i've got something for you that just absolutely blows my mind and some weeks
i simply can't wait till food bar friday to bring it to you
it's happening again to me this week sharing Miller out of New York
New York has a brand new five song EP with a brand new album
you're real soon that is absolutely all right man the stakes are high
possible to wear out a CD i'd like it done it with this one
check this out this song is called waste my breath i know you're going to love it i'll see
you on friday but you got to get this thing on as soon as possible check it out
sharing Miller out of the D.S.C
oh you lied you said you lost your family so well in 1993 oh oh oh
to when he's white and he said she was a photograph some apparition from your past
until i heard her voice a last on the land of his lab if you're still wasting her time
darling please don't waste mine now i'm always my breath on the rise
oh oh oh you're such a never finished school but the little hips is NYU oh oh oh
no no you're saving god father what you're doing brood where the one sees
but i have never seen your cry you can't smith deep your pony
and your crazy eyes I smuggle in I just wonder if this is William think of her last night again
If you're still wasting a time
Darling, please don't waste mine
I'm always my breath on the rise
I'm always my breath
I keep driving through traffic lights
Cause when you're alone, you believe every light
And I don't want them to keep you overnight
When she's the one being satisfied
If you're still wasting a time
Darling, please don't waste mine
I'm always my breath on the rise
If you're still wasting a time
Darling, please don't waste mine
I'm always my breath on the rise
It's at a James Beatles Otis running
She's got like 8 or 9 tracks up on the pot
That music never
I'm definitely gonna listen to some of the stuff she has
That's cool, waste my breath
Links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Okay, I got this sales call which started four minutes ago
So I've really gotta go
I'll be back tomorrow
We'll have lots more to talk about
I love you, I mean it in the home
Well, in some cases maybe
Hey, live your life with passion and please enjoy your freedom
What's left of it?
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear