Delta Sierra Charlie, 7-5-8
This is the daily source code
The daily source code
For $16 billion worth of airplane strap to my ass
For the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need not deep increase in
I like to think I'm flying into this journey
I'm guessing it's a crazy, good
To see you again, name of the way you don't record
Now it's me
Why haven't seen you since gone
Now it's when it looks like time still rings
You can't blame
I guess why I'm flying in the fields
And then it's another monkey morning comes
Why me up again
Once again
I've to think you know what this is
I feel it's gone
Now it's time to take this moment
But let's call you
On the way near
When I'm feeling
Feeling like I want you right
Feeling like I want you
Overworked and done
Dumped across my fingers
On the hole in the wall
It seems to me like you got it
But hey, I'm stuck in my head over the wall
But yes, why I'm flying in the fields
And then it's another monkey morning comes
Why me up again
Once again
I've to think you know what this is
I feel it's gone
Now it's time to take this moment
But let's call you
On the way near
When I'm feeling
Feeling like I want you right
Feeling like I want you
When I'm feeling like I want you
Going round and saying
Dumped across my fingers
But I'm going this thing
That I'm beliving
It's got a hold on me
Oh, I can't see
Feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel
it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, I feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feeling it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it
more about those guys. Hey, y'all. Hey, everybody. I do in Delhi source code episode number
7508 coming to you from the curry manner. We're located on the west side of Gtown here
in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford. Boy, you know, I'm feeling really good today.
It's not a spectacular day. Not as good as it's been the past couple days this week, but still
temperatures are nice, a little bit of wind, a little bit overcast, but hopefully it'll hold
up a little bit for tomorrow because I'm planning on flying. Basically flying Patricia's suitcase
to the Netherlands. She has another live show on Friday evening, and I refuse to go through
that whole rigour roll when I have a perfectly fine aircraft sitting at not 15 minutes away from
here going through the whole easy jet thing. Of course, part of that is actually traveling with
the luggage that's what makes it really tedious. I'm going to accompany her once again and I'll
take the luggage over and then Friday night she has that live show. So it may actually mean that
the food bar festivities might not take place. This is only going to last a couple more weeks,
but you know, I got to support the lady P and her show Biz and Devours. And of course,
last night we had our coming out party of BT Pod Show in the UK where it's still known as
as BT Pod Show, not mevio. Of course, it's a different perception of pod casting here amongst
the advertising industry and also amongst the audience. Man, we had shortage house, which is this,
there's no one flying over a kind of low. Shortage house, which is this really cool private club
on the east side of London, where you probably wouldn't be roaming alone at night, unless you're
actually invited into the club. And it was awesome. We had 200 people probably throughout the
course of the evening. Journalists from media and advertising and consumer. We had all of our
most, I saw a lot of our BT Pod Show talent and producers walking around, sea liberties,
de-lebrides, super agent Keith. It was awesome. It was really, really, really cool. A lot of people
said to me last night, you know, I know all about these types of things, you know, you go to a minute,
it's okay, but this is a proper party. So I was quite pleased with that. Of course, had to get a
pretty early this morning. I'm still working on seeing how well the format of the source code
translates to terrestrial radio. It's very interesting. People are getting into a couple of things,
like the voicemail, that's pretty novel. But also instead of Twitter, you know, in the Netherlands,
I don't think Twitter has the same type of footprint that it has in the U.S. certainly.
And what people do use text messaging. And so on this show that we do in the morning,
people can send a text message to a short code for two, four, two. And it's kind of like a
poor man's yet very expensive Twitter. I think it actually costs more money for them to do that.
Anyway, amongst all of this, my friends, I've really let my prostate cancer prevention quotient
quota slip a little bit. And this is, of course, somewhat concerning.
Hey, Adam, it's been on desert. You know, when you're reducing your risk of prostate cancer,
cancer, you're not just rubbing one out, you're trying to rub out cancer. Thanks a lot. Bye.
There you go. That's a slogan, rub out cancer. Come together.
This is a public service announcement. Good friends of the Charlie Madden. We must come together
in the place for prostate prevention, fill your five quarters every week. Pay for five
quadrups, even. Okay, dude. Oh, speaking of doing that show, you know, I query why the
using the, basically, 120 kilobits of bandwidth in total, 64k going out, 64k coming in,
which is basically what this ISDN connection does to the studio in the hay.
You know, and the latency is almost nothing. It's like 60 milliseconds. And you know, I thought,
first I thought it was the codec, because they're using an AAC, things the LDJs stereo codec.
And I thought that was the reason. But a lot of people, including, oh, wow, PWB sent me something,
Philippe sent me something. Everyone, basically, came up with the same. Well, it's,
let's see, Bob died actually. He didn't give me an answer. He said, oh, by the way, I love
the new sound. Also interested in your comments and ISDN wondering if your codec is Glenn Sound. No,
it's just the, it's the actual codec machine is a tail loss, which is kind of the tried and
proven system. Anyway, he's been listening since the curry castle days. But here's the,
here's the answer read this one from Philip. The reason for this is simple, because ISDN reserves
these 64 kilobit all the way from you to the receiver. Like this, you are sure that at any given
time, you will have 64 kilobit available on the internet, which is a packet based best effort routing.
You'll not have reserved constant bit rate pipe of 64 kilobits or faster, but probably some
hundreds of kilobit best effort routing. This means that you can burst until some hundreds
kilobits a second, but no guarantee on constant availability. So essentially, it's a different,
although we call it a codec, and of course it is being encoded and decoded, the actual connection
of ISDN is a guaranteed in total 128 kilobit circuit. And that's why even though I have much
more bandwidth than not available up and down, there is some buffering involved. And when I think
about really what's taking place that I have to say, the guys as Skype did do a pretty bang-up job
on that thing. It really does work well when you consider what has to happen. By the way, it
kept on ringing just while I was producing this show. And it auto answers. And I could see that
there was some signal coming through. The lights were going on. So I opened up the microphone,
which was still hooked up to it. It was BT calling me. For the third time I might add British
telecom, saying, would you like a free advertisement of this number in the ISDN yellow pages? I'm
like, no. But it was kind of weird because she came to the speakers, you know, she was thought
she was probably calling a digital office line. So she came through the speakers in the headphone,
and I was talking back on the microphone like this is indeed quite trippy. I wonder if I can make
a regular phone call to a regular line. Probably not. I guess it's only ISDN lines. I can call
unless I reconfigure it somehow. I'm sure that's probably possible.
If I do have time to do the Fubar festivities on Friday, it will be thanks to the brand new
microphone preamp that my father-in-law made. Remember, he's 82 years old and he's soldered together
a preamp that I've tested it only briefly. It is kick ass. It's miniature. It's portable. It
works in a nine-volt battery. Has perfect connector setups. Everything is just in the right
place. It's in, oh, man. And I hooked it up. And, you know, I got to do a lot of adjustment. Also,
he did some cool stuff with the adjustment knobs. They're sunken. So the ones, you know, you've kind
of set it all up and you throw it in your bag or whatever it has also. He made a little nice little
carrying case for it. So I would have a beautiful guy. The knobs won't move. So once I've set it up
for my sound the way I like it, I'll stay that way. And I'm very excited to test that on the road and see
how it does. Let me see. Oh, yeah. This was kind of interesting. You know that a lot of people
asked me, I guess I forgot to mention Christina Flunker driving test. Unfortunately, on the parallel
park, she had a couple of other minor things and the parallel park was in a weird spot. She's
really good at because I've practiced this with her a lot and she's good at doing parallel parking.
So she was disappointed, but she wasn't quite shattered. And, you know, I said, look,
you know, when you pass the test, then you'll be ready to drive and until you pass it, you're not.
But so, of course, now I have a Renault Twingo sitting out collecting dust in the driveway.
Hey, Adam, just listening to one of the ESC's and your mentioning your girl's new car, Renault Twingo.
I'm happy to report that actually all the Twingo that Renault makes are made in Slovenia where I
come from. Good luck with Renault Twingo. Cheers, fine.
Dude, well, thank you so much. I have to say the Renault Twingo is a fantastic automobile.
I'm very impressed with it. It's, you know, it kind of drives like you're sitting on a nice,
comfortable lawn chair. You know, and it's a zippy for its 1.2 liter. Of course, it's, you know,
five, five on the floor. And it's got, you know, the iPod connectors and all that groovy stuff.
It's good, man. Well, you guys in Slovenia doing some good work. Appreciate it.
What other cars do you guys make out there, I wonder?
Oh, okay. Let me see. When else came in. There's a lot of, actually, some stuff about Britain that
I want to, I want to discuss. Now, I think maybe it was Monday or was, yeah, Monday,
I played a call from James. James was not angry, but James was resorting to Charles and,
well, Charles is Charles, or Drunken Londoner. He actually phoned in two comments. One,
when he wasn't drunk, which he actually made a lot of sense. And I'm going to save that one
for a different day. But he called back probably a couple hours later, completely hammered.
And you know how much I love Charles when he's drunk. Hey, Adam, Highlander, Donald.
Oh, wait a minute. I'm sorry. We're going to get the Charles in a second.
First, let me do the Highlander down under because he's going to talk about Charles and about James.
Hey, Adam, Highlander down under here, calling in to sympathise with Charles, the Drunken
Londoner, over the scandalous decision to bail out your key banks with government bonds.
Charles did a totally failure frustration. And to James, who also called in,
it's not as simple as just voting these fucking leeches out. That would imply that the general
population have some idea of one. Outrage is actually is, and to want to act on it.
So this is, of course, relating to the recent mayoral election, Boris Johnson, the wacky one,
is now mayor of London. And Charles was not happy with that. I think if I got it right, yeah,
Charles was not happy with that. And of course, there's a lot of stuff going on over here,
like the bailout of the banks in the UK to the tune of $100 billion. Clearly, they don't know anything
is to what's going on. Charles's last comment was, what the hell can we do about this? And I believe
it only a way to get some movement for change is to educate the wider population as to what
all this finance-lingual means and make them understand the implications of a £50 billion bailout
and that they should be after these bastards in government for, well, for basically for
treason against the state and its people. Adam, you're broadcasting in podcasting, godfather. Do
know anybody in mainstream TV preferably independent like the BBC who would be interested in producing
a modern day, topical, informative and appealing documentary on how finance and money works
and an idiot proof fashion for the masses? You know, that's a great question. And actually,
I received some, a couple of people sent me a link to something called The Money Pool, which I've
not looked at yet. I think it's like 45 minutes or an hour. So that may be really good.
But I know exactly the person to do this. Maureen Goldthorpe, who is a documentary and she does
a lot of popular documentaries about popular musicians, sometimes celebrities. It's just
interesting people in general. She goes, travel's all over the world. And I met her
around Christmas time, I think, a super agent Keith introduced me to where she's a fantastic lady.
And I think she would be absolutely perfect. And I will definitely tell her that this is a great
idea. And so what she's independent, what she does is she presels the idea to either
to ITV or BBC or whoever is interested. And she goes out and she makes it. And she has such
reputation and standing that I think she can pretty much do anything she wants. I think it's a great
idea, fantastic idea. Of course, I got to think about a cool and snappy name to give the whole project
some muscle to it. So maybe you can help me out with that. If you don't, then I have the
left field idea. No, okay. Well, you got another idea. I love it. Go ahead. Sure if it would work,
but wanted to run it by you and the chocolate heads anyway. So my suggestion is to utilize the
listeners of DSC in some sort of distributed computing model to produce an end, it is guide to
modern money. If each of them or listener contributed say two or three minutes worth of content
on one aspect of finance, from essentially agreed framework, could be assembled into a money
podgymentry to be disseminated over the internet to the masses. Do you think that would make an
interesting social political experiment? If it were to be successful, I'm sure the eyes of everyone
in the independent media would be open to spending more time educating the wider population
into the collusion that happens between government and central banks to suppress our rights
and freedoms by controlling everything to do with money. So before normal, hope you win Monday,
yeah, Matt, Matt this week's question, educate, to protect and enjoy your freedoms,
mind, peace out, from each day and under. Keep on rubbing it out for cancer, my friend.
Yeah, that does sound like a very interesting social experiment,
but I think the need is pretty dire to get this running quickly, so people do indeed understand it.
And maybe a media or BT podshow can help finance some of it. Yeah, there's the will work
something out on that end. I'm also thinking Peter Day of the BBC would be a good guy to do
something like this. He actually does shows that he calls it podcast, you know, so this is
and I've been on his show in business, which also airs on, I believe, Radio 4, Radio 5
on the BBC. I like the idea, man, I'm definitely going to follow that up. Now, following this up,
let's hear from Charles completely hammered. He is our Charles, the drunken Londoner.
Hello Adam, is your John Londoner, Charles? I have actually been thinking it's time.
Oh, yeah, lovely. I am now home and I think my dirty chicken and I have finished my
beers at our melt at home and I want it to stay there. Oh, man. Everyone that you meet on the
tube that is drunk and disorderly, fuck them, fuck them. So this is a referring to Boris Johnson,
our new mayor and London who has said as per June 1st, it will be forbidden to have an open
container of alcohol with you in public transport. They're wankers. Anyone that you meet on the
tube that's all on public transport, they're drunk and happy, go inland. That's the way should be.
English people generally, they're happy and silly and fall about and just have a good time.
Unfortunately, there is a small bunch of people that they're aggressive and generally you can put
that down to just people with bad manners. But that's not what I want to talk about. What I want to
talk about is some of here I'm now sleeping with my windows open, some are happy like what to
drink. And I wondered, does anyone out there know about ball shaving?
That makes it every minute. Ball shaving, you say? I'm at this lovely local yarn, Aix supporter,
expert bullhood have been turned into a nice guy. He used to use one of those products that
dissolves hair on public hair. It's almost the metro sexual moment if you weren't so hammered
their Charles. You're referring to Vite, I believe, which we have discussed on this show several
hundred episodes ago. You can use one of these products, it dissolves all the hair. He said
anything below the way Scott has, even did his link, which I thought was a bit weird, but he tells
me that most German and Dutch men, with all of the whole fucking, sorry, swearing again,
I had come earlier, and I'm sorry about that, I don't know, on that last comment, the one before
the one that I just left earlier, anyway I'm rambling to come, so I'm just like, look, does
do any European or any Americans shape all of their balls and the whole cracking fact thing?
I'm a trainer, personally, I'm a trainer, I'll put my hands up, I trade, I like him to be neat,
I don't get rid of the whole lot. What do you love this anyway? I'll rambling on you, never say it.
Yo, I will do. Hi, Will. Well, okay, that's good for a survey amongst the chuckleheads. We
can certainly do something with that. I might even add it to the official survey, which of course
is linked every single episode from dating sourceco.com in the show notes. So are you a
shaver, a milter, a trimmer, or are you a wild one? Those are your four choices. I might
as we'll tell you right now, I'm a milter. Adam, what's going on? This is back in Vegas. Just listen to
the second episode of 55, the Bluewater Friday, and you play America, fuck yeah, I'm a team of
America. It's one of the give you a little slight correction there. Of course, that is
Traitor's thinking. However, that is the band DVBA, and you don't know what DVBA is,
the foreign term, and I mean, double vaginal double anal. If you see in the movie, or Gazmo,
they talked about quite frequently in one scene. And that's why I just wanted to give you a
little correction on that. So I'd like to know, all right, take it easy, love you, no homo,
and all that good stuff. Oh yeah, and my questions, please once a day, every day. So just like
another experiment, take care.
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel on this week's show. We've got a big review of GTA 4. I also have
a little go with Iron Man as well on the 360. There's a great new tech demo of the alone in the
dark game, the brand new one, and you can win copies of Speed Race, it'll fall the week. That's all
it gamesweasel.com.
Just what is it that you want to do? We want to be free, we want to be free too, to do what we want to do,
and we want to get loaded, and we want to have a good time. And that's what we're going to do.
We're going to have a good time. We're going to have the party.
So we want to be free, we want to be free.
We want to be free too, to do what we want to do, to do what we want to do, to do what we want to do,
to do what we want to do, to do what we want to do, to do what we want to do, to do what we want to do,
to do what we want to do, to do what we want to do, I want to be free too, to do what we want to do,
Just what is it that you want to do?
I'm gonna get tips out, tips out, I'm gonna get tips out, tips out.
Hey!
We want to be more free to do what we want to do.
You want to be more serious and more free to do what we want to do.
We want to be more children.
We want to be less Sydney because I am now in isolation.
I have some time to do my part of these things.
I have one.
What is the fundamental role in working around environmental wealth?
give them a silver platter or do tell you know we can all just make the claim that this
new killer stuff that he's talking about all that stuff that stuff the rusty
are playing with it's your noble that's a new killer stuff and a good stuff now
that's the new clear that's the nice stuff we want people to talk to a lot of
people pronounce it right maybe maybe we'll be able to rebrand that and if you go
with the right pronunciation I have a suggestion here if you break down the
word into two parts of the first syllable new new is good people like new
so we can go with the whole new thing know what that whole new thing and
the second syllable well if you just felt like is pronounced it's the word
clear it's clear and clear is good we like clear I really like clear this
clear is clear carbon there you go it's new and it's clear of carbon that's new
clear there you go my god and you are a genius I love this new clear new
clear powered by new clear new clear this bus powered by clean new clear
energy yeah sounds good man I think you're on to something here I'm learning
right there I really don't know if that's getting one going to fall for that
but hey who cares if I could come up with let's see 42 single not curling
any kind of relationship and because I'm single and not curling any kind of
relationship here comes I'm not a big problem I love you I'll be right here
blah blah blah and I'll hold her oh yes I love you know you can trust me
because I'm a folder right on I love it man good later new clear thank you so much
what a great idea okay it's the new it's the clean new clear
energy clean new clear energy new clear new clear new clear new clear hmm I think
you're on to something my friend for sure okay one more thing here for the
past couple episodes have been talking about this but acuclote.com before I say
that the portions of the show of course are brought to you by e-music and if you
go to e-music.com slash daily source code you'll get 35 MP3's of your choosing
for free with absolutely no obligation so that's well worth the ticket and the
price of admission and acuclote was an advertiser I think they're thinking
about coming back and it's Sean actually the marketing director over
acuclote are called in and we've been talking about the effectiveness of this
as essentially the same type of advertising as e-music or the Nokia internet
tablet or other things you may have heard on the other mevio and beaty pod show
programming and this is one of the most distinct well put together thoughts I've
heard in a long time and it's about two minutes but I think it's well worth
it because oh hell it's about the future of a part of the the medium that we're
working on here check it out hey Adam Jeffs asked from Florida checking in caught up
a bunch of Charlie's over the weekend and wanted to chime in on your questioning
why the life insurance ads didn't perform as well expected on the daily source
code I think a lot of it has to do with context I think when it comes to what
I'll call personality media and I think that podcasting and media casting certainly
falls into that category and I mean the personality media is where the audience
has a strong connection with the host or host of the show and relies on their
personality and relies on that connection I think that advertising and that
situation works best when the ads are things that stick within the context of
the show and the context of the listeners perception of that host or host is
so that the recommendations carry a great deal of weight and that's why the
advertising when it's in that context works very well so I think that in the
case of a listener to the Charlie ads for media, music, technology all make good
sense so when you're promoting a no get any 10 or you know the music accounts
or things that are really fit within the context of the Charlie your
recommendation is is a really powerful on the other hand I think life insurance
is somewhat of a non-secretor for the Charlie it's not something that's
typically discussed on the show and it's kind of how let's feel then as a result
I think we instinctively kind of bundle that into the category of regular
advertising or you know media type advertising and therefore it doesn't have the
same impact and it doesn't have the same response that you would expect as
something that really fits nicely within the context of the show and fits
nicely within our perception of the host as someone who is highly qualified
strong and credible recommendation for something not that you would be
credible for life insurance it's just a little bit too far out of context with
the show in my humble opinion anyway there's my two cents and I didn't click on
the insurance debt but I have purchased many other items that you've
recommended on on the Charlie including a no get at any hundred first time
around anyway long time listener love your hair love your no home home
yeah yeah yeah I hope you win hopefully all win of everyone's win appreciate my
freedom I could go on forever but you'll cut this off anyway take care
I don't I never cut that stuff off man I will cut that off you don't mind okay
man thank you so much for sending that in and I was listening to it again
and thinking yeah you're right but you know it's extremely relevant a lot of
the people who listen to the Charlie are my age should be thinking about this
younger folk should be thinking about this as well and now I actually feel that
I haven't done a very good job at thinking about you know how to present this
and maybe the offer isn't isn't good you know just saying 70% off if you go
to acycote.com slash dsc I presume it still works actually or call 1-800-4-107-214
I think maybe need to talk more about how life insurance works what the
premiums are what the deal is we're kind of payout someone will get how do
you choose your beneficiary I mean it is kind of important stuff you know I've
hired people to give me this type of advice but anyway I enjoy the conversation
I want to continue that particularly and I'll do that more at the end of the
show probably as a reason since it's about something that may not be just
everybody now this my friends is a special treat and I want you to call me up
voicemail numbers of course and show notes a daily source code.com tell me which
famous producer is singing the lyrics to this classic Frank Sinatra song which I'm
going to leave you with today it's the summer win
what with me all summer long we sang a song and strolled on golden sand to
sweet hearts and the summer win like painted kites those days and nights they
went flying by the world was new beneath the blue umbrella sky then softens
a pipe of man one day it called to you and I lost you to the summer win
the autumn win and the win you win they have come and got and still the day those
lonely days go on and on and get you tied his love of life new nights that never
ever.
Who is that mystery man if you don't know then well you don't know the summer win
but I have a lot of fun to listen to particularly because I know the guy pretty damn well
and that's it for seven fifty eight on the account for daily source code what I'm going to do my way take this
up to a thousand and then stop counting we're just going to continue to know anyway adam
media dot com you can find show notes at daily source code dot com and of course the
blog at curie dot com and uh... folks in the uk know you had a lot of a uk talk today
please feel free to call in a voice mail lines listed in the show notes all right that's
it all i can say is oh boy oh boy oh boy you should enjoy your freedom and live your life with passion
another fine media presentation stick it in your ear