So tell me, how long have you been having these delusions?
Well, doctor, it all started daily in dreams, the paranoia about the oil companies.
I guess it all started from listening to the daily source code.
There you go again, it's your delusions of the daily source code.
But, but doctor, doctor, it's a show without him curry.
Yes, you say it is a show, but of course you have the delusions.
The delusions of it being daily.
What do you mean, doctor?
Well, this Adam Curry doesn't actually make a show every day.
It's sometimes a Wednesday, sometimes a food bar Friday, sometimes a Tuesday,
but never it is a daily.
This delusions, they're getting in your way.
You'll never recover as long as you continue to think of this as a daily source code.
So, so, doctor, what's the solution? What can I do?
Well, you must, you must come up with another word for the, the, the, the daily source code.
Perhaps it is the delusional source code.
So here it is the delusional source code.
With Adam Curry, the, the, the number, seven, seven, six.
Through the, you have another word for the, you have another word for the, you have another word for the, you have another word,
you have another word for the, you have another word for the, you have another word for the, you have another word for the, you have another word for the, you have another word for the,
you have another word to be a, I would like this question right?
6 billion dollars worth of airplane!
Wipe to my ass!
Then the next generation radio content emit yours!!
We don't need not even know what to do to keep being serious again!
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk!
...
discard this bull!
аров curry!
Am!
Hmm, this is a mom ko
This is a thousand of our life is a moment.
And we all stay alive.
Of course, this is the new dreams.
And we all stay hungry.
And we all stop.
And we all end up with the earth.
And we all stop these stairs for you.
And as time goes by, we all stop.
So, so, so, so.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I got so much trouble on my mind.
Me, it's too big.
Here's your ticket.
Hit a time I can't wait.
To pull the fuel to push the back, the back, the back, the back,
So I sat in a chatting snack, the back, now ready to make it.
Here's my favorite season, low low.
You'll never be able to let needles fall low.
Please let any stage of nature,
Please the pleasure bringing trainer.
The way I've never put in it, what I'm giving up.
Exxon the place, now.
I don't know what about later.
Past now I know how to point the flag of noise.
And I've headed up to here.
Here, far away I've got to go in here.
Right up instead of red just a bit of gold.
Not to in this side, I'll hold on.
What?
Keep from getting jerked fingers from waves.
So we passed him a better day.
He's home.
Not a 50-bowl.
Never follow his home.
Still trapped the mold.
Never question what I am God.
No, sir.
Let's come and look around.
What are you talking about?
Where did you get some?
What's up?
It's all about what's up?
Come on, man, it's just the facade.
Okay, let's chase that child with the ball.
I see it all like it was in the fire.
Let it take out all my clothes, the plane would just be gone.
If you want me out of playing, give it down with y'all.
What's in your ventilation?
World domination.
The ventilation is just an energy.
It's an energy, it's an energy.
It's an energy, it's a throttle.
Oh, that's a sky.
Turn it on, it's a vision.
If you want me to tell you what I'm gonna do,
it's my journey day.
Give me that.
Come on, come on.
Come on, breathe me out.
Let it matter, put it down on the plane.
Give me something that you never had.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
God bless you so much.
Welcome to the terminal.
Come on.
Yeah.
Discovered on the source code drop,
peeping off episode number 776.
Welcome to the terminal.
Everybody.
It's the Charlie coming to you from Surrey.
The affluent suburb.
That would be Gilford, G-Town.
I love this kind of stuff.
It's something about angry black men.
I think it really does it for me.
Of course, I have no idea who it is,
because the tracks once again were uploaded with no data.
Come on, guys.
When you're filling up the drop, which, of course,
you can find the drop.io slash daily source code.
It's listed in the show notes of daily source code.com,
and curry.com.
Please give me some info.
I'll be linking to all these songs today.
And hey, how you doing?
I'm back from vacation.
I did it.
I completely unplugged a full week.
Actually a little bit longer than that.
If you think about it, it was 11 days completely unplugged.
Oh, man.
It was so nice.
The south of France.
Of course, I got to give you a little vacation wrap up.
And actually, upon returning,
I found that good old Ray, of course,
raised the subcontinent and a chuckle head,
who's been out there for quite a while for a number of years.
He actually kind of put together a little recap of where things are going,
some of the topics that we're going on,
and moves right into a commercial type of venture,
and a song from the soundtrack of my life.
I figured I'd play that for you.
And then we'll get into everything,
because there's a lot of meat on the bone today.
Oh, we want you tonight, Ray.
Oh, we will you there, Adam.
Oh, we've got a meal, but I can't stop it.
Sava.
And I wish it's right to soundtrack hell.
60km south west of the city of Nissan, the Mediterranean coast.
It's a French Riviera, man.
Nice.
Or nice.
Or Levant.
DuPance.
It's a dread-trabble land to celebrate your free days.
So, if you watched the two of the fronts,
actually I have no idea,
do the American people notice these hundred and eighty guys riding on a bike for three weeks.
All across France at all.
Do the Americans like cycling.
I mean, they've got Greg Lamont,
and actually became the first American cyclist to win the two of the fronts.
In 1986, when some strong,
he won the two of the fronts in a record-breaking seven consecutive years.
I mean, well, if you like to watch the best of the best,
the pizzas in the five, the two of the fronts is really the place to be.
And that's what you're looking at the sport, right, Adam?
To watch the best of the best, like soccer, the cup fever.
Cycling in a specially the two of the fronts is watching the best guys from all over the world,
riding the most exciting and the longest cycling that's all across France
with a big finish on the Champs-Élysées in Paris.
This year on Sunday, July the 27th.
Good morning. This is your wake-up crew.
By the way, really exciting what you're doing on Aeroclassic Rockheadham
haven't got the time to listen every day,
but I've heard you shaking up the Hague,
the political capital offered the Netherlands.
Way to go, dude.
You know, I've got a kind of job
where listening to a radio reaches a home at a level.
I made it.
Believe me, I really tried to catch up with your podcast,
the wake-up call, but they're so long, man.
You know, when I'm listening to the DSC,
I know it's 45 minutes most of the time.
I can listen to my car during my 25 minutes drive to Amsterdam
and after nine hours of chasing bad guys,
I listen to the last part of the show.
It's nice. It sounds different.
I like the subjects,
and I just like the thought of being part of a greater area,
instead of being the pitch in the pie.
I like the chucklehead community,
and I think you're doing a great job on a Charlie.
So how about that DSC daily source-goat thing?
What's up with that?
I'm aware of the fact that there's a problem
with a daily part of this name,
but I don't care if you're shit.
I really don't have a problem with the fact
that you're not making a show every day of the week.
I am proud of things to do, you know?
So in my opinion, you can keep it this way,
but maybe the rest of the chuckleheads
want to rename the DSC in...
Uh...
Diviated source-goat,
dominant source-goat,
data source-goat,
compressed source-goat,
digital source-goat,
the hydrodynamic,
the democratic,
the drunken source-goat,
but maybe the delicious source-goat,
now let's do the drop-eye source-goat.
The deadly source-goat,
the dream of source-goat,
the deep source-goat,
how be my guest?
It never gets any better than the daily source-goat.
That's the name of the show, man.
So,
change the whole name,
something completely different,
or keep it going.
I'll let the chuckleheads help you.
So, Adam,
what do you think about this?
Soundtrack to my life.
I'm Gary.
Let's take a look at the landscape on a road trip through your life.
Adam Clark Curry was born on September 3,
in 1964,
in Arlington, Virginia,
and moved when it was eight months old
to Uganda,
in South Africa.
It was the year in which US President
Lyndon Johnson declared a war on property
and Bob Dylan turns the Beatles
on to cannabis for the first time.
But there also was a Roy Kelton Arbison,
like many artists,
the big omen taint his success
as the British Invasion Sweat America in 1964.
His single,
how pretty woman broke the Beatles
strangled hold on the top 10
soaring to number one on the Billboard
charge and number one in the British charge.
The record sold war copies in the first ten days
of released an any single up to that time
and eventually sold over 7 million copies.
Adam Curry's soundtrack to my life
takes a trip down memory lane 2,
in 1964.
A top of the hour going to go home
and it's kind of curry.
a top of the hour going to go home
okay
a bottom of the day
a top of the night
The man must be the big ol' Roy Arbison, all pretty woman and big hit in 1964.
The year our friend was dropped on this planet.
So Adam, what was your family situation back in 64?
What kind of house were you living?
What kind of job was your father doing?
Do you remember anything of these early years of your life in the US?
I did you move to South Africa.
I would go through the soundtrack to your life.
And for now take care.
And if you like it, I'll be back next week with a soundtrack to your life from 1986.
Alright, Ray, on the Charlie, my brother, thank you so much.
I love that.
Absolutely spectacular.
A wrap-up of everything.
Now you're done.
Now you're up to speed.
Now you know what's going on.
Besides the fact, of course, that I'm going to tell you about
the vacation in the south of France.
I've just decided to say France now from now on.
That's my first British pronunciation that I'm bringing into my vocabulary.
Because when I say France, it sounds so American.
And people look at me funny.
But of course, it's Americans who say, oh, you say France.
So that's kind of funny.
Anyway, so we were visiting.
We did something we've never done before.
We stayed with a friend.
He invited us to stay at his house.
By the way, many panelists, I might say.
So our buddy, Michelle, he owns the largest nightclub in Syria, I think,
which happens to be in Guilford.
And we met up with him at the BT Pod Show Christmas party.
He crashed the party with a super agent Keith, who, of course,
we've been working with for over a year.
And that was the introduction.
And we really got on well.
And he said, you know, once you guys come down, hang out.
He's divorced.
Sorry.
He's not married to his daughter's mother.
It's how's that for political correctness, huh?
So she's 12 or 13, her name is Nicole.
And she was going to be down there.
So kind of like a sibling vibe for Christina.
And he had some other house guess over again.
You know, like a mini palace with a huge Olympic size swimming pool.
He did nicely to 28 degrees centigrade.
I mean, it doesn't get any better than that.
We had 30 degrees outside.
Right on in San Rafael right near the sea right near the harbor.
We rented a 40 foot power boat one day.
And we zipped across to San Trope, which is about a 20 minute.
Well, I don't want to say a flight because this thing was going so fast.
Of course, we also had a captain to steer the boat for us.
Head lunch at the famous club sank on sank club 55 right there on next to Nikki Beach.
I mean, we were, I mean, this is kind of place where PDD shows up with his helicopter.
In fact, it was kind of funny that my partner Ron Bloom was in that same.
And we probably were no more than 10 kilometers or part for the space of about a day and a half.
As he decided last minute to go out to San Trope as well.
And so, you know, he just kind of hung around on July 14, which is kind of the French independence day,
but steel day.
We were invited by someone Patricia knows to a rooftop celebration with a party on the rooftop.
And a view of the fireworks. And boy, when we got there, I mean, this thing was right next to the Carlton Hotel,
probably one of the most expensive real estate spots in the world.
And it was like an enormous penthouse deck with, I don't know,
there must have been 70 people on the deck.
I mean, it was just outrageous.
And I complete view of the water of the bay and that the fireworks display.
And it was a real posh posh.
She, she type of vacation. It was great.
And our host was very gracious.
He was almost like a Julie from the love boat.
You know, like a cruise director taking us somewhere every single day.
And because normally, you know, we just kind of like veg out and do nothing.
And hang by the pool, no more bored within three days.
So there was not a moment of boringness to be found.
And I got to tell you, I really like the south of France.
They had vegetables.
And fruit that actually look like vegetables of fruit because, of course,
they're not genetically modified.
Boy, what a surprise there.
And the food was just delicious.
And now I don't know.
My French even started to come back.
I was actually quite pleased with myself.
And in general, I have to say, I very much look like going back there.
It's not quite as hot as Portugal or Spain or some parts of southern Italy.
The weather in general is really nice.
It's just a, it's great.
And I can fly there with a delta share.
Not that we did that, of course, because the ladies would never fly for three and a half hours with me,
which is about what it would take depending on the road weather and the wind conditions.
But, no, good.
You know, I think we'll go back for sure.
Now, upon my return, we got back late last Friday night.
And Saturday, you know, it's still kind of a time.
Even though once only one hour as we still had a little bit of a time difference.
And I was like, I'm got to go get myself a 3G iPhone.
I actually tried on Friday posted a picture on curry.com.
901 Friday morning when they went on sale worldwide.
There was a hundred people outside the O2 store in Guilford, no less,
which really blew me away.
So, of course, I didn't buy one.
I didn't even look for one in France.
In fact, I stayed pretty much disconnected and only read the financial times every single day,
which we'll get to that later because a lot of shit that I was reading that I don't like.
And a lot of things really opened up in my mind.
More awakening, I would say, more red pill stuff.
So, and now, of course, I'd also been reading about the launch in the FT,
and Patricia had her daily mirror, whatever, and there was a couple other papers laying around.
But mainly in the FT.
And, you know, I started to notice a couple of trends.
Like, well, of course, the built-in GPS isn't all that hot, it turns out.
Of course, there's no turn-by-turn directions, at least not with a voice, like a proper navigation system.
I guess that's forthcoming.
Of course, a lot of noise about the app store.
What else was there? Oh, battery life, still pretty limited for hours.
If you've got everything blowing full speed, you know, that kind of stuff that's a little bit irritating.
And so, I came up with an alternative plan.
First thing I did is I upgraded my iPod Touch, which, of course, is exactly the iPhone,
only without the phone and the 3G part.
It's got Wi-Fi and everything else is pretty much the same.
Oh, it also doesn't have a camera.
But, you know, I've been using my Nokia E61I for that, which has been okay.
It's the same quality camera that's in the iPhone, including the 3G version.
And, I should revisit that joy-coost spot.
Because that essentially can turn your Nokia or any other Symbian-based phone into a Wi-Fi access point using your high-speed 3G.
And, of course, here we have HDSPA, which is a high density maybe, something packet access.
I don't know.
Emily, it's HSDPA, I don't know.
High-speed, it's HSDPA, high-speed digital packet access.
I think that's what it's called, which can get you up to, they say 3.6 megabits per second.
But, in general, I see it probably happening around 700 kilobits per second.
It's not quite a megabit, but still way faster than whatever I've seen coming out of, you know, a traditional 3G.
I think is what they call it.
And, I got a message from Candyman, Luke, and he said, hey, you know, did you ever receive that E71?
Because I guess they were going to send me the new Nokia phone, which I hadn't received.
And I said, yeah, don't worry about it.
You know, I'm getting the iPhone.
So, it already said, please don't send me anything.
It calls for a kind of field of blides if they do send me something to, you know, go out and tell people about it.
But I was kind of reading up on it.
And so, I, you know, I would basically say, thought to myself, well, look, now I'm running the, all of the iPhone iPod Touch 2.0 software.
I've looked at the app store.
And there's some interesting things in there.
In fact, if I pick it up right now, let me see what apps do I have installed.
I've got flashlight.
I love that.
So, I, and in fact, I use that quite a bit using the screen with high density light as a flashlight.
VNC, I've got the aviation software for flight, which is like 65 bucks, but very cool for getting up to the minute information.
I've got Bloomberg installed Twitter-rific for Twitter weather bug near times and the remote, which lets you control iTunes via remote.
So, that's all pretty handy stuff.
It's pretty cool.
It's a zippy.
And I enjoy it.
There's nothing like browsing the web on the iPod Touch on the iPhone.
That without a doubt, hands down.
It beats everything.
The size of the screen, the interaction with the fingers, the tapping, love it, nothing compares.
No matter what.
So, I figured I'd go into the city and I'd look around.
And, you know, I stood in front of the O2 store and already heard that, you know, they were probably sold out.
And right behind me was a Nokia store.
So, I said, you know, maybe I go look at that communicator that E90 or whatever it is.
I'm just looking for something that can run Joy-Coost spot at this point as kind of an alternative.
That will let me browse at high speed connecting basically the iPod Touch to a phone.
And this thing is kind of plastic and kind of big looking.
But next to it, they had a singular one single model of the E71.
And I was surprised.
Like, wow, this thing is beautiful.
I mean, it's the first Nokia phone that actually looks high-class upper-scale,
the classy, just beautiful.
And that's the guy turned it on for me.
And I'm amazed at the speed of this thing.
And it's got a GPS built in with turn by turn.
Voice instructions.
It's got a 3.2 megapixel camera.
It's got all kinds of extra goodies.
And really, the biggest problem I've had with my Nokia E61 eye,
which I like very much, particularly with the full size.
Full query keyboard.
It's just that the process was a little bit too slow.
And this one, the E71, I think, has a 400 megahertz processor.
And this shit is just flying.
And I'm amazed.
I mean, the internet telephone works without buffering and, you know,
cropping out merely because the processor can just handle it.
So I'm like, okay, that's it.
So I bought it.
Not cheap, by the way, to get an unlocked version like 350 pounds.
And I have been totally in love ever since.
This thing is amazing.
Even the web browsing isn't too bad because of its speed.
I mean, it's just so incredibly fast.
But really, running it with joy coospot and the iPod touch is a phenomenal combination.
But this thing is so cool.
It even has a little business card scanner.
You take a picture of the business card with the built in camera.
And it OCRs it optical character recognition.
And then you can add it straight to your address book, all the details.
And I tried it on my own card.
And it really works.
It's outrageous.
And so I'm still getting used to it.
Figuring everything out and loaded up some cool symbioness.
And I must say, I must say it is now that they've got the speed of this thing up.
It's great.
And of course, you get like your five hours continuous talk time,
14 days stand by time.
I mean, you know, real proper technology in there.
So I think I found a beautiful, beautiful combination.
And as we progress through the use of it, I'll let you know how I get on.
But I'm so far, so good.
I'm very, very happy with what I'm seeing.
Now, since it is vacation time and since I am very proud that we've got this big name
sponsor on the show.
I just want to talk about budget rent to cars.
By the way, with today's oil prices, which I'm sure we're going to talk about later.
I mean, why the hell would you have a card?
You know, if you really need one, just rent it.
And if you want good looking cars, and I know this from my own experience, particularly
budget on sunset in California in Los Angeles, he's got cool looking cars as well.
Even though they're, they're called budget.
They got hot wheels.
So I've got a special discount for you.
$30 off weekly rentals or 10% off any other time period.
And what you want to do is go to budget.com slash DSC.
That'll be your code to use if you get to the site any other way.
But just go to budget.com DSC to get your coupon.
And you get that $30 off weekly rentals or 10% off any other time periods.
And this is actually, this promotion is doing really well.
There's a couple more that aren't running so well that I want to find out from you guys.
Why not? We'll talk about that later on in the show as well.
So big boy service without the big boy upgrades.
There you go rent like a genius budget.com slash DSC.
Again, sourcing music from the, from the drop drop.io slash daily source code.
This one is actually a little bit more noted on this one in the, in the upload.
Akira the Don, a very appropriate is we're talking about what's going on with the oil prices.
And of course, they've dropped significantly.
Oh, not that speculators have anything to do with it.
Oh, no, when a drop is just what?
Supplying demand reversing all of a sudden, please give me a break.
Don't talk about that.
Prepare to listen to the bankers.
Just.
I would see in the whole world, and he can't take his life
Fuck, say that dude was spasin' out on PCP
A son and coke and a food
I'm like, I really well, and I show that shit on the news
Whether they choose it's only show the one side
They got the people outside right in
Coppers on childhood, and she's right
They need you give a fuck about blacks
She just didn't make sense
These are questions I ask
Then I'm on the sole layer, a click and links on
Jason's looks at
Concert answers are fine food
And Nixon instigated institution
That has the part
This is banned to US Constitution
And they banned a very crisis
Such as, you know, all the national opposition to the US invasion
Of course, as they can stop martial law
If there's right, and in several US safe
Semotainously, I was like, oh yeah
I see nothing at home, just in town
It's like black
They get fake news and the cause of it now
It's black, you know
They get fake news and the cause of it
It's like black
They get fake news
It's like black, you know
It's black, you know
They get the cause of it now
They get fake news and the cause of it now
The population are just fit for a reason
Carrow should have been home for treason
We buy strawberries at a season like babes
Oh, so when you're up, you thought
You don't stop, you buy cuffs
Then it's out to the next thing
Settlement to sex, strings, and flime
The last case, and when the work
Cakes, a king, make us quick
Catflakes should get shelter
He gets cracklakes with crashes
Have a fina around me
Then he's got the money
Settlement to sex, and the star
It's some of the guys in the club
The guys above them are the guys
Blaine on their club
The guys, fuck them are the guys
Call that ice cream
Guys, my sweat's like dead guys
Most success, they're just disguised
Settlement to sex
Settlement to sex, they're just disguised
You want a healer?
Settlement to sex
The common suits and ties
Necinos of sex
He's like, a king, you want a healer
Settlement to sex
J loyal中国
And to hell and I've heard
Well organized in the ranks
I thought we were the fact
The world back we should gather with tax
All they do is fuck
I can't miss it much juggly
If someone wanted you to land back
Five times back control they promised you
They were your education
The borders right there and right there for us
Cause they beat the car
For its paypal
These lungs are maybe that's like
Oh, you wanna fuck you
If you're only in your home
You just hours are keeping every kind of credit cards
Like what's that?
Come snatch it back pretend you think you are all exactly what you choose
Remember where they go
Cause now the chips ring
I'm supposed to be going to you
A cure of the dawn
It's the bankers man
I'm telling you it's them dirty bankers
I'm not talking about you
You're a local city bank or your bank of America
You know as some kind of like ATM based business
I'm talking about
The big guys
The guys at the top names like Rockefeller, Rothschild, Warburg
Those are the ones you got to look out for my friends
And particularly this oil thing man
This is someone just pulling the levers
Just trying to make it all work
Cause we're gonna right now we've got inflation
And we've got an economy that's stagnating
Right?
This is happening across the globe
You're seeing banks that are almost going out of business
Wait
I mean look at this
Look it's so simple to see what's happening
Europeans raise their interest rate by 25 basis points to 4.25%
That means of course the dollar has to change
But you know how do we combat that?
Well let's just pull the lever on the oil
Down it went
Down almost 15 bucks a barrel of oil
How coincidental by the way
That it stopped around 130 dipped a little bit below
I'll tell you why
There was an enormous amount of option put options contracts at 130
This means someone is betting against the price
The price will be going down
And if it hits 130 that's where they start to make the big money
If it goes even lower that's where they start to make a real spread
That's the reason it dipped down to 129
No other reason the demand in all of a sudden stop
Not that much
Oh yes sure there were some reports
But I'm telling you it's crap
It's all crap
Yeah let's listen to it today
Today's the 21st of July
Let's listen to a CNN news update
And let's see if we can dissect what's happening here
Listen to this crap
A wobbly economy has made many Americans pinch pennies
A little tighter
CNN's John Lawrence has details
That's not a journalist say high fuel prices
A rough housing market and other concerns
Have caused many consumers to hold on to their wall
It's a little bit tighter than usual
It's not holding on
It's hanging on because we're getting screwed
It's not like the gas pumps have dropped the price
In fact they're probably going to go up a little bit before they come down
You mark my words on this
We're losing wealth
We have to learn to get that
We're losing wealth because the federal reserve is now handing out billions of
Dollars for free in loans
Which means they're you know printing money
Not really printing and it's just a computer database entry
But it shows up in all the systems
It is a global finance system you know
So that means our money is becoming
Worth less
It's exactly what we have to do
Robert Brusko with fact in opinion economics
Is it might take a while for the country to bounce back
I think that one of the problems is that people talk about this task
Period like it spends so bad
And my concern is that the worst may still lie ahead of us
Yeah, there you go
I agree with that as well
I think we're in inning four
And it's probably going to be a ten inning game
A recent survey from Nielsen coast is 63% of Americans have cut their spending over the past 12 months
Joe, wow, do you hear how that shit's edited man?
What a puking voice that is
John Lawrence
Yeah, yeah
Treasury Secretary Henry Paulson says he wants to have a safe and sound banking system
A safe and sound banking system
There is no cause for concern
Please return to your homes
Act normal and purchase through amazon.com
Watch television and buy stuff
In the 75 years we've had the FDIC
We have not had a single deposit or lose one penny
Yeah, this is ensuring your money in the bank
I'm worried about that man
I'm spreading my shit out
I don't want all my money in one bank
Even the fortest bank
Which I also bank with
In Europe is having troubles, man
You know, and they only secure so much
Take it out, put it into something else by some oil
However, Paulson tells CNN's late edition
The number of troubled banks will increase
As they cope to struggle with big losses on bad mortgages
Yeah, duh
More housing data on tap this week
A report regarding
Your house is now worthless
Previously owned homes sales will be released on Thursday
But let me just explain one thing
Let me try this because this becomes so abundantly clear to me
How these banks operate? What a scam
So if someone puts like a hundred thousand dollars
The posits that in their bank
That could be me by the way
By law they're allowed to multiply that by ten
And lend it out
So it's fake money
It doesn't exist
Because they're not actually handing you a check
If you go get a mortgage for a hundred thousand dollars on a house
No, they just put a little checkmark
And minus a hundred thousand in your account
In your cell on the spreadsheet
And they add it to another person
Is that like a hundred thousand dollars in printed money
Or gold transferred hands
It's like a check, it's a piece of paper
And that they created out of thin air
Do you understand?
So you worked really hard
I put a hundred grand in there
Which even though it's paper
I did it with actual work
And then they get to lend that nine more times
And that money is just fake
It's not real
So when someone can't pay back the loan
That's when they start to scrap it in the real wealth
You know you work hard for that
It's a house
A house is really worth something
And then that way they can just go ahead and steal from everybody
It's become so abundantly clear to me
And it's just so incredibly wrong
Well we gotta do something about it
I might have some ideas later on
By the way, this one kind of lost in the shuffle
It's been hanging in the queue for a couple of weeks
It is our European correspondent
Our sabond known as comic strip blogger
Some about France
So let's see what he's got in store for us today
Hello
Adam Lekiri
He was here, you're again, you're a correspondent
He has been
Yes
So let this news is that
Members of EU Parliament called MEPs
I'll get to think now
New shiny TV train
That's one of those high speed trains
The commute between the Brussels and Strasbourg
Yeah, this is crazy man
The European Parliament
I think the French got all bent out of shape
And they wanted to have
They wanted to have the European Parliament
What's this?
No, no, no, go away
One to have the European Parliament
Near their hometown
And so we wound up with two
We're including Brussels
And so they shut all back and forth
Like every week or every month
Of God knows
There's such a waste of money
And it's a good opportunity to
Reminds to everybody
That is squandering of money
By having two locations for EU Parliament
It's a fault of France
100% fault of France
All the France
That despite the petition of over one million EU citizens
I repeat one million EU citizens
Side petition against it
But France still insists on keeping this location in Strasbourg
In France even it is not used very much
So clearly France is much much worse
For European Union than Ireland
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm totally there with you man
In fact, Sarcosi
President of the European Union for the next six months
And of course, a main man in France
He's in the Ireland today
And you know what he's doing
And this has really pissed me off
Because I've been reading it
I've been tracking it all week long
It's like they're just not going to accept this no vote
On the Lisbon Treaty
Which of course really is a fundamental change
In our fundamental inalienable rights
Because it is a constitution
I've read it
No one can dispute what these protocols
And amendments are
The treated as law
And all of the member states that ratified this
It's law
And I don't like it
And we've discussed it and we've read it
And there's a lot of really weird shit in these laws
You know, yeah, you have the freedom
To of movement and just freedom as an individual
Unless of course you have a communicable disease
Or if you're a vagrant
Then you'll be arrested
Death penalty no
Unless you're trying to escape a rest
Well, that's no reason to kill anybody
And that shit's going into law
And they're pushing it through
They will not accept the no
So now there's basically only a couple of options
One that people are talking about is a two-speed Europe
Where countries who don't ratify
Ireland of course is the only official one
And then there's a five more couple of them
Could be on the fence
I don't know by the way
Did that
Get ratified in the UK
Is that lawsuit get resolved by that one guy
Who was suing the government
If you know, let me know, please
So anyway, countries that don't ratify
They would still be operating on the niece treaty
It's ridiculous
This is how desperate they are to get this done
And I'm seeing laws show up now
I'm seeing shit happening in Europe that is wrong
The first one is double jeopardy
Now double jeopardy
Of course it's a exciting round in the game show
But it essentially means that if you are
If you're charged and you go to trial
And you're not convicted, you cannot be tried for the same crime again
So this is like the OJ Simpson
Which of course is a perfectly example
That not being an unfortunate law
So I think we pretty much know he killed his ex-wife
And Ron Goldman, her lover or friend or whatever
Of course, we don't know that for sure
But it sure seems like in fact in the civil suit he was found guilty
But in the federal suit, not guilty
So we can never be tried for that again
Even if they have pictures of him actually killing them
Now this of course is sad
Because here's a guy who gets away
Literally with murder as far as I'm concerned
No proof of that
Even wrote a book
If I was going to do it here's how I do it
G-O-J thanks for that
Of course even throwing the guy in jail
Even putting him on death row
Nothing will get the coal Simpson and Ron Goldman back
Which that's obvious
But really this law is very important
Because you don't want the government
Hounding you
Because if there was no double jeopardy
Then let's say here's one
That I've actually had happened to me in the Netherlands
Where double jeopardy is about to be dismissed
The internal revenue
They said oh you owe us like a million dollars
And I said no I don't
And in fact even did some nasty shit
And went to the press and it became a big hoopla
And later the judge said
You know what? You don't know anything
In fact they owe you a public apology
Which they had to do
Now
Let's say
This double jeopardy is gone
Somewhere down the line they could easily say
Well we got some new evidence man
We got a picture if you do a stop
Man they could just start up a whole process again
And again and again and they can wear you down
Law suits are not fun
Courts are not fun
And they could use this to mess with you
Now we're already enslaved in so many ways
Now this is this is bad
It really is bad
There's a reason for this law and it's to protect our rights
So across Europe this is now being phased out
In Ireland in the Netherlands
In fact they even think Australia is considering removing this
So this clearly larger forces at work with an agenda
And they're smart about it
Okay, so I'm again
Europe as a free trade zone
Which of course is what the European Union started as the European economic community
The EEC
Now it has to be like the United States of Europe
And now I'm against it man
This is wrong
This is really wrong
And I don't trust these guys anymore
I certainly don't trust our cozy
Man this guy just look at him
Just look at him
You can't trust a guy like that
Oh man
Hey um
There's a very cool let me see if I can find it here
Um
I'm missing something
Oh wait a minute
Before I even get to that
I gotta tell you
I've been invited to a host and event
And I'm gonna do it
And I'm really really psyched about this
Doctor Ron Paul
Is throwing something titled
The Rally for the Republic
And this will be held simultaneously
In the same week as
The Republican National Convention
Which will be held in Minneapolis
So this is also taking place in Minneapolis
And I don't
It's a big venue
It's like 15,000 people
And there's lots of music stars
Of course Dr. Ron is gonna do a speech
And it's uh
Well here's the actually I have this bit for you
The website is not yet
Rally goals and issues
Americans inherit from their ancestors
A glorious tradition of freedom and resistance to oppression
Our country is long been admired
By the rest of the world for a great example of liberty and prosperity
A light shining in the darkness of tyranny
Join the revolution
The hell does that
Hold on a second
I'm sure you're not hearing this
Okay, that's coming through
Ah, crap
Let me get back to that
So tomorrow the website goes live
It's Rally for the Republic dot com
But right now you can
It's not up yet so you'll probably be redirected to the campaign for
Liberty dot com
So anyway so on the second they have this 15,000 person event
Then on the first they basically have
I mean I would almost say it's tailor-made for chuckleheads
They have they've gotten a football stadium
And that's where all the people who believe
There's reptilians the UFOs are coming
The tinfoil hatwares
The conspiracy theorists
But also Amy Allen
And we're working on some other really cool artists
They're all going to have their own special event
Which is kind of the hard core to kick it all off
In fact that is the core base of Dr. Ron
I love that
And I'll be hosting that event
September 1st in Minneapolis
I'm really really psyched about it
So I'll be telling you more about that as it goes long
And maybe we could even do a meetup
With a bunch of a bunch of chuckleheads
Which I think would just be extremely cool
Now quick note about Drobot
This is this hard disk that never runs out of space
Which we've got an amazing deal on
But I haven't you know not a single chucklehead
Is purchased one and I'm wondering if you guys don't like it
If it's if it's just not you know if it's just not floating
Your boat if it's not
Taking on the boxes because we have a fifty dollars off the Drobot basic unit
And fifty dollars off the Drobot unit which which come bundled
It comes bundled with a two terabyte or four terabyte drive
All you got to do is go to drobot.com slash dsc
And you can get that fifty dollar off
But no one has purchased one
I know I've mentioned a couple of times on the show
And I'm just wondering if you're not interested
Then I'll just stop
If you have questions about it
There's a cool video on CNET
I know Cali Lewis has been talking about this thing as well
But I'll put a link in the show notes to this CNET video
Because as well we'll take a look at this thing
It is awesome
And I have one on order myself
It's going to the condo in San Francisco
Just to save on shipping
So I'll bring that back with me
I think I'm going to go in a week or two
So keep you up the speed on that
Let me see
Man I have so much to talk about in so little time
And I haven't even done any voicemail comments
There was probably about
I don't know
120 of them
Then I'm going through painfully one by one
So look for if you say something cool
And then look for that
Coming up in the next week or so
Let me see
There's so much other stuff to talk about
Yeah I think really just my total awareness
And awakening of what's happening in the world
And actually I also took a couple of books along with
What was the one I liked a lot
Oh I bought a shock doctrine
I know me client
I've talked about her on the show before
There was a video that she kind of discussed this book
And so I finally had some time to read it
And it's really interesting because it gave me a lot of clues
A lot of code words to look for
Particularly that shows up in in print
And really the understanding of how shock works
And you'd see this word shock a lot these days
Remember this really is a type of code
Excuse me
I just thought of it and say
What happens is
When either
The shock is either put in place deliberately
Think possibly 911
Or think oil prices rising
Astronomically all of a sudden
In fact that is literally in the press called
The oil shock or another shock based on oil
When that shock hits and of course it hits our wallets
It hits our heads were confused
We're freaking out
That's when all kinds of shit starts to change
That's when you're going to watch out
That's when stuff like the codex
Alimentarius sneaks in
We're all of a sudden now
There's rules on what a tomato can look like
Remember that we talked about that one last week
Only four types of tomatoes
Please do not deviate from the tomato blueprint anymore
After Katrina which of course was arguably a natural disaster
First thing that happened
Guys swooped in there and they got rid of the public schooling system
This is why people were still homeless man
Even this is the all of course
But people were in the astro dome
Camped out
Was it the astro dome
Anyway
The stadium
And these guys swooped in
And they changed the whole schooling system
Now you get vouchers for charter schools
In other words
A commercial schooling system
And this is systematic my friends
This is what I'm seeing
In Iraq, in Afghanistan
There are no there are no guys on KP on kitchen patrol
No
We've got Burger King and Pizza Hut
And we've got commercial laundry companies
And everything is taken care of
And everything is commercial commercial
The military industrial complex
Has spread like wild fire
It's not just the military industrial complex
No, now it's the schooling industrial complex
It's like when the tsunami hit
What's the first thing that happened
Everybody lost their shirts, their lives
And their beachfront property
That is now taken over by property developers
And turned into tourist hotels and other tourist shit
And the guys who were like fishermen and shit
Gone
They don't own it anymore
This is how the shock works
And it's all based upon the learnings of Milton Friedman
From the Chicago School of Economics
Who literally thought that it would be a good idea
And man there's world leaders who just have
You know are the cycles of this guy
He's passed away now
The cycles of this guy
And
His idea was have a commercially run government
Which is okay
You know in some ways
But it's not going to work
Because people get greedy and rip you off
And this is where all this money is just being taken away from us
And it's happening at this very moment as we speak
Money and wealth is being taken away from us
Anyway, I feel really good about all this stuff
Because once you can see it once you've figured it out
It really is quite powerful and empowering
Here's another example
This is cool
From this is London.co.uk
Actually I saw this so the newspaper version of this
How China's taking over Africa and why the West should be very worried
And here's a picture of Chinese president who in tow
With the Zimbabwe president Robert Mugabe
Because China's moving in man
And Africa's looking towards the east instead of the West
And Africa China's going to go in
Great Africa
Like the West has been doing all of these years
They're going to promise all kinds of shit
Take all their natural resources
And then leave them to rot
Once it's the economic hitman theory
You know we all will promise all this stuff
We'll put a little mark here in the database
And new problem
We'll take care of you
There's already 750,000 Chinese in
Let's see where it was
Are they just in if they set all of Africa? Let me see
Now you'll search 750
Yeah
With little fanfare staggering 750,000 Chinese
Instead of an Africa over the past decade
More are on the way
The strategy has been carefully devised by the officials
And Beijing where one expert is estimated that China will eventually
Need to send 300 million people
300 million people to Africa
To solve the problems of over population and pollution
Holy crap
You got to read this article
And by the way, I'm also linking to
I got to figure out a better way to position the drop
That is so powerful
I love the drop
We should make more use of comments
And by the way, there's also a phone number
You can use to call in a voicemail into the drop
Which would be even cooler if we started using that
I might start promoting that
But wow
Crazy, crazy stuff
Alright, I got a couple more things to talk about
But first, uh, or see, I guess a music
I'm going to want to promote something
Hold on a second
Jesus
What's that?
God
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week
Show we found real tournament
Three on the Xbox 360
I get all 40 with Beijing 2008
The official game of the Olympics
We look at brothers in arms, house, highway
And we've got some news from E3
That's all at Gamesweasel.com
This, this, you think it will be so good
I don't worry
I couldn't resist
Uh, so some news from the UK
And then I got one more piece of news from the US
Uh, the horrible, horrible thing
That has been discovered
There's this, uh, this place called Jersey
I think it's the Isle of Jersey
It is an island, I don't know what's called
It's just called Jersey as far as I know
Part of the United Kingdom
And, uh, horrible discovery
And over, like a hundred people have complained
That they were abused at this children's orphanage home
Over, you know, many decades
And, you know, and people may like, ah, your cookie
It's not true
And, of course, there's a local government, you know,
Very powerful officials on such a small island
Well, just, uh, like two weeks ago
This always seems to happen in these high-up political circles
Which really drives me nuts
Uh, they found a bunker nearby this orphanage
And in this bunker, under an old war war two bunker
Uh, but they found all these torture chambers
In fact, they found 65 baby teeth
They found charred bones and remains
Pieces of a child's ear
I mean, and this is exactly what these hundred people were saying
It's like, this is nuts
I mean, sexually abused and beaten
And you should just, you know, look for the stories
Although the kind of hard to find
And I'm really suspicious about what's going on there
So, um, the story is that a lot of high-ranking officials
From the local government were involved in this abuse
Which, of course, could explain
If that were true, why, you know, the stuff has been stifled
And now the main guy who was doing the investigation, you know,
All of a sudden he's being replaced
He's going into retirement within a year
I mean, that shit stinks
Look around the web and you look at child abuse and politics
You could just google that
You'll see all kinds of stories
In fact, you, the older Chuckleheads may remember
George Bush Sr.
And the rumor is about the White House and Boys Town USA
In fact, there's a documentary somewhere online
That, uh, that was never broadcast
I was forbidden
Uh, but it really follows this
I want to ask the guy's name
Ah, I can't remember the name of the guy who else was in
But it was a name
Oh, Lawrence King, there you go
It's just, yeah
He just got a wondering, you know, is it just coincidence
That this always ties back to politicians
Or is there something about power that drives people crazy
Or, you know, is this...
Endemic to, I don't know, it's driving me nuts
It's driving me nuts
And I think we got to, and we just got to bite the bullet
Open up a conversation about it right here on the Charlie
And then finally
This is from, uh, I love this
This is from a UPI United Press International
As an official, uh, an official news story
But it's kind of sketchy
Now, of course, we'll be talking about all the saber rattling
With Iran as they call it
So-called saber rattling
Which, of course, is completely based on the Iran's threats to start
Flooding the world's markets with cheap oil
That sold in euros, which would, of course, would kill the dollar overnight
Jerusalem, July 20th, UPI
An unnamed Israeli security official claims US President George Bush
Will attack Iran
Blate this year
If talks on the Mid East Nations nuclear program falter
Now, of course, they've been given two weeks to come up with a
Basically a statement that says, oh, we're not going to build any more
We're not going to enrich any more uranium
Even though it's, uh, our own, uh, research has shown that they're not
Developed, haven't developed any, uh, nuclear weapons since 2003
And this apparently is purely for, for energy purposes
Israeli website, Debka file, I'm sorry
Delta Echo Bravo Keto Alpha file.com Debka file
Coating Israeli National Radio reported Sunday that a quote
Highly-placed security political official said that Bush would order the attack
Between November 4th, the date of the US President's election
And his last day in office in January 2009
Should Iran not agree to abandon its efforts to enrich uranium
Debka file.com said the official made the statement
Shortly after Sunday's talks between Western powers and Iran
And Geneva ended in a deadlock
There you have it. We have a date November 4th
There you have it. And, you know, I think that, uh, just evaluating the situation
It really won't matter who wins the election
If it's McCain or if it's Obama or some other something swoops in
It's just not going to matter this shit is just going to happen
And it's fucked up and it's wrong
And Iran is a nation of young people
75% of the country is under the age of 30
Are we completely nuts? This has to stop
We cannot but this happened. We can't have this shit happen
Not under our watch
Go to our home
In two, three, four
Nothing but a chemical in my head
Nothing but laziness
I don't want to read the books
I watch movies
It's not me
I don't want to play my keyboard
I watch movies
It's not me
I don't want to play my keyboard