Did you real what I said?
Are we clear?
This is the deadly source code.
For $16 million worth of airplanes trapped by us.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
Telling this blood in the disco text.
I'll take what we've become.
Come on, let go.
I can't ask you to let me.
I want you all the stars, nobody.
Don't say so.
I'm on the sea, I like the stars.
I know.
You're broken on the inside.
The city is flowing through you.
That's what you've become.
To believe this is nothing we're saving.
There's love in the disco text.
I'll take what we've done.
Come on, let go.
I can't ask you to let me.
I want you all the stars, nobody.
Don't say so.
I'm on the sea, I like the stars.
I can't ask you to let me.
I want you all the stars, nobody.
Don't say so.
I'm on the sea, I like the stars.
You know, I'm not sure if I get off the concert.
I'm not sure if I get off the concert.
If you're a great brand new week, it's going to be a busy one.
I've got meetings on Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, maybe even Friday.
But they're not in the city.
One of them is in Kent, one of them is Sussex.
So that's just about an hour's drive away from the manner.
So I may be able to squeak out some shows.
Certainly a football Friday is in the works.
And today we're going to focus on two things.
My fellow Czechaheads.
We're going to focus on the real reason behind the high price of crude oil.
And what we can do in the meantime to alleviate our high energy prices.
At least for our automobiles and other internal combustion engine powered vehicles.
And I'm going to need your help because I haven't been able to corroborate everything.
But these two stories, I'm very excited about both because I just like the some logical reasoning behind it.
And particularly on the short-term interim solution to paying less for driving around.
I'm very excited about that because I think this actually works.
And I'm waiting to test it myself.
So we got a lot to go through.
And well, let's ease into it here for a second show.
Let's just before we get into it.
Because this is going to be a major they work for us show.
I can guarantee you that.
Let's ease into it nice and slowly here.
You know, Adam Hay, it's a group from Michigan.
Thank her.
Listen to you talk about the assessment you got.
You know, I got a assessment as well.
And it's going through the process of looking at upgrading now.
Well, hold on, let me just say.
I don't have just a assessment.
It's a 1A2RG from 1984, I believe.
So it has a big wing.
It's the last time they, the last year they even made the 1A2 with retractable gear.
And constant speed propeller.
It's a complex aircraft.
It's the flying station wagon.
I love it, too.
Also the assessment.
I'm looking for something that's got a little bit more speed to it.
You got to check out a mooney.
Excuse me.
Did I mention I get 150 knots indicated air speed?
Mooney Bravo.
Mooney Ovation.
Mooney, a claim.
Wow.
To those think of us.
I don't know if it's actually responding to the conversation I had with John C.
To Vorac over the weekend about the the serious jet, which will be available in 2010,
which I'm saving up my pennies for.
Oh, boy, what I love to have that.
Well, if we talking about a previous conversation on the Charlie, I'm not quite sure.
But I'm good for now, man.
I, until I get my, my instrument rating, I'm pretty good with the, with the Delta Sea.
All right.
The acclaim actually, I think, what's it?
Two thirty seven.
What it's rated is.
Yeah, no.
These are like 190 something.
It's those of Bravo.
The safest airline or safest airplanes in the industry.
There's never been a case of whenever breaking up in flight.
Yeah, I know guys who swear by Mooney's.
Now, if you should look this up.
M-O-O-N-E-Y.
Mooney aircraft.
They're beautiful machines.
But you know what?
They're really quite narrow.
And I do like to take people along for ride once in a while.
And it's just, it's, it's a little bit narrow.
It's, I think I would have to say it's the Ferrari of the single engine in the skies without a doubt.
But also, I want something that's pressurized.
When I, when I upgrade, I'm going straight up to pressurization so that,
I can take the lady Patricia with the up to altitude and she won't feel uncomfortable.
So, that's kind of the criteria there.
Just rock-solves.
Like, flying a tank through the air.
I'm also pre-cultivation to check all those outs.
And anyway, take care.
We think they work for us.
And the tailwinds, my friend.
Now they do tailwinds.
Tailwinds.
I'm pretty sure they do work for us.
I just got a reminder of it constantly.
And boy, are we going to do that today?
So, one of the things that we never really got into,
which I think I brought up a couple of weeks ago,
is about Florida-dated water.
And of course, Florida has been put into drinking water supplies globally.
Now, often on, lots of countries have stopped doing it.
And in the United States, it's literally by state, I think.
And of course, the, the big reasoning behind the Florida Asian of the water
has, has been, well, you know, it's, come back to tooth decay.
And, um, which is just kind of weird,
because when you go to the dentist and, you know,
back in the day when you got your fluoride treatments,
I don't know if they still do it the same way.
Um, today.
But you sit there with these plates of gunk,
and it would slowly drip down your throat,
and it would make you all nauseous and shit.
Uh, but you were definitely when I suppose to swallow it.
And, you know, when I'm drinking tap water,
I'm swallowing it.
I'm not necessarily swishing it around in my mouth.
But okay, you know, um, it's, it's what we've been told.
So I've been buying it for these many years.
Until I read the book Legacy of Ashes,
uh, which is a history of the CIA,
and according to, um,
sources very close to this.
Uh, that would be my uncle.
Um, it's pretty much spot on.
He says the book is, uh, pretty much the way it went down,
which is a sad, a real sad commentary.
Um,
but there is a passage in there where the, uh,
uh, the CIA talks about, uh,
uh, I can't remember, it's a report,
but it's also a firsthand account.
Talks about fluoridating,
a camps water to make the, uh,
uh, the guards more complacent,
and maybe a little bit lazier,
and generally easier to just go into that camp and get what they wanted.
Um, and it was just easier to convince them through the,
uh, fluoridation in fact.
Um, and I'd have to, I should look that passage up because I've talked about it a couple times.
Uh, and I will do that.
Um, the person describing this,
uh, incident even says that they had overflurited the water and everyone got the runs.
You know, it's, it's, it's not just an offhand mention.
It's really in there.
And, uh, so it says always made me question fluoridation of water,
which I believe is now being started up again in Britain.
And, you know, you just got to think, you know,
why these guys doing it?
You know, in Britain, yeah, you think that we could do a lot of work on, uh,
on people's general dental health care here,
but seems like fluoridating the water is, uh,
it's not really the way to go, you know,
how about, uh, putting it on the health care for starters.
And then this comment came in.
And once again,
made me think about what fluoridating water really might mean.
Hi, Adam, Eric's performance.
I wanted to talk a little bit about fluoride and my personal life.
I didn't always live in the Pacific Northwest.
I used to live down in Riverside, California.
And I was in the rat race man.
And, uh, our water was fluoride, uh, fluoridated.
And, uh, and I never even noticed it.
And, and now I'm up here in Portland,
and we don't fluoride the water.
And it's like my life got lazy.
It's like everything is more clear now.
It's, uh, as if a veil has been drawn away from my eyes,
and I'm much more informed, uh,
and active than I care more about what's going on.
And does that mean that the fluoride did that to me?
I don't know.
But as it's just a great, um,
common sense correlation.
Maybe.
You know, maybe.
So, uh, those bastards they worked for us.
And, uh, I'm going to go down to city hall right down.
Make sure they're doing their job.
We'll talk to you soon.
Yeah, right on.
You do that, my friend.
So when I get reports like that, I'm thinking of myself.
Mmm.
That's very, very strange.
And in particular, when I see, I was actually,
I was just, while he was talking there, uh,
I was seeing if I could find a recent report.
I thought that there were, um,
hmm, let me see him.
Maybe I'm not, I'm on the UK thing here, honor.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
Mmm.
Let's see.
Floor dating water.
Searching.
So I'm going to just sort by date.
That's probably better.
Ah.
That's all US, US, US.
Maybe I should just try fluoride.
Fluoride in water.
Hmm.
Somewhere I saw that was happening again in the UK.
I've got to go back and check that, which I will do.
Because I think it's happening, my friends,
particularly in light of what we're going to talk about.
Um,
regarding the actual reasoning behind the high price of crude oil.
I think the squeeze is, uh,
is coming to fruition.
And in fact, there's pretty much general information out there.
The things are starting to happen.
And it's just little things.
But it's always the little things that you see first.
And before you know it,
the cage has fully enclosed around us.
Check out Charlie Delta Lima,
our favorite Charles the Drunken Lundor,
what happened to him just the other day in the city of London.
Adam, hi, Charles.
Uh, I was going to just call in and say to anyone that's interested in broadcasting
or, uh, some of it's shaped nothing.
And anyone who's interested in broadcasting,
should listen to Stephen Fry's latest podgram.
Haven't done that yet.
Charles, but I certainly will.
About the BBC.
It's well worth listening.
Okay.
The other thing is, I just want to stop to search for a policeman
a common garden tube station.
Listen to this,
common garden tube station.
Uh, common garden is a beautiful place of London.
I think it's W1 or W2.
You know, it's, uh, it's just beautiful.
It's high class.
It's, uh, very expensive.
It's, but it's beautiful.
It's a nice area.
Nice surrounding.
Charles gets stopped at the tube station.
That's the subway.
Randomly stopped, I presume.
Well, no reason.
He just said, can I have a minute?
Nice and cool.
Yes, sure.
At which point?
I didn't want to allow to leave while he searched me.
I had to give over my personal details,
or which issue may weren't going any further than on this piece of paper.
Well, he, I presume, would be a constable, uh, a police official.
So, registered.
So, he said, yes.
I said, well, he can, well, it's an ID.
No, he said.
I said, well, I'll give you a fake, uh, name and a death sentence.
That's all right.
And he just looked at me and shrugged.
I said, what a waste of time.
He said, you need to speak my supervisor.
I just had a whole massive on conversation about how it was for my protection.
Why is taking my name?
Well, I was on stood outside of a Tuesday,
and it was all these onlookers.
And passing judgment as to why I've been stopped in their heads.
Mainly weren't who cares.
That's not the point.
They're taking my name and addressed it.
For what reason?
How is that protecting society that that man's looked in my bag?
Really?
It's ridiculous.
What a waste of time.
I'm ashamed of this country sometimes.
Many of that.
Yeah, sure.
I'll work for us, then.
Yeah, hell, yeah.
Yeah.
My friend, my friend, it's starting.
And if my research from over the weekend is correct,
this is just the beginning of a very painful journey.
But of course, we can stop this.
So let me tell you what I've learned.
One thing led to another, actually.
I was turned on to this energy-saving device,
or concept, really, of which a number of devices are made,
called the Hydroxy Booster.
And I'm going to talk about that a little bit later on in the show,
which is basically a very simple way to create hydrogen
from water, from electrolyzing water.
So basically putting a current through water,
and mounting a small set up in your automobile,
creating a vapor of hydrogen,
and injecting that into your engine,
basically through the air filters, through the manifold,
or the air intake.
And it's quite amazing because people are achieving
if I can believe the results are spoken to a few people personally on the phone,
who say they are seeing these results of fuel efficiency improvement.
And sometimes, well, the average claim seems to be about 25%.
But I have seen claims up to 50% or even higher.
Which, of course, when you're talking about $4, a gallon of gasoline,
if you can get 25% efficiency, that effectively is a buck less.
So that's a really big deal.
And that's a short term solution we're going to have to implement
in order to get through the following period.
And this period is not going to be good.
And this period is probably for the next six months.
Let me explain.
So I ran across, I'm going to bring up curry.com
where you can find this for yourself.
So in my research for alternative fuel, et cetera,
I come across a link, which leads to a Google video,
which is a lecture from a guy named, there he is,
a guy named Lindsay Williams.
Now, Lindsay Williams looks a little bit like Charlottom,
hasden, by the way.
And this is an hour and a half long speech.
Yeah, back in the early 70s,
he was a pastor on the North, on the Alaskan pipeline project.
And he was there for many years.
He was basically the pastor and, you know,
of course, in a way psychiatrist and a sounding board
for the thousands of men who were working up,
and women who were working on the Alaskan project,
the Alaskan pipelines.
And so he actually, he befriended a lot of people
and including the CEO of one of the large oil corporations
at the time, which I think has since been bought
by one of the other big six,
what is it, five or six companies that you have now.
And so it became very close, and he actually witnessed
in a board room, and this was in the mid 70s,
when they struck a huge oil field on the northern slope of Alaska.
I think that's what he says, the northern slope is the way he calls it.
Or the northern shelf.
And this oil field in Alaska, which, of course, is US territory,
is perhaps the largest in the world.
And he was there when they were celebrating
and just freaking out about how this was going to be headline news
the next day, this was going to be it.
Finally, America had energy independence from the rest of the world.
Our worries are over.
We could be filling up gas for a bucket gallon,
at least by today's prices, buck buck and a half.
A lot less back in the 70s.
And they were all elated.
And this guy witnessed it.
He keeps talking about how he was there.
The next day, he gets called in and they say,
look, you never heard about that.
That never happened.
We can't talk about it.
And there's a couple of reasons.
And this guy actually wrote a book called The Energy Non Crisis.
William's L-I-N-D-S-E-Y.
Williams.
And he goes on in this lecture, which you can watch,
at curry.com.
Just watch the Google video.
He goes on this lecture to describe,
basically why the price of oil is so high today,
and who is in control of the prices.
So it gives us a little bit of a history lesson.
So again, this is like an hour and a half,
but it'll really help if I give you the synopsis.
There won't be a big surprise.
Pay off at the end, because I'm going to tell you
who's jacking these prices up.
My theory is not far off from Lindsey Williams theory.
And I'm saying theory, because I don't know if it's true,
but man, this guy comes across as incredibly credible.
So you'll remember, some of you remember,
if not, you can look it up in the mid-70s.
Henry Kissinger was the Secretary of State,
I think, or was the Minister of Foreign Affairs,
Secretary of State, I believe.
He went around to the Middle East at the time when,
by the way, in the 60s, and the late 60s,
a decision to pretty much been made by the powers that be,
that we were going to be an economy based on crude oil.
And that mainly has to do with transportation and plastics.
Everything that's plastic eventually comes from crude oil.
So although it's not the largest use as far as I know of crude oil,
it certainly is a very important one.
So crude oil was going to be our economy,
particularly as it comes to transportation.
So that decision was made.
There were a couple of decisions they could have made.
I presume if you're going by 2020 as hindsight, right?
But it was kind of a setup because here's what they did.
Henry Kissinger went to the Middle East and went to every single country
when they were still, you know, camel jockey's riding backwards.
And he said, you know what?
We're going to buy oil from you.
We're going to make you rich.
We're going to make you rich beyond your wildest dreams.
We're going to make you leave your harem rich.
Okay?
Now, there's only one thing we do.
We're going to sign this contract.
And we're going to buy all of your oil.
But the deal is A, you're going to only buy and so you're only going to sell all oil
to anyone who wants it in the US dollar currency.
And B, you're going to take a portion of percentage,
which by the way, Lindsay Williams never mentions what it is.
But you're going to take a percentage of the money you receive for your oil.
And you're going to buy the American National debt with that money.
Okay?
Now, this corroborates, by the way, with the book,
Confessions of an economic hitman by John Perkins,
which I have talked about before, and I've talked about it with John C.
to Warack, I know, agenda.
Where, indeed, these economic hitmen went into all these countries
and would convince the leaders to basically sign on the dotted line,
by the way, giving them hundreds of millions of advance,
you know, just to start off with.
And they would then receive all this money from the World Bank
and the International Monetary Fund to get set up,
to get everything rolling, and subsequently,
so there's a lot of, not real money flowing back and forth,
but a lot of paperwork, a lot of computer database entries
as to who owed what, because these guys, of course,
were actually buying the American debt,
which by the way, today, I think stands at nine trillion dollars.
How do you run up debt, by the way?
Well, one way to run up the debt is by giving everyone
universal health care, that would be a way.
But of course, the way that is typically chosen by the United States
is to wage war on people, and war, of course,
always makes some people a very few incredibly rich.
That's the whole military industrial complex.
So they got this rolling, and of course, the entire United States economy
now relies on the fact that oil is traded a button sold
in the US currency, so there's always a need for dollars,
and you can see where that has now gotten a little bit out of whack,
where the value of the dollar has gone down,
so more dollars are printed by the treasury,
and we kind of get in this weird spiral.
But why the high oil prices?
Well, here it comes. You're going to love this.
So there's a couple of steps before oil gets into your gas tank
as gasoline.
The first is getting the oil out of the ground,
so that's what they do in the middle east.
They get it out of the ground.
Then there's a middle guy, and that middle guy basically determines
what the price they're going to pay for that crude oil.
And then that middle guy, again, he's sitting in the middle,
enables the refineries to buy it.
Now, of course, the refineries have benefited tremendously
from these high prices, but they are not the ones to blame.
They're not the ones jacking up the price.
Of course, they're benefiting from it,
but they are not at fault.
And of course, from the refineries, it gets their gas stations
and gets into your tank.
So who actually manages that little in-between piece
when it comes out of the ground in the middle east?
Just imagine it's spurting out of the ground
now it has to be traded to anyone who wants to buy it
and, of course, in US dollars.
That, my friends, is the World Bank.
The international monetary fund.
And they do that.
And this is all according to Lindsey Williams,
but Boyd is the sound right to me.
And they do that with a calculation.
Part of it, of course, is the, you know,
the national debt gets purchased back,
but they literally can decide what the price is going to be today.
It's completely up to them.
If they said tomorrow, you know what?
We'll make it a hundred bucks.
They could make it a hundred bucks, no problem.
Because the middle east, they're just saying,
all right, yeah, what are you going to pay us for it?
They're not negotiating.
They're just taking whatever is decided by the powers that be.
In this case, the World Bank of the International Monetary Fund.
Now, there were two countries in the Middle East,
who did not sign this deal when Henry Kissinger went around
getting everybody to sign up to a fantastic way.
And by the way, it's, what a great idea.
I can totally understand the scam
and how they set it up.
And it's obviously very, very controlling.
But in a way, genius to set it up to have the American economy
basically continuously be fueled by literally fueled by crude oil
and the fact that everything is bought and sold in dollars
and that a portion of all the money spent
goes straight to financing the national debt,
which, of course, made a whole bunch of other people really,
really rich think about how a burden as an example.
Can you guess which two countries didn't sign the agreement?
The first one was Iraq.
Yeah, what a surprise there, huh?
That's why George H. Bush had to go in
and had to go and kick Saddam's ass and get him in the line
because he was threatening all kinds of shit
about what he was going to do with his oil,
which, of course, is one of the three largest oil fields
in the world underneath Iraq.
And he failed basically.
He had to wait eight years for his son to do it.
That's right.
George W. Then George W. has succeeded
because he went in.
He had, well, effectively Saddam was saying
got taken care of.
And as you know, the large oil companies are now splitting up
all the money there.
They're taking care of everything.
They're splitting up the oil and they have control.
Of course, it's, you know, democratically approved contracts
and all that kind of crap.
But we know who's really in control, right?
So he succeeded.
Interestingly, though, even though we have all this new oil
that's going to be coming in, haven't had oil from Iraq
for the past 30 years in the United States,
interestingly, price of oil hits 142 goes up a little bit higher.
Hmm, I wonder why.
Well, what's the other country do you think?
Yes, the other country that never signed,
the agreement is Iran.
Now does that war-mongering and saber-raddling start to make sense?
Why does even Hillary Clinton or Barack Obama?
Why are they saying, oh, yeah, you know,
well, you know, if there's, if we weapons a mass destruction
we got to go in there and kick Iran's ass.
It's not about that.
According to this theory, what's happening is Iran
and you can look this one up, just Google it,
has threatened two things.
One, they're going to set up their own oil exchange.
We've talked about this before.
Two, the oil exchange will trade in euros,
not in the dollar.
So, if Iran and, of course,
they've actually promised to flood the world markets
with cheap oil traded in euros.
So let's just imagine that happened for a second.
Iran, which is one of the top three, you know,
largest oil fields in the world,
just like Iraq and Saudi Arabia.
And, of course, we have Alaska in the US,
so let's say, top four, top five.
If they tomorrow decide to flood the world with cheap oil
and base the payments on euros,
the American dollar will collapse overnight,
including the entire economy.
I mean, people will be, as far as I can see,
will be taking wheel barrels full of money
to just go buy bread, familiar, doesn't it?
Sounds familiar.
So, of course, the exact same would have happened.
If all of a sudden, the word had gotten out
that, oh my goodness, we have all this oil.
We're no longer dependent on foreign oil.
Everything we need for the next 200 years is available in Alaska.
What would happen?
We'd have no one to buy our national debt.
The exact same thing would happen,
the dollar would collapse.
There's a tremendous conundrum.
And from what Lindsey Williams says,
all these guys are in audit.
Everybody knows it,
but they can't, as he says,
they can't tell the American people because,
well, I guess we'd freak out.
But what they have decided to do instead is to bomb a ran.
And from all the data I've been able to collect,
it appears that this moment of a ran flooding
the world markets with cheap oil is drawing close.
They're oil trading boards.
They're exchange.
Opened in February.
Now, it seems there were some sabotages
to their undersease cables.
You might have picked up on that here or there
that some cables were cutting.
There was a question as to how that happened.
Well, it totally fits in the line now with this story.
And they're open.
They're trading.
And indeed, they are trading in euros.
There's not a lot of activity going on as far as I can see.
But all they need to do is say,
you know what, guys, we've got tons of oil over here.
Once you get it, we'll sell it to you for 20 bucks a barrel.
But oh, by the way, it's not actually in bucks.
You're going to pay, I guess it would be like 12 euros a barrel.
Could you imagine that?
So this cannot happen.
And this is the reason why there's,
there's all this threatening language going out towards a run.
Now, why is the price of oil still so high?
So I think we can kind of draw two conclusions here.
One is, someone needs to be making a shitload of money.
That would be the world bank.
What are they doing?
They're trying to, I guess, repay or pay down the national debt
before any huge massive event would take place.
Like, you know, if, for example,
Iran flooding the world with cheap oil,
can you imagine that if we had a $9 trillion debt,
$9 trillion of national debt,
that all of a sudden, you know,
can barely be paid off because no one's trading oil
and dollars anymore.
And that would be, you know, that would be horrible.
So I think what's happening here,
and this is kind of what William says,
we are actually at this point,
being taxed through the high fuel prices,
paying back our own national debt.
Other countries are paying back national debt.
Interestingly enough, all a whole bunch of third world countries,
all of their debt got wiped off.
The world banks said, hey, you know, you guys are done.
You don't have to pay us back.
I think it's because we've paid it back.
So this warrants a lot of investigation.
Because if what this Lindsey Williams says really is true,
and this is a video you'll see this from October 2007,
where the price of gas were still around
under $3, and he literally sits there and predicts he says,
the price of gas is going to be $45 very soon.
And if we don't do something about this,
if we don't force George Bush and Dick Cheney to come clean
and say honestly, what's going on and why they went into a rack
and why they want to bomb Iran,
if they don't just come clean and say it so we can have an open dialogue
and work on this problem as a global population,
then indeed we're in for some shitty times.
Shitty times ahead my fellow chuckleheads.
And I'm not looking forward to that.
When I hear all these calls coming in about Florida,
should I hear noise about randomly being searched in London?
Makes me worried.
So what can we do about it?
I'd like to hear from you.
I'm going to play a song for you now,
and then we'll talk about how at least we can stay mobile while we're fighting
this seemingly crazy situation if true.
Let's just assume it is for arguments sake, okay?
I'm going to play a song for you.
Yeah.
Eagles, P Betterl California, live.
I showed up on the source code drop.
Drop.au slash daily source code.
Great place for additional information.
Shuckleheads from all over the world posting cool stuff.
It's kind of a blog.
It's a community blog slash.
I love it.
those guys, great company, cool stuff you're doing. Okay, so from our own
little hotel California where you can check it, check out, but you can never leave.
How do we power ahead? How do we keep moving with four to five dollar a gallon
gasoline and really nine to ten dollars over in Europe? Well, I've been looking
around and so I came up with this concept and really the original bleed I got
was from a couple of sites where I read about this guy named Stanley Myers.
You may remember him, he apparently created a dune buggy that ran completely on
hydrogen gas, created on the fly from water, which is just fabulous. Now, he passed
away, of course, as all kinds of conspiracy theories about what happened to him there.
And I've really been researching from most of the weekend and it seems like this whole
interim step, this process called hydroxy boost, which is basically creating a
little bit of hydrogen on board while you're driving, mixing that with the fuel.
Of course, the hydrogen is going to take place of regular fuel, but it also burns.
So you're basically using, yes, less gasoline. And, you know, you're supplementing that
with with gases, which consist of hydrogen, which will also explode and will also
power your engine. And I've been looking at all these science that have been
cropping up. And of course, this is not really a business. You know, I see a lot of
people trying to make a business out of it. And you could make one for yourself, you know,
by yourself, for yourself from parts from a hardware store, probably, you know, if you're
a novice or if you're even expert, even better, if you really good with your hands
unlike myself, you could probably make one for like 50 or 60 bucks, get all the pieces
that you need. So these people out there selling kits, you know, ranging from
what looks like a jam jar with electrodes in it and some pieces of tubing to
really nicely constructed aluminium things. I mean, there's a whole range.
But really what's interesting to see is that these sites have really, you know,
they've been around for a while. This is not a new technology by any means. In fact,
you know, creating, you've probably seen this at school at high school, maybe even
in your science class, where you create hydrogen from two electrodes, put into
water, you put a current on and then you can ignite it and it will actually burn or
depending if you if you trap it or if you can make it explode. So these sites have
been cropping up in the past six months. And this is obviously because now it
really makes sense. You know, if you have a little bit of fuel efficiency, and again,
the jury's kind of out, but it looks like fuel efficiency is somewhere between
25 and 50 percent. And it, of course, reduces your CO2 emissions because
part of what you're burning doesn't actually release any CO2 emissions, because
the, the final product of exploding hydrogen is water.
Now, that said, I want to try one out on the, on the jag. I desperately want
to try one out. And, you know, I've, I've spent probably in total 10 hours
non-stop in aggregate, 10 hours of looking at different sites, looking at
different kits, you know, there's, you know, do I need some kind of electronics to
fool my, my engine management into, because of course, it's a newer vehicle
into thinking that, you know, the mixture has to be leaned a little bit. There's
a whole bunch of stuff. And I'm sure out there somewhere in the audience is either
a chucklehead who is experienced enough and understands this that he can enlighten
us, or perhaps even people who are already doing this. I've not heard a single
person ever mentioned a hydroxy booster. Hydroxy, also known as an HHO
generator or a hydrogen generator. You know, there's all kinds of sites. And
most of these sites are, you know, bordering on MLM type activity, multi-level
marketing. Um, it's like, you know, fuel, water, car, dot com, and go ahead and just
Google, um, hydroxy, hotel Yankee, Delta, Romeo, Oscar, X-ray, Yankee,
booster, hydroxy booster. Go ahead and Google that and you'll find a whole bunch of
sites. Uh, maybe I'll put a couple of them into the show notes at
resource.com. But man, oh, man, I'm very excited by this because for a relatively low
cost, I'm seeing testimonial. And I spoke this morning to someone in, uh, in Holland,
who's actually had one installed for six months. He says, I'm getting, um, about a
40% increase in, uh, in fuel efficiency miles per gallon. It says the car runs
quieter. It runs better. And it feels like it has more horsepower, which is by the way,
you know, kind of the same benefits we saw with biodiesel. Although biodiesel is still,
you know, you really got a, you got a process that you got to make it, you got to
make enough of it. And this, you know, you're talking about, you know, like a
leader of water. And you can drive five, six hundred kilometers on that. And it
will supplement, um, it'll supplement what's going into, you know, the, the, the
mixture that's going into your engine. Therefore, effectively reducing the amount of
water that you have to use. I mean, if it really does work, and this is, and again,
for everything I'm seeing, I think it does work. I can desperate to try one out.
I don't know if there's anyone in the United Kingdom who's doing that. I'd love to
get something local because I'm sure that me with my two left hands, I'll need some help
installing it. It's not really difficult because essentially nothing goes into the
engine. You know, you install the unit. You got to hook it up to power. Um,
and of course, you got to, you know, set it properly. So it gets to, you know,
it's all about the management of how many amps you're putting into the water to,
to start separating the, the water out, breaking it down to produce the hydrogen.
And, you know, then also the thickness of the tubing that you want to,
literally stick into your, your intake. So your air filter is pretty much where
most people seem to be sticking this tube. So, you know, it's completely
removable. You can take it out when you sell the car. Um, and, you know,
and this is like a non business community oriented type thing that we could
really work on together. Again, no one is going to make this a business because
all you're doing is selling pieces of plastic that fit together.
And the total value of the parts really isn't all that high.
And it's kind of like, it's like an open source thing. You know,
there's, yeah, there's patents all over the place, but the basic principles
everyone can apply. So, you know, there's no one who can really corner the market
hence doesn't seem like anyone is really doing anything on any kind of scale.
If someone is, please send me a link. If not, let's figure it out together
and I'm desperate to try this out. This is so exciting to me if it actually works.
So what should we do? Want to play on now? I'm not going to play another song.
I'll just end this show. Let me see. What do we have to time watch? Yeah, perfect.
Okay, so hopefully tomorrow I'll have some answers and we'll go down these two trails.
Again, I'm looking for corroboration of the Lindsey William story,
which is just frighteningly you think about it. And of course, a
minor little light there at the end of the tunnel of our hotel California is the
fact that we might actually be able to travel cheaper. Shipman, I'll fit
off at one of those suckers on the Delta Shira. I'm loving that idea.
So until we speak again, keep the voice mail lines buzzing. You can find them at
dailysourceco.com. Drop anything you feel is relevant to the
chuckle heads at drop.io slash daily source code. And of course, you can always email
email me at amercurry.com until we meet again.
Live your life with passion and while it lasts. Enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation. Stick it in your ear.