September 5th, 2008, it's Fubar Friday.
This is the Secretary of War at the State Department of the United States.
We have a problem.
The company wants something down about the sluggish world economic situation.
The problem is that the running bar is a little thin lately.
We need to manipulate some growth.
We know that there's a alarmingly high number of young people running around in your country
with something to do with a drop from over the police.
The damaged private property all says it will fight forever.
About time, this is the biggest struggle with these people.
Thousands of near-two are crawling over.
The companies think it's time to laugh the sound of a series get together
and start another war on home.
A president who already loves the idea of all of those miserable,
dreaming over his two bro, people running down the road,
thinking not to fire.
Oh, don't just leave up for us.
The government thinks it's been a real thing for years.
Oh, we're gonna move going away from the minister's brazeness.
Oh, hell.
I can't have said no fun with that.
What do you say?
Oh, we don't even have to win this war.
We just want to cut down on some of these things.
There's no relation.
Now that you've started the draft,
the draft is meaningful.
We can, we'll call up every last gun
so we can get our hands on it.
Give them an hour or two to learn how to use an automatic rifle.
We'll end them on their way.
Oh, follow on.
We don't have Northern Ireland.
We're proud to be a president of South America.
Oh, well, let's just cook up a good,
so be a threat story in the Middle East.
We need that oil.
We're going to be already done.
Girl, we can not think it's just a grudge.
It's even show up.
Oh, I can't.
That man is unrivaled.
Oh, we're right in the feather figure of a bunch of like we did for that one.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Just cook for a minute.
Oh, we can make this war.
So be it.
The more people he killed in this war,
the more the economy will prosper.
Oh, we can get rid of practically everybody on your own.
Do, do, you do.
Come.
We won't be here tonight.
Take every blow for our welfare right off the theater.
Oh, no, where is our food demonstrator?
Just pump up your truck for temporada.
Thank you so much.
Have a couple of Pupples, some dot hair on it,
and Mbem!
That means some sweet Wegover.
Puss and brag, do you hit next?
We ain't everywhere, dear neighbours.
We ain't everybody posing with MSD,
They never got to, your ride.
All right, you have to learn a bunch of things that's fine.
It's easy.
All right, we've got our cards, kids.
So interested in beer.
Very good beer.
We've got many factors here, Bob.
Again.
Oh, no clear.
Thought I was there back here.
I don't even know what it looks like.
But how about it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's excellent.
We knew you to agree.
The companies will be very pleased.
Delta share a Charlie 787.
It's fine, everybody.
It's time for the football.
For $60 million worth of beer, play extrapped by us.
For the next generation video content in my ears.
We know you're not thinking it turns in.
I like a drink of wine.
You can turn it.
Oh, I've got to take this out of the car.
That's a credit with success.
The ambition for access, access.
As the top of the month, it comes a bottom line with success.
It's a credit with success.
It's time to finish the money.
That's the defeat we're really bad for the honey.
Maybe honey, but you money way of mouth, bit run into town.
It's been a few months, honey.
All of us are sick.
It doesn't feel like freedom.
We're the family, we can't jail.
We're the living dog who'll pay your praise.
It's time for the money we're really good.
We're the family, we're the family.
We're the family.
We're the money we're good.
Success is a credit with success.
We need to find for the people that like sex.
As the top of the month, it comes a bottom line with success.
It's a credit with success.
All of us are sick.
It doesn't feel like freedom.
We're the family, we can jail.
We're the living dog who'll pay your praise.
It's time for the money we're really good.
it's time for the money we're really good.
It is time for the money we're really good.
It's time for the money we are really good.
It's time for the money we're really good.
I'm really good.
The money we're really chilling in is great.
It's time for the money we're really good.
that makes total sense with all of the Atlantic activity
taking place between Jamaica, Cuba, the South Coast,
the Florida, the Gulf Coast, everything's connected.
So when a butterfly flaps its wings
if it can stir up a hurricane, well,
then you would expect as they're calling them now,
the Atlantic storms to be connected to all of that.
So we've got a lot of wet weather.
We have the chance of some flooding.
It's just another day in the neighborhood.
But yes, everything source from the drop,
drop.au slash daily source code.
Let me just write down a note to myself.
I wanted to put a redirect on,
I'm going to make drop.daleesourcecode.com,
go straight to the source code drop.
And maybe even I'll make a drop.curry.com, go to it.
Whew, I got some news from those guys.
Later on, today we've got a full blown, full on,
full bar Friday.
Everything you'd expect, all of the awesomeest music.
And of course, aggregating the real news
from around the world, some things,
super important, some things less important.
First of all, let me tell you,
the thank you all very much for the birthday greetings
that you sent me most of it through email this year.
In fact, I only received three physical cards,
which is the least I've ever received ever,
in all 44 years that I can remember.
One from Patricia, one from Christina,
and one from Christina's friend, Dexter,
who I'm sure would be hearing about
in future episodes of The Charity Dexter's cool guy.
Finally, a boyfriend, I actually kind of like off the bat.
And everything else came through email.
There was so much, literally,
and I haven't been able to respond to it all.
Of course, I've marked everything.
Oh, make sure, I send a nice little note back to everybody.
I hope I make it through as you so much,
just so much that came in.
And the email's been hopping in general, man.
It's like, all this stuff has happened at the same time.
We've got, well, we're gonna talk about that today.
We've got Georgia heating up again.
We've got possible Iran attacks heating up again.
We've got the financial crisis melting down even more.
Of course, we've got the biggest show on,
or the second to biggest show on Earth,
I'd have to say the Republican National Convention,
still number two to the Democratic Convention,
television wise, from a show perspective,
show business, as you know, politics is, of course,
show business for ugly people.
But with Sarah Palin in there,
they've got some good actors.
So that part, I really like.
And news today, I've been waiting for this
when I haven't looked into the official report yet,
but the news is on that British Airways triple seven
that landed short of the runway.
He threw about a thousand feet short,
and severely damaged the plane.
And one person was seriously injured,
but everyone else was okay, of course.
They're saying, now, it was ice in the fuel line.
Whoa, that doesn't sound like, here.
The accident, there was not the fault of the flight crew,
as the Air Accidents Investigation Branch
has said in internal reports.
So once again, this is another internal report,
not the full blown deal.
It also ruled out the problems with the amount of quality
of the fuel focusing instead on build up of ice
in the system.
This is not very good, and I'm not quite sure how that happens.
I don't know enough about these aircraft,
but ice in the system, it's not supposed to happen.
And still, I guess there's no word on holding
down the entire fleet.
Oh, here we go, Boeing recommended all 11 airlines globally
that fly triple sevens with the Rolls Royes engines,
including American and Delta Airlines,
takes steps designed to minimize chances of ice build up.
This sounds like a pretty serious flaw to me.
So still waiting for the final report
from the A, it was the A-A-I-B.
That's the British version of the F-A-A.
And we're at T-minus five and counting my friends
September 10th will be the 10th day of the nine month,
ninth month of the eighth year of the year's 2000
of the millennium, 2000, second millennium.
That's when they fire up that the L-H-C,
the Lord Hadron Collider in Geneva.
Now, of course, we've talked about this in the Charlie,
and we've gone through multiple explanations,
but still there were not one but two lawsuits,
one from the U.S., another one was European lawsuit,
whose aim it was to stop the physicist at CERN
from flipping the switch on this thing in five days from now,
there's still a concern about creation of black holes
and the earth being sucked inside out.
I don't know, but I don't think they're going to stop,
but I think this thing is all go ahead
and all lights are green, all systems go.
They're still trying to find out exactly what took place
in the split, literally, split second
after the big bang occurred, which,
and here's the thing that I don't understand about this,
because this is a heavily subsidized project.
We have about $14 billion is what it's cost.
I think over 30 countries have participated in the finance
and have scientists on the scene,
a lot of them really young with the snappers.
I can say that now that I'm 44.
But if this is to show something that happened
after the big bang, doesn't that do away with,
I mean, doesn't that go head to head
with a lot of the Christian Democratic parliament around Europe,
I'm thinking of Germany as an example,
the Netherlands, this is obviously,
you're talking about divine creation versus evolutionary theory.
How come there's not a whole bunch of religious groups
up in arms about this?
If they're not out to prove that God's for real,
they're out to prove the, well, something they call the God particle.
It's the, what is that called?
The Higgs boson.
Oops, what was that?
Battery full.
Oh man, next week remind me, I want to do a,
I get another little update on the E71.
I've learned some more things, found some new software.
There's the Nokia cell phone that I bought instead of an iPhone.
Pretty much still all good stuff.
I just, I won't have time for it today.
So T-minus 5 and counting, September 10th,
that's, let's see, six, seven, and as I Wednesday,
next Wednesday, let me just check on the calendar real quick.
A bit shit is.
Yeah, next Wednesday, September 10th.
I wonder what time they're gonna fire that thing up?
Wait, it just, ah, kind of, kind of frightens me.
So as I mentioned earlier, I had some news from the drop.io folks.
Well, I think they, they actually called themselves dropio.
Dropio, I'll just call them drop.io.
They have an extra feature, which is not officially released yet,
although it does work.
I don't know if they've put anything in their homepage,
but they call it the paywall
and they've done something really interesting.
You could now, and this is what I like about what these guys
do, and they're just tying in all these APIs
into a basic kind of web-log like format or a storage system.
It goes way beyond file sharing,
as the chuckle heads will know, we use this extensively
for the preparation of the daily source code.
And it's for links, it's for notes, it's for embeds,
it's for voicemail, which finally some people
starting to use a little bit more, I appreciate that.
But now you can also hook it up to the Amazon Payment System.
So you can close off a drop and give people access
based upon a payment.
So you could say, well, you can look at this one time,
we can look at it for a day, for a week, or for a month,
based upon your payment.
And it all runs through Amazon, which I guess you can
mean, means you can use a credit card.
I don't know if they take PayPal, but certainly a credit card.
And I think this is a very interesting addition
to the drop scenario.
I mean, for instance, you could make, how about this?
If you want to go buy a song, or if you want to sell your song,
or sell anything, any type of digital asset,
you put it into the drop and you say, look,
once you've paid your money, you can access the drop and download it.
I think you could even set it up for multiple accesses.
So you would have maybe 10 times to download something.
There's all kinds of really cool opportunities.
And I'm even thinking, Devor, I can I
might want to look into one of these and see if we can get
to make some money out of no agenda that way.
You know, maybe giving you access to the show notes
for an extra payment.
I don't know.
Well, we'll try anything at this point.
We're so freaking desperate.
But good on those guys at drop.io, because they
whoa, sorry about that.
Because they really got some awesome stuff going on.
And I think it fits in perfectly with what we're doing here
with the audio production distributed independently.
Here's the flow box.
Source from the drop, of course.
This is We Are Winning on the Charmly.
787, full bar Friday edition.
Driver games are sitting down to the planet
after school program.
The religious fanatic hosts footage of an
interfaith service project.
The group of teenage boys watches a video of a
public page with his son.
An adult film star.
From their portraits of elderly couples.
Full of love and smiling.
A regular executive, according to the law, is apology.
A policeman makes reverse 911 calls,
instructing residents to nature's streets.
The patriarchy for children.
She's wearing an orange dress,
and holding a kids' line.
She's ashamed of her abilities.
The treat is not an opium.
Women and children from live,
walk on tuning, stand and be counted.
In the belly of the voice.
There's no civilians women.
Children from live listen.
Consider this a disc or the warning.
The virus imminent pollution.
Gathering tough particles.
What a thing, through smoke stacks.
Airways, man with.
Disimformation through fetching the labels.
Delete the virus, alert the masses.
Much of my wing crosswinds.
Send black hawks toward hurricane survivors.
Rose is sprung from empty lungs.
Inside walkfronts.
As if his burikers move undetected.
Through concrete jungles.
New forms are beginning to take shape.
Once occupied minds are activating.
People are waking up.
The insurgency is alive and well.
Rise to the blue box.
Portrait host.
Do American internship.
Foundations of the world.
An assembly line.
Send the resist.
Reviews.
In 438.
Direct.
Love wants to the traces.
Super 40.
Rumble into fortresses.
Plast across the globe.
Broken porcelain.
Rise to black blue.
Red blood stains from decompressed diamonds.
Hammered the battle cry into Braille studded armor.
Building up in you world.
Do not sit tightly by.
Enough remaining neutral.
Do not rely on this broadcast alone.
We are only as strong as our single.
There is a war going on for your mind.
If you are thinking, you are winning.
Resistance is victory.
The defeat is impossible.
Your weapons are already in hand.
Reach within.
And find the means by which to gain no freedom.
Hide with tools.
Your faith is a matter of everyone you know.
Decide subject.
Ain't that the truth?
The floor box.
She known from the handlebar.
So I want you to play previously on the Charlie.
This is we are winning.
Acceler.
Excellent.
That's right.
Just be in a wake.
We have the tools.
We have got them.
And our fingertips utilizing them as we speak.
Through programs like this.
Very one.
The daily source code.
Of course, it's the food bar Friday.
Lots of stuff to get through.
Actually, this comment will kick off the next section.
We're going to discuss.
Add a very important.
I was just watching John McCain and the Sarah Palin thing.
And going, wow.
It's like a magician.
You know.
There's a still canker chip over here.
Don't look at what's really going on.
You know, Cheney is in Georgia.
And the Dutch are out of our ran.
There's U.S. ground troops in Pakistan.
What the hell is going on?
There is no coverage in the mainstream media of this stuff.
And you have to hear your opinion on that.
Well, why do we can train my hand?
Hell, yeah, my brother.
Yeah, of course.
You know, that's that's what it's all about.
I told you the Republican National Convention, just like the DNC.
Biggest show on earth.
The, the second biggest show, the Olympics was used for the.
The cowardly attack of Georgia on to South Assetia, which, of course, has been distorted
in most of the mainstream media as Russia being the bad guys.
Now, Russia not exactly the nicest guys, but they're all thugs.
And all of them are.
But that's right.
Dick Cheney got it right here.
Of course, good links in the, in the show notes for today's program.
I've got this new system worked out where it's really easy to transfer all these links over.
So this is a BBC story.
U.S. vice president, Dick Cheney has said,
Ukraine has the right to live without fear of invasion,
adding that the U.S. stands by its bid for NATO membership.
Now, notice this is about the Ukraine.
Okay, he's, he's all over the place.
He arrived in Ukraine and then he hopped over to Georgia and just a billion,
a billion dollars in aid going to Georgia based upon, I mean,
it's so easy to see what's happening when you, when you really let it all unfold,
but the, the little details are just phenomenal.
So obviously, Republican National Convention going on.
That's what's dominating the news.
Cheney's over there and he's, he's hooking up his buddies.
And it's all for good reason because what happens when, I mean,
NATO is not necessarily about protection about, you know,
if we add Georgia and Ukraine to NATO.
It's about selling weapons to them.
That's what it's about.
So these guys won't be tinkering around with AK47s,
which by the way, work pretty well.
They're cheap to make, but you know, it'll be American stuff.
American weaponry.
That's what it's about.
So that billion dollars in aid is,
it's, it's really going to go right back into the,
the military industrial complex.
Unfortunately, you know, these countries will have to pay.
It was a Georgia if they get a billion bucks through the IMF.
Or how it doesn't even matter how is given to them.
There's always interest on it.
They'll never be able to pay that back.
And that's when we take over and say,
all right, well, you couldn't pay that.
So we'll take our collateral, which, of course,
is usually taken in the form of rights to minerals and gas and oil.
So the system is still in full swing.
But this one I hadn't heard yet.
And I, and I did like it as a kind of an extra theory.
News, this is from the Irish Times, IrishTimes.com.
And this is another, a little byproduct of this,
this whole Georgia South, the city, a Russian bad guy thing.
Is that Putin, I'm not Putin, I'm sorry.
It's our cozy.
That's the, the president of France, of course.
And he is, you know, currently they hold the presidency
of the European Union.
And let me see, the headline of this story,
lack of Lisbon Treaty hinders EU response to Russian action.
Well, isn't that interesting?
There are fears in the EU capitals that the crisis in Georgia
could spill over into other countries in the region with large Russia
minorities, such as Ukraine and Moldova.
Speculation about a new cold war is also gathering
either in peace and Brussels, which is move surprisingly quick to put itself
in the front line of peace efforts since full-scale conflict
broke out on August 10th.
I'm going to see if I can find the quote here.
That's our cozy is saying that really neat here it is.
Here we go.
Negotiating a ceasefire forcing Russia to backtrack on
his decision to recognize the independence of South the city
and Abkhazia are two different things.
And the results of the summit highlights Europe's limitations
when it acts in the field of foreign affairs, particularly in its
dealings with Russia and then he goes on to say,
look, essentially if we get this Lisbon Treaty work
and then we can really stand together as a united front,
which of course goes right back to what the with Irish who
voted no, the only country of the 727 member states to say no
to the referendum, no to the Lisbon Treaty.
They were right.
They said, hey, this is about creating a European army.
They don't want any part of it.
We don't like it.
We don't like that way.
And here it is.
Circusy saying, you know, we're severely hampered.
We can't do anything because, you know, we really don't have all the
means. It's all in the Lisbon Treaty.
Do you think all of this was planned one way or the other?
Do you think it was kind of, you know, this is why they were
rushing to get this thing done by October.
This Lisbon Treaty to form the United States of Europe.
Wow.
I'd say it sure seems that way.
I'm just going to stick with, with this particular part of the
world for a second article from the Times online.
Even though Georgia is not yet, and it'll take some time and
some ratification and whatever is necessary to get into
NATO.
Of course, the US were, you know, big proponents of it to start
off with.
They have already hooked the Georgian radar systems into the
NATO early warning system.
This according to the Times, which I'd say is a pretty reliable
paper in many cases.
And, uh, there we go. Alliance officials alliance.
Who's the alliance? Oh, the US led alliance.
Interesting.
Nice. Anyway, so we're in a new alliance.
Alliance officials said the arrangement enabled NATO radar
specialists to be linked up to the Georgian radar systems.
It means NATO can now see what the Georgians are seeing through
the radar as effectively allowing the alliance.
Start fleet alliance.
To monitor what is going on over Georgian air space without having
military assets in place.
Cracky.
I mean, can you imagine someone doing that like in Canada?
Or it just, you know, figure in the US or Mexico?
Or Texas for that reason?
Can you imagine this taking place right across, you know,
sovereign border?
And meanwhile, Putin, I mean, this guy's got it made.
He's, you know, he's paid off the entire debt.
He's paid off the debt, the Russian debt to the international
monetary fund.
Um, paid off all the debt to the Roth child who, uh,
you know, had billions outstanding.
This is, and of course, the way he did it was quite
interesting and, you know, pretty much unscrupulous.
He just nationalized all of the oil companies and the gas companies
said, screw it.
We're taking all this.
We need this money.
We've got to pay off this shit.
So we stand alone without being under control of who typically
runs the world certainly is running America.
The Roth child's Rockefellers, et cetera.
Um, and now he's, uh, a Mr. Hero mode.
If you haven't seen this, you've got to check out the link.
Where he saves a TV crew from a tiger.
This is pretty funny.
Yeah, a tiger.
Where were they?
We're hunting tigers.
What were they doing?
Let me see.
Um, he was taking a break.
Uh, in a national park to see how researchers monitor tigers in the wild.
And then one of them that, you know,
escaped and started running towards a nearby camera crew and, uh,
superhero Putin shot it.
Although it's kind of unclear.
He says, Mr. Putin quickly shot the beast and sedated it with a
tranquilizer gun.
It does that mean that he shot him with a real bullet first and then the
tranquilizer gun or was he carrying a tranquilizer gun.
And then this other story, which you probably didn't catch.
I just love it.
Bring on the sleeves.
Oh, shit.
The page is gone.
What's up with that?
Ah, it's horrible.
Well, the page on ABC news, which now seems to disappear from their website,
headline Putin denies affair with beautiful gymnasts that
that we could have some fun with that, but apparently not.
So, um, you know, now on top of the Dutch pulling out of Iran,
because they said that they got word of, uh, some kind of, uh,
event that'll be taking place in Iran, um,
the fact that, uh, you know, it looks like Israel, uh,
Israeli fighter jets and I'll be, uh,
uh, using one of the other airports in Georgia.
You know, it looks like something is imminent.
And it's, it's just, uh, it's so blatant now.
You know, even, even the shit that, uh, the Chinese saying,
and in fact, let me see if I can bring up that story about, um,
it's, it's all about oil.
It's all about the pipelines.
It's, uh, how they want the pipelines to run.
They don't want to build new pipelines.
So they, they don't go, they don't go through Russia,
but then run, you know, through Turkey.
And meanwhile, you know, what is indeed, you know,
thanks for the call, man, what indeed is going on with Pakistan.
So now we're in there.
We're ambushing presidential motorcades.
We're landing with helicopters.
And I mean, what the hell, and why is that not being reported on?
Very, very little, in fact.
Now again, you know, my theory that the mainstream media
has got great journalists, but it, you know,
that it's just not getting through the editors, you know,
the DNA of these, of these media companies aren't allowing it through,
but let's get some, let's get some ink on what's going on
over there in Pakistan because these guys actually do have nukes.
And it seems incredibly unstable at the moment.
But, uh, and all, it's so open now.
It's completely clear.
It's so easy to see that the Bush administration, Bush
Cheney administration, they have been after oil from day one.
Hundreds of thousands of people have died for it.
And all Americans have that blood on their hands one way or the other.
And we've got to stop it.
So wake up America, please.
And the rest of you, hey, you Brits.
It's, uh, you're in this too.
You're a part of the, the Dutch Anglo empire building system.
And I think the Brits are still out to, to crush America.
Certainly looks that way with the, uh, you know,
European Central bank rates remaining at 4.25%
and the UK, I think it's still at 5%
all the money is flowing out of the United States.
You know, it's, it's economic warfare as well.
That's really what it is.
And Russia, I think, has gotten smart.
And they've stepped out of the system,
keeping our eyes on this, keeping our eyes on it for sure.
Hey, and it is, of course, Friday, which means we've got some typical
food bar business to take care of.
Hey, Adam.
Number 137, and we're going to start right away with intro.
All right.
Uh, that's, uh, almost a sting.
See the Durandran Sabre prayer, or is the police, maybe?
Number two.
Uh, David Bowie, this is not America.
This is not America.
Uh, that one was easy.
This is like 84, 85.
And number three.
Oh, yeah.
There will be prints.
And the sign of the times.
Okay, so I'm going to, I'm going to stick with the police on the first one.
I can't remember the name of the song, though.
And time's up.
And this is answer number one.
Number two.
2.
1.
One, four, six.
The hell wasn't name in the song?
Here comes.
2.
30.
40.
I think I get at least one point for the...
for the band.
Don't I?
Number one.
Rats around your finger to the police.
Yeah.
This is answer number two.
Ninety, Ninety five.
There we are.
David Bowie.
From the Falcon and the Snowman, the soundtrack.
For extra points.
For the Snowman, the American.
Hell, no way.
I'm gonna recall.
It should all look on the top.
This is not America Day for Bowie's answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
Oh yeah.
This is Prince.
In fact, the skinny man died of a big disease.
With a little man.
Answer number three.
Prince.
Sight of the Times.
And that concludes hit number 137.
All right.
So Adam.
How did you do this week?
Well, I actually got five out of six there.
But considering I knew some extra trivia about David Bowie,
I think I got a full six, don't you think?
Oh yeah.
That concludes this hit test.
Thank you for playing Adam.
Thank you sir.
Everyone else, thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll hope to be back with another hit test.
And in the meantime, you can find the answers to this.
And any other hit test.
And also the links to iTunes.
So you can buy the track.
Featured on the hit test online at hittest.meapyote.com.
See you next week.
All right.
Hopefully.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And remember to try to think with your hearts.
Bye bye.
Be back.
Test at gmail.com.
info.
.
Yo.
Thank you.
I believe I actually skipped over hit test 135.
But I'm going to keep that one.
One of these days, I'm sure young won't be able to make one or something.
I'll go wrong and then I'll have one stacked up.
So young was one of the many people who sent me email a couple days ago when one of the
greats left us just unbelievable.
It was a real shock.
Because, you know, you hear this guy multiple times a day.
If you listen any mainstream media, you know, radio or if you watch television.
But also, he really was pretty big in the podcast.
And lots of people worked with him and ordered up some of his work and his services.
Of course, I'm talking about Don Lafontaine, the man who he didn't just, he's not just famous for the line in a world.
But he really changed the face of movie trailers.
Significantly.
Just trailers in general.
And really turned that into a fabulous art form.
And it would just seem like such a nice guy.
Never met him personally.
I know a lot of people who work with him.
And it's a real real bummer.
And he will be sorely missed.
If you want to know who I'm talking about.
And there's lots of shows out there that have interest from him.
I just dug up two.
I think I got three or four.
Just so you can kind of remember in a way as a tribute to the great voice of Don Lafontaine.
Adam Curry was just a guy with big hair.
He sold his first company and thought he'd just kick back and take it easy.
But he never counted on this.
Adam and Patricia, the king and queen of the manner, or just the lady and the tramp.
Only on the daily source code.
Definitely one of my favorites.
And then there's this one.
Of course.
In the world, we're women.
We're comfortable shooting.
And technology has changed the way you get your entertainment.
This is the pod show network.
No big media.
No excuses.
No BS.
Somewhere he has one with my name on it.
But I couldn't put my hands on it that quickly.
Rest in peace.
Don Lafontaine.
We shall definitely, definitely miss you, my friend.
Adam, this is John.
You're going to get some of on the floor convention.
This is the last pedic convention where we're going to nominate John McCain.
As our president, our nominee for the Republican Party.
Last night's wrong.
All of those with a rather quieted down.
I heard only one statement.
He held his name.
I think that was Alaska.
Most of the other states just didn't say his name.
There is some confusion as to whether or not the votes that were he ended.
Actually, because we're he ended into the RNC.
We'll be counted for wrong.
If the state delegation didn't have to say his name.
There may be some confusion as to the fact that he didn't get any vote.
So I think that's been reported in the meeting press.
That's actually I think we're a member of.
On average, probably two, three, four, five, six, seven,
go slow on default for the each name out there.
So again, as that will be reported.
And then we'll come out later.
Maybe some of the check-in to it.
So if you are in the official word as to what happened.
Anyway, that's your report for tonight.
Let's fight.
All right, man.
It was kind of hard to hear what you were saying.
That's why I didn't interrupt.
It was probably the culmination of the cell phone and the crowd noise in the back.
But yeah, from the convention floor.
Yeah, you know, Ron Paul had the rally for the Republic.
And I think it was wildly successful.
Though, of course, again, in mainstream reporting,
almost not present at all.
And so I guess there's some question about the votes.
It doesn't really matter.
I mean, it's all about the show and the television audience
that gets sucked into it.
And the system works perfectly.
It really does.
I mean, yeah, man, turn on Fox.
Fox News is amazing to watch.
But you've got to be careful because you've got to know the code, right?
You've got to understand that that very moment you're watching.
Programming of your brain is being attempted.
And particularly in Carl Roe, man, Kaiser Carl.
And he comes on Fox News.
It's like he's almost like he is truly Dr. Evil.
And you know, he's just sitting there,
country, he's still pulling strings.
Either hammer, some clone or some body,
some central command,
start fleet command that pulls all these strings and comes up with the talking points.
And probably even calls the camera shots for all I know.
It's just amazing.
And of course, that's a press as all the other news,
particularly the Georgia stuff, the Iran stuff and
Henry Boy, how about how about the economy?
Oh, man.
There's a lot going on there.
Let me see.
Oh, I got a promo.
And you know, you used to play a lot of promo
as a daily source code.
And I'd love to get back to playing some more of them.
But people just kind of gave up on sending a man.
I'm not quite sure why.
I'm not sure if promo is or exchanges at all anymore.
They're certainly welcome here.
Obviously, I try to keep in between 30 seconds in a minute,
because sometimes people send it three, four minute promos.
You know, I just don't have the time for that.
But happy to do it, happy to spread the love
if you send it in or better yet to leave it on the drop.
Drop.au slash daily source code.
Don't adjust your dial.
It's true.
It's back.
Bigger and better than ever before,
and coming soon to an MP3 file near you.
The Matt Gifford Show.
One year later, that none of the wiser.
So join me as we embark on a new journey of discovery.
A journey filled with fantastic music, featured bands,
comedy antics, and more fun than you can shake a honey badger at.
Find out more at MattGifford.co.uk,
for slash podcast and subscribe to the feed.
The Matt Gifford Show.
It's what your ears will make for.
You look particularly lovely today, by the way.
How generic is that?
Thank you.
I feel so particularly lovely today.
And don't forget for those of you in the UK,
we now have a big godaddy.co.uk promotion.
A code.uk domain names with use the code of your favorite show in the UK.
You won't get a cheaper anywhere cheaper than any other outfit in the UK.
Brought to you by those fine folks that go daddy.
Fuck yeah.
Let's talk about money for a second.
Great article in agorafinancial.com by Ian Matias.
I think that's a high pronounce it.
It's called money to burn, and I'd really like you to take a look at this because
it goes very deep into what the Federal Reserve has been doing
in lending money to banks.
And they do it through a number of different,
well they call them facilities.
So we have the TAF, the term auction facility,
which offers banks billions,
literally billions, and I think it's 28 or 35 day loans,
and it's below the Federal Reserve's published lending rate.
And this is, and it's not, I mean, we're talking,
eight hundred and ten billion dollars that has been lent to financials under
these TAF auctions.
In fact, this article takes it even further and says at current count,
the Federal Reserve has lent out about 1.5 trillion dollars
to financial institutions.
This is so rough.
And it's so funny because now if you read through a lot of financial news,
you'll see that even the Rothschilds are in trouble now,
which of course is exactly what I've kind of hoping would happen.
These guys got to feel the pain too.
They've got hedge funds blowing up left and right.
They no longer have debts outstanding to Russia as we discussed earlier.
Then there's this T-S-L-F, I'm not quite sure what that is.
But it looks like sometimes they're doing 20 billion dollars a day in loans.
And they do it in all these crazy instruments,
and they're essentially shitty subprime rate back assets
being traded as national debt.
I guess they're both worth the same at this point.
But please, don't look at any of the financial markets.
Please pay attention to Sarah Payland and her kids or grandkids or whatever it is.
Please watch the greatest show on earth and don't pay attention to things like,
oh, let's see, the global food crisis.
Another good article you might want to skim through.
World Bank reports, global food prices rose 83% over the last three years.
And 45% increase in the world food price index during just the past nine months.
No wonder people are going to the streets.
I mean, there's countries where Haiti.
Food prices increased by 100%.
Prime Minister was forced out of office.
People took to the streets, people had been killed, injured.
Very little reporting on that.
Very little about what's actually going on.
And this could happen in our backyard.
I'm already seeing the inflation in the UK is well over 10%.
That's what they're reporting.
So maybe it's even higher than that.
People are being pushed towards the poverty line with an amazing pace.
And not to mention, as I said, look at Haiti.
I mean, there's plenty of other countries where it's really, really, really bad.
But that just doesn't reach us.
It's just amazing.
I said.
There's so much to go through with you today.
So now China, which, of course, has been buying up the US national debt,
every running out of money.
Oh, this is from the New York Times.
Of course, China has been in a buying binge in the states for the past six or seven years.
They own about one trillion worth of treasury bonds and mortgage back debt issued by
Fannie Mae and Freddie Max.
Of course, the value of all of this has gone down.
So what do you do?
I mean, there's only really two choices.
It's just like if you were investing in the stock market, either you take your losses.
And losses on a trillion bucks could be quite a bit.
Or you double down.
So they want to buy more or they're thinking about buying more.
But they don't have any money.
They have the Central Bank of China.
Only has 3.2 billion dollars.
At a certain point, you get used to all these billion numbers.
But there is a limit to it.
There is only so much that's available.
And of course, the people's Bank of China, they don't, they like to have some more money.
They'd like to invest.
They'd like to double down.
But China's saying, well, look, we're not going to just print up more money.
Because that'll cause inflation in our own country.
Once you understand this stuff, how this economics really works,
it's so simple.
And it's all these central banks manipulating everything.
And they're not working together anymore.
And it's falling apart.
Let's see, does anything here?
This is just shocking, really.
So they're trying to raise money.
Where they're going to raise it from?
Who has money left?
Russia, perhaps.
Here it is.
Here's the story on the banks borrowing more from the Federal Reserve.
This is just a corner copia of cool news for you to prove through.
Federal report, and they don't report everything.
But this is a good one.
And you won't read this on the front page of USA today.
A Federal report released Thursday said commercial banks averaged 18.98 billion in daily borrowing over the past week.
That was compared with a daily average of 18.47 billion in the previous week.
Billion.
This is nuts.
They've got to shut it down.
There's no more money.
The only way to go is to print even more.
Keep your eye on that.
Make sure you know what's going on.
Because, man, I got to go get me some gold bars.
Having money is useless.
It's not.
Not going to be any good anymore.
No worries.
Salvation's coming October 14.
Well, we wish it done the shroud of elders.
And we're waiting for that money from Ed McMan.
And we're drinking the literary aid.
Fountain of youth.
Well, we follow what the daily borrowers go send.
Taking legal doses of MTV.
Downing into bedside kindness rate.
Try to treat cancer when the fruit is cured.
And waiting for the meal free.
Your mental illness is a great match to the world.
And we're even cut as easy as it turns around.
Great match to the world.
And we're never really sure.
If we're up or down.
We're on a dirt court out in space.
We're without nobody to know.
We'll stay still.
If Jesus came back today.
We'll be trying to book him all day.
Hope we'll win the free show.
We'll make the greatest and the greatest.
Getting children older from our toning bags,
channeling, improving,
earning a plane, and trying to figure out what the door is the same.
We're in purple town
We're on a different spot out in the place
So we're stuck to where it's not snow
But we don't know
It's still changing the game back to the place
They try to book it all
But when we know
Because this is the place
This is the place
This is the world
This view
This is the place
That is the place
We're going to play that.
This view
Thephere
There are so many to go
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey brother what, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
And we'll never make sure if we're up or down
It's the night
I think I'd actually be wearing high school school flags
Yum, yum, yum, yum
I think I'd stupid, dude
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum
I think it's stupid
I think I'd stupid
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum
I might be deaf
I think I'd say screaming
vida stir, the wind
Candy
Kong
Gold
Contyr
athon
Kong
Contyr
Party
It sure is a great big, stupid world, and we're all in it, my friends.
Channel dance tonight.
Oh man, hey at least we're awake, right, at least we see what's going on.
And this October 14th thing, I'm pretty jazzed about that.
You know, and I am way open to the possibility of extraterrestrials
surfacing their ship for 3 24-hour periods, plainly visible to us Earthlings.
To let us know that there's a way out, and they're going to help us.
Hell, I'm open to that big time.
Episode 787 of Daily Source Code, it's the Fubar Friday.
You might have seen on curry.com earlier in the week, I put up a YouTube video of Adam Savage of
Mythbusters fame. He was at Defcon, maybe. He was one of these hacker conferences.
He was talking about an episode that we're going to do about the
hackability of credit cards that include RFID chips.
And in the video, he says, oh man, it's like Discovery Channel wouldn't let us do it.
There was a big hassle, so that's never going to make the air.
And now there's a retraction, as listed on the consumers, he says,
you know, actually it wasn't the Discovery Channel was the producers of the show beyond
productions who decided not to air the segment or the show.
Now, I don't actually know if they created the entire show, I can't recall if he mentions that
and there's a original video. I actually know what we could do. We could probably
probably play this, let me see. I have my browser now tapped in.
Oh, wait, oh, yeah, here it is. Let's look at the video.
Let's listen to what he did with to Adam Savage said. This is the initial video where he said
that they are testing things for yourself, not assuming that the man is taking a question from
the audience. So, this is probably going to flow right into it.
RFID. Now, I know that Discovery still have the earth.
Are you taking a wrong? Do the RFID thing?
Yeah. Why did you know?
I'm sorry. I'm not here. It's just not going to happen.
I tend to discover, here's what happens. Here's what happens.
I'm not sure how much of the story I'm allowed to tell, but I'll tell you what I know.
We were going to do RFID. And on several levels, we know how hackable, how reliable,
how trackable, et cetera, et cetera. And one of our researchers called up Texas Instruments
and they arranged a conference call between, I think, Torrey and the head producer over there
for the other team with a walk of it. Right. So, it sounds like they were just prepping the
prepping the episode. And that got pulled. Anyway, so he says it's a producer. And even though
he really says the Discovery Channel said, no, there's a retraction on it. So, I can look at it and
show notes. As the power, that's how it goes. And here's something folks in the UK, my fellow citizens,
the councils in the UK. So, here we have the Guildford Council of the Town.
Our recruiting citizen snoopers, citizens snoopers to report littered louts, dog followers, even
people who failed to sort out their rubbish properly. The environmental volunteers will also be
responsible for encouraging neighbors to cut down on waste. Excuse me, I just have to admit some
kind of gas after reading this. I don't care, yeah, I really don't care what the governments
and councils, you know, what they want to do to restrict our freedom, but we cannot allow ourselves
to fall into this one. We cannot be snooping on each other. In fact, we need to have signs that
said that we can post in our windows at home that say, I'm not going to snoop on my freaking neighbor.
No way. We should be snooping on the council. See what those guys are up to.
This is just nuts. I haven't seen an advertising campaign yet, but the minute I do, I'm sure we're
going to have to, you know, photoshop it and create an anti campaign. The Liberal Democrat
controlled council denied the volunteers will be asked to spy on their neighbors. No, no,
these are all people who care about the environment and they will be ambassadors for their area.
A spokesman said, they'll be there to report graffiti abandoned vehicles and local vandalism,
not to report another individuals. Oh, no. The volunteers will be trained on the council's
waist and recycling policies because that's what all those kids are doing. You know, they're recycling
incorrectly. Those vagrant kids bullshit. Hey, don't fall for this trap. That's really, that's like
really fucking bad news. We shouldn't be doing this. Don't spy on your neighbor. It's just not a good
policy. All right. I want to pop back across the ocean to the Republican National Convention
rage against the machine had a, an anti, really an anti war concert they put on.
At a certain point, officials pulled the plug, pulled the power. And these guys just walked out into
the audience and they started talking to the audience and actually, I want you to listen to this.
And then they actually started doing accapella version of one of their songs.
It is never, never advocated violence. We've always advocated a direct opposition to
unjust wars, like the one started by John McCain and the Republicans and Bush and all of them.
That's why we're here today. Stay in peace, all over the world.
Now, in order that peaceful opposition, we wish that the police and the state here in Minneapolis
would do the same thing. It's like thousands of people here. They're just standing in front of the
stage yelling. The reality is, we're just forming these decisions from Los Angeles who've used
our voices and our talent and our musicianship and our words to stand up against these unjust
policies and why the fuck are these cops all afraid of us? Are they afraid of us?
No, no, no, no. They're not afraid of the musicians. They're afraid of you.
So let's tell you what? This is good stuff.
These guys rock, man. The more I learn about rage against the machine, the more I'm real.
like in their shit. So now, um, so it's, you know, they're just a crowd. They've got like one body guard and the crowd is just, you know, oh, oh, now they've got a megaphone. This is cool.
Everybody needs a megaphone to do an acupella.
They forgot.
Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben, oh Ben, oh Bangon, baby, oh Bangon, baby, oh, baby, oh Bangon, baby, oh, Bangon, hey Bangon, oh Bangon, PDA, oh Bangon, oh Bangon,
This is all through the megaphone.
Mr. the crowd man are going nuts.
We now weed the lab.
It is all over.
My money is out.
So remember Joe.
Pick you up.
This door.
warning of your car.
Let the ball stop.
Follow the sagt over.
It will shake.
It begins hit not higher.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, no, come on, the cross ends tight, give the stop, give the other, give the other, give the other
Throw out the feet from above the feet
Pick up the trick that's called into your heart
Way down your family
Go away, guard at Jules Mr. Bill
They also come to us
Check out the problem
Hold the key
When I'm walking for the show
What day is it today?
It's Friday!
I'm a day Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, full about Friday, I have a final fun phone
to read.
Yeah!
That was raved against the machine and bulls on parade, start off at Capella there.
The R&C anti-war concert and move right on into the full blown track here on the
787, your full-buyer fro-buyer friday edition of the source code.
Looking forward to a nice weekend of course so weekends are holy these days.
You need to chill out, take some time, it's going to be a wet one.
Anyway, final thought of the week, well, you know what, we've obviously got our eye on
the ball, don't be misled.
This is what it's all about, there is truly a war going on for your mind if anything.
So you got to take clear headed, always question what you're reading but make sure you're
read a lot and help each other out.
These aggregation sites are fantastic like drop.io where you really get a lot of the news
that you just don't see in the headlines.
Keep watching that stuff and stay in touch with the earth and each other.
You know, maybe sometime during the weekend you'll just chill out, we'll take a couple
of minutes, plant your feet firmly on the ground.
This by the way is done best if you're actually on the ground floor as in level with the
earth.
And just imagine your your feet shooting root deep into the earth's core and feel of
vibrations, feel your own vibrations as they should start to move to a higher cycle.
And let that feeling come over you feel how it's starting to give you pins and needles
in your ankles and up through your calves and through your thighs and through your pelvis.
Your shockers are opening up and you too will feel at ease and at peace with the world
because no matter what we think we can do in our arrogant nature to mother nature, she's
always going to win.
So we might as well take care of her and be in touch with her so we can feel what's
coming next.
Let's put it that way, that'll be the final thought of the week.
And of course we'll be the final thought of the week goes one final song.
All of these from the drop you can find them at drop.io slash daily source code if you're
looking for them.
This one kind of starts to rock out but gets into it slowly, I think you'll like it.
United abominations on the football friday edition of the Charlie.
With that leap and a bigger threat, they will lose you when one way or another will
be so happy.
Where we are, it doesn't go the worse.
And you win it right, you can't be any more art than you are right now.
The key to end is undone.
Another mushroom cloud, another smoking gun.
The bread is real, the look is key.
It's key to end.
Don't tell me the truth, I don't like what they've done.
It's made that time, it's a united abomination.
With a gathering agent, the decision to end.
These are secret passages.
It'll take you side, be it to one new.
The feeling's in our hands.
You made very the bodies.
When you can't bear with the ties, won't it fall still?
That feeling like ever art.
No, not me.
Like what they've lost forever.
Think you win it right, can't be any more art than you are right now.
The end is undone.
Another mushroom cloud, another smoking gun.
The bread is real, the look is key to end.
Don't tell me the truth, I don't like what they've done.
It's made that time, it's a united abomination.
With a gathering agent, the decision to end.