I'm coming home to reach this country, my territory, away from the soul, the Apache, the
The command sheet, the Rappelhole, the Navajo Terrorist, we talk Africans from their country to
build our way of ease and catch them in sleep and living in fear. Terrorism, we found a grenade
and killed innocence of veyens, babies, non military personnel, we found the Black civilian community
of Panama, with stealth bombers and killed unarmed teenagers and toddlers, pregnant mothers
and hardworking fathers, we found codophies home and killed his child, we found the Rappelhole,
we killed unarmed civilians, trying to make a living, we found a grenade and stood in, to pay back
for the attack, for an innocent kill, hundreds of hearts, working people, mothers and fathers,
who left room to go that day, not knowing that they'd never get back home, we found a Russia,
we found a Russia, and we found a far more than the thousands in New York and printed on it,
and we never found it in it.
He's crying in the playground, I was picking up children, I just couldn't go so far,
he was not soldiers, people just trying to make a day by day, we have support and sleep,
terrorism against the Palestinians, and Black South Americans, and now we are in danger.
Because it's tough, we have never seen it, and now we're all pregnant back into our home,
right now, America's security is coming home, Delta shared Charlie,
7-8-0, $16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
in the next generation radio content in my ears.
Anybody, let's say,
people, who are these words, they think that you and I have, people like I,
they think that it's not feeling it, I can't you, see it, I know why you can't,
you don't tell me what it means, strangely, the symbols they make by,
let's message you, question it, the message you're sweating, the meaning is missing,
anybody, let's say,
people, who are these words, they think that you and I have,
people like I, they think that it's not feeling it, I can't you, see what I,
can you, what I, can you, what I see, can you, what I hear,
and do you feel like I, they feel, they can't you do like I, they do,
do you see what I see, can you, what I hear,
they think that you and I have, they think that you are like I, they think that you are like I,
these words, they think that you are like I, they think that you are like I, they think that you are like I,
The table on death, love of the name of that band, sleeping away, kicking off
daily source code episode number 780 hey everybody how you doing coming to you from the
affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gulfard in the United Kingdom where we're under constant
watch by millions of cameras and now birds in the sky listening to listening to our
every phone call every computer transmission yes we're under siege and so happy to be
that way yo everybody it's Tuesday August 5th 2008 um important day for myself and the
lady Patricia um a lot fortunately she doesn't have any time to come and talk about it
because she's uh leaving tomorrow morning very early to go off to uh be and yet a judge
again in a new talent competition in uh in the Netherlands on television um
today's our uh wedding anniversary two decades ago my friends so we've been together
for 22 years on this day uh it was a Friday in New York City uh one phone call
the lady pee and I said uh what do you think uh baby is today the right day she said uh
yes sunshine and good day is a Friday I grabbed Mr Steve Leads as my uh witness we went
down to city hall we got married actually had the car uh commune car I believe it was uh sedan
a circle the block while we're getting married and uh we drank the champagne in the car before
we even back at our 56th street uh 42nd floor apartment the beginning of uh quite an adventure
and it has not stopped and by the way all that seems a little literally just like yesterday um
and the nicest thing today was this beautiful car that we got from uh from Christina
who uh by the way is turning 18 and in 20 days 22 days oh where's the time going and there's so
much to do and I'm just finally waking up myself and figuring out what's going on and feeling
great every single day so before I forget I love you lady Patricia uh today's uh program is entirely
sourced from the uh from the drop drop dot io slash daily source code uh which uh as you know
has now been disconnected from Twitter updates sorry about that minor snafu talked about it
I know agenda with John C to Warack over the weekend on the on the Saturday show a number 40 check
that out if you want to hear all kinds of uh uh cookie stuff that we talked about over the weekend
today though um as I said everything source from the drop uh except for the uh a couple of voicemail
calls and actually now I think about it you know you actually can leave voicemails on the on the drop
as well and and I'm I'm just loving this thing I'm using it as a as a as a complete uh really as a source
for almost everything you guys send so much cool stuff and it's neatly organized in blog format
like that is a real way to you know it's better than tagging it's uh it has easy download links and
if you actually use the number then I wouldn't you have to go anywhere else to check out the uh the
voicemails and then everyone have a record of the voicemail that you sent in uh which is great in
case I don't use it on the air which obviously happens because there's just not enough time in the
universe to play all the comments uh if you want to take a note of it here's the number and I'll put
it into the show notes for the data source code drop uh plus one this is what we want to put
into your cell phone so it works from anywhere in the world plus one six four six four nine five
nine two zero three now here's the bummer part and this is why no one will ever use it you
have to use a pin code to actually get through which is two triple zero six which is really easy
to remember because it's kind of two you got three zero's two times three is six two triple zero six
and I thought so and I was entering the studio complex uh let me see a couple of uh interesting
little bits of news that I wanted to share we do this one actually from uh just the other day
the Royal Bank of Scotland even thought the credit crisis was bad well it's uh it's definitely
causing shock waves over it and notice the word shock shock waves over here the Royal Bank of
Scotland which actually happened to count with the Royal Bank of Scotland this has less to do with
the count holders at least until they run out of money or out of deposits um and this is more about
shareholders uh but to unveil the biggest loss in UK banking history after taking a hit already
of almost six billion pounds from the quote credit crisis not even calling it subprime anymore
that would be twelve billion dollars Britain's second largest bank is this week expected to
reveal a pre-tax loss of at least one billion for the first six months of the year with analyst
warning it could slide to as much as 1.7 billion in the red holy creaky crepola that's a lot of
money and uh I don't think it's over everybody I see was in the financial sector talking about
you know the state of where we're at is just like freaking out let me check oil for a second
because uh the drops below a hundred and uh uh hundred and twenty oh interesting it's a hundred and
nineteen and that's today uh Tuesday August 5th though who knows it's all over the map no one really
knows what the hell is going on but one things for sure the banks are running out of money and I'm
trying to come up with a really easy way to explain how money works and particularly this business of
uh fractional banking fractional reserve banking where essentially if you give me if I if I
'm a banking you give me ten bucks but I can then go ahead and I can use that ten bucks nine more
times in addition to the one I'm already holding as long as I hold that one and lend that money out
that's one part the real uh part is the uh is the interest and here's just here's a little bit of
brain work I want you to give yourself okay if there's a there's a known quantity of money in
circulation right if it's phantom if it's paper it doesn't matter let's just say there's a hundred
some things what kind of hundred trillion doesn't matter just a hundred if of that one hundred
half of it is lent lent out to people so they you know borrowed that to buy houses and cars
kitchens and go on vacation you know pay for college pay additional medical bills if a half
of that hundred fifty is lent out at interest that means that there's more money has to come back
than is actually in circulation so where does the money come from the money can only come from other
people within that system and that's the people who fall off the edge you know your house is
foreclosed on they take your car away uh you fail to repay your student loan and get all kinds
of other crap coming down the pie catch you when you fail that's when uh that money is taken away
from you or that that value and then it's distributed usually back to the bank so I'm trying to find
an easy way to explain that so because we really have to understand what the hell is going on
with our money because that's where the inscrute and and of course money is in in general the root of
all evil also want to bring your attention to i'm pretty sure that in the in geeky circles this
story has been circulating Gary McKinnon this is the kid literally i have to say kid he's um
i don't know he's like he's like he's about uh late twenties maybe early thirties now but in
2000 uh 2001 he had watched the disclosure project which we talked about here on the daily source code which
was released in 2001 where you had a whole bunch of uh officials from inside the air force and
other governmental agencies including NASA saying you know UFOs exist we've had contact with them
and i'm willing to testify before congress so this guy who basically is the has the equivalent
hacking skills of a Microsoft certified engineer by his own admission uh when and start snooping around
and wound up actually finding any any basically was really using Microsoft technology so it's just
how secure it is of course it wasn't locked down the uh the the admin passwords are all blank
and he came up with uh one picture which uh i'm trying to find it now not the picture itself
because you know actually didn't even really see the picture other than in some low res almost like a
vnc you know screen copy he found that in uh he had found two folders of uh spacecraft apparently
or craft one marked touch the other one untouched and probably the more interesting piece of data
that he said he's seen but did not download was a spreadsheet uh which listed quote non-terrestrial
officers and quote fleet to fleet transfers and it had names but it wasn't specified if this was like
extraterrestrial um officers or fleet or if uh if it was maybe air force i mean that this is what
he says he saw and so the guy's been sitting here and the u.s wants to extradite him and they want
to throw him in jail and they really want to throw him in jail for like 60 or 70 years you know
trying to get the maximum uh out of uh i guess it's like five five years and five thousand dollar
fine for every computer you quote destroy or or break uh in a hacking attempt so uh uh the
guy is definitely uh definitely going down for a long time if they get him and he's been and he's
been uh wow there's something wrong with the sound here today i'm just gonna ignore it um so this
Gary McKinnon has been fighting this and he uh he just lost his uh appeal for this extradition by the way
there's no agreement as far as i understand between the u.s and the u.k. for extradition
yeah there's a one-sided agreement uh which of course uh the the british government signed the
u.s. government apparently has not signed and so they're gonna they're gonna send this guy out
he hasn't been tried here in the u.k uh there's been no real proceeding as far as i can understand
they're gonna throw them over to the states and because of this because of what he did i mean yeah
it should be stopped yes you could make an example of him but 60 70 years extradition
getting thrown in jail and this is a heavy ass shit man and why what's so important about these
pictures that he only he saw hasn't made copies over hasn't shown us at least or this spreadsheet
i mean you guys someone must really think this guy is extremely dangerous in order to
to put him into this level of uh uh i'd call this beyond harassment it's it's just a little bit
crazy uh all the links by the way you can find on the drop at daily source code or drop
out of your slash daily source code but today i will also be posting all of them in the links
at daily source code dot com okay all right so uh and there's so many cool phone calls that
came in so much excellence stuff first i got to play something that's a little bit the light
hearted here this is from our buddy Ray he's totally making this into a it seems like a weekly item
it is well what can i say the soundtrack to my life
soundtrack to my life my life let's take a look at the landscape on a rope trip through your life
this episode of anchors the soundtrack to my life brings us back to 1987 and was 12 years old
during 13 in September i'm living with his parents and some sisters in nestle and omsle very
small but beautiful village just outside the southwest of Amsterdam and when for his education to do
and still i can say i'm glad to fail that time for you for a progressive religious high school
in the south of Amsterdam during this school period and of course the start of his purity
and was getting very interested in radio and transmitting he had to rebuild his whole transmitter
with streets probably handled the street with his parents and was having such a good time with his
broadcasts and so on to one of the people who is 27 and so yes the skyder
well here we will have you radio transmitter you've got to be a piece of junkie also
maybe i've got to have some music to air so i'm stepped on his bike
waiting to record store and what is first two singles ever what's David Bowies sound
the vision in last year was first forty five
and the other one was uh i know what it was help me out uh Detroit spinners
i know what it is man it's the rubber band man yeah correct to monday hi hi
soundtracks my life before the forty five has a group of friends from furdale
michigan just outside Detroit who came together to make music started the spinners
their song rather than man spend three weeks at number two on the US Billboard 100
and talked to the dust of four in the beginning of this week's road trip and the curries
the soundtrack to my life takes a trip out and we're laying to 1970s and we don't walk in pain
and we don't run out don't be late cause we ain't got time to turn you and me we're going out
catch the play and sound guaranteed to follow your minds so high you won't come back
you're amazing man you'll never find a sound like a man man you're bound to just throw
the only one when it's all you can
all this thing is outside everything you've done seems to come out right once i went to hit
them play the club outside town i was so surprised i was hearing the time i was sounds
can't put down when i saw this short thing i was with the man between his toes yeah
my life's so hot cause i'm back when it's all you wish there's no more love
they all they said for the whole man who never heard sound like a little man
man you're bound to just throw the only one when it's all you can
i think i'm a man i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm
i'm home i'm home i'm home swim oh you know i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i'm home i
For being an open way, they can tell it to make you so much better about yourself, it's just so eventually all from me, about the fath man to remember him and the speech without it shall end it from nothing to nothing to say.
So what are you doing?
You talk about what you want to know.
Who is Skybird?
I think you got inspired to come to me.
And how am I the sun, man?
And you played it over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
stuff and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over right over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over God Eve,
behind that about about the kid and being called fat and turning
into a song about rubber band man. That's cool. But actually I missed some
of the scratches that were that I knew exactly where you would hear the
scratch or the little ticks in the in the record. I was I could I could
my subconscious was like waiting for that to come back. It wasn't
skybird actually. I know what you're talking about man. This is T-burdened.
Oh yeah, the good old days of the CBs. Yeah, I was way into that shit.
I had a single side band and would use either USB or LSB. By the way,
that's why USB originally meant was upper side band before it became a memory
stick. And then you had LSB, which is the lower side band. And what you do is
you'd cut a diode attached to one of the prongs on the chip in your I think
maybe it was cutting a diode or jumping it with a wire. I can't remember. I had
one of those radio-shack realistic base stations. It was a fantastic fantastic.
So on 12 watts, P-E-P, peak envelope power. You could actually get to higher
frequencies. Effectively, you know, turning your 120 channel citizens band
transmitter into like 240. And you know, it could talk with from the Netherlands
from the house where we were at man. I could talk to Ohio to some of the KMG
people who were also on those frequencies illegally. And KMG stood for kiss my
grits. Why don't I remember all this stuff? I could go into that quite quite
some length, actually quite some depth. I had an antenna of five and a half
meter antenna, which of course is exactly half a wave length of these 27
megahertz transmitters, the CB band. And I had it hooked up to a hinge. I could
pull a rope from my room, which the rope went over the roof. It was, you know,
kind of camouflage roof. And through a series of pullies, and I could erect this
five and a half meter antenna to then start broadcast. And because of course, it
was all illegal. And and honestly, blessed my parents, man, for let me do all
that shit. I cannot believe to this day. They actually let me kind of wear
with all of that. All right. Of all the phone calls that came in through the
voicemail lines, phones, phone numbers listed in this show notes of daily source code
dot com. The most response came to the call that we received last week on the
full bar Friday from Chris from Seattle, I believe, who just doesn't believe that
911, there was any cover up involved. In fact, he went, he was quite passionate
by saying, you know, if any news organization actually had this information, it
would be the story of the year. There would be the richest news organization in
the world. And I think I rebuttered him well enough. And you can find a copy of
that rebuttal and of his original comment on the on the drop drop.io slash daily
source code. But he did call back in again. And this is in response to my
response. So let's get this out of the way right off the bat. And everyone's waiting
for it to hear more from Chris from Seattle. Oops. Sorry. Here we go. Hey, Adam Chris
Cochrane here from Seattle. Just listen to your response to my call last week about
you being full crap. And I said, oh, yeah, there was that too. I find it interesting. I
think you're missing a huge, huge point here. And as you point being, there's a huge
difference between rumor, mongering and journalism. Journalism is supposed to be
oh, rumor, mongering and journalism. You mean like when I turn on these six o'clock
news and I actually see stuff about the terrible triumvirant of Brittany, Lindsey,
and what's her name? Paris. I mean, that's all truth that we're reporting. They do
on them. I mean, they they have the actual information. They have the actual facts. Come on, Chris.
They're reporting of facts as it become available. Now, I think that's a very simplistic
view of it. But that's what journalism is supposed to be. And the news agencies that
we're talking about are supposed to be journalists. Okay. Fact. No building native steel ever
in the history of buildings made of steel. Fact. This, by the way, is not something
you'll find in the 911 Commission report. Fact, no building native steel has ever completely
collapsed or even partially collapsed onto itself due to fire on September 11th, not one,
not two, but three buildings of steel did this for the first time ever in architectural
history. Fact. Now, we all know they're seeing us a bunch of crap. We all know they lied
to us. We all know they've been the story toward whatever specific agenda that they want
to, you know, portraying the media or whatever. But the bottom line is they have to report
facts. Your question was, well, how come the Warren Commission report are the 911
Commission report got so much press. But all these other areas don't get press. Well, the
real reason, because the Warren Commission was a guided commission. Now, I don't know exactly
you're absolutely right. It was a guided commission. In fact, go look at the names of the
commission, the people who put this together. Look at the executive director and then Google
this name for me, Chris, Philip Zelekau, Philip the way you'd expect to spell it. Zelekau
Zulu echo Lima, India, Kilo Oscar whiskey. Just Google his name, okay, and see who
his friends are. Wasn't supposed to be a bipartisan report. He, he, he, not only is he
personal friends with conglies arise. He actually wrote a book, whether you got to be
pretty good friends to write a book. That's not very partisan. In addition, he wrote
some very interesting material about public myths. And in fact, some of his material taken
from my belief is dissertation was actually copied and used in the project for a new American
century. I mean, you can find plenty of this stuff. Just look at the top five links when
you Google his name, okay? So let's just keep it that for the second about the 911
commission. I don't think they necessarily told the 100% truth. I don't know. But
I want to do know is this for multiple people who suppose we had some accountability
going through all the information available to them. And or what they claim was the information
available to them. Again, I don't want to discuss the whole of the theories or the best
part of this. But my bigger question is, by the way, the 911 Commission report is
a theory. It's exactly what it is. It's a theory about a conspiracy to attack America.
It's a conspiracy theory. Only it's one that's published that has an official seal of
approval right on it. Again, go look at the people who are on that commission, okay, Chris?
And then you tell me what's fact. And how come, by the way, there's not a single solitary
mention of World Trade Center number seven in the entire Commission report. Not a single
mention of it. You know, so I guess we can exclude that from their conspiracy theory and we can
create our own. Wouldn't it be nice if they actually came out? They being the Commission
or whoever's in charge today and actually provided some information or their version of
the conspiracy theory about World Trade Center number seven? That will be kind of nice.
Why? Because I think that's an A more fun topic talk about. And B, it's actually more important
topic. You'll use all of this that crap are entire lives by the media and by government.
So the bigger question is why? And that's where the conspiracy theories come in.
Ah, okay. I'm glad you asked why. Well, of course, if this was set up, you know, why
was it set up? Well, just look at the geography and then look at all the wars that are
taking place, man, that'll really start to take, explain it all. And look at what's what's
actually happening before our very eyes. It is, it seems like things are even moving faster
when you see how, well, now we have the European Union, although not quite because we want
to be a lot bigger than any other union that we have, which I think is we're currently
operating under the Maastricht Treaty. So we need to have all 27 of these countries to have
all this universal law and have the European army. We already have the money, which has
been integrated a couple other countries want to have our money as well for reasons. They
think is good because they'll get big loans, which of course, they'll never be able to pay
off. They'll get that from the European Central Bank and the European Investment Bank.
But that's why they're ramming through this Lisbon Treaty, man, because they want to
have that. And then we have our Asia-Pacific Union. We have the newly announced Mediterranean
Union, which we didn't really need, but we had to group a couple more countries together.
And then, of course, and you watch, Chris, you can call it crazy now and you can not believe
that we're not sitting on the, that we're sitting on the biggest story of our lifetime
and that we're not reporting it. It's not being reported on for us, the North American
Union. Now, you'll hear this mentioned on, on different program that you may not watch
typically like CNBC. Blue dobs has talked about this. You take blue dobs serious to see mainstream
enough? Sure. But one guy is not going to make the difference. One guy talking about it doesn't
make the news. Everybody has to follow it. And as we've spoken before, when there's
directives from above in the DNA of a company to not talk about it, it just doesn't happen.
But you watch, those unions are going to be all put together and then we'll have a one
world government on top of it, which is literally what Ronald Reagan and George Bush
for the senior engine, you're have literally talked about the new world order and you
all live in perfect harmony. Unfortunately, look at what your own government is doing to you.
Let alone some guys who are abstracted up three levels higher and don't really don't give
a shit about us. That's why they're doing it because that's where all the power is. That's
where all the money is. And absolute power corrupts absolutely. And power is a very, it's I think
the strongest Afrodisiac known to mankind. And obviously to hybrid kind.
For instance, I mean, that's the question I haven't heard you talk about yet. And that's the
question that I'd love to hear you address is really why. You know, yeah, there's a bunch of
freaking conspiracy is going on. People can spy all the time in the world. Why? Why are they doing
it? Just for world power. I'm glad. Already in power. How great. Love you.
Yeah, well, no, no, no, no. I love you too, man. Of course. Yeah, well, of course, it's all about power.
It's exactly what it's about. And this probably, you know, amongst the the true owners of the
universe, you know, Rockefeller, Rothschild, Warburg, there's probably competition amongst those guys,
too. And you know, someone that probably all get ready to stab each other in the backs as well.
That's why they come up with all these secret societies to, you know, keep some kind of brotherhoods.
They don't go kill any other. But history is littered with this shit, man. This has been going on
for eons as long as mankind has been writing about it. You know, truly a Caesar.
The Apatra. Oh, um, these are just some recent ones that should ring true. Look, and Hitler.
Okay. So, and, and when it comes to the third Reich, wow. I mean, media had a lot to do with it.
Go Google, uh, Mr., uh, Mr. Gubbles. Go Google Hen. GO E-B-B-E-L-S. I think it is.
And, uh, you'll start to wake up, Chris. And that's actually what I hear. And that kind of makes me smile
when I hear your comment. Because I know that you're getting close. You're asking the right questions.
I think you have to do a little more research. And don't worry, man. You're not, you're not,
you're not, you're not cracking up. You're not a nut. You're not freaking out. If you start saying
Jesus, Chris, I can't, I actually believe in this stuff. This stuff is really convincing.
Because at the end of the day, um, us waking up, we're waking up to a lot of things.
Yeah. So, you might not be waking up to the big global grand scale. Maybe that's a little
to a big fee to see at this moment in time. But, you know, look at what you're putting.
Look what you're paying for, for gas prices. And you'll look at what your, what your tax dollars are
doing. That everything's tax, man. Everything. The roads you drive on. You know, if you drink,
alcohol you drink, if you smoke, the cigarettes you smoke, uh, if you, you know, this, uh, this
tax is on, this is a tax on shopping. This is a tax on stuff you buy. This is a tax. Everything is tax.
And it's all going to your government. Do you really feel you're getting value for the money?
If you're working for five, six, maybe even seven months out of the year, working for the
man? No, I know you're not feeling that way, man. Uh, switching gears. Uh, there's a lot of,
uh, I don't understand why this all of a sudden is such big news. Well, actually, I do, I guess,
because, uh, that's how it works, right? When it catches on and it goes viral, then it's news.
So, I guess there was a confirmation from, um, uh, border and immigration, uh,
actually, it's a customs and border protection agency. Uh, that, yes, they, uh, do feel that they have the
right to search through laptops and any other, uh, electronic devices that might have hard drives.
You know, it could be cell phone, your iPod, you know, video, tapes, audio tapes, and, uh, they
can take those for investigation. They've had that right and they've been doing that for, uh,
for a long time. Um, and the law is very, very clear. When you are outside of the
US, when you're at the border, you do not have the civil rights of a US citizen. Now,
do I think that we have, do I feel that we have inalienable rights and rights as human beings?
Absolutely. Are those being violated? Yeah. I mean, dude, I used to remember coming to the
US, it would be like, hey, welcome to welcome back home. Welcome to America. It's not like that anymore.
And for me, in particular, because I'm about to make another trip coming up this week and coming
out to the States, and I know I'm going to go through the whole rigour roll again. In fact,
I'm, uh, just to make absolutely sure, I'm cleaning out the entire cache of all my browsers,
Joe, that didn't, you know, nothing can be found. I don't want any questions whatsoever about
anything. Um, because it could absolutely happen. They could absolutely take my laptop and
look through it and give it to me whenever they feel, um, they want to. And, uh, as the law stands
now, yeah, they have that right as nothing to do with, um, with the US Constitution,
as everything to do with our attitude, that's for sure. And that, and does it piss me off? Yeah,
absolutely. And, and so what are they looking for? They're looking for, it's always the same things.
They're looking for, um, stolen software. They're looking for stolen music. They're looking for
child pornography. And, of course, all kinds of terror stuff. Um, so I just wanted to say that,
you know, this is not new. They've been doing this. And they've been able to do this. And they've
been quite harassing to me. I'm usually detained for an extra hour and a half to two hours. Every
single coming, every single time I come into my own country with the US passport, I go through this.
I keep, you know, filling out the forms. I fill out the freedom of information, act, and, you know,
and then, so I can find out what they have in the database. I know what they have in the database.
They say they're looking for some other guys, some other Adam Curry from Nebraska. You know,
please go look for him. Get this guy. I'm tired of him. You know, they can't seem to change that
information. Uh, so right along with this, this is a great story. Those of you who've been listening
if you're a true chucklehead, you've been around, you know about the clear program, uh, which have
been harpen on ever since I saw at launch at San Francisco Airport. So this clear program,
we willingly give up your biometric data, namely your fingerprints and your retinal scan.
To the, uh, to the feds through, uh, you know, through another, through another party, through a
commercial party, in this case, the clear program. I can't forget who actually, um, runs the company.
I mean, we looked into that before. It's actually a Silicon Valley guy who's had some moderate success.
And anyway, I've been way against this because, you know, what you get is you get into like a
faster line. And of course, they check you out, they continue to monitor you. Members are monitored,
so that you're completely in the clear. So to speak. Oh, uh, a laptop was stolen. If you hadn't
read this already, it's just if it's too funny. A laptop was actually stolen from the clear program
people at San Francisco, SFO San Francisco Airport, which included, oh, like, uh, 30,000, uh,
members, names, passengers who had one of these, 30, actually, 33,000 applicants.
Information included names, addresses, birthdays and in some cases, driver license and passport
numbers and other data. Like, yeah, you're biometric data. And then, uh, who's it as the gall to say?
Whoa, is it some, maybe it's just the passenger? Yeah. So in this story, I'm reading, they pull out
some, uh, a traveler, uh, Giovanni Gallucci. He sounds like a traveler from outer space.
Your information is everywhere. And people volunteer. Their information on places like Facebook on Twitter,
my space and stuff said Giovanni Gallucci, a traveler. I guess it's just one of the
many ways that people can get our information. I mean, you hear about it all the time.
Laptops being stolen says Scott bottles. A traveler. Yeah. But it wasn't combined with your biometric
data, with your fingerprints and your retinal scan. And of course, they'll deny that that was a
part of what was stolen on the laptop. But this just goes to show. And who stole it? You know,
no signs of a break in? This is very, very worrying. All of this stuff. But I'm so happy now.
I'm really, really happy that I fought against this program and we'll not become a part of it because
it's see, there you go. Told you so. Crazy. Let's see what else we got here on the phone lines.
But I'm going in there. They go in my Easter breast still for the morning.
You know, names of daily source code for about the delusional source code.
Yeah, functional source code. Delusional. I'm just reading the news for you today, man. There's nothing
delusional about it today. It gets source code. It's delusional source code. So it's 24 feet with
no words and under the peaceful space for us. Great work. I'm just going to keep it daily source
code for now until we come to something different for some reason. But think about the word source code.
Actually, when you think about that, I'm finding that this program, this show has actually
changed my DNA somehow. It is, well, maybe it has loosened up or energized or awakened a part of
my DNA. And source code is really a part of that. I think that maybe I'm injecting source code into you.
So take that and come up with a name. I'm injecting source code. I'm upgrading. We're upgrading
all the time. I called my sister the other day who lives in Italy, Willow. And she was actually
as she was camping. So I didn't want to ask her about this because she had just gotten there.
But you probably heard about Berlusconi now putting soldiers onto streets in some of the major
cities in Italy. Berlusconi, of course, Sylvia Berlusconi being the prime minister of Italy,
who has been the prime minister before. I kicked out for a while, came back because all kinds of
shenanigans he's involved with. He also, by the way, owns the largest Italian media companies.
Is there conflict of interest there, perhaps? So he's got thousands of troops on the streets
of some of their big cities like Malon and Rome. And was there any other streets they mentioned here?
Malon, Rome, Naples, Palermo, Venice. And from this report, which comes from the telegraph in the UK,
anti-gathering laws were enacted, which means you could not have more than three people standing
together in the street. Otherwise, it would be seen as a gathering.
Why? What is going on? This is crazy. A Chris in the Christen Seattle. Do you hear this, man?
Wouldn't that be weird if all of a sudden we had the troops out in the streets and you couldn't
have more than three people gathering together? This is Italy, man. That's supposed to be democratic.
Speaking of that, I'm actually moving a story up here. Gosh, and I can't wait to post these
links because they're absolutely excellent. I saw this from a couple of different sources. I'm just
going to post one of the links. This is about a drug bust in California. And this was in the Los Angeles
times. And you can actually go to the Los Angeles Times website and you can, you can, and this actual
page that I'll put in the in the show notes at dailysourceco.com. It tells you what to look for and
where to look for it. So there was a bust of, and there's a whole story here as to why there was a
medical marijuana facility was rated by federal agents. So the Los Angeles Times post these pictures
online and you see a whole bunch of police and then you see one shot of a guy who was also clearing
out some, you know, box of either marijuana or plants or other paraphernalia, whatever the
guys, he's, I'm just going to enlarge this picture. He's got a, it looks like he's got a Glock nine
with sophisticated holster. He's got on. It's not like a standard issue. It's got a leg strap.
And what you can clearly see is that the guy, by the way, has a ponytail and a go-t. He's wearing a
blackwater t-shirt. And I sure hope this barks off some some questions that we can get some answers to.
I mean, is it already now at this point where we have blackwater, who, of course, are delivering
troops, some call them death squads, but troops into a, into a rock. I don't know if they're
now Afghanistan or not, but I think there's tens of thousands of them. Are they now actually
doing the work of the police? Do we now actually have a private police force? Are we outsourcing
some of this stuff to blackwater? You know, please, someone, let me know, get into this.
This is just absolutely amazing. And I'm just full of good ones today. If you've never seen
Fedspending.org, go check it out. They actually have a list, you know, for fiscal quarter, 2008,
the first quarter, the top 100 recipients of federal contract awards for the first three months of
2008. How much money they were receiving? What a great site this is. I guess they kind of reverse
engineer the, what is it? The federal procurement data system. So they can find out who got what
and how much money they got paid for. And then they link it through to where the work is being
executed and what congressional districts those are in. So let's just take a look at this,
talking about privatization. This is obviously mainly about the war. Number one, and this is only
for three months, right? For the first three months of the year, the Boeing corporation awarded
just chive $3 billion, which is only by the way, 5.8% of the entire amount of contracts awarded
in the quarter. And so if you click through to it, you know, it's a aircraft rotary wing,
which is helicopters, research and development, operational systems, services, basic research,
other demands, defense, advance development, et cetera, et cetera. So let's just go down to
list. Number two is Lockheed Martin with $2.5 billion. North of Grumman, they make battleships
1.6 billion. Number five actually is the company that the economic hitman, John Perkins worked for.
If you've never read the book, confession of an economic hitman, please do you'll learn about
this company that received $1.4 billion in the first quarter of 2008. I mean, it's just, it's
all a military industrial complex all the way down until, well, I did, Dick Cheney's going to be
pissed off. KBR, which of course is, uh, as a part of Haliburton, only 383 million,
huh, they're not doing so good on their quotas. Um, it's just, it's all, it's all, um, logistics.
Oh, Glaxo Smith client number 47. What are they provide? $165 million. Let's see. So I click through
chemicals, $165 million worth of chemicals, and then $194,000 on drugs and biologicals,
$32,000 a medical and surgical equipments, equip instruments, I'm sorry. Another 32
grand for laboratory equipment and supplies, and then 5,000 for pharmacology services, $165 million
for chemicals. What chemicals did we need? And what are we doing with them?
Oh, please have a look at all of those links. You will not regret it, I guarantee.
Let's play some more songs. Again, all of this coming off of the drop it to drop.co slash
daily source code.
Got to get the big pay. I got call note to rent and of the nonsense that's slowly turning
me into a slave, but it's okay. Because of the crew, I got the best clothes and the best
neighborhood, and that's when it's about the American dream. We in the rack range,
but the rats one queen in and up seen a mountain, more than I can count. So I'm all
breaking hands that I'm drowning in. In the oceans of life, I've read full of strength.
And my head extra smashed, just pound it down. He come to tears up the cloud,
the hardest thing in the whole town this time. But my friend, that's inside. He's sitting
by my mind. He comes to everything, I'm on his mind.
I got to peek out, just to make sure, but say, because these times is changing and reshaping
in the summer, I can't face in a filestream. We got religious people, church and a whole
world we got. Bems and holes, once, boys and girls we got. The media telling us who's the
blame, but who's the media who's really running the game. Gotta get up, gotta shake it off,
just like the longest, unsunger in the dark. I'm getting confused, I'm getting upset,
things don't work out, I'm up in the check, regrets, creepers up my window, my life is
reaching up her window. I got to know my what's raking in gold, but she said, and dream, I'm
wasting time, because everything I want is mine.
Gotta get up, gotta get up, gotta get up,
have an inflatable grey day, and everything's okay.
I'm doing fine, just don't look it right, I am just fine, believe, and everything's okay,
fine, just don't look it right, I am just like the one I got to get up, gotta get up, gotta get up,
gotta get up, gotta get up, gotta get up, gotta get up. I got to get up, gotta get up, gotta get up,
I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I
got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up now, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up all night, and get up, I got to get up all night, and get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I got to get up, I
The way to the world, living in the American Dream is...
...and getting a snickers on.
You gotta have the right car.
Oh man, what's that? That's no ending.
What kind of ending is that?
Crap.
Alright, a couple more things is we're moving along in time here.
Here's a story I want you to track.
Oh, particularly Crest and Cricin' Seattle.
I really want you to track this story, man.
Because actually we've got a phone call about it.
And this is just too much happening when it comes to people who are involved in governmental affairs.
And I'm killing themselves.
For the most peculiar things and reasons and the way you're doing it is just lots and lots of questions.
Adam, Eric and Portland.
Eric.
Bruce E. Ivan is dead.
Yes.
Apparently, reportedly committed suicide right before being arrested in connection with the
Anthrax attacks. I can see that I'm state.
Something smells fishy about this.
I think we need more research on this.
Yeah.
For the call...
Alright, Seattle, that said...
Oh, yeah, here we go.
The newspapers and the media wouldn't hold back on the story.
Remember, after September 11th, we were in shock in 177 days later.
Anthrax was set to ABC News, NBC News, CBS News,
The New York Post and other media outlets.
It's a clear case of intimidation.
If you follow the 911 story, you will have something bad happen to you.
On October 9th, Democratic Senate Leader Tom Dachel and Patrick Lazy.
Get Anthrax sent to them.
Again, clear intimidation, military grave.
Anthrax.
You know, intimidation or in the case of the news media distraction, perhaps?
I mean, there was a lot going on.
Fact, Chris.
Man, that ground zero.
That got chopped up real quick and carted off.
And it's now buried where no one can go and do any forensics on it.
Fact.
Here's what I want you to take a look at.
This is when I come across this one.
This was pretty interesting.
It probably came from the drop.
American every man.
It's a blog, okay, from Willy Loman dot WordPress dot com.
But Willy was reading this story in the New York Times.
And he saw that the story was actually changing it as he was reading it.
And he's he's documented some of these changes.
So that's the first thing to take a look at.
Also, look at the methods used by the FBI,
claiming will be the methods where there's they prove that Bruce Evans or
Ivan's that he actually did this.
And it includes some newfangled DNA type of science that has never before been used.
Yeah, okay.
But the thing that really bothers me about this, the most.
The really, really bugs me is if he's a guy who works in a lab and has access to
contracts.
And he wants to kill himself.
Why does he as the reports claim take massive doses of Tylenol with coding?
And it literally says massive quantity.
I mean, the guy just like shoving this down or throw it.
Isn't there an easier way to kill yourself?
If you actually know how to do it and you've got access to the stuff to do it with,
which could kill you quickly painlessly.
Or as far as we know, just put you to sleep.
I mean, that's weird.
You can't deny that's weird.
And there's been a couple of other really weird ones.
Paul Willstone starts talking out about the Iraq war.
And his plane crash is any dies.
If you were a U.S. senator and you go against the Bush administration,
you could have bad things happen to you.
So I encourage that guy to research 9-11.
Research physics of WEC7.
How did that fall without getting hit by a plane?
Research the intimidation.
Research the Senate assassinations.
Research Bruce E. Evans.
Apparent suicide.
Crazy is out of the box today.
Awareness is not a metal mental.
Disorder.
And I'm wide awake in train.
Yeah, baby.
Let me say.
Then there's, here's this other one, man.
This is, this is also a bug of me.
Brigadier General Thomas Tinsley.
Suffered a gunshot wound to his chest.
Late Sunday night and was pronounced dead within a half hour.
This is the officer who commands an Air Force wing in Alaska.
And they're calling this self-inflicted.
Better known as a suicide.
He was, he now he had just resigned in June under pressure in an agent's,
quote, agency shake up.
We should investigate that.
I think someone had to do with procurement, but you don't know.
What's going on in Alaska?
And here's this Brigadier General who apparently is so embarrassed about what he's
wrapped up in in his life.
He's going to kill himself and he shoots himself in the chest.
Come on.
That just makes no sense.
The truth can be crazy.
But I think that needs a little bit of research.
Absolutely right.
We got to look at these things.
Let me see.
Did I have another one here?
No.
By the way, I would suggest, you know, the nine eleven, which, you know,
this is now seven years ago.
I want to continue to research that looking for the truth.
I think maybe I want to, it's never going to be a waste of energy.
But there's so much more.
We have to kind of start to jump ahead and see what the next step is going to be.
That's what I'm doing.
You know, I'm looking beyond what they're going to,
once the Lisbon Treaty is rammed down islands,
throat, and island is either no longer a part of the EU,
or is on a slow track or a secondary speed,
or basically ignored and but we left the bleed to death.
I'm looking beyond that, you know,
and I absolutely personally am convinced that something is completely wrong with nine eleven,
and I don't know which of the theories isn't play,
but something happened there that never should have happened,
and there is culpability, and it's on our government,
and we know who's involved in the shenanigans.
But researching that over and over again is not going to prepare us for the next big thing,
or the next thing that's going to happen.
So I'm paying attention to all the post-saber rattling that's going on about Iran.
I'm looking at Russia now saying,
hey, why don't we go into Cuba,
and let's make friends with Cuba again?
You know, why?
Because the US is like putting rockets in their backyard in Poland,
or attempting to.
In other countries, right near Russia,
you know, what's happening with China?
Man, pay attention to all of that stuff.
That's where you got to start doing the research,
listening to what people are saying,
reading it,
and it is being reported on.
Absolutely.
Even all this crazy stuff about,
about Bruce Ivins.
You know, I think versions of the truth are being reported,
and all kinds of vitally information,
and you can get it from the New York Times.
You can get it from other places that,
you know,
should include people who were reporting fact,
and I do believe there is some fact in it,
but the major talking points as they're known,
the real agenda just never comes up.
It means it does,
but not with enough people.
It's like this show.
This show will never be a worldwide phenomenon.
Why should it be?
Because it had to be mentioned,
at least every week in every newspaper,
every television program.
There's so much distraction.
You forget about it.
Sometimes I even forget about this show.
There it exists.
All right.
Let's wrap this thing up.
One more on all here.
Now I had a DSC in Oregon, actually.
Now in London.
No, welcome.
My friend.
On a job up here.
I'm amazed at the news coverage.
I see I don't know how many people handle the TV in London.
It's terrible.
I'm working.
What we have in America.
I'm not quite understanding if it's terrible,
good, terrible bad.
I mean, I'd love to know what you're talking about.
I mean, in general, the news coverage is certainly not as much of it.
There is some more in depth reporting.
I feel.
But yeah, I'd love to know what you mean,
what by terrible.
You can't tell me that Fox News is great.
I haven't noticed this into the show.
But, uh, and to calling on Skype, not cool.
So that's just online and say,
it's good that people are waking out,
but now we need a direction.
We need to know where we're going.
We need to know what our response to the leaders are.
And how we can achieve, you know,
a correction to all the bad things.
Whether it's a conspiracy or not.
Um,
Oh, okay.
Well, let me, let me address that right off the bat.
So waking up is really all takes waking up and talking with each other about it.
It's all that it will take because then we,
the conversation will guide us.
This is exactly how the presidential briefing,
the daily presidential briefing,
where we found out and this is fact.
The president Bush was absolutely briefs
on what was going to happen on 9.11 in time.
He was briefed.
And how did that get released after the White House refused to release it?
You know, classified your eyes only because everybody was talking about it.
And they couldn't get away from it.
And the news organizations then can't ignore it.
Everybody was talking about it.
We've got to be talking about it consistently.
Everything that we have going on now in our,
in our lives.
It has to become a part of our vocabulary.
And you have to, you know,
you have to dose it because you can't just be in the business meeting and say,
you know, well,
um, that's great.
We'll do this contract until 2015.
But we're all going to die before the end.
The illuminati are going to get us.
No, that's not exactly going to work.
But you can slip things in.
And you'll see if someone's concluded.
And nine times out of ten.
If you slip something into a conversation,
someone will say, why, you know,
this funny, you say that because dot dot dot dot dot.
And that can usually result in a very interesting conversation,
because it is happening.
Now, whether you think it's the,
the aliens who are doing this to us and waking us up,
whether you think it's the Mayan calendar ending in planet X,
new burrows coming to save us,
take us away, kill us, pick, pick whichever one you want.
Or, or we're just evolving once again.
One thing I know is there's a cage around us,
and that cage is created by bankers,
not the bankers you read about in the news,
but the bankers, bankers, the big guys.
Those are the ones that if cage us in and they're right now,
they're, they're taken up all the money,
all of our money from all of our hard work,
all of the value we've created on earth is being taken away
by these cock suckers.
Okay, just realizing that is a step in the right direction.
That's what I think.
We got to take steps too.
There's no immediate fix.
Just like this hasn't happened overnight.
The European Union,
which is heavily contested the way this thing is being run.
Go look at European,
Google, European Parliament,
Demonstration.
And look at the demonstrations that are taking place in Parliament.
Have you ever seen those shots of like Japan,
where in Parliament, where they're all,
you know, jumping on each other and beating each other up?
It's just a little, it's a little bit,
it's not far from that.
Okay, it's really being done with words,
but there's a lot of beating up a lot of signage,
a lot of t-shirts, a lot of protests.
By the way, you don't hear about that too much.
It's not reported widely.
The same way we don't see flags,
drape over coffins coming home with our dead boys and girls.
You don't see that.
It's still a fact that reporting on the numbers.
Talk about that stuff.
Help people to wake up to these facts.
We're really intelligent, all of us.
We can figure this out.
And for us, it won't happen overnight.
But once we start talking about something,
the conversation will take us somewhere,
and something will happen.
Good will come of it.
What are we going to do about it?
Nobody talks about that.
They all talk about how bad it is,
and how terrible things are,
and how things are need to change,
but nobody gives any idea.
So if you're in Europe,
you could just slip into a conversation and say,
you know,
well, that of course is,
presuming that the Lisbon Treaty will be ratified,
and Ireland will be forced to accept it.
Just throw that one into the conversations.
You know what people most like to say?
Damn, man.
That thing sucks.
And you could say did you read it?
You say,
and of course I'll say no.
Don't worry,
none of the politicians did either.
It's a legal document.
Then we're supposed to not look at the small print.
You'll have a great conversation,
and maybe even a better business relationship for it.
The only thing that seems to keep popping in my head,
is,
oh, we need to pre-fight a lot as the individual.
We need to take responsibility for our actions,
and to take the responsibility of others,
for our actions away from,
yes,
they work for us,
but they're not working.
Maybe we need to start working for ourselves,
and start moving forward,
rather than just talking about it.
Anyways, love the show.
Who knows,
maybe we'll see each other in the downtown area,
somewhere if you're ever down there.
Right now, I get a slow.
You break it up.
All this and keep on talking.
You know,
I'm sorry,
you're breaking up there,
but I appreciate the comment,
and that is my answer.
Just wake up,
talk about it with other people.
Don't go crazy,
but talk about it.
You'll have a better life like this.
You'll get laid more often guarantee
from your friends at the Charlie's house.
No delays.
Looks like everything's so tough to think.
No cancellations,
reservations,
you don't walk,
and don't cause a thing.
No.
So if you feel it like you need to live,
all be out.
Come along with me,
we're going to have a good time.
Let's take a nap,
play your life,
let's take it,
we are high,
when you never spend it for,
baby,
we're going to show.
I'll take you,
I knew my wish,
so you learn how to run.
Let's take a nap,
play your life.
Hey,
hey,
ay,
But good time, it's a good middle play, you are
Say it way over, way you've never been before
Baby, we go to school
I said, if you're under my wings
I'll steal your love of mine
Every ride
Oh, yeah, I'll go first, pass
So, baby, hold on tight
Because we take all pass
So, baby, I'll shout
I'll steal your love of mine
Call me, Sue, or be the sign
If I hold someone, it's a bye
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Say, don't use your love
Baby, if you're under my wings
I'll steal your love of mine
Let's take an hour and tonight
Come on, come on
Come on, come on. If you're under my wings
Let's take you away
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
.
from the drop.
the drop.
drop Danny O. Slash. Daily Source Code.
Sarah Bergas.
you can take him here, you'll hi how you go to heaven.
Yeah, I'll take virgin Atlantics leave you.
hour, just tell a port baby.
Airplane Rye.
They wrap it up.
They put a high up speed,
off to San Francisco. It's been a while. And we'll have a show before then. I'm sure Lady Patricia's
out tomorrow. As I said, she's she's actually going until and she comes back on the day that I leave
which sucks. So we're going to miss each other. And then I'll be out and I think the pot daughter
is actually she's at some festivals or concerts for two days and camping. I'm going to be
all alone. So that means we'll have plenty of room for some cha cha action everybody and bring
all the hookers. Okay. By the way, but when I was introing that song, I was thinking, what
it? I should really do a commercial. Let's see. Do your own research. 9-11. 9-11. Do your
own research. Talk about politics with chicks. It'll get you laid. I got to work on it.
Okay. Tomorrow. Maybe tomorrow or Thursday. I'll talk to you soon. Can't wait to talk to you guys
again and keep all the phone calls coming and keep the great contributions coming
in through the drop there because as you can see, I actually use them. Until we meet again,
my friends live your life with passion and please. For as long as it lasts, enjoy your
freedom. Another fine, medium presentation. Stick it in your ear.