Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony
ear buds with style meets sound.
You are listening to a man who tried to smuggle mouthwash onto a jetliner, Adam Curry.
There's a reason for this, there's a reason for this, there's a reason education sucks,
is the same reason that will never, ever, ever be fixed, instead of going to get any better,
don't look for it, you're happy with what you got, because the owners of this country
don't want that.
I'm talking about the real owners now, the big, the wealthy, the real owners, the big wealthy business
and just the control things and make all the important decisions, they get the politicians,
they're there and you're relevant, the politicians are put there to give you the idea
that you have freedom of choice, you don't, you have no choice, you have owners, they
own you, they own everything, they own all the important land, they own and control
the corporations, they've launched this important pay for the Senate, the Congress, the
state thousands of city halls, they've got the judges in their back pockets, and they
own all the big media, all the big media companies, so they control just about all
of the news and information you get to hear, they got you by the balls, they spend
billions of dollars every year lobbying, lobbying, to get what they want, well we know
what they want, they want more for themselves and less for everybody else, but I'll tell
you what they don't want, they don't want a population of citizens capable of critical thinking,
they don't want well-informed, well-educated people capable of critical thinking, that
I shouldn't let, that doesn't help them, that's against their interest, that's right,
you know something?
They don't want people who are smart enough to sit around to catch a table and figure out
how badly they're getting fucked by a system that threw them overboard 30 fucking years
ago, they don't want that, you know what they want, they want obedient workers, obedient
workers, people who are just smart enough to run the machines and do the paperwork and
just dumb enough to passively accept all these increasingly shittier jobs with the lower
pay the longer hours to reduce benefits the end of overtime and the vanishing patient that
disappears the minute you go to collect it and now they're coming for your social security
money, they watch your fucking retirement money, they want it back so they can give it to
their criminal friends on Wall Street and you know something, they'll get it, they'll get
it all from you sooner or later, because they own this fucking place, it's a big club and
you ain't in it, you and I are not in the big club, by the way it's the same big club they
used to beat you over the head with all day long and they tell you what to believe, all
day long beat you over the head of their media, it's only what to believe, what to
think and what to buy, the table is tilted folks, the game is rigged and nobody seems
to notice, nobody seems to care, good honest, hardworking people, white collar, blue collar doesn't
matter what color shirt you have on, good honest, hardworking people, continue, there's
a people of modest beans, continue to elect these rich cock suckers, they don't give a fuck
about them, they don't give a fuck about you, they don't give a fuck about you, they don't
care about you at all, at all, at all, at all.
And nobody seems to notice, nobody seems to care, that's what the honors count on, the fact
that Americans will probably remain willfully ignorant, because the honors of this country
know the truth, it's called the American dream, because you have to be asleep to believe.
And you're just as fucking me, I'll go for meals, big breast hit, treat it like
guests, I'm serving, take the breakfast, put it back, tonight three things to come, money
sex, sex, just like it, I'll get a full skirt, won't be pulled up, this is like
these are sex, these nuts, make the one she wrote, and it held them in the chalk, mix
sex, take, skit, make it go, all this money, make a bitch go, come, hook on the tip or make
a bitch go, no, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm
gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom,
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom,
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane,
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom,
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom and Jane,
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane,, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane,
Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom and Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom, Jane, I'm gonna put you my mom
You know what, I'm gonna scale up for the beautiful day today, my friends.
I mean, blue skies, completely blue skies.
Why am I not outside flying around the countryside, huh?
What's wrong with me?
Well, that's because I'm here for you.
Bring in you another sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-h-h-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, what an opening, huh?
That's actually a YouTube video.
Of course, I'll put a link in the show notes.
All you got it by now, dailysourcedcoat.com.
Sent to me.
Who was it, Cannes on?
Let me just open up the Gmail Messenger.
Let's see if there was an actual name.
It was sent to a couple of people.
Cannes on Foster was also sent to, let's see...
How it's turned a show?
Yeah, yeah, sent to me in the stern show. Okay, interesting. I wonder if I would play it. Nice, nice images to go along with that.
And it does kind of make you think, you know, when you see what's going on with the primaries.
Of course, the word now, by now, I think all the votes are in. It is early afternoon on Wednesday.
January the 9th, 2008, looks like Hillary Clinton took in the New Hampshire primary.
Although it's kind of, we talked about this yesterday, and of course, no one called into actually explain how the caucuses and the primaries work.
So I'm not going to try to attempt that again.
But actually Obama and Clinton finished in a dead heat because they both have the same amount of committed delegates.
So again, it's not about the popular vote. It's about how many delegates you bring in. So really it was a tie.
Ron Paul looks like he came in fourth or fifth on the on the Republican side. No delegates from what I can tell from from the New Hampshire primary.
But at least he's above Giuliani. That's for sure. But really when you think about it, it's so true, man.
It's so true that we are bought and sold many, many times over.
Was another, I was a great link. Remember, I, I think I told you about the the sovereign wealth funds that are now being created.
You know, we still have this credit crunch.
And the banks are, you know, need to be bailed out.
And so who's helping him? But these, these wealth funds, these sovereign wealth funds, which means basically other sovereign nations are lending the banks money.
And this is great article by Donald Strassheim Forbes.com. Again, I'll put a link in the show notes to that as well. You've got to read this about China.
And they are accumulating about a billion dollars a day in foreign exchange reserves, essentially buying the United States, or at least the Wall Street part of the United States.
It's really quite unbelievable.
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, meanwhile we're just follow along with the news and pretending that it all makes a big difference.
All right, actually, did you see the Ron Pauls on Leno again? That was pretty interesting. After he was excluded from the Fox News debate.
And it might as well get into this right away.
Yesterday, the new republic came out with a scathing article, which was, it was really weird because they're quoting all these news letters from 25, 30 years ago that went out under Ron Paul's name.
It's just, you know, although they're quoting them, of course, there's no actual source material, no links.
But, you know, as usual, a million people sent me the link to this new republic article saying,
Oh, Ron Paul's clearly in trouble. He's a racist. He's a bigger, he's an anti-Semite. And, you know, this is something that's been around for years and years.
Apparently, in Ron Paul's illustrious political career, actually, let me go to his website because he released a statement which I've just been copying everybody on.
I'm sure if you're following the, if you're following the the primaries.
Oh, crap.
Something was wrong with my router here at home. I'm not quite sure what's going on, but periodically just crap's out and it'll give me, you know, like can't make a connection.
Here we go. Ron Paul's statement on the new republic article.
I'll just read this to you verbatim.
In response to an article published by the new republic, Ron Paul issued the following statement,
the quotations in the new republic article are not mine and do not represent when I believe or have ever believed.
I've never uttered such words and denounced such small-minded thoughts.
In fact, this article was really unbelievable and think about the timing of it, huh?
Coming out on the eve of the new Hampshire primaries.
In fact, Ron Paul says, I've always agreed with Martin Luther King Jr.
that we should only be concerned with the content of a person's character, not the color of their skin.
As I stated on the floor of the U.S. House in April, 2019,
I rise in great respect for the courage and the high ideals of Rosa Parks, who stood steadfastly for the rights of individuals against unjust laws and oppressive governmental policy.
So that's the denunciation of this just fucked up article.
That again, included no direct links, no sources, no page numbers, no research whatsoever that you could actually delve into.
But the whole point is, and this is again, a quote from this news release, the story is old news,
that has been rehashed for over a decade.
It's once again being resurrected for obvious political reasons on the day of the New Hampshire primary.
And here's the important one.
When I was out of Congress and practicing medicine full-time, a newsletter was published under my name that I did not edit.
Several writers contributed to the product.
For over a decade, I've publicly taken moral responsibility for not paying close attention to what went out under my name, indeed,
on these so-called newsletters, nowhere was Ron Paul's name, listed as a by-line.
But it's just amazing how this stuff propagates through the internet.
And maybe something I should pick up with John C. Devorek on this week's episode of Noah agenda,
where he thinks that the internet is only going to make news reporting worse,
and that the truth will have a much harder time bubbling up to the top because of all the disinformation.
I have to agree that it's starting to look like that because a lot of really smart people,
you know, just took this new Republic article as face value and said,
oh, well, clearly the guy's a bigot, he's a coo, he's a nut.
And it turns out that this has been something that's been going on for over a decade.
And that has already been rehashed even, it's even been discussed in the New York Times.
But still, you see how people catch on to this and take a lot of what's just written word as the absolute truth.
Interesting.
Thanks a lot of you for sending in suggestions, comments, both about doing live shows,
which I got a pretty good list here of, let me just see if I can bring it up.
A list of different systems I could use.
A lot of them are video related, which is kind of interesting, but what I'm looking for really is,
you know, so we'll, what do you have, just in TV, you stream TV,
stick cam, mogulus, 10 mile per hour dot com.
What is that?
Some people even suggesting using Twitter to announce the fact that I'm going to do a live show.
What I'm really looking for, the streaming out portion is not that hard.
In fact, Casplaster Mike even offered to build a right into Casplaster.
That's the easy part.
What I'm looking for is, how do I bring people into the conversation?
It's got to be some kind of hand-raising system where I can see a chat room, see where someone
says, hey, I want to talk about this.
I need to be able to click a button and that person's audio needs to be coming in through
my mixer so I can put it right, put it him or her right onto the show.
Doing that with video is not necessary.
I really want the audio portion.
So still on the lookout for something that'll work.
And of course, there were a couple of audio suggestions about what we should do to bring some new
creativity into the Charlie for 2008.
Adam, hey, this is Mark again in Los Angeles.
I just want to call you back on show 706.
You know, towards the end there, you're talking in the show a little bit.
Maybe it sounds like getting away from some of the politics.
We're just cool.
I think that we can beat this thing a lot.
What is, you know, we're hoping that Ron Paul gets a little bit more ink.
It looks like he is.
And I think the DSC has done some good things.
But just to turn it a little bit, it back to the roots.
Dude, go back to what you do best.
You know, talk about the music, talk about the band, talk about shit.
What you're doing every day and go on on some of those adventures that you went.
You took your mic out there.
You just take a walk and just, we like to hear your, at least I do.
I like to hear just the rock and roll dude and just, and just keep it light and fun.
And get away from all the bullshit that's out there.
Because we need some fun, dude.
We need, we need the DSC and I do.
I want to fucking four or five right now.
Stop and go traffic and I got to listen some good tunes.
Kind of get a guy out there that's just, right, right, the wave a little bit.
And just what's happening around.
So anyways, that's what just I'll shut up now.
But all the best.
Right on.
Love you, it's just a good, but no homo.
Can't say it all the way.
Yeah, I hear you, man.
You know, that is, of course, a great suggestion.
And really it's just that I've been home, I've been sick.
There's been, you know, all this crap that it's really is an interesting to talk about.
Literally crap when you consider how sick I was.
So that's why I've kind of been, you know, sucking air for material.
But there's going to be a lot of talk about the pod show network that I'll be doing in the next couple of weeks.
You know, we're working on changing the way that we do what we call talent relations.
I'm inserting myself very deeply into these new methodologies.
We've got, you know, some some great new ways of communicating as some new people who are who have joined the
talent relations group.
We have a lot of opportunities coming up, particularly with the launch of V3, V3 being the entire
new pod show dot com site, which I think we're just weeks away at this point from going into a closed
beta.
And there is so much work that has to be done and so much so much so many great things that
producers who are on the network and people who want to join the network and participate in
that I think I'm going to be talking a lot about that because it really is extremely exciting
shit that's coming down the bike.
So look for a lot of that.
And also I want to talk a more about the shows that you guys are doing out there.
What the hell are you doing?
You know, I've, I have to admit that I've been kind of in my own world.
It's been so incredibly busy for the past few months that I just, I just really haven't had,
haven't had the opportunity to delve back into what you guys are doing.
And so send me promos.
Let me know what's happening on your show.
I want to talk about that.
They came from Japan.
Robots who are supposed to be entertaining.
Robots who are supposed to be homeless.
So much for that.
From Mark Gilchumodonamkoff, award-winning author and creator of Shadow Force, and number one
with a bullet comes his most off-the-war audio book yet.
Robots run a mark in the city of Los Angeles.
Something manned he's bound to come.
Subscribe today and listen for free.
A transistor rodeo.potcho.com.
Kicks off January 11th.
Do not miss it.
Brand new music now from the potsafe music network.
I think this one's coming out this week.
It's from David Usher.
Neil Beer sent me this one.
Happy to play it because it kicks ass.
Chaka Dogley is beautiful.
I'm the chacha.
All the words we throw away, like they forgots, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the script's real right.
In the cold, the way we love, the way we hate, it's quiet in your room.
All the words we throw away, like they forgots, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, it's quiet in your room.
All the words we throw away, like they forgots, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, it's quiet in your room.
All the words we throw away, like they forgots, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and higher, throughout the day, and large and cold, the way we hate, they just keep filing higher and large and cold, the
was to get someone to underwrite for about $2 billion, the catalog, and they can't find anyone to do that, because there is no money available for it at the moment, so these guys are an incredible kimchi, which I think is swahili for shit, can't quite remember anymore, linked to that in the show, to DailySourceCode.com.
Hey Adam, this is Joel Welsh, I've been a listener since summer of 2005, and I'm finally motivated to call, because there are really two very unique things that I feel I have to share, I think you'd be interested in.
One is, I just finished listening to the DSC number 659 from September 4th, and I listened to it on January 7th, so that's the first unique thing, and I'll tell you a little bit more about that.
This was the show where you shared with us about your cat, Sidney, and the touched me very much, because we just recently went through a similar thing with our cat Moses, a very quick illness, 12-year-old cat, and yeah, man, it really hits your heart and...
I'll just correct you there, the cat's name was Cindy, and we miss him dearly, every single day. Was it really September 4th?
It seems like, in some ways, only yesterday, that he got taken away from us so abruptly, in other ways, it seems like Eons ago.
Yes, I remember, thank you.
Change your life, and we'll never get over it, certainly. We still have Joshua, and so that's wonderful.
But I was just reminded that, hey, it's been four months ago that you shared this very special thing in your life, and I'm learning about it now,
and it's because in August of 2007, this past August, I took a break from listening to the DSC, and I just picked back up in mid-December, but I stayed subscribed that whole time.
And when I wanted to start listening again, I decided I didn't want to miss anything.
I did such a part of your daily life for so long that I didn't want to miss a show, so I'm catching up.
Yeah, it never ceases to amaze me that people actually do that.
And I always say, please, take a break whenever you want to.
If you feel like you need to, you know, just step back from the earbuds for a while, that's completely okay.
But it never ceases to amaze me that people come back to the show, and then we'll pick up where they left off.
You know, sitting through tens of maybe hundreds of hours to catch up with the conversation, and I'm flattered.
No doubt, but I really don't understand it.
I really don't.
You don't have to. Don't feel like you have to do that, but it is obviously very much appreciated.
A little bit at a time, and I just thought you'd be really interested to hear that there are listeners like me that stay subscribed and catch up.
Even though it's, you know, it's been on four months behind.
The second thing is that I think is unique that it's worth sharing with you and your audiences.
I'm actually a startup company entrepreneur.
I've been the chief community officer at startupnation.com for the past four years, and now the CEO of a brand new startup company,
which will level the playing field for high school student athletes and kids in the performing arts,
so that they can showcase themselves for college scholarships and college showcase you.
We're going to have a public, public launch. They're spring with their website.
It showcases you that time.
But what you need about this aspect of me as a listener to the BSC is I listen to the BSC to gain insight into how you are growing and managing pod show.
I usually skip over the songs, although young pellets hit test rocks.
And I always listen to everything that Patricia has to say.
Yeah, me too.
But really, I believe that you and pod show are on the cutting edge of growing and internet based company, and that's what interests me the most.
So I certainly do have some catching up to do.
I can tell you exactly what your life was like in early September.
It would be fun to learn if you really have abandoned the idea of getting a replacement iPhone,
because I'm doing some researching on a new phone purchase myself right now.
So thanks Adam, love the DSC, and I hope your day is sensational.
Thank you, man. Well, you're in luck because, and I don't know how long it's going to take you to catch up to 707.
It seems like there's quite a number of hours to go through.
So feel free to skip ahead.
Yeah, as I said, I'm going to be talking a lot more about that as we've got V3 coming up.
We've got this thing.
We've got hundreds of producers who are just chomping at the bit to do more.
We've finally figured out a lot of our marketing initiatives.
So you should have a lot of fun listening and paying attention to what's going on.
And regarding the iPhone, yeah, you was, you know, I've actually, you don't, but other people know.
I reverted back to the Nokia E61I as my phone still loving that.
And of course, haven't talked about this in a couple weeks.
The Nokia N810 internet tablet is my new device of choice.
It fits beautifully between the phone and the laptop.
And this thing just kicks ass.
And of course, I was hoping that I was going to be able to offer it at a significant discount to the Chacha audience.
Before Christmas, didn't pan out.
There was all kinds of stuff that, you know, just didn't happen.
What can I tell you?
Part of it was agreements, part of it was some technical issues.
But it looks like by the 15th of this month, we'll finally be able to bring these to you at a great discount.
Well, I'll be Hawking it because I love this device so much.
So just stay tuned to the Daily Source Code for more.
Jersey Todd has been raving about this guy.
His kids 15 years old and he's got a couple of songs on the pod save music network.
I got to tell you he's damn good.
Jason Moss, come back home.
I'm the journey.
All people change and I guess I did too.
It's not your fault that the flowers won't bloom.
I couldn't say that we're too bad it's years in our eyes.
In couldn't change that we're too bad it's grown.
Such a shame.
My predictions were wrong.
I couldn't say that we're too bad it's out in the sky.
And I want you to come back home.
Don't forget the faces you left alone.
In the dark you'll find the light.
It seems to me that I couldn't come.
A warning sign that we're going to fall.
So tell your friends that it looks like we're all going down.
Love once strong, it's now fading to cry.
Looks as though time has torn it away.
The piercing silence will open my eyes to the pain.
I want you to come back home.
Don't forget the faces you left alone.
In the dark you'll find the light.
I want you to be okay though you've departed.
Your soul will stay in the dark you'll find the light.
Baby soul you'll see that it was a man to be.
Baby you'll find the light.
My kids got some chops and there's nothing like a four and a half minutes song to enjoy my tuna for sandwich with.
Jason Moths come back home.
It's like a 12 minute special on the guy.
I've got a lot of administration to take care of to have tons of links in the show notes.
I've got all kinds of new messages from the savants who you are used to hearing from on the Charlie.
Programmer sent me a note to that.
I heard you talk about Al Qaeda being a translation meaning the database in Arabic.
My mother's Lebanese and no Arabic so I ran my translation by her.
She said it means the file as in a Manila folder containing sheets.
Which I guess is kind of in a way like a database.
Well, this could be construed he says as a rudimentary database.
He said I actually had grand visions of Oracle hosted on CIA servers in Afghanistan.
I'm sure not the only ones who would you kind of make the clarification on your next show.
Absolutely.
And thank you.
Programmer for a.
I skews me.
Forgetting the the official translation.
Hey, here's a guy who promised he'd be back in 2008.
Comic strip.
Higher Adam Strawberry.
So we have a new year 2008.
And this year has been declared as EU year of intercultural dialogue.
Because in EU still some citizens think that they are better than others.
For example, why it's better than people of color.
West EU, better than East EU.
Catholic, Catholic, better than Muslims.
And it all must end because three EU citizens sit in the same boat.
Also think you winky should be able to carry his men back proudly in the whole EU.
OK.
Respect you.
You.
All right.
OK.
What we'll be looking forward to a lot more from new comic strip blogger.
Yes, of course.
We all have to get along at the EU.
Master sure.
Let me see if there's anything I've overlooked for today's show.
I had tons of notes here.
Let me say.
I think I'm pretty much pretty much on everything.
Yes, it's actually pretty good article from Professor at the University of Chicago law school about the one laptop or child.
I will do that tomorrow.
I want to play one more song that has been sitting in my cube to play on the Charlie for about a month now.
Ingrid Michaelson, the way I am to wrap up today's Charlie.
I'm trying to show how see you if I know what I mean.
Just leave back a relapse.
If you were falling, then I would catch you.
You need a light.
I'd find a match.
Because I love the way you say good morning.
And you take me the where I am.
If you are chilly, here take my sweater.
Your head is aching.
I'll make it better because I love the way you call me baby.
And you take me the where I am.
I'd buy you again.
When you start losing all your hair, so I'm patches.
To all you tear, because I love you more than I could never promise.
And you take me the way I am.
You take me the way I am.
Short, sweet, and generally just really nice.
And of course, pod saving.
You should just take me the way I am.
And that'll do it for today's daily source code.
Pretty sure I'll be able to get another one done for you tomorrow.
So at least a three show week.
Look out.
That's another one of my resolutions for 2008.
I really want to get back to doing more shows.
Still looking for ideas on how to do live programming.
So looking really for some infrastructure.
Let me know what it will work for you.
And of course, everything discussed on today's program.
You will be able to find all the links to in the show notes at daily source code.com.
Send me an email.
Adam at podshow.com any old time.
And I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Imagine headphones without wires.
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset.
A rechargeable listening experience with 11 hours of music playback.
So you and your music are free to move.
Take up yours at Sony.com slash headphones.
Sony wireless headphones.
Your music are unplugged.