Hello Adam, this is Grandpa, no not your grandpa, but I may everybody's grandpa, maybe
two years old, my kids, kids call me grandpa, so I'm grandpa.
Just want to say that I've never had a problem with prostate cancer, and I think you've
explained why with this whole rub one out for cancer.
Thanks a lot of sense, and to you all this, who have a problem with you talking about it
because they want to put an image of you doing your business, maybe I can make them feel
a little better by thinking a grandpa at 82, rubber one out for kids, yeah, the thought of
Adam is so bad now, is it?
Think about it way, listen into the DSC, 769.
For $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, done the next generation radio
content in my years, I like to think I'm flying to the future.
Take a sad song and make it better, remember to let it reach your head, but you can start
doing it forever, hate you, don't make it better, take a sad song and make it better,
remember to let it reach your head, remember to let it reach your head, but you can start
yeah, I love to let it reach your head, and make it better, take a sad song and make it better,
remember to let it reach your head, remember to let it reach your head, remember to let it reach your head,
We were made to go out and get out of it
We don't let you know, we don't let you know
We don't let you know
We made to go out and get out of it
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not, no, no,
Sounds a bit like a football anthem doesn't
I don't think it could be further from the truth mash up by DJ Moore and I believe I sourced that one from mash up town now come
Beatles versus Beck Jude is a loser baby, so why don't you kill you hey, everybody welcome to the Deadly source code episode number
769 coming to you from the
affluent subwoofer serino as as Gilford
Sorry about the footballer Friday. It got pretty footballer, but man, what a Friday. We had how we had the Lisbon treaty being voted
down by the Irish. We had the Netherlands kicking Francis ass in the European Cup finals. I mean, it was just it was just victory all around. It was fantastic. I loved it
I will say something funny happened to me on the way home
Friday as I was flying the Delta Sheriff back. Of course, I recorded the trip over
which was episode 767 or 760 I don't remember any more. As I was at the Rotterdam Jet Center, I noticed that
and I should have taken a picture. I can't believe them such a dick that I didn't. I
waxed it didn't just notice it was hard not to see that there was little old cute Delta
Sheriff standing nose to nose with the royal jet, which I think it's like a 50 passenger deal. I mean, it's a it's a it's a real big plane
and had the opportunity to meet the prime minister of the Netherlands who was off with all of the
cabinet members. I was interested through the Dutch Foreign Affairs Secretary of State and it was pretty cool.
So who knows? Who knows? What kind of conversations we can have soon on the Charlie? Would that be funny if we had a young
painter Balkan and a prime minister of the Netherlands on? Well, it could happen because man, I tell you this this
Lisbon treaty. Well, we'll be talking about that later on today's program obviously, but first a couple of
responses to the sound seeing tour that I did with the November 277 Delta Sheriff going from
Fair Oaks here in the United Kingdom, not far from the affluent suburb of Surrey actually over to
Rotterdam and the Netherlands. Of course, I told you it's best to be enjoyed if you can put it on your car
stereo while you're driving around. In fact, even better if you have someone else driving and you can just close your eyes, but that of course is
you know, again, only if someone else is driving, right? November 277 Delta's Sierra
I'd like to congratulate you on your best at the so keep it coming. Absolutely love love love stuff and
the guy at the departure frequency is one two seven points for our good day.
Why do you seven four good day? I love it when when airplane geeks fall down.
I don't this is Charlie Delphi Lima. Ah, Charlie Delphi Lima that would be Charles the drunken
Londoner, of course. I've just been listening to the AC. I have no idea what it was, but I'm currently on the
out for 31. It sounds like a kill foot. The south of 31. I mean, I've heard this before.
I'm just listening to the AC that you put out of your flying to the Netherlands and I wanted the phone and say
how much I enjoy it, a flicking on found it. So I'm going to be down the road
way down the earth in three. It was just, I don't know, just navigating cars hearing the
trucks going over a single spot like, yeah, it's a big deal. Man, it's just really exciting driving
along. And I enjoy it. Thank you very much. So Bush has been coming on Sunday's tomorrow
that'll be at five spots. Yeah, right on. Charles, well, he enjoyed it. That's nice to know.
But a lot of noise there on the recording Charles and he didn't mention something about about Bush
coming to to London. And of course, he'd, I think it was Charles the drunken London who
phoned it and said, you know, we're going to have this going to be a protest. It starts at one
o'clock. And yes, there was a protest and not a lot of people showed up though about
2000, two and a half thousand people. And of which 25 got arrested and I saw some of the pictures
in some of the papers today. Man, look, like, oops, that's the lady Patricia's just brought me
shake, love her for that. And look like the cops were pretty damn aggressive, man.
And it's certainly that didn't get a lot of coverage. You know, the way we would have
hoped it would have, but, well, certainly support that. And if anyone was there and if
you had an issue with the protesting, I'd like to know why the cops started hammering
everybody and why they arrested people. What went wrong? I mean, couldn't this just be a
a com protest? Very interested to know. If you know, please give us a call on the
voice mail lines or drop me an MP3 if you don't mind.
Hello, Adam, I'm from Germany here. Just looking to see 76 data, I think it was
while hiking around here. Being a pilot myself, I really like the fact that you
brought tons of recall of the thing in the air. And this thing, Germany, flying
is still something that many people are afraid of or don't know how it works or
think it's only for the rich. Yeah.
Hey, Marcus. These days, it is only for the rich, man. Holy crap. I can't believe
how much it's costing the flying now with a fuel price. I mean, no, no. I'm sure
I've once seen that going shut the F up. Who cares about your problems with flying?
You know, I've burned about 60 liters an hour. Of course, I get quite a
distance. You know, I go about 170 miles on that 60 liters.
But wow, it's become rather expensive. I think the most recent fuel
price I got with VAT, so that's all the tax putting was about one pound
60 per liter. You can only imagine how that shit starts to stack up
after a while. And I remember filling up the aircraft completely
full for under 300 pounds. Only, you know, I don't know, six months ago.
And now it seems like I can't get away for less than 500 if I
feel of a thousand dollars to fill up the plane. It's not really,
it's not really for everybody anymore.
In fact, it is for rich people.
I have to fight to the sometime because obviously I'm flying. I'm not rich.
I mean, I mean, beyond what you would consider.
So I really liked that I was thinking this morning about recording
a traffic pattern flying a motorglider and putting that out somewhere.
So people can better get it on the standing of what
needs to be done to fly such a plane.
Yeah, you should do that, man. I'd be interested to hear that because
it's a hell of a lot quieter than my plane.
Motorglider, all you might hear the put put put put or it could even
be even softer than that. And of course, really, I think it just
wins, shushing by. That should be cool, dude. You should do that.
Anyway, I think you could do that more often.
I think it's really interesting, especially if the weather is not so nice,
like the way you headed this time.
Anyway, thanks. I think I'm supposed to say they work for us.
But yeah.
And they absolutely do.
One more about this before we move on to another topic.
What I'm doing, man.
Fuckin' love that start to zero.
I don't see her. I don't see her.
I don't see her. I don't think that's not where I was fuckin' play it.
On the cast, out of where the base is.
I don't know.
I think I'll do it.
Yeah, it's ready for us.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Yeah, go name, thank you.
Yeah, that's the way to play it, man.
Wait until I get better, and I get, you know,
like a turbine or a turbo prop or something like that.
You know, we'll just have a nice wine.
I can't wait.
That would be a WHINE, not WINE.
So of course, the Lisbon Treaty,
The Lisbon Treaty, holy moly, unbelievable what's going on here.
Over the weekend, lots and lots of coverage, of course.
This is a huge deal for those of you who haven't been following along.
Essentially, the Irish voted no to the Lisbon Treaty, which is a version
of a constitution for it, the European Union.
Excuse me.
Oh, that really felt good.
The constitution isn't really the right word.
Of course, the word constitution was scrapped from the Lisbon Treaty,
or really from the constitution to become the Lisbon Treaty.
It's like an legal document that talks about a lot of things in very complicated language,
not really telling you what the hell is going on.
But it will shift, I believe effectively, about 50% of all governmental powers
in each of the 27 member states, over to Brussels,
or alternatively, distractsburg.
Remember, they have two seats of government and the alternate cities,
because I don't know.
Someone got pissed off and they had to do two.
It's like a childish baby thing.
Anyway, so now ministers of the European Parliament,
foreign ministers are foreign affairs, they're saying,
you know, so this treaty can't be pushed through.
It can't go into effect unless all 27 member states ratified.
Ireland now is said no way.
We don't want it, we're not going to ratify it.
So it shouldn't be happening.
And now there's all this like, well, how about two out of three?
You know, we could do another vote, or we could isolate Ireland.
I mean, it's driving me nuts.
It's like move on.
What you guys are going to do is just take a piece of paper,
and write down 20 points about what this document says.
In plain English, plain Jane, please.
Hey, you work for us, do some.
And then we can actually decide on the issues,
instead of trying to ramrod something through,
you know, 26 of the member states,
leaving only one hole open, oops, G.
Do you think that if all countries that had a referendum,
we wouldn't have a lot more no votes, of course we would have.
Because people are suspicious.
They don't understand that they can't read these documents.
I tried.
It's complicated.
You can't get answers.
There's no FAQ.
There you go.
How about the FAQ treaty?
That would be something for you guys to look into.
Hello, Mr. Curry.
Still Sky, you determined you pulling in from Dublin, Ireland.
I'm here, actually.
My second week at my new job, working for Google,
from hearing Dublin training, man.
No, that's the job you took for less money.
Makes sense.
It's Google.
I hope you got some stock.
Wow, man.
It's a great experience, great experience.
Hey, I actually really called in to say,
big thank you to Terry.
Terry, thank you for the great audio clip.
Now, every-
Oh, this is Terry Little Red,
who sent in a sexy audio comment.
I believe that was to help out with the prostate cancer prevention
Quote.
Time to work on my prostate prevention quota.
I got your beautiful voice in my mind,
and I don't have ugly queries.
Bounding through my brain.
It's very, very nice.
You're very nice.
I really appreciate the gesture.
There's one problem though.
I still have visuals of Curry.
Maybe if you shoot me like some make-up pictures,
you know, eliminate that problem as well.
Terry, thank you very much.
Look forward to seeing those pictures.
Check out my blog, people.
The J-Node.logspot.com.
T-H-E-J-N-O-T-E.
Docs, Docs, Docs, Docs, Docs, Docs, Docs, C-A.
Bye-bye.
All right, sales guy.
I thought he was going to be in Ireland
about the treaty.
Clearly, I was wrong there.
Somehow, the masturbation always seems to creep into the show
at one point or the other.
I had a big spread of Jones.
You'll probably get this in in different ways.
But according to Aunt A, the Irish State Bullcaster,
the good people in the Republic of Ireland have voted
no to the list been treaty.
Yeah?
Good one.
Yeah.
I got thousands of messages, emails, text messages.
And of course, it happened when I was actually flying back.
So the minute I got in the car at the airfield,
here at Ferrox, I turned on the radio.
And I was like, boom.
By the way, I really liked the BBC World Service.
Man, it is really superior to a lot of just the newsbotons
in general, of course, on regular radio 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
Well, the radio 5 does go in a radio 4 goes into depth
into a lot of topics, which is nice.
But the world service, the quality of course is shit
because it's a medium wave.
But then again, it's almost like listen to a really bad MV
three-file.
Oops.
I didn't want to play that one.
Here's what I wanted.
Come extra.
What do you think?
Will it be about Ireland?
One can only guess.
Hello.
Adam.
That's where you present your carry.
So, in the year 2004, Big Bang EU Entertainment took place,
and old EU members thought that new EU members
will hinder the development of EU.
But the contrary is through Polish immigrants
have extremely high work ethic.
No lesser than Koreans and Japanese,
and the Czech beers are the best in the world.
And the Kritek Estonia has created
a software that you, Adam, carry, and your Uncle Dvorak.
Use every week Skype.
Skype.
Yes.
Recently, the old EU members,
Netherlands and Friends have rejected new EU constitution,
and last week also Ireland
that would be the third word country
without many, many billions of subsidies from EU.
It does.
Well, let me finish one.
Has rejected EU treaty.
Biting the hand that was feeding it.
You know, doesn't that say something there?
Comments your blogger?
I mean, doesn't that?
Is that exactly the way it should be?
That they said despite that they're getting a billion euros a year
from the European Union.
They're still saying, hey, hold on a second.
You know, we don't like this.
Obviously, people would know that they're putting that at risk.
Again, I think it's just because they don't understand
what's being said.
And, you know, and ministers of European Parliament have
copped to this.
I said, yeah, yeah, that's true.
We really should do a bit of job.
Well, now's your chance.
Now, you guys going to go to it.
You put up a website with 20 or 40 points and say,
this is what this thing is about, and here's what
each issue is.
It's that simple people.
Without which, the new EU treaty,
without which the economy of EU will be damaged,
because in fact, EU will not be able to work smoothly.
I see, I don't know, I just don't agree.
I think the EU so far is working fantastically.
At least, at the surface level,
it seems like a lot of things are going well.
No matter what this document says,
it'll take years and years to implement everything
and smooth over whatever bumps are bound to be in the road.
But what is it?
What will make it run smoother?
What will make it run smoother than it is right now?
Please, someone explain what the treaty says.
And the comic strip blogger,
since you know it's a well, give me the 10 or 20 points
that are listed in this treaty.
You're the EU specialist.
Go down the list.
It's 269 pages.
It weighs 11 pounds when printed out.
Please tell me what it says.
You're going to be able to face globalization.
Nobody wants real globalization, man.
Because that means there's a new world order.
Wake up, CSB.
Well, I will continue to like Irish people anyway.
And I will not stop buying Q&A and Guinness,
but now we only need to rethink future of European Union.
Europe.
Hmm.
Well, I don't see there's a problem with the future of the European Union.
First of all, we've got the same money,
which is a good start, at least most of us, too.
With the euro.
It's a strong currency.
We have a great time with playing football against each other.
That seems to be working out fine.
You know, you have this downers like the Eurovision Song Contest.
But in general, I think we all like each other.
We get along.
We work with each other's countries.
What do we need to do?
What do we need to shore up here?
What are the things that and what benefit will it be to the citizens of the European Union?
That's what I want to know.
Just make it simple and tell me.
And I bet you that people, if they see the benefit, they'll vote for it.
It's that simple.
Hey, Adam.
It's a topic right here.
And this is not about new currency.
No.
Hey, I just picked up my Saturday edition of the Wall Street Journal.
Top headline.
Europe and turmoil after Irish vote.
Apparently, the Irish have rejected the Lisbon Treaty by 53 to 47 percent.
Yep.
What do you go at them?
They work for us.
It's not like I had anything to do with it.
But if I change just one person's mind, then I'm very proud of that.
Actually, I got an email that I want to share with you.
This came in today.
From I think it's Daniel.
Hi, Adam.
Yeah.
My name's Dan.
I'm one of your few underage listeners.
Just wanted to say I really appreciate all you do for us.
Can't wait to listen to your show when I get home from school.
I agree.
Mainstream media is just drugs for your brain.
That's why I listened to the DSC.
Also, I'm thinking about buying the new iPhone 3G when it comes out.
It'll be nice to know what you think about it.
If it's mail, 16, live an upstate New York student.
Love, you know, homo, great hair.
Hope you win.
Remember they should work for us.
Hey, Dan.
Well, I'm going to get one.
I think that comes out on July 11.
I'm going to get a UK one because I really need a good UK number.
And besides, I think that deals probably better with the UK version.
And I'll let you know how it goes.
I'm sure that dropping in the toy that will still be a no-no.
But otherwise, I think it's as we say here.
It's taken off all of the boxes.
Jesus.
Put back.
Hi, Adam.
It's Matt from Gamesweasel.
On this week's show, I review Rates driver grid on the Xbox 360.
Also play Lego Indiana Jones on the DS.
And you can win copies of a loan in the dark for the Xbox 360.
That's all the gamesweasel.com.
Yeah, just wanted to remind you that we had this new product, new sponsor of the Charlie.
And for those of you who use hard drives, external hard drives, like a USB or a fire wire drive,
for big media files.
And I have mine on order because boy, do I need this device.
And I know other people that I know people do use a lot of Photoshop files.
These are gigabyte files.
And man, when you look at the archiving process that I have to go through on this show,
I'm going to let me take a look.
Excuse me.
Oh boy.
Nice shake.
Let's see how my MacBook Pro, which, of course, I'm using to record the show.
I now have 57 gigs available of a total 148 gigs.
You know, that's not going to last me all that much longer.
I've only had this thing for, what is it?
Nine, ten months, something like that.
Now, I use an external USB, so USB drive.
It's one of the, you know, like a let's see, which I'm not, I'm not too keen on let's see actually.
I use that for backup with time machine.
But really, I just like to have one drive that can store all of the source code files,
which is just a lot, you know, concerning all the source material.
And then, of course, the, the actual renderings, and then there's the project files.
And they'll, and believe me, not a lot of work goes into this.
And so this Drobot is essentially, it's an external drive that, it works a bit like a raid
where it's fail safe, but it grows as you grow.
Oh, yeah, it just keeps on growing, baby.
And the way it works, I can't wait to get it.
The way it works is, you put in a drive.
I think it's like almost like a regular ATA based, you know, like a western digital.
You see, I'm just a raw drive.
You slide it into a slot.
Yeah, that's like your one terabyte or two derabytes.
You even have four terabyte versions.
And, you know, then if you need more space, you can just pop in a new one.
You can keep popping them in.
You can actually upgrade them.
So if you had, you know, let's say four one terabyte drives.
You could take one out, put it in a four terabyte, you know, put it in a four terabyte drive,
without, you know, losing your data.
You can even do it on the fly, hot swappable.
It's really outrageous.
It costs $499.
There's a bundle they have now.
Actually, so it's safe.
You want to buy the regular unit, the Drobot basic.
It's $50 off if you use the code DSC, obviously, for daily source code.
Then they have the bundle, which is the Drobot unit with a western digital green power,
one terabyte hard drive or a two terabyte or four terabyte.
Actually, only last till June 30, you see, you have to hurry up on that one.
Also, $50 off.
Use the code DSC, go to DrobotStore.com.
And now, let's try and solve the hit test.
The hit test.
I'm counting casting.
I'm going to miss this, you see?
Hit test.
Hit it test.
Young boldness.
Hey, Adam, it's time for the hit test again.
And this is intro number one.
Straight to it.
Please, y'all.
It's in a one of these starting something.
Got to be starting something.
No, it's Michael Jackson.
Number two.
I'm sure it's like earth wind and fire or something like that.
I don't know the song.
Earth wind and fire.
And number three.
Don't push me because I'm close to the edge premise to flash with the message.
Yon, making it easy on me today.
And these are the answers.
The hit test.
From 1979, answer number one.
This is Michael Jackson.
Love me.
Did I see you?
Can I say one of these starting something?
Because that was wrong.
Obviously it's don't stop.
Don't stop to get enough Michael Jackson's answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
From 1980, earth wind and fire.
I still don't recognize the song.
I can't let go of earth wind and fire is answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
From glass everywhere.
People pissin' on the fidget no to just don't care.
I can't taste mouth.
Can't take the noise.
Got no money to move on.
I guess I got no choice.
Don't push me because I'm close to the edge.
It's I'm trying not to lose my head.
It's like a joke with some times.
It makes me wonder how I keep going under.
From 1983, Graham has the flesh and the fury is five and the message.
And that concludes here's number 126.
So Adam, how did you do this for you?
Well, I think in my haste I messed it up on Michael Jackson,
but I'll say two out of three then just to make it fair.
Like always, hitters.mefio.com is the place to find the answers to this and any other hitters.
And also the links to why two, so you can buy the tracks featured in the hitters online.
Thank you for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I'll be back for another hitters.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And remember to try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
Be back.
Hitters.mefio.com.
Info.com.
I want to play something completely different for you today.
I've done this in the past.
Guys got some new tracks up on the Potship music network.
And he is a complete virtuoso.
His name's Welp Rivera.
Influenced by the heaviest rock bands in the world.
He takes it to the classical tip.
Orchestrated for the Charlie.
This is Tears.
Tears.
I've done this in the past.
Holy crap.
I love it.
It's so bombastic.
So huge.
And yet.
It's harder.
Oh, damn.
Well, Roberto.
You know, that's coming out of a computer or synthesizer.
Man, it just blows me away.
What is doing the orchestration is awesome.
It sounds authentic.
It doesn't sound like like meaty or anything.
It's just awesome.
Fantastic.
I could listen to that.
When you crank that up on a pair of really good speakers,
it will freak you out.
I guarantee.
Adam, it's sweet from the Bay Area.
So we're just doing some thinking.
You know, we've been talking about dual clear energy for a while here.
And I haven't open minded.
But something's caught in my mind that.
I don't think we've talked about.
And that's it.
We've got a couple of nuclear power plants that are active in the Bay Area.
One's on East Bay.
And if you press another one and there's definitely one on the central valley.
Rancho is big.
And just after 9.11.
The press jump over on A.
You know, these things are protected.
And the turn is fixed target.
It's probably going to be the nuclear power plants because they can create.
You know, a strong nuclear blast out of these things.
By doing X, Y, or Z.
And we're in danger.
And we've got to get the protected.
And of course, they've never been protected.
Now, I know.
Atomic Rod Adams.
He has jumping out of his feet right now.
If you're seeing the play this on the show.
I want to know why that's not true.
I want to hear the atomic rod explain to me that it's not.
If that fear was overblown.
But better yet.
I want to know why.
I want to know a little bit of detail.
Why is that not true?
What has changed?
Why is that?
Why isn't it clear?
Power plant is not as dangerous as they used to be.
I haven't read a lot of detail.
It's true somewhere out of the load to hear that.
Yeah.
You know.
Yeah, they were crushed.
What's that?
What's going on?
Hold on.
Oh, no.
This is weird.
Something's happening here.
I'm not quite sure.
Where's this coming from?
Do you guys hear that?
This is freaking me out.
Hold on.
I don't know if you can hear this.
But wait.
Let me.
Maybe if I get rid of this.
Well, that's stop.
Yeah.
You guys didn't even hear that.
Did you?
Yeah.
Oh, crap.
I'm sorry about that.
Okay.
I don't.
For a second there, I considered editing that out because you couldn't hear what was going on
because I hit a web page and it just like freaked out on me.
So forget about it.
I won't do that.
Yeah.
Very interesting.
And of course, completely in line with what atomic rot has always been saying,
that, you know, this is like all perception.
So what you're saying is after 9-11,
people were talking about the vulnerability of nuclear power stations
in San Francisco and the Bay Area.
And nothing has been done to protect them from any type of terrorist attack.
And of course, there's lots of nuclear moon juice factories around the United States
and around the globe.
So atomic rot.
That is a great question for you, my friend.
You know, I got to get raw to jingle man.
He deserves it by now.
That's for sure.
Looking forward to that answer.
And also, did you hear about this other?
This was great.
This has been circling around the net.
See, where does this article come from?
Times online.
Apparently, a scientist who I think is operating
in the Bay Area.
Yes.
See, the company is called LS9.
Has developed a DNA modified bug in insect
that when he eats like wood chips,
he actually poops out oil.
Crude oil.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
It's too funny.
And so now, of course, they have to see if they can make this bug poop on scale.
But, oh, my gosh, can you just imagine the branding we can come up with for that?
Oh, that's beautiful.
Yeah, LS9.
Lemus here and nine.
You've got to check this out.
I'm sure they have a website somewhere.
I can't find it.
But anyway, if the story goes,
the scale is really the big problem right now.
If they wanted to produce enough oil for the United States to use on a daily basis,
they basically would have to have a plant.
For growing these DNA modified bugs,
you know, the size of like a higher or something like that.
So that may be a non-starter, but still very, very interesting.
Let me see.
I got to wrap this up.
I got like a conference call coming up and all kinds of stuff going on.
Of course tomorrow.
I think let me just check the calendar tomorrow.
I'm home as well.
Tomorrow is even a slower day.
So the storm, I don't want to promise anything.
But I'm definitely trying to get a couple of charities out.
Because I know we're on to a couple of topics here that are just going on fire.
And we've got to keep tracking this Lisbon treaty.
Because who knows what they're going to try and pull on us?
You know, those guys that work for us.
So now we've, see, we heard from Charles of Drunken London at the beginning of the show.
And this, you'll probably like this.
Because I have three, three voice messages from him.
So the first one you heard.
Now check this one out.
As goals, I'm home in London.
You know, I am, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know who you are.
Well, I'm there to meet today.
I'm hanging out with her for the day.
And she said to me, you can't be a prime minister if you're Jewish.
And I said, what?
What?
She said, well, this really had to convert to church Winkland.
So I know you're sort of American Dutch and now an Englishman.
But do you have to be?
I think Charles is already living up to his name on this one folks.
He's Anglican.
To be the prime minister of England.
Is it?
I mean, is it?
Yeah, like you report into the head of being this church.
Yeah, it's just being clean, right?
Yes.
It has the English church.
Whatever the fuck that means.
Is that the way it is?
Is that, is that?
You know, Charles, that's a really good question, man.
I had no idea.
So if you want to be prime minister, you have to be a member of the Church of England.
And if you are of a different faith, you have to convert.
I don't know if that's true.
You know, England doesn't actually have a constitution as far as I know.
But as they refer to the Magna Carta a lot.
And I know I know how to pronounce it, but I'm sorry.
I don't actually know a lot about the history of the Magna Carta.
I have seen it with my own eyes and the museum.
I'll have to look that up and see what's going on with it.
What?
Yeah.
Is anyone out there can explain that?
And also, could maybe your sister, he's got a cool name.
Something might blossom.
Willow.
Hello.
A little bit about this Roman...
What's the word?
There.
That's just been elected as sort of Neo-Nazi reform Neo-Nazi.
But he says he's going to kick all the Romanian down.
And supposedly his police forces are already burning down the houses of Romanian chipsies
in Rome.
Yeah, comics are blogger mentioned something about this maybe last week, about two weeks ago.
About this guy who's like, I don't know about burning down the houses, but yeah, I'm sure
Willow will be more than delighted to check in with the report.
Oh, yeah.
I've got a rambling.
Yes, you have my friend.
You go swim, but ready to pop it.
Dude.
You're too funny man.
I love it when you call it.
He has one more that he's so plastered.
He's so hammered.
And it's the funniest one yet.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to save that one until tomorrow.
Adam, hey, Friday 76 daily source code.
Excellent.
Thank you so much.
It was fantastic.
And one more thing.
You know, there's two people.
Doers and talkers.
Thanks for inspiring.
And it's just a handful of us that talk.
Dude, we could change the world.
I really believe that.
So to all the viewers out there, thank you.
Thank you.
I'm already to be a one of them.
And I really appreciate the ESC.
It's part of my life.
Thank you, Adam.
All the best.
And you're absolutely right.
They work for us.
I know a girl.
She puts the color inside of my way.
But she's just like a maze.
We're all over the world.
I'll continue to change.
And I don't know like it.
To stand on the steps with my heart and my head.
And now I'm just starting to see.
Maybe it's got nothing to do with me.
So people need to call for a chance.
So people need to just wanna be.
So people need to just play the game.
Oh, you see that skin, it's the same, she's been stale in there
Since the day she saw him walking away, now she lives
Clean it up and mess it me
Some people said, oh, I'll take
I miss this poor man like y'all
Some people think we know the truth
That's the truth, that's the truth
That's the only way to pull you away
And be the world on the silver bed
And what would it be?
We know when to share
But no one who truly cares for me
Some people want it all
But I don't want nothing at all
If you're a new baby
If I ain't got a new baby
Some people want it all
But I don't want nothing at all
If I ain't got a new you, you, you, you
So far there's bigger to your darkness
The darkness will let you turn
Because we can't love it
We turn into lovers
So much bigger to your darkness
Still, as you can bring
You find out how much they can take
Those will be strong
And those souls are out
Those will be calm with our warmth
And what about you?
Can't hide me
So far there's bigger to your darkness
The darkness will let you turn
Because we can't find out how much they can take
So far, let's begin to your darkness
The darkness will have a lack of time
Because they come and love us and turn into my lives
So far, let's begin to your darkness
The mash of this world of course was especially for fathers day
For all the fathers out there
I did definitely source this one a mash up town.com
Dr. Art really hit home with that one mash of those two songs
Well he didn't do it but posting that one with us two songs mashed together
Particularly if you've got a daughter then
Well you can know how I feel right now
If you feel the same with you have a daughter or a son
Or if you're a daughter or a son
Which I guess we all are in one way or another
Hey guys, it's been fun going through all these topics
Looking forward to your responses email
Adam and mevio.com
That's Mike echo Victor India Oscar
You can go to curry.com
That's where you can find the latest blog post
And of course daily sourceco.com
As we can find this show
And all of the archives
Until we meet which I'm pretty sure we'll be tomorrow
Make sure you enjoy your freedom
One out last and leave your life with passion
Another fine mevio presentation
Stick it in your ear