This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
This is Sergeant Enes,
Nud Parker of the National Transportation Safety Administration,
Department of Homeland Security.
Not performing full body cavity searches.
I'm listening to the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Adam, is that you again in my line?
I thought I'd just gave you body cavity search.
Not just 10 minutes ago.
That's what I thought.
Alright, you asked for it.
Bend over.
Here comes the daily source code.
Number seven, one, five.
That's $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying to this joint.
Fantastic, it's Adam Curry.
If you lead when you stand in everywhere you go,
you will bleed where you land in.
Everyone will know when you need her.
Surely you will know it was me who was standing,
and feeling for your show.
So I've been seeing you and me as fish that can only grow.
Because everyone knows I gave you everything.
But you got the best of me.
Hey, what a shame.
That was the only one who didn't know what you had done to it.
Because all you ever do was blame.
If you were for illusion,
pause it on the frame.
You can draw the conclusion.
Everyone's the same.
I was a fool from the get-go.
And you would take a sea of the things I should let go.
Since then I don't need anyone.
I'll be seeing you and me as fish that can only grow.
Because everyone knows I gave you everything.
But you got the best of me.
Hey, what a shame.
I was the only one who didn't know what you had done to it.
Because all you ever do was blame.
Hey, what a shame.
And with my cowbells.
You got the best of me.
Hey, what a shame.
I was the only one who didn't know what you had done to it.
I don't care what I say, y'all
I gave you everything, you got the best of me
Hey, what a shame
I was the only one who didn't know what you had to say
What a shame
How you ever do is blame
Sister Hazel from the Podsake Music Network
Shane, they're from Florida
Think of the show notes of dailystorescode.com
It's stealth and share of Charlie episode number 715
It is Tuesday, January 29th
Is it 29th already?
What happened to January?
What did it go?
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Sitting here in the Curri condo
Overlooking the access ramp to the Bay Bridge
And looking at the tower of death because I do have a different set up
I'm not at the Bay Bridge right now that I'm fully on the Mac
With Ableton Live
Thank you so much for sending in comments
Suggestions about the sound quality
Once I get the MIDI controller in place
It'll be a lot better obviously because I'm still kind of using the mouse
To basically control the faders
Not the easiest way I think to do in the world
I hope you had a good weekend
Oh man, it's going to be another week here in San Francisco
More meetings, more stuff
I'm actually feel pretty good
I feel reasonable despite the long hours
And getting a real early
And basically not knowing where my body is
935 in the evening right now
Sitting at the dining room table
As I've taken over the new spot here
You guys watched television recently
I just hadn't turned it on since I've been here
And I turned it on and it's like nothing
It's like repeats and apple ads
That's all I'm seeing
See a lot of ads for the apple air
Their new laptop
And then just repeats
I mean if I were network executive
I'm looking at the fox right now
At least I have it on the background
If I was a network executive
And I needed to go and repeat stuff like house
Which I think is actually a brilliant series
I really like watching that
Why do the Christmas episode?
It puts me off immediately
It's a repeat, it's freaking Christmas
Just doesn't make any sense
What is making sense my friends
And a lot of you have been sending in comments
And I really appreciate it
I'm starting to understand the demographic profile
Of the typical daily source code listener
And guess what?
There is no typical demographic
Of the daily source code listener
It seems like we've got 20 year olds
And 40 year olds
No one who's anywhere in between
Has called up or written in yet
But a lot of interesting people
Hey, I'm just cold
I'm going to try again
Just a look is
And on your last show
You're just asking about the age and demographics
Of your audience
So I'll just tell you a little about myself
I'm 22 and male obviously
As most listeners are
I'm going to college for management information
Wait a minute
That's what you say
I'm hoping that there's some women around
System so that I graduate this fall
And I just think that
Imagination is probably a great one of the end
Because I've been around for the
Since I've been born
We've seen the rise of the internet
And the rise of cell phones
And I'm probably far the last generation
It didn't actually
grow up their entire life having all that stuff around them and it's just awesome to
think about how much change has happened in just the last 10 years in technology
was it's just awesome anyway I've got more to say about other things you've
been talking about but I won't bore you anymore I'll say it for another day.
Another day.
Alright man thank you.
Appreciate it.
So I can to we got a new VP of sales at Pod Show is named Chris Little that's a very
interesting guy and knows a hell of a lot about advertising and sales and he's but
he's also like a lot of really good sales guys I'll just say sales guys for a second
here because we also have sales girls, sales girls, sales girls, y'all.
You know very masculine type guy and you know there's a lot of I would have to say
a particular vocabulary that say it that kind of like what kind of come in a way and
I don't want anyone to take this the wrong way but in a way they're also great sales
guys are like great traders on Wall Street and you know what I'm saying and so really
really to the point and in your face with what they're saying and so we're talking
about you know I said it you know Chris you know this is really interesting I've got a
I mean I've been asking people about about who they are and and what demographic profile
they fit into and seems like I got 20 year olds 40 year olds they're all kind of
interested in one out of all but most seem to be interested in technology one way or the
other and he said yeah oh totally man you got Jack and Jill's I said what you got Jack and
Jill's listening like what is that mean apparently Jack and Jill is a term in the advertising
business where Jack is a guy who's usually in IT or tech or is making a lot of money or by
regular standards a lot of money and Jill is always looking for the right Jack because Jill
wants to sub zero freezers in the micro is this is real advertising speak right but just crack
me up to think that because I got this visual of all you guys out there you know you're all Jack
and Jill's so here's a Jill actually Gene I should say Adam what is this you say no
chicks listen to the show don't forget me American chicken Holland I wrote it in before oh
and I'm 30 years old by the way there you go exception to the rule love the show keep it up
but don't forget chicks do in fact listen to okay now I like that I'm not allowed to ask for
naked pictures anymore as you know my wife has forbidden me from from doing that but I was thinking
it for sure hello Adam curry this is Mark thank all I am amazed at the Ron Paul supporters
in my local community there are so many Ron Paul banners flying everywhere in our house
and I'm amazed by that because I haven't seen a single Hillary Clinton banner I haven't seen a
single became nobody except for Ron Paul I think that's good news my friend
I love you Adam curry bye yeah you didn't actually tell me where you're from but that's
for sure the Ron Paul supporters and it seems like we're we're getting stronger and gaining more
momentum if you didn't know already we're going for the gold we want to raise five million dollars
for Dr. Ron Paul's campaign by February fifth which of course is a super Tuesday it's coming up
this Tuesday go to RonPaul 2008 dot com and donate let me see how he's doing actually haven't
I haven't looked recently let me just this is kind of weird I only have one monitor now
so he used to to multiple monitors gosh let me see let's see Ron Paul 2008 see where we are
going for the gold five million wow wow what is he up to now three point seven oh we'll make
five million easy oh that's great that is fantastic I'm very happy about that and I'm really
happy for for a couple of specific reasons the extremely attentive and yes in some cases fanatic
Ron Paul supporters have been mailing in and this is this really irks me let me just
bring up this email this is in regards to the BBC the BBC have the US election poll tracker
and it's I guess it's a flash widget let me see yeah it's a flash widget on this page of course
I'll put a link to it in the in the show notes a daily source code dot com so you can click on
Democrat and then you see the candidates and then there's you know like the poll numbers and
it's a it's a real nice graph stuff but but here's what's interesting and this was brought to my
attention by uh Brennick Jones says hey Adam check out this BBC news webpage it contains absolutely
no mention of Dr. Paul I wrote an email to the BBC below asking WTF is going on except I was
more polite and also more pointed can't believe their response well first let me tell you what
what the deal you always with this so the Democratic candidates on this poll tracker are Hillary Clinton
John Edwards and Barack Obama so they've got three in the race if you click on the Republican side
and it's loading up here you have Mike Huckabee Fred Thompson, Mitt Romney, Rudy Giuliani
and John McCain Fred Thompson dropped out of the friggin race he's he's not even he's he's with
drawn so of course the point is that Ron Paul is not listed so Brennick sends an email and says hey
I'm puzzling up set the BBC news website is chosen to ignore Dr. Ron Paul from the list of
Republican candidates whilst the full Democratic possibilities are shown what can this mean is this
an active sabotage censorship or just complete an utter incompetence to miss out just one
candidate deliberate or accidental deliberately surely here's their response I'll I'll I'll do the
BBC a voice come so good at it thank you for your email regarding the amount of coverage devoted
to particular candidates it is of course a judgment call it's better that we have not covered
Mr. Paul to any great degree I'm sorry it is true that we have not covered Mr. Paul to any great
degree although we have mentioned him in several articles if he continues to do well or better
than expected we will certainly devote more space to him his policies and his campaign
bullshit I say, bullets on you all that's such horseshit you know and this just this just really
show and by the way I don't believe in any conspiracy that the BBC is you know trying to keep
Ron Paul they're just stupid they're dumb tools they just copy shit from around the world they
don't actually do any investigation you know if what a contradictory message that is he came in
second you know the guy is he's definitely on the map and I'm sorry how can you have Fred Thompson
up there if he's withdrawn from the race and not have Ron Paul total total bullet bullet
bullets shit that's what I'd call it can you tell him a little bit tired and then I got this other note
this is also pretty lame very typical just opening up the Gmail message here
from George Adam greatly appreciate your support and official endorsement of course
Ron Paul for president great to see so many endorsements coming to Ron Paul despite the
media's lack of attention MTV in alliance with my space is running their debate form on February
second in an absolute stab in the back of young people MTV is decided to exclude Dr. Paul
from the mix while still inviting the extremely lagging Rudy Giuliani who has half the votes
that Ron does in the primary and caucus season as you probably already know I figured with your
time at the channel if you were to bring it up and become out spoken on it we could get this
corporate bias BS out to more people nice way people just because you worked on the station bubble
and of course he says well this this is probably a hit job put out by Viacom and it's medium
conglomerate friends news corp and maybe maybe look they're just looking for sex appeal
and honestly Ron doesn't have sex appeal you know Giuliani's local to New York so that's easy
you know they just invite him he just hops in in a government vehicle and drives on over
but yeah that's lame let me see who was it the thought MTV was cool I don't think they've been
that in a long long time anyway we'll continue to support Dr. Ron in the independent media we'll
get him his $5 million and we'll continue to support him super Tuesday could be very interesting that's
when for those the outside the US that's when a whole mess load of states do their caucuses
in the and do their primary voting and that's really the day when when we hope to see Dr. Ron
move ahead and by the way I did have you know maybe it's just a wishful thinking or a dream but
somewhere in the back of my mind something was scratch and saying you know if he doesn't get the
Republican nomination I have a feeling that with all the momentum and and everything that's happening
I think he can't can't do anything but run as an independent I believe people will really rally
around him and almost almost force him into it and he could do it because really all you need
is just tons and tons and money and the reason why he's been with the Republican party besides
the fact that he feels he's a true Republican which I think there's a lot of merit to that statement
is because there's no way to get into the debate if you're not affiliated with either of the big
two parties of course it's clearly not a guarantee oh whoa is me yeah this has been from Oakland
I'm one time missing sorry I'm calling I just thought I'd give a call sounds like you have an opening
for financial or economic advanced I yes indeed we do no word from the nylon so he's I think
he's a slit off the bar stool and given up his slides leave me a quick message a couple questions yet
I'm trying to show first of all you had asked what the official definition of a recession was
yes indeed I think it was a couple people are saying that we're in a recession as comics
were blogger keeps saying it's a what is the official definition of a recession a lot of people have
their own kind of colloquial definition of the official definition is a two consecutive quarters
of negative growth in GDP kind of a tough thing to do but happens from time to time and the
other weird thing about recession is you don't know you're in one until you're in one because
the whole two quarters of consecutive declining period okay so are we actually in one at this point
also you said stuff about the said and how they control interest rates and you think you're
given a little too much credit there that's a lot like saying that Microsoft and Intel can
completely control what goes on in the technology industry wow that's not exactly what I meant
but I think it goes beyond interest rates they're the guys that actually maybe maybe I should
shut up and listen to this to the expert you are the new savant my friend let me just go take a
back seat that has absolute control over one interest rate alone that's kind of discount rate is
the rate at which banks will end to other banks that also has a fed fund target rate this is
the rate at which the federal and two other banks but this only a target on that control that
through open market activities buying and selling bonds all of their interest rates are determined
by market forces and kind of supplying demand so hope that helps keep up the great show and
yeah we'll talk to later thanks man and call in any time you you hear by our best out with the
crown of official savant of the charlie and nylon could suck it yeah I've been keeping up I've been
watched I think I think it's just a great headline right now you know the you know the stories
about recession but the fact is I think wall you know Wall Street is rebounded the shorts of all
covered it's just uncertainty it's just you know basically it's it's the banks not trusting each other
that's that's the biggest problem right now and I think we're we're now in ining I'd say it's almost
time for the seventh ining stretch of this of this crises and we will come out of it and I don't
think we'll actually go into recession because that's that's yes technically it's two quarters
of downward growth is that we saw or or loss of GDP when I've even forgot the definition but
it's also just a mindset it truly is oh speaking of mindset man I hope in my big fat mouth about
this trial that time Warner cable is doing in uh Beaumontaxis lovely Beaumontaxis for
meatard bandwidth and I just want you know because I got a couple comments here which aren't really
pretty I just want you to understand that I believe that the meatard bandwidth situation
is not going to be about overages I mean there are certain ISPs have had it myself
where if you go above a certain amount of bandwidth per month then they they either they
cap you off and they start to give you shitty bandwidth or you start paying and you know an
exorbitant amount per gigabyte transfer or even per megabyte in some cases excuse me
I believe that and we go to a truly meters situation I believe that you you know all of these numbers
have to change I think I truly truly think at the end of the day it's going to be better for the
consumer you'll find that you're going to be paying about what you're paying today for the usage
you know that you apply to the network but that the people who are really sucking down tons and tons
of of huge media files and are running bit torrent and you know just our um and other peer
to peer programs they're just going to wind up paying more and I have to tell you I'm all for it
but this is not about taking the current pricing structure and applying some kind of overages to it that
of course would be horrible and that would suck that's also not what I'm advocating I also don't see
how that can happen because there would be a revolution a revolt and there would and competition
somehow would come into it or you know or would just shut down the internet maybe hi Adam this is Justin
I respectfully have to say fuck you tell me that I should have to uh have meter bandwidth man that's
just not cool I pay something like uh $60 or somewhere around there a month right how much
ban with do you use for that 60 that's what I'd like to know in fact we should be able to meter that
right why don't we all check and see how much we're we're downloading I'll make it concerted effort I
maybe I can do that at the router level I guess maybe my my Wi-Fi router I can I can set it to zero
hopefully and then see how much ban with I actually use on a monthly basis and then calculated back
because I pay about the same about 60 bucks US for for for for the bandwidth now it's it's unlimited
as far as I know I've never got an overage charge um and but that should be enough that should be
enough for me to do all the things I want to do but of course I'm not running continuous you know
ban with sucking programs although some of my neighbors clearly are because band as I get messed
up once in a while but okay the fuck you was received to download all the content that I want
and I don't want to have to worry about overages like I do with my cell phone I would have that
in the back of my mind and I just I just don't want to worry but then again on the other hand I
have to listen to what you tell me because Pod show is able to host my Podcaster free
was no downtime that I've been made aware of so you're doing something right yeah and it's free to
you but it's not free to us I mean it actually does cost money if someone accesses your file and so
one listens to your show or watches your show whatever it is what show is it by the way you should
tell me and you must know what you're talking about time you want my show to succeed so there
must be something that will fold you understand and if I was afraid of running out of bandwidth
though I'd probably be less likely to try out new shows new Podcast dude just would always be
there in the back of my mind what's the luck in the UK or the Netherlands I don't want to
sound like a stupid uninformed American and come across like I'm afraid to change if it's
it's working somewhere else maybe Germany's doing this why don't we try it out like they're doing
and remind me of the days back when you'd have to drive around to the end of your driveway
because you had run out of bandwidth no it wasn't bandwidth there's a little long ago it was
quite that it wasn't quite that they love you no homo great hair 33 yeah uh my stock
strapping anymore I maybe a hobo no homo emohobo god remember that one yeah um no when that's
when we just moved to the UK and I actually couldn't get a connection so that nothing
to do with overages or anything like that what if just what if it turns out that you only
needed to pay 40 bucks a month on a meter bandwidth plan you know the fact of the matter is
we've we've kind of been hoodwinked by by this advertising about unlimited bandwidth which of
course it's not I mean that's the real problem is truth and advertising if you advertise unlimited
bandwidth it's unlimited bandwidth and if it's a little asterix then your full of shit but I
believe just looking at the prices and I and I do think I know a little bit about how it works
and what it actually costs because you know if someone's downloading a lot and you got a lot of
people downloading a lot then somewhere along the line something has to be upgraded so we need
a new router or new switch or a new line or extra capacity brought in so it's not free for the
the people delivering the bandwidth to your home um but it could just turn out to be not that's why
I disclose some of the pricing for for gigabytes that's being charged on the other end of the
pipe like on our end where we send stuff out you know it's blown nine cents per gigabyte oops what
was that that was weird oh boy let's just hope it hangs together um yeah it's less than nine
cents per gigabyte it's actually transferred so it could turn out that you might be paying a 20 or 30
bucks instead of 50 or 60 it's actually could pan out that way so I'm not I'm just not jumping
to conclusions about this meaded ban with being all about overages which I don't believe time
Warner has said at all they've just said they're experimenting with different types of
meadering if anyone lives in Beaumont, Texas or if you know anyone who lives in Beaumont, Texas
it might be a part of the plan could you please give me a call I'd really appreciate it
Adam Curry you really really really need an education on what teering means all right
no company on planet earth will make demands to change to a system that will reduce their income
oh hold on a second I got to stop you right there you're taking this meaded ban with
conversation to the company wants to make less money oh that's just ridiculous dude
has nothing to do with it it's just not gonna happen and never gonna happen you sound like one of
those guys who suck in the ban with pipe all night long but here's structure that is fair to the
customer will result in significantly lower money for the companies
so you're about it the industry standards 10 cents a gigabyte that's what I as a consumer can buy
without buying a ball I could buy one gig at 10 cents yeah that means if I've done it
a 500 gigabyte of data which is more than twice the cutoff point that heavy users are hitting
1225 gigas a year the cutoff point a lot of users are hitting when they get cutoff from the
internet then they won't tell you what the limit is that's twice as much that's only 50 bucks a month
dude it's called a commodity that's what it is it's a commodity so yes commodity prices go down
over time particularly this type of commodity absolutely that will happen well it wants it look
it's not gonna happen for everybody you're conveniently taking out of the mix the people who are
sucking up tons of ban with all day and all night who also may not be paying hundreds they may be
paying 50 or 60 we just don't know we don't have all the information but it is interesting
that at least these trials are being put into place and if we can get some more information so
just rambling around then we could actually make some informed or could have an informed conversation
about it but anyway let's listen what I'll check to say I'm paying 65 dollars a month for internet
access do you tell me there's a lower my bill to below 50 dollars a month that could be over there dead
fuck hey it's making a sound like the man yeah good bellow not everyone's out to screw you
continuously they're doing that I truly believe the ISPs are trying to figure out how to make it
a little bit fair for everybody and we have to get there it's like you know maybe a better
analogy is the road okay so you're driving I'm looking at the the on-ramp to the bay bridge actually
that's the off-ramp that I'm seeing and we actually cars and once a while I'll see an SUV and then
then I'll see a truck I mean aren't there different pay scales in what these vehicles have to pay in road
tax and and registration taxes aren't there different tiered pricing schedules in that for the type of
use that you're making of the road I mean a truck or time weigh in on this man what do you pay
do you pay more for your for your rig than what you're paying for your for your car and is that
because of the size of it and the weight of it and the how it taxes the infrastructure and you know
it's it just makes sense the second problem there is no such thing it's competition
you say well somebody that's coming to you right no they won't do you know how many internet
providers are available to me one yeah now you do have a point there of course that's not the same
situation for everybody I think I have a couple choices here in San Francisco those choices will
expand I do believe that they'll expand their number of a number of ways and wireless choices are
bound to expand but it could take another five years could easily be ten years but it will eventually
happen and that all is down to you my friend the consumer to put pressure on companies and if necessary
on congress that's where they're there for precisely one I don't piss off comets because of the
only one I have unless I want to pay ninety bucks a month for a piss ass whoa a satellite connection
now hold on you do have a choice you got a choice there it's not a great choice but you got a choice
true or not with so much latency that I can never do anything live he you have no idea the
reason you want to switch to tears structure so they can what they're going to do is they're going
to find out what the average balance of their average user is and that balance is going to cost
whatever we're paying now and then all of us who actually use our internet connection or it's
well so you don't actually know that you're just making it up it could be it's a possibility
but boy what a stupid way out for those guys and you don't have to test that in uh
boom on taxes we already know how that works now I think they're trying something new again if you're
in boom on we got to hear from you big dime so trust me to your internet is not the way to go
everything else is going away from here in the that every single industry where they had a
tears structure the customers got screwed every single one still a phone bills were a couple of
years ago come on man that's right that's that's a great example look at what phone bills were
a couple of years ago and where is it today you can't argue that there haven't been tons of deals
tons of different ways to to to get the type of package that fits for your profile of usage
that's what these weekend and evening minutes are all about and you're five friends that you know that's
packaging that's marketing that is truly how American enterprise works when bringing more value
to the customer and it's part competitive and oh it's actually it's all competitive there's there's
the point right there you know I used to pay a lot more for cell phones in fact look what happened
in Europe with the with roaming charges you know they were trying to shaft the customers with
that and the government stepped in said wait a minute why because of pressure from consumer
work in the system where there isn't a reasonable control of what you pay online do you get
balance from anybody so they have to compete but you have one type going to your door there's no
competition and no incentive to be fair to you they will screw you see I had a Christmas
all right Chris in love at town so that's your situation but of course time warners not just in
your town is the only one they're all over the place so we'll see what happens we'll see how it shakes
out but I just don't think it's all that bad oh no fellow airman calling in and I'm this a woman
another cut that's called in little busy lately seven inch and five years in the last week and
no I don't fly the triple seven luckily all mine occurred on in the simulators so just have to
my annual recurrent training but I want to call and Sam so glad to hear Patricia's better
little answers to what was going on well I'm just glad she's still on so so much better
on my way to St. Thomas I'm sure you got the FQ whether up there with FQ whether here but
St. Thomas I'm going to go stick my big toe in the ocean for you so I can't tell when's my friend
and we'll talk to you again soon yeah our oban tailwinds back at you inside works if you want to hear
Robin and his lovely wife inside works calm it sounded like he was actually in the cockpit when
he called that and he does that from time to time if you ever wonder what the what the pilot should
do in upfront when you're flying you know to some warm destination to recording podcasts that
doing shows not actually flying the plane oh I need some music hey Adam Wayne here from the
world's Wayne podcast the world's Wayne calm I know you dig discovering your music so I thought
I'd just send you a heads up with a few tidbits first off from the pod save music network I've
got lead rocker from the stray cats with rock and harder I just interviewed him on my show and he's
still killing audiences all over the world check this out
next is a song called anchor from an Omaha band called Civic Minded check this out as well
right and now for a little more twang for your buck here's another Omaha band called
the Pendrakes and their song Deadman Break
last but not least another Omaha singer song
writer Brad Hoshah with taking me to you I really like this guy
well that's it you know all these songs are all pod safe again you can find the rocker on the
on the pod safe music network and I always tell bands to get their stuff on the PMN and by the
way all these songs besides the lee rocker when you can find on my worlds of Wayne
PMN site so for any podcasters out there that want to download with their all pod safe so check it out
choose you Adam love you love you show big hair yeah great hair hope you win etc that was just
checking out your site worlds of Wayne dot com make sense of course that's pretty cool man that's a
good idea I wouldn't mind if you said you know like an overview like that in one to week or something
or and then if you sent me the links as well just so I could just like copy and paste the
writing to the show notes I definitely put that in the show that's cool man because I'd like
to go and review a couple of those tunes that you play that was great awesome my mouth is now
working perfectly well tonight hey Adam it's Kevin Crossman from the backpack podcast
yeah scruncher anyway glad to hear that the NHN promotion is working good here to suggestion
for getting some more exposures for that discount as well as your show we should
hook up the guys over at in gadget tell them about this promotion and I'm sure that they
would be happy to cover it blog about it you know for their audience would be very interested in
the 15% discount so talk to the guys in the gadget keeping it a little posting about your
discount and I bet that would drive a lot of traffic over to your site anyway just a suggestion
keep up the great work by a good idea Kevin you know we have the first the first stage of
pod show network shows then now in on this promotion selling the Nokia N800 10 internet tablet
and I love this kind of stuff because this is a great way for people to make money it's also in my
mind it's it's the new version of advertising and if you see it at how creative people have gotten
them making videos and showing different capabilities of the device and Marcus couch man the
scenes he did something very similar what you just suggested with with in gadget he he added set
up the minute we got the codes in he had a nice posting that he I guess he had he talked to the
guys over to internet tablet talk dot com I bet he got a ton of traffic from that so it's a lot
of inventiveness and people doing stuff you know through their shows and in their show notes
and and what's great about it for the audience is you guys go to 15% discount yes of course I have
code you can use to get that 50% 15% discount on the any 110 if you go to the show notes
daily source code dot com you'll find the link to the store and of course the discount code is daily
source code new countries now live to purchase this this is from the candy man he sent me the
following list Ireland Belgium the Netherlands Denmark Sweden Norway Finland Austria Switzerland
now also can purchase the Nokia 8010 internet tablet a 15% discount specifically by using
the code of your favorite pod show producers program code thing mbob hey Adam hey my name is Scott
men's from east Tennessee uh our Knoxville in the states and I thought you might be interested in
our new video podcast I've just learned about you and all you've done for podcasting just recently
in September when I attended the podcast expo in Ontario and your show has been a lot of fun to listen
to for me and it's certainly been part of our inspiration to do our own show we're just getting
started with something then I think it's a one of a kind at this time my wife and I do a show called
the sweat cast that's right this is an attractive title my friends wet cast and we broadcast six days
a week on use stream from our home gym as we do our daily workout we've been doing our first seven
shows from the treadmill and the stationary bike and then we'll soon be incorporating strength
training into the show as well we publish the show as an MP4 file via our RSS feed and we play
upbeat pod safe music from music.podshow.com we discuss urban legends tell a joke or two and then we
close the show with the recording about the same to the day yep we're also big fans of Father
Roderick's daily breakfast this what cast is targeting baby boomers Adam in their 50s and 60s
people that maybe don't normally listen to podcasts with a positive message about the importance
of exercising especially in your retirement years and those years leading up to retirement it's kind
of a fun way for boomers to get back in shape by subscribing to the podcast and taking it along
to the gym who knows it might just be the reason to get mom or dad a video iPod for their birthday
so check us out if you would at sweatcast.tv where you'll find the show and all the links
keep up your great work Adam for all you're doing for new media and there's no chance you'll be
attending the pod camp in Nashville is there I'm sure they could make room for another speaker
I hope to meet and have a beer with you sometime in the future man thanks I totally I do it I'll
totally take you up on the beer for sure yeah I played the promo for a number of reasons one because
what's a new show and I'll promote anything and you send me a promo I'd love it to be a little
bit shorter than the two minutes if this one is but you know me I want to get people stuff out there
but also I went to the site and this is a funny show so as wife is indeed sitting on the
on the stationary bike and he's on the treadmill they've both got their headphones on you know he's
a whole laptop set up and the and he's got the he's got the the treadmill on high speed he's
really really running along it was just it's cool you should check it out put a link in the show
notes of course the daddysourcecode.com something else that I did the other day that I wanted to share
with you guys I'm not gonna play the whole thing just a little piece of it we're coming up on the
25th anniversary of Michael Jackson's thriller when he released the thriller album and the record
company has commissioned Joseph who's who's been around creating audio and really before podcasting
out have to say he has own little company and and he's taken it upon himself with this for this 25th
to produce a series of thriller cast with a list of interesting people who either
no Michael Jackson or in the music business and I'm not quite sure well somehow he came upon my name
and he asked me to participate and what I want to do is I just want it because he sent me the
what we did is we did like a double ender so he called me on the phone and we talked and I recorded
my part of the conversation so that he had a you know a reasonably good quality copy of
me talking just I play a little bit of this because when these things drop when this starts I think
it's gonna be a great series so this is a part of my thriller cast I'm ready let me just check let me
make sure it's all right I meant that's not it that's the raw file I'm a dope crap hold on a second let
me uh oh that was dumb sorry oh my shmuck well how come I can't find it oh man wait
I mean oh I have to do it on this Mac a file name that's it what oh crap all right
I don't know what I did with it now I set it up so beautifully and then I go and screw it up
way to it maybe it's soon uh bear with me you guys get nothing better to do you're on your way to work
anyway you know care and listen to me rambling maybe if I uh maybe I put it into iTunes you know boy
oh what did that do oh no I didn't mean to open that this one monitor thing is killing me
here we go iTunes let me just see if I can find this um hey how long does iTunes need to open up huh okay
here we go uh I'm looking yes found it okay so I think if I take no that's the same one
crap okay well I'm sorry you have to wait until tomorrow to hear that then I will leave you
with a song that should be on the pod safe music network this week a good buddy mine Steve leads
from New York um he had actually turned me on to this before and I said the same I think I said the
same thing at the time which is you know dude this needs to be on the pod safe music network because
if I play it I know exactly what's gonna happen people are gonna want to play this on the show because
the song is just absolutely awesome there is a youtube video it goes along with it so I'll put a link
to the youtube video and hopefully on the pod safe music network very soon you're gonna dig this
JTX I'm gonna party like a rock star
I'm gonna party like a rock star hit a bunch of stiff bars wake up naked in a hotel room
mama see at the windows look up on the window and everything again will not over you
I didn't tell a song for the round around my heart and party like a rock star
after all the nights we spent cutting on the couch and all the parties I passed up because
you didn't feel like going out I can't see you Steven Tyler didn't put up with crap like this
it's not a make it up for what I miss I'm gonna party like a rock star hit a bunch of stiff bars wake up naked in a hotel room
mama see at the windows look up on the window and everything again will not over you
I didn't tell a song for the round around my heart and party like a rock star
come on I'm gonna party like a rock star hit a bunch of stiff bars wake up naked in a hotel room
mama see at the windows look up on the window and everything again will not over you
now just imagine you had a really good quality recording would be even better
please get those guys on the network perfect love it it's kind of the underbelly version of
the what nickel back is doing these days you know this is the true the true spirit
party like a rock star JTX that's that obviously is the YouTube sound I'll post that link
daily source code.com hey I found the the thriller cast of course handily title that's Adam
Curry v2 that's why I couldn't find hi this is Adam Curry of the daily source code and of course
the former MTV guy welcome to my thriller cast
the first time I heard through actually I think I was in college I went to college for about
three months which is very successful the educational career of course in West Virginia but I
just can't listen to the whole thing when it comes out it's cool because I like that it's only
it's in my pieces like 11 and I like 12 minutes long and it's all right you know it's
I like that kind of format and thank you very much for sending in all of your records for
upsol the organization for the preservation to the soundtrack of our lives you can hear the first episode
at opsol dot pod show dot com i'm gonna produce another couple episodes this is the cool thing about
is I can sit down and I can now that I know that people are interested in it I can you know produce
five or six of these in one session and the goal would be to have one of these every single day drop
out can you just imagine having a show with a great soundtrack to your life to listen to every
day you can have it all it takes is well basically for you to send yours in because I need a
lot more before we can get to the daily's but some really good suggestions some really good
ones have come in so I'll be producing one of those also got to do a couple of podfinders I'm
way behind on that and what else uh oh yeah there's a company I'm trying to run thank god for
Mr. Bloom all right everybody I'll talk to you tomorrow please remember live your life with
passion and enjoy your freedom another pod show podcast stick it in your ear