Daily source code, episode number 781, my fellow chuckleheads, brothers and sisters.
Today we're going to do something entirely different for the footballer Friday edition
of the Daily source code.
We start with what will hopefully be the first in a series of something I'm calling Confessions
of a multimedia hitman, barred of course from the eye-opening, expose confessions of
an economic hitman by the courageous John Perkins.
His book was an important piece to the puzzle that I've been assembling over the course
of the past six months.
So my borrowing, the nucleus of his title is intended to be attributed as well as a contribution
to the dismantling of the machine.
Now I say it's been a six-month excursion, but the process has actually something that's
been taking place my entire life.
Very much like one of those tabletop jigsaw puzzles that we used to put together as kids.
My mom, of course, always taught me once you've got the corners and the sides squared away,
the rest just kind of falls into place with exponential ease.
So the people that make up this community, that's you listening right now, have mostly been
along for this ride of mine, unknowingly, despite this though you've certainly been my
wingmen and have kept me safe throughout and it's highly appreciated.
I hope for you to understand what I mean by that as I move on through the story.
Okay, so now that I've baited you with that intro, you probably feel you deserve an explanation.
Well, you're right, and we're going to talk about it right now.
Imagine a world where you wake up one morning only to realize that everything you believe
in your reality, so to speak, functioned entirely differently from the way you've been
perceiving it all of your life.
A world in fact, where the truth is often the direct opposite of your reality, I'm going
to give you a second to chew on that one, which actually it's not too hard.
Our popular culture is inundated with this concept from the colorized awakening for Dorothea
and the Wizard of Oz to Neo's never ending battle with Mr. Smith and the Matrix.
Nothing is as it seems.
Take the red pill.
Follow the yellow brick road down the rabbit hole to unveil the man behind the curtain.
Then click your heels three times and say, there's no place like home, there's no place
like home.
I really love matching these two stories together, and the combination of the really
reflect the findings of my research.
So let's look at this for a second.
Dorothy and her friend's reality was a belief system that they had no courage, no heart,
no brain and worst of all, no home.
This reality was really bestowed upon them by the master of the universe, the Wizard of
Oz, who is great and in control.
Of course, we know that through the sheer willpower and faith, this gang, Dorothy and
her friend's unmasked the wizard, only defined out that he's actually a pathetic little
man pulling all the levers behind the curtain.
So once the farce of the wizard is exposed, their reality changes and then their true
potential is returned to the including heart, brain, et cetera, and home.
Now in the Matrix, taking the red pill allows you to be decoupled from the machine that
kept you alive through the transmission of a computer generated world into your brain,
feeding you only the necessary nutrients in order to use your body as an energy source
to keep the machine running.
Hopefully you've seen both of these movies, if not, you should stop this now and go
take a look at them.
So thousands of hours of following conspiracy theories, reading ancient scripture,
painstakingly trying to understand truth and mathematics, watching and learning from
the research of thousands of others, has brought me on this numerically significant
day, of course, the 8th of the 8th of 2008, to pass on my findings to you.
My story is about power, three kinds of power, the power of our minds, the power of
rule, and the power as in what makes our lights glow and keeps our vehicles moving,
individually and collectively, these three forms of power all consist of energy.
So let's start off with the power of our brains.
The human body is a very sophisticated machine.
It functions autonomously.
It takes its instructions from the brain, which works a lot like your personal computer.
It has processes that run all the time in the background, like collecting your mail or
scanning for viruses, those kinds of processes.
It produces output in the form of light display, sound, and action, or movement, and it takes
input.
But instead of clunky keyboards, we've got major asthma, Joe, when it comes to our scanning
and processing ability.
But of course, I've get to see a demonstration of a computer that can read a play by Shakespeare.
Remember, then engage in audience with this portrayal of the story, taking external
cues from other, while in this case, it would be other computers, musical or lighting changes,
audience feedback.
But then again, I'll be the first to admit that the Honda robot walking up a flight of stairs
is quite an impressive start, but still not quite as cool as our built-in computers in our heads.
So frankly, we're pretty impressive straight out of the box.
We're designed to be programmed.
We can execute programs on command or in the background.
It's all a part of our learning function.
You don't need like a C compiler for this.
It's much easier to program the human brain.
In fact, from a very early age, we get programmed by input stimuli and repetition,
those two things, input and repetition.
And of course, that's done until a program is running properly, at which point we move on to learning
something new.
Copping our parents is how we learn to communicate as one example.
Looking both ways before crossing the road is another program that is essential to our safety,
and is either taught over time by repetition from our parents or other programmers,
like teachers or other family members, or it could be programmed into your brain by a shock
to the input system, such as narrowly being avoided being hit by an oncoming car,
or maybe being hit if you survive it.
The shock treatment embeds a lot of information deep into the system,
and the next time we receive input that we're about to cross a road,
that program will be automatically recalled and executed.
Pavlov proved the working of this program ability over 100 years ago
with his dogs and their salivating.
You can Google it.
If you want to program a person to react in a specific manner, to a specific input,
all you have to do is continuously repeat the input instructions,
and if possible, provide a reward when the person reacts with the desired action.
So today I'm convinced that the process of learning code written for us in this manner,
executing it uses only a tiny fraction of our full processing capability.
If our true brain potential is the world's most powerful supercomputer,
then we are right now still in the equivalent of the advocacy age with a knowledge of what this
gray matter between our ears is actually capable of.
As I just said before, at any time, if you feel the need, just stop,
to stop this show, obviously, if you can, and Google for any more information.
Just type your full question into Google.
Google knows exactly where to send you because all your questions have already been asked and answered.
Many times over, I know I've done the research.
So throughout our evolution, regardless of how we came to be,
we have evolved our thinking processes.
Our communication skills and our self-awareness.
This is always reflected in our technology and, of course, that's what people are digging up tools,
right? That's what you always see. So let's focus on power as an energy that makes our world
function, specifically electricity. And now you'll definitely want to Google Nikola Tesla.
He was instrumental in bringing electricity to our civilization more than a century ago, the generator,
alternating current, the Niagara Falls power plant, radio wave transmission, the
Bobbin in your car, all Tesla inventions without power or energy.
You wouldn't be, you wouldn't be listening to this show.
Poof, no PC, no internet, no toothbrush, no motorized vehicles.
If only we had an unlimited supply of electricity, then everything would be just perfect, but we don't.
Humanity instead was directed down to path of creating energy from pieces of the earth itself,
instead of the energy that it already consists of.
Let me take you back to the Wizard of Oz. So we've got a cunning, sad little man, apparently,
he figured out a way to be in control or in power, if you will, of the whole land.
Because it was the Wizard behind the curtain who was pulling all the levers,
remember that, creating repetitive illusions that enforce Dorothy and her friends into believing
that they needed to stay on the path on the Yellow Brigroad. And psychologically abused them
into believing that they weren't worthy because of their so-called deficiencies,
which didn't even exist in the first place. The Wizard created a reality, a program of code
that was executed by pulling levers that created scary inputs to the group's on-board
processors in effect, enslaving them to his every command. So how does this translate
to 2008? As a businessman, I can easily see how compelling it would be to have control over
the world's energy. I mean, it's even more powerful than controlling the world's money, right,
because everything all starts with energy. So in the context of the world, the beginning of the
20th century, the concept of keeping the world on the path on the Yellow Brigroad by using my
form of energy would be a very nifty proposition indeed. And of course, the best way to undertake
this mission, you know, the 80 years ago or whatever, would be to start with a lot of money in the first place.
So at this point in my story, the research that I did let me down many paths from the illuminati
to reptilian bloodlines to UFOs, planet X, there are many historical research paths to explore.
I don't really recommend it, mainly because it really doesn't matter at this point. Following
the money, though, which is easy to trace leads to the true owners of the world. It's just a handful
of families who control the resources that powered our world, which I'll just call these people
the energy elite. The names are instantly recognizable. You can easily connect all petroleum-based
energy sources to names like Rockefeller, Rothschild, or JP Morgan. In fact, it was JP himself,
who was one of the Tesla's original investors and acquired many of his energy patents,
which formed a foundation for an energy empire. Now, when you think about it, that really hasn't
been much in the way of evolution in electricity since Tesla 100 years ago. Yes, you're the
some significant enhancements certainly for storage, but in general, no innovation.
My conclusion is that energy innovation, particularly Tesla's, was stifled in lieu of this new
black gold that would power the generators to create a world of energy and motion based on oil.
Okay, fast forward to the Matrix movie, where a world's generated for us, remember that right
from a computer simulation, injected into our nervous system and our central processing brain cells.
So in the movie, we're actually hardwired into the system. It's not likely, of course,
the one day we're going to wake up and find ourselves attached to tubes and a tank of
from elder hide. And it's also unnecessary because it can be implemented wirelessly this type of
reality world or virtual reality, if you think about it. The most significant wireless input
device we have is our eyes. We also have four other sensory inputs to use. So, you know,
when an illusionist makes his assistant levitate or maybe you saw David Copperfield
make the great wall of China disappear, we see the illusion. And of course, we're baffled by it,
but we know that it's a trick because of the context of being aware that we're watching
a magic show. However, if you show the simple act of making fire from a match to an
digitist tribe that's never met any other kind of human being, of course, you'll instantly
be either loved like a god or feared like one. Media, in particular television, is a trick.
If you want to see how effective this box of tricks really is, please Google the Zen TV experiment
I've talked about this for years. Really, it's like they'll take a half an hour, maybe try it out.
It's an incredible eye opener. And I know because I was a multimedia hitman, a member of the
deception device that was hijacked by the energy elite to program your brain so you'll be a functional
piece of the gears that make their machine work. Not that I was ever aware of my role, of course,
the time, as are most people who work in mainstream media, it's baked into the DNA of media
companies. It wasn't until late 2001 that I realized my task was not actually to bring
cool music videos and juvenile fun to masses of teenagers, quite the contrary. I was merely meant
to keep the enslaved entertained until the next commercial break. I participated in
pressuring you or your kids, maybe, to buy products like Nutrigina, Skittles, Budweiser.
If you don't use this product, you'll have horrible acne and you'll never get laid.
Hey, be cool, drink, Budweiser. All the cool kids are doing it. You don't want to be a loser,
do you? You ain't got the thing. You don't got no bling. You need more stuff. Buy more stuff.
Need to borrow money? No problem. American Express can help. That is good. Buying stuff is even
better. Mx by the way, was the original owner of MTV before they later sold it to Viacom,
selling debt to kids. So once you understand television's true hypnotic mission, it becomes
easy to see how MTV could shamelessly drop their core music-based programming for complete
mindless exploitative programming. Laura Minwinder, young, shown heroes who measure their success
by the size of their crib or the pinpage of their ride, having ready to be pre-programmed shop
a hollocks by the time they're ready for their own super sweet 16. Then, of course, Tia Tequila
takes over to introduce to these fresh new human robots, the concept of sexual exploitation.
Obviously, I'm exaggerating to a certain degree, but I hope you get the point.
Of course, I'm not condemning MTV or the people to work there or even the program for that matter.
Unfortunately, you'll find that programming format of most mainstream media follows the same
principles, creating a reality in our minds that is a servant of the energy elites agenda and
it's working. What used to be called a human interest piece in the news 25 years ago,
that's now evolved into a culture of insatiable craving for celebrity gossip. It's been woven
into the fabric of all media. Just as an aside, you're going to hear me use the term programming
in the context of a computer to run a software program, as well as programming that consists
of the content transmitted to you, for instance, via television, radio, the internet. Both
consists of digital information. Both cases are intended to be input into the appropriate
computer processor, even a real computer processor, or your brain processor, to make the
machine perform an action or movement. Just like a computer program, I can write code to make
a PC, perform some action, a media programmer, and they call themselves programmers can create
content that will make your brain react in a predetermined manner. That in turn can trigger a
physical action in the body, like purchasing a product you saw advertised on television.
As shit really does work, you know? Of course, I promise. I'll elaborate more on this programming
and how to identify and protect yourself against it in future episodes of this series.
Which would just be a part of daily source code. We'll just keep on going with the source code numbers.
But once in a while, we'll do some different like this because if you really can,
figure out how it works and you understand that it becomes ineffective. Once you're aware of the code,
it can easily be barred from executing into your personal super computer brain.
And many of you who've been listening to the source code for a couple of years already know
how this works. Thousands still think of Senseo when you hear somebody burp, and I'm confident
many of you will think of Senseo when you gurgle your last breath on Earth and you're going to
curse me for it and I'm telling you, if an XVJ with a podcast can do that, imagine what people
with money and a plan could accomplish. The media distorts the truth almost by definition of words
like Edit, Cut, Zoom. Of course, we all saw the events on the fold of 9-11, right?
Or did we only see it on TV? If you truly believe what you saw televised on that day, then the television,
and everything else you see on it is your reality. Now this doesn't mean that what you saw is
either true or false, but it certainly cannot be compared to actually being at ground zero
seeing it happen. That is someone else's reality. If you're still following this, please paint
yourself on the back. You're probably already in a state of awakening. Now although electricity
in other forms of oil-based energy are the main tool of the energy elite with which to control
the masses over the decades they've built up an impressive infrastructure of government,
social and monetary systems that they control entirely. Their Wizard of Oz levers include
interest rates of central banks, aggregation of nations like the European Union to implement
bodies that hijack the democratic process, food and energy costs, and of course mass mainstream
media. All for the continued exploitation of us. Their slaves who they feed the bare minimum
and nutrients only to suck us dry of all of our true possessions are brain power and working
force. It's all for their benefit to continue building their wealth and power machine. That is
very much like the matrix, but it's just a metaphor. This perpetual system, however, has one fatal
flaw. It must continue to grow in order for it to survive. It's just like the corporations.
You look at the branch, you know what the tree's going to be like in vice versa.
Corporations need to grow in either two in order to survive, stagnation or blockage is lethal to it.
We actually were seeing proof of this in the current meltdown of the financial system,
which is in its pure essence, very easy to understand. Most people don't because it's presented
in the most confusing manner possible through the media. Only to be thrown, of course, into
the bit bucket by our brains. We're actually taught not to understand it. For if the source code
of the financial markets is truly understood, it's easy to see its vulnerability. It needs us,
the slaves to be indebted to it in order to prosper. The financial system is in meltdown
because its controllers took their eye off the ball. The machine was put into overdrive for too
long at overheated. Now, there's got nothing left to feed it with. Our physical presence cannot
be burdened with any more debt. That slows down parts of the machine like the banks who
in turn are interconnected to each other through their own debt system. This phantom money that
was created is finally being exposed for its true value. It's nothing more than a number in a
spreadsheet or a number written on a piece of paper. Once all of our houses, cars, and other
true physical stuff has been repossessed, there'll be no more meaning to the concept of money.
Remember that none of this machinery would ever have been created had free energy been available
to everyone. Even a century ago, the concept of free energy was considered a real day record
for the architects of the slave nation because free ain't no business model. Of course, it's entirely
possible that Tesla's concept of free energy does work and was kept from us. Just as it's possible
that extraterrestrial beings have brought technology to our planet only to have a concealed
from us by the energy elite. More likely, I think we are about to discover it ourselves.
Thanks to the evolution of our species. But even this discovery will not easily make it into the
consciousness of all the children of the world as most are still fully engaged in the multimedia
machine that is entertaining us to death. Perhaps it's the prophecy of the Mayans who predicted
an ascension of our awareness with the dawning of the age of Aquarius in 2012. I'm not ruling
out travelers from other worlds or dimensions who are assisting us, but I'm certain our DNA has
been divinely pre-programmed to evolve and due to centuries of suppression. Unleashing our full
potential could have an effect equal to the pressure relief of a champagne cork being popped out of
its container allowing its contents to spew out freely. There are many examples of higher consciousness
at work in our surroundings, particularly in our children. They're the next generation. The internet
was of course the elite's big cock-up. Since they themselves are stuck in ancient culture and
think they never saw the rapid evolution caused by a 24-7 interconnection of the enslaved populace.
Communities form produce useful tools, open source software is a great example of advanced
collaborative collaborating minds. Most contributors to Linux only know each other through email,
web, IRC, chat, and the source code management system that spits out software, which is far
superior to that offered by the elite in many ways. This program is another example of a product
created by collective minds. Social networks, wickies, blogs, Twitter, all tools we use together,
often to great benefit of the community that is using the tool. A look at the contributions
that come into drop.io slash daily source code, which is in turn is running on a system given to
this community, which is just us chuckle heads, but the people who developed drop.io. I don't
need to pay a producer to guess what you guys want to hear on their show. You actually upload it and
give it to me. I just glue it all together. No money ever changed hands anywhere. Except of course
for the money that needs to be fed into the machine somewhere down the line in order to get the
electricity to actually make it run. Just envision how much better and less restricted Google would be.
If they had free electricity to work with, they wouldn't need investors or shareholders,
possibly not even staff. We send audio and video in mere seconds around the globe.
Less than seconds. We have direct wireless communication through cell phones and text messages.
It really can't be too much of a leap to take these concepts to the next logical stage
of bypassing the analog inputs and controls like eyes, ears, and touch to one of mental transmission.
Everybody's witnessed some form of telepathy, perhaps with your partner or a family member.
If we don't have that kind of capacity, in the 99% of our brains, we don't know how to use yet,
then that would be an incredible waste of space up there in our heads. I simply cannot resolve
that who or what designed our beautiful body machinery wouldn't have added the required bits
to our brains to make us capable of infinite system upgrades. My recent experimentation with the
hydroxy booster, which you probably heard about on the show, it really depicts our current evolutionary
conundrum perfectly. Despite very smart people assuring me, this home-built concept of extracting
hydrogen from water and mixing it with a fuel supply that goes into my car cannot work due to the
laws of physics. I personally have been enjoying an average of 25% efficiency in fuel consumption.
They told me it could not work, I'm seeing it work, and I'm not alone. Thousands are experiencing
similar results worldwide. It almost no cost since the system is built with readily available material
and an endless supply of water. By now, of course, you understand why this fabulous invention
isn't plastered across the front pages and news programs globally. The energy elites just won't
allow it. Not that they have to hide these developments from anyone. They simply just don't allow
why distribution of the information unless it's packaged in a, that's crazy rapper.
It's far easier to hide a huge secret in plain sight than it is to cover up a lot of little ones
with secrecy. As my partner Ron taught me from his mainstream music production days,
if you can't cover it up, turn it up. As we continue our conversation in future episodes,
we'll talk more about the development of free energy by these brothers and sisters who've already
freed their minds from the machine. Their joe cells, their zero-point energy concepts,
built on the work of people like Tesla, will eventually lead us to our birthright. I'm convinced
at this point you've either declared me a complete loony tune or you might feel something familiar
about my story. Either way, most of you are still very much asleep in the reality created by
the masters that own us. Many of you are awakening, seeing the truth that lies within, identifying
the malicious code that comes out of us from all directions all intended to keep our machines working
for them. And so we live in duality. The elite's machine is creaking under the strain of
itself inflicted girth, while our intelligence has far surpassed the simple program set to
infinite loop that we've been running. And as always, it's all about the timing. If the machine
comes crumbling down, which seems as exactly what we're witnessing with the money meltdown,
enough of us need to be awake and prepared to take action. For those not awake, the shocker
of the machine's demise, I fear it will be too much to process in a short amount of time to be
useful to oneself in the world when it happens. I mean, taking me six months to go from
watching zeitgeist the movie to be able to articulate my story with you to you today. And that
is actually my role to assist in your awakening and to communicate as much learning as I can.
Now, I don't see an Armageddon arrival of graze, platings, tall blondes, the earth probably won't
come to a screeching halt, complete with tsunamis, earthquakes, and land mass relocation,
nor do I fear black helicopters are going to whisk me away in the stealth of the night. But
I certainly am not going to rule any of it out.
Four years of conversation that we've been to having has brought me to this point.
Many of you may feel the same. Some may be afraid to speak out in fear of ridicule.
Fear not chuckle heads. Together we're going to face the future. The light that is our destiny.
Welcome to the next level. Welcome to the Awakening.