This is rake, reporting live for the TSE 7667, coming to your right from Kilford.
I don't know what's going to happen.
People being evacuated from the scene.
I don't know what it is.
Some advice.
It's big.
How is the meat?
Somebody must be living there.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm trying to get in.
Where I have.
I'm now entering the garden.
It's a big, big house.
It looks like little catful, something is meat.
I don't know what's going on here.
Somebody's singing inside.
There's some kind of ritual going on here.
I've been trying to look through the window.
You look happy.
The flag.
My god there's doing a guy behind the trunk.
I'll make it.
What have we to do in here?
Come on.
A lady standing on the table.
I need something.
Trying to understand.
I don't know.
I got to go in.
It's crazy.
It's $67.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
The next generation video caught anybody years.
We don't need no steam.
I like to think I'm flying into the kitchen.
I'm testing.
It's a matter of curry.
I'm in one of the fall of the process.
Never need a more lines than the sand.
No one I wanted.
I know what I don't want.
I need the angry elephant.
I need the junk.
We can guess.
Got to find a store to hold.
This is some cash in on the one in place.
We're talking hate.
Talking in circles.
Trying to cut the teller because everyone is trying to chase.
We say we say we're just waiting for.
We say we say just we're just waiting for.
We say we say we say we say we're ready for something.
Some are in a dark dead corner of America.
The manufacturing estate is stream of sheep shots.
Miss information, and I'll need other non-to-paylafays.
me say we say we're just waiting so long.
We say we say just we're just waiting.
We've been waiting, I know the promise is you made
We say we say the right for something
This can't be all that you've got
We're all that we've got
This can't be all that we've got
We're all that we've got so we're all so trolling
We got so on the car
We're all we got so on the phone
Stars roll and we got so on the car
We don't tell you
We say we say we're the winner
We say we say just we are
We're all we've been waiting
I know the promise is you made
We say, we say all right, but nothing new
Along our Jind's
We made you one day
And all my evaluated
You exposed to me
We say, we?)
Only we don't the same
L.E.A.
somewhat
We absolutely are
The Charlie, did he source code episode number 767
Hey everybody how you doing?
Coming to you from the
The affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford.
It's Adam here.
Hall, my goodness.
This show that I'm about to rip out for you,
I'm gonna rip one out for you.
I actually prepared it yesterday.
Mondays have just become incredibly full with production.
Because stuff comes in over the weekend.
Of course, we did a football Friday,
but I really didn't check much of the voicemail Friday
or over the weekend.
It's stuff just keeps streaming in.
And then Mondays, like, okay, let's see what we got.
I gotta listen to all this stuff.
I don't want to miss anything in cases of great nugget in there.
And while there are some fantastic stuff
you guys have sent in, it's gonna be,
I don't know.
I'm feeling like I'm fitting into a new place in my life.
Does that make any sense?
Some people may describe it as a pathfinder role.
I'm not quite sure I'm trying to figure it out,
but all of these, what I certainly year go
would have considered to be political topics.
I'm really interested.
And you know, I've been home at the Curry Manor for a while.
And you know, so I've got some time to take a look
at stuff and read websites.
And particularly the European Union website,
which is available in eight million languages.
It looks like, but wow, man.
There's a lot of interesting stuff going on.
And it turns out it's not really political.
It's just life and stuff that kind of interests me.
I don't know if that makes sense.
Well, they probably doesn't everybody.
I had him here from Portland about this politics thing.
What the hell are you talking about?
You didn't make any sense.
Are you planning to run for a seat in the EU?
Or is it, if you want to do a political show on radio?
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
I listen to a drive.
Come on.
He's basically talking.
He's, are you going to work for us?
Oh, dude, I already do work for you.
Are you kidding me?
I totally work for you on this show, certainly.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, no.
I don't want to run for anything.
Absolutely not.
That's a shitty job, man.
Being a politics.
Remember, politics is show business for ugly people, so I can be in the real show business.
But it does seem like, you know, this is kind of circle of news, you know.
And I'm starting to discover, certainly in Europe, it's a lot easier to pin down.
But essentially, there's, you know, journalists just sit around and wait for either talking
points, which are distributed directly from a government, I guess, certainly in the states
from the White House, you've heard of those.
Either that or, you know, they'll look for news releases or press releases.
Like, there's a very slight nuance between a press release and a news release.
And I see lots of companies and think tanks and other organizations, some of them, non-governmental
organizations.
And they sometimes confuse the difference between a press release and a news release.
But it doesn't matter because that's what journalists will pick up.
And that's where the headline comes from.
And then I'm starting to learn how all these trial balloons work where people float stuff
up.
And I've, I've always started to make a study of it.
And it's very interesting.
What is unfortunately very disappointing, something that I'm noticing now with this, this
thing I'm doing in Holland in the morning, where I basically taking everything I'm learning
here on the Charlie, all of these different aspects, learning how to look at things, learning
how to use the audience, that would be you guys, the chuckleheads, you know, to get information,
trust the information, you know, build up savants status with people and have an ongoing
dialogue.
And I can almost, no matter what topic I bring up, I can almost be assured that one of
one of you guys is going to call in and either set me straight or give me some additional
information or basically contribute to what we're talking about.
What really upsets me though, what I've learned with, with trying this experiment on the
free-to-air broadcast radio in Holland, which of course is a microcosm.
And none of it does anyone any good outside of Holland because they speak Dutch, you know,
so it's not like a world global changing thing.
But what I'm noticing is that it's so easy to get answers from people in, you know,
offices that actually matter.
In fact, today, check this out.
Here's what happened this morning.
We got a phone call and it was a member of Parliament and he said, you know, I've been
asked to meet with the Hadim Karzai, who is the president of Afghanistan, who's visiting
the Netherlands for two days.
And I have to say, I'm looking at this guy, I'm like, XCIA, X-Tali-Bahn, if you can
believe it, at least according to reports I read.
He was with a Tali-Bahn before he, I guess, went over to the other side.
You know, United Nations, he walks around with a cape and with a hat with, you know, it's
not like that says uniform or anything, that's just, you know, his style, which by the
way is made of where to, I had it here, aborted lamb fetuses, now take it with a grain
of salt because this is a Fox News report, but it literally says, oops, hold on, just
reloading the page, where are you?
Though the hats are unmistakably dashing, the method of their production is a bit stomach
turning.
Shepherds in northern Afghanistan slaughter the mother, then remove the fetus, whose
downy fur is incredibly smooth because it's never been exposed to the air or sun.
Sometimes shepherds wait for the U to give birth before killing the lamb.
Each lamb is so small, its entire pelts is needed to produce one hat and many pelts are
needed to make the waist length carcuru coats, which is that cape that the guy's wearing.
Tell you know, that's like, that doesn't sit right with me.
I don't know, it just feels kind of weird about that, you know, and also the CIA thing
and the Tali-Bahn thing.
So anyway, so this, this member of parliament hears this and this of course is the point
that, you know, he's hearing it at a certain time when he's basically waiting to hear someone
talk about him and there's a whole, whole relationship thing there with that radio brings
to the table that is very hard to do in, you know, in our type of delivery and he says,
you know what, I'm going to offer your audience, its arrow classic rocks, so I called that
audience, you know, to me are the arrowheads and there's a crossover, by the way, there
are chuckle in the arrowheads, both in one and he says, I'm going to give your arrowheads an
opportunity to ask a question and I'll ask Karzai because I can ask one or two questions,
I want, I'd like your audience, what question do you guys want to know?
And I'm like, oh man, this is so fucking cool, why can't I get that shit going here on the
source code and I, you know, I realize that it's because they're all still in that old system
and, you know, it's how it works, you know, this is radio station is like ranked 9th or 10th,
you know, it's like no one cares and so even with whatever listeners there are, you know,
they do care and you can actually have a normal conversation with them, all the stuff that I've
learned here, I can apply there and I'm thinking, I gotta get some kind of national radio thing
going on in the US to affect the same type of change and, you know, obviously we're really
doing a lot together here, we're having great conversation and each in our own ways,
creating some small piece of individual change but it's got to move to a much broader platform
and I'm just not sure how to do it yet or, you know, what is the best way, because you don't
want to revert back to the old and then get stuck there, not be able to bring people forward,
to obviously, you know, like I'm doing in the, in the mornings on arrow, it's, you know, it's
there's a podcast version, they slice out all the music, of course, except for I think the
Daily Mashup and, and actually there's a lot of activity there, so, you know, that's good,
but there's still there's something about the live interaction and I think we probably
have to wait until we're a little bit further down the road with technologies like YMAX and maybe
we'll ultimately have cities that are just, you know, an entire cloud of connectivity and then
we can really do some real-time conversation and sometimes, you know, particularly with, with topics
that are very, well, very timely and topical, sometimes it just makes a difference. I'm kind of
stuck in that, so what am I doing with all this political stuff? I'm just trying to figure it out,
man, trying to figure out what the hell is going on in the world and trying to figure out how
I can affect it, if, if at all. And of course, I'm armed with Vice-Savans here today on 766.
Comic strip, Comic strip, Comic strip, Comic strip, Comic strip, Comic strip,
of course, I'm talking about the Lisbon Treaty, which is going up for vote in a public referendum,
the Irish should get to vote in two days from now on the 12th and I, of course, can expect
comic strip blogger to check in with a note about Ireland? Yeah, Adam, at least I think it's very,
so here is ESP, okay? Yeah, you correspond to Euro 2008, so can a trend-pantship script just
started in Austria and so on. By the way, can I just say what an awesome game that was last night,
Holland against Italy? I mean, it was like, you know, the old guys, like, cry for nascans. It was like,
they were back again. It was just fantastic football. Three zero against Italy, the world champion
is totally creamed them and I have to admit I stayed up in quite the whole game. It was absolutely
awesome. Yes, CSP. It's a run and they take place only in one single years, so it is a big
event for Europe. Europe, the same continent that started to where it was, where 91 million people
were killed. 91 million people. Okay, who needs the CIA World Bank? But when you've got CSP,
huh? Do you get it? Yeah. So nowadays, Europeans fight each other only in Kitch-Song Contests
and Sports, PC Europe nowadays is mainly due to existence of European Union. Yeah, that's a good point,
I guess, but that's what all these contests are about the European Championships, obviously. And of
course, that drastic, dreaded Eurovision Song Contests. It's better than killing 91 million
people, although some of those songs came pretty close. That's now after Eastern Notchments
needs new regulations for functions smoothly. So I kindly ask Ireland to fault yes, please one
3th. That is not the same as EU Constitution. And yes, dear Ireland, you can keep your low taxes
with this one 3 to 2. Yeah. I appreciate comics to blogger calling in with a
provoad for the referendum. The Irish will be voting on in two days time.
So let me just say, you know, yeah, of course we need laws, but you know, I did kind of
track this document and no, it's not an official Constitution, but it does refer to the original
document named the Constitution. As you know, I went in and found all kinds of different pieces
of legislation that were very broad, but can be adjusted nationally, particularly though,
unfortunately, when it comes to your basic human rights, which is kind of weird. I would say just
because of the unreadability of it, that alone should be reasoned just to say no, because you just
you just impossible to read. You don't actually know what it's about. I believe that what this
really is all about. And there's a couple of major topics like immigration policy, your European
wide immigration policy, that makes sense, but there's also the European army. I do believe that
if this goes into effect that a European army will be created. And of course, that's a big desire
for a lot of politicians, because a lot of the sectors they represented work with and should be
working for, but sometimes they take it a little bit too literally. You know, war is good. War is
big money. You get to make stuff. That's what the joy strike fighter is all about. You get to make
part of the war machines. You get to profit from it. So I'm a little concerned about that,
but in general, just on basis of how this has been ramrotted through every other single
parliament in the of the member states in the European Union. That's just the unreadability of it.
I'd say forget about it. You know, come back and show us something we actually understand and
that we can talk about. Maybe we'll decide if we have to vote on it or not. But it's not a good
example of you working for us. But your point is well made, uh, comics are blogger. Of course,
we need to figure out how to work together. Uh, but it should, I, in my opinion, it should be
something that we all can understand and not just the, uh, the political elite in Brussels.
You know, Adam, hey, Kurt here from Michigan now. I'm going to expand on an earlier conversation
for you. You know, uh, travel frequently through a skitball airport and answer the M on my way to
Prague. And, uh, you know, there's only a reason to schedule yourself for a long layover.
Let me guess what those two reasons would be for a long layover in Amsterdam.
Good ball. Uh, one being a trip downtown to, uh, and a couple matches, two of you have
prostate cancer prevention. Hold it. Hell yeah. On the second is two of those at the coffee shop
that's made to your trip home a lot more comfortable and enjoyable. In this curious, let's see, uh,
wasn't in pretty, as they classified me as a junior addict in the, uh, read the front door of a coffee shop.
And I'm trying to speed out a lot of the back doors. I mean, I have to worry about getting shot
in the back. And, uh, second, uh, curiosity would be, uh, you know, they're also going to try to take
away the, uh, the second reason for a, excuse me, downtown, uh, on a layover, uh, just curious
about what you thought for on that. Ew, they were for us. Yo, man. Well, let me, I'll tell you what I know
or at least what I've heard, so that's what I think I know. And pretty much the ladies and I guess
there in Amsterdam, there certainly are some men. You know, the famous red light district,
it's pretty much, uh, it's going down the tubes. Now, there's no Dutch prostitutes anymore, which
kind of made it, you know, what it was, it was kind of the, I don't know, now it's all Eastern block.
Um, and they're really trying to move everything into brothels and they're making, they've made
brothels legal. Uh, but then there's, you know, there's some problems with, they've had some problems
with the, um, money laundering and no kidding through, uh, through some of the sex clubs. I mean,
right now, there's a, you know, there's a rather conservative government in place. I would say
certainly from a religious standpoint. So the crack and down on it, uh, one of those, one of the
things that is often discussed in, um, in the context of the European Union, when it comes to Amsterdam,
is, uh, obviously about what they call these soft drugs policy, soft drugs being, uh, marijuana
mainly. I think that's pretty much, I think I don't think they want to say the word marijuana. It's
whether you say soft drugs, because really soft drug is only one. Um, and you know, in context
with the European Union, um, all, well, all you really hear from politicians is, you know,
it's not like all of a sudden, every country in the union has to allow soft drugs. What they're
not saying is that they're quietly, of course, closing it down entirely. Um, if you own a coffee shop
and you sell it, it can no longer be a coffee shop, you know, you can be a coffee shop now. And for
ever as long as you maintain it and remain solvent, if you go out of business, I think there's only
120, seven left in the entire country. Um, so it's, uh, obviously, it's going away. And there's a
whole nother reason for that, which is something I'm probably not going to get into today. What I've
been getting a lot of messages about this thing called, um, Codex, Alimentarius. If you haven't
heard of it, Google that Codex, Alimentarius, uh, which is Latin for the food code. And, um,
the food code is one of the things that's going to be used and already is being used. I would say,
uh, to get rid of, uh, not just, well, there's all kinds of laws against marijuana, but
this is the law that is taking away, um, our basic rights. And in the EU, it's pretty much, uh,
it's pretty much law already, although, so that's to be harmonized as they call it. Um,
and basically it says, okay, no more vitamin D, no more vitamin A, you know, we'll determine
what's good for you. We'll determine what food you can eat and how it's, uh, processed. Oh, by the way,
all food that you eat has to be radiated. You know, there's a lot of shit going on with that. What
I'm still learning about it. And it's going to be another one of my path finding missions to figure
that out. But the real important stuff, hookers and drugs. Yeah. I think that's all over my friend.
Adam White, Charles, your son, London. I'm getting kind of tired of that, Monica.
Well, then stop drinking. Uh, it's Charles London. Uh, I'm in Pearlwood Square. It's beautiful
Sunday day. Damn, it's hot. Oh, Carl, I'm three W. I'm looking at several square, which is full
of all the beautiful. Oh, yeah, you know how beautiful the ladies are in London when the weather is
fine outside. Uh, Sunday. There is a demonstration against George Bush coming into the UK,
uh, Parliament Square, one o'clock in the afternoon. On the street. Uh,
chocolate heads might want to know about that. Uh, you may not want to tell them.
All right. Of course I do. I'm just confused that this coming Sunday or is this last Sunday.
I didn't even know he was coming over. Uh, let's just get the info again. Did I miss it? Did I miss
a whole demonstration? No. No, I couldn't have missed that. Parliament Square, one o'clock
in the afternoon. Sunday, Parliament Square, one o'clock. All right. Let me get, let me
join being to that before anyone goes off and, you know, it may have already happened or not
happen. I don't know. I didn't even know Bush was coming over. Well, I guess it makes sense.
Isn't he honest to wear now saying goodbye to everybody? Okay. Well, so what are the details?
We just stand around and say Bush go home or, you know, do we have a message? Do we have a point
to make? You know, he's Dennis Kassunich, Kassinich, a Democratic representative in the United
States as yesterday, I think it was. As he said, I want to impeach Bush 35 counts of high crimes
and treason. Yeah. I got to stay on that one too. I hate it when stuff just like pops up and
all you got to say, I don't know him to anyone talking about. I don't think they take Kassinich
seriously, which is a big mistake because that guy, he's got like Napoleon complex. He's going to
fuck someone up and it just may be George Bush and good on him. All right. We'll check on that
demonstration for sure. Hello, Adam and Sandy. Hello. Well, you can cut the first bit. I was told that.
That's all right. Take your time, Andy. No worries. Um, hold on. I'm in Sandy and it was
extremely concerned about your story yesterday about the, uh, Lisbon KT. And seeing comments on
your, um, webpage saying, uh, from someone saying that they couldn't actually find the words
that you were talking about and decides to track it for itself. I went to the European Parliament website
and I'm looking at the page, the charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union,
possible to write the life in their concerns in the overview that the delegations allowed
in respect to their resulting from a lawful act of war and of acts committed in time of war or
imminent threat of war were abolished on the first of July 2003. Yep. Under that is a link to a PDF
file, which is a complete text of the charter of the charter. Um, and looking for the words that you
were talking about here, I find them. There's only time perhaps as people look at one example
of just pick one around them. The detention of a minor by lawful order for the purpose of
educational supervision or his lawful detention for the purpose of bringing him before the competent
legal authority. Um, now what I take that to me is if there is already a lawful order for the
detention of a minor in existence that does not conflict with their right to liberty. And similarly,
if you go through the others and view them in that way, it's possible to interpret these as explanations
of what things will be put already exist, which will not conflict with the overriding rules
of the human rights. I hope that helps. Um, great here. I hope you win folder, uh, red pill, uh,
sits in Pinkland, etc. I love you. Uh, me, Oklahoma. All right. Hey, thanks, man. Yeah. Well, so this is
my point. It's like how confusing is that? We have to go back and back and forth between three
different documents and the national law applies. This supersedes that it just seems too complicated.
As I said, you know, and I'm suspicious of that. I really am. I'm just suspicious of
suspicious of complicated words. And you listen to Dennis Cassinnish in, uh, in the Senate the other
day. And you know, it's like real simple. He's saying, okay, here's what he did. Here's the law that says
where you can't do that. And it was understandable. And this is just poor. Maybe it's a language thing.
If there's English in English, I guess. Maybe politicians English is different, but it sure seems
like lawyer speak to me and it's just tough. Uh, Joe, hold on. Charles is back.
Hi, let me show you what you're doing. Listen, let me show it. Now we saw stuff. Listen.
This is what it's like to be an Englishman. We are doing more than we love ourselves.
I don't think I can say anything at all about that Charles. Other than I appreciate you call
up my friend. You're the savant, whether you're drunk or not. Here's what I haven't played
in a long time. Feed Hopkins and become. My life's in this array is so where I feel. It's just
where I wouldn't have it any other way. Life has a funny way. I think it's what they say. Yes,
what they say. Surprise and you're reaching every day. So let me sing this song and it won't take
long. For the melody to what you're in need then we can sing this song. That's a day is long
and that's a melody that you're free. And it goes, La la la la la la la. There's a little more to learn from
every one. La la la la la la la la. No one else has the answer over there.
Oh, I can just be loved and become. Oh yeah, so many things to do is a time and nothing
never time and nothing. You need another year just to get it done. It's hard to overcome
or feel our dreams yet live our dreams. What I've been human still we must become. So let me sing this song
and it won't take long. For the melody to what you're in need then we can sing this song.
That's a day is long and that's a melody that sets your mind ahead. It goes, La la la la la la la
there's a little more to learn from every one. La la la la la la. No one else has the answer over there.
Oh, I can just be loved and become. Oh yeah, so many things to do is a time and nothing
can laugh away the pain. La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la a la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Patricia who said, the song sounds like being in love feels hell yeah
It Hawkins and become on the daily source code episode number
All right, got some fuel and energy talk coming up about
Nothing better than a promo about biking
Before we get oh shit, I forgot something hold on
I forgot something very important
About Pete Hopkins. I think you can find him on the e-music and I got to remind you guys
We still have the promotion going on you get 35 free songs 35 free mmp3s
If you go to e-music.com slash daily source code and I'm pretty sure Pete Hopkins is on there
So let me know just want to make sure
And Pete when you come out to with some more stuff man. We need it all right
As I said oil talk coming up specifically about diesel and some exciting news about a new automobile
Also atomic rod checks in with some more
Ranting and raving but all great information about atomic waste first though
Let's roll out the bike promo
The breast cancer fund in partnership with the Oakland yellow jackets and team lunatics are please
To announce the sixth annual bike against the odds toward the East day with four challenging routes
Ringing from 30 miles to a full century with 10,000 feet of climate
There is no clear line
The ride takes place on Saturday August 23rd in Oakland California several of the well stock best areas
Have panoramic views of the San Francisco Bay and the delicious organic lunch and entertainment massage
And to health expo waiting with the finished line
The breast cancer fence mission is to identify and eliminate the environmental causes of the disease
Check out their latest campaign at pureprevention.org
To sign up or to sponsor a cyclist or a team please go to www.breastcancerfund.org
Stroke B-A-O their pledge taking website makes the fundraising as simple as sending out an email to your friends and family
Inspire the people in your life to question the chemicals they use in and on their bodies together
Prevention is possible
Maybe intuition or evidence as the vision
Any final words no
Yeah, so that's obviously a good one the promo could have been a bit snappy or damn
But I find that an incredibly important cause so I want to make sure I play that promo for you
And of course any female chuckle heads out there if you want an expert breast exam
I'll be happy to do that for you
All right big oil Jesse on the honk her big oil Jesse what's going on?
Hey, Adam is Jesse in your hands. It's a guy that tries to hybrid and works for the oil company
I was impressed with the quality of information you got about diesel prices and I think
I think excuse me. I mean, it is the chuckle heads of odds you've touched on on the main points
The end of the time I am taking oil and the ultra little self-reduced the regulations that went into place
Not so long ago in the world like demand for it are the key factors as one of your colleagues pointed out
I thought I'd bring up something else because a lot of it the heat and and
The heat comes from the public to the oil companies come that at the pump which is
April and of course, but more so than ever before the gas stations if you will they're making less money than they ever did before
I want you guys to pay very close attention to this because it really blew my mind when I heard this comment from big oil Jesse
Gas stations making less money than they ever had listen to them. Let me walk you through a little bit
Say they only ever try to make 10 cents a gallon the US firms here 10 cents a gallon
Most people are paying with credit card these days and say the credit card company takes two cents to that right they because they take say they take two percent of
Transaction in terms of dollars so say gas was a dollar
Fights making the gas stations I can 10 cents credit card fees are taking two cents well now if yes, there's four bucks
The gas stations still only try to make the 10 cents
But now the credit card fees are up to eight cents in that case and the gas station is only left to two cents left over
Those most figures on exact obviously I've been my brain hurts for a long a second
So you're saying if it's if it's two bucks
Then they're taking two cents the credit card companies are taking two cents and those guys are just trying to make ten cents, but isn't the ten cents?
Hmm
Yeah, I guess the margins aren't with the with the pump with the pumps I guess it hurts my brain little
I'm obviously taking your word for it to be go to Jesse
They're trying to make things work for them, but
The fact of the matter is it's not the gas stations making the money they're making less money than they ever did before
It's upstream it's the refiner's and the fires of the product
Yeah, or wherever that may be again and maybe in the middle. He
Thought that might be interesting. Thank you. All right big oil Jesse
Yeah, it's as I said it's it's complicated and
But you know, I'm still pretty convinced this whole thing pretty much hinges on
Speculation investments and I was just a whole lot of me grabbing for a second the financial times for today
Ah
Sorry about that the financial times front page fuel strike fear sparks emergency measures
This is over here in the UK
Strike could prompt more widespread fuel shortages than those caused by the strike at the grandchmoth oil refinery in April
I'll look at like a four-day strike by the the guys who ship the oil the tanker drivers
And they're just not gonna ship it anymore
That's pretty crazy. Let me see why why why why why why they want
Okay, I see why five hundred tanker drivers employed by haulage companies
Hoyer UK and suckling transport said there's a name for you hey everybody. I'm from suckling transport
Are threatened to strike for four days from Friday. This coming Friday after the claim for a pay rise of 13% was rejected
This is all part of the problem, you know, we've we've got inflation and
People need to make more money to be able to make ends meet
So these companies, you know
And I believe that this you know these companies they gotta be making more money with a price of oil unless I'm nuts
Unless they're nuts
Now they gotta they gotta pay up
I mean there's a lot of money going around in that oil business. They should be paying their drivers
Anyway, let's see what Paul Nichols has to say always nice when podcast Paul records an MP3
Come hello Adam Paul Nichols here podcast pull that come long time listen to your show and haven't listen for some time
But start listening again. Yeah, we know all about your habits Paul as I needed to some help to paint my door and windows
Yeah, that's what I'm good for man now for the rest of your life whenever you smell paint
You're gonna be thinking of me
Programmed your brain and had a couple of these shows on my on my iPod
Just a very quick call rid of fuel think it's something I've been talking about and thinking about for a long time
Over here in the UK as you know we're paying 10 or more dollars a gallon
I was one of the suckers that bought a diesel car when the government announced that diesel would be cheaper
And of course
It's much more expensive now to purchase that
I've sent you a link to an article that is really interesting
Tars are the Indian
company that manufactures vehicles
Reckens that within the year there will be
Putting into production and air compressed vehicle and it has absolutely no emissions at all
Yeah, I took a look at this thing. It does look pretty cool, you know
What these guys have done is very simple. They've taken the same principle of it as a
With a as a combustion engine
Except instead of a spark that it makes a little explosion and then pushes the piston down in the cylinder
There's a burst of compressed air that comes in at some amazingly high pressure and to these cars are essentially carbon fiber
Compressed air tanks and it's and you know they got some power
I'm not quite sure what the power to wait ratio is and you know the cars of course look completely
Dorky and you're not likely to get laid in it, but if those things came out now
I'd be driving one for sure
I'm absolutely certain that the government will do everything that they can to try to crush you so to keep it down
Yeah, so that's the thing we got to look out for you know, so what you know
You know the story about the electric car right Google do a
Google video search for that one what happened to the electric car
We do have to be we got to keep our eye on this and what let's watch the inventor
You know that Indian guy who invented this watch his back, please
And make sure the patents are secure
So we can actually get this into production because if you think about it
We're paying well a high rate tax owners anyway we're paying 40%
at the moment and
That's that hits the wallet hard
We're paying 17 and a half percent VAT and then of course
We're paying nearly 70% on our gas as well and it doesn't surprise you to know that hardly any of that goes back into the
Go back into the government coffers that are to finance
Public transport or anything other with them now where does it go and I'm ready to be surprised
Oh, it's only a very small Mac does that and the AA go on about a lot
Anyway, um, it will be very interesting to see if this air compressed vehicle does make it to the streets because I tell you what
I'd be the first in line to buy one
No, no, no, no, man, you'd be number two because I'd be a front first on paying 70 to 20 penned
a week at the moment for a petrol just to get back and
Forward to work in my wife has a car as well, and it's just becoming
economically unviable
Very mindful of the three-minute thing. Don't worry. I'm gonna keep it very very short, but
The government recently the archives
Showed us that the government's not public
Publication excuse me of the fact that
Tobacco had a link with cancer because it would hurt the tax revenue and
Is that really true?
They stopped publicizing that because they didn't want to hurt tax revenue. I have a hard time believing that, man
Let me see let's see what my pack says here
stopping smoking reduces the
risk of fatal heart and lung diseases smoking kills
UK duty paid that's just absolutely shocking now if
As true to their word as they are and they want to help the economy they're gonna do everything like can
To reduce the tax
pound
To help the economy and of course to help emissions by this air compressed vehicle
Let's wait and see my guess is we'll be waiting a long time
All the best mate. See you. All right, mate. Thanks. Let's stay on top of that because that Tata thing is pretty amazing
Just Google the Tata motor company
And there's a couple of Google videos about it too. And you know as I said it's like, you know
It's not the sexiest thing but you fill it up in three minutes with compressed air and if you don't have
a compressed air nozzle anywhere near which by the way I think every service station in the world has
compressed air. I don't know if it's at the right kind of compressed air but they certainly have
compressed air to fill up your tires with I don't know if it's enough power or pressure to
to use
but otherwise you know this thing has a little
built-in compressor on board and
I think you plug it in and then it runs for four hours and your tank is then completely filled up total cost
two dollars
All right, a little more so I'm before we bring in a timing rod
You just don't hear shit like this on the radio
and that is the big benefit
Trinity Lake girls so like fast cars too
and a tiny red carpet but it was for my brother not for me
Later on that afternoon I hid it in my room
Dad was mad, but mama can't do a call
He said girls like fast cars too
Speed ain't just for boys
It's something about the sale
I've done a week in yours
and we love to look and feel
I've bought it from it's steel
but my soul is what makes the ladies move
Yeah girls like fast cars too
When I got my first real hard I thought I was dealer hard
Daytona rain up and down the street
Sifter mounted on the floor pretended
Three was on the door one turned off the key and I was free
On those long hot summer nights
I pinched out that light and with a wing I'd be a lot of sight
Stake girls like fast cars too
Speed ain't just for boys
It's something about the sale
I've done a week in yours
and we love to look and feel
I've bought it from it's steel
But my soul is what makes the ladies move
Yeah girls like fast cars too
So, Mr. Let's see if here's what else you got right here
You can skip the fancy SUVs
I'm looking forward
I'm branding to the door
Many apple and high stream machines
That girls like fast cars too
Speed ain't just for boys
It's something about the sale
I've done a week in yours
And we love to look and feel
I've hauled it from it's steel
But my soul is what makes the ladies move
Yeah girls like fast cars
The most fast cars
Girls like fast cars
Don't get much more market than get my friends
Girls like fast cars too
But you will not like my tata
In fact, you'll stay away from my tata
I'm gonna get laid in the tata
But you'll save the planet or something like that
Oh boy, okay
I'm gonna wind it up for today
As promised here's a atomic rod
It had all kinds of questions about atomic waste
I think the dog is trying to give me a message
Have a listen to the latest from atomic rod
Adam atomic rod, I'm here
Atomic Insights.blocksbut.com
Herjue question about the Russian mineral
That seems to be able to remove radioactive isotopes from water
I'm not an expert in that area
So I'm having a few of my own Uber so I want to look into the matter for me
Now for a rant
If you're interested in a venue, you can adjust one more demonstration
Of the successful conditioning
That you and most of the rest are thinking of has received from people
That simply do not like nuclear power
And about how much you have learned about how nuclear is cleaned
I can drive down energy press by replacing coal and oil
And how much our nuclear analysis improve
You all come to a point in the description where you ask that is all good
But what do you do about the waste?
All right, all right, I rod
Dude next time
If you're writing this down just slow down a bit slow down
Yeah, and you got time to get it
I know you're trying to get it within three minutes
But just slow down because it's important stuff
And now everyone's focused so pay attention
The condition has gone off for decades
Compared to all of the source of human and true power
Nuclear efficient producers remarkably tiny amounts of waste
You could put all the useful that we have ever produced into a single football stadium
And still have plenty of room left to spare in the entire US
Wait a minute, is that really true?
Is that all that it is in a football stadium?
That doesn't seem right
All that we've all that we've produced all nuclear waste into one football stadium
I mean, that's not a lot of that's true
We have only three operating variables for the rest of the somewhat contaminated metal concrete
Protective clothing and other assorted debris from plant operation construction deconstruction
Those places are tightly controlled and exceedingly well organized
The total lamass devoted to properly storing radioactive materials
Let's go from nuclear power plant operation is incredibly small
Perhaps a few hundred acres
The best news is a large portion of what's currently considered be radioactive waste can and should be recycled
Into either new plants or new fuel bundles
Now take a hard look at the competition
The world smokes decks and tailpipes
If you millions of tons of deadly waste products add into our shared atmosphere every single day
All right, I wish you were to done this slower, man
I really do because your point is so well made
You know
How come there's no well?
We know why there's no information if all you're saying is true, Rod
That's
That's how we're talking about one football stadium
Yeah, that's a big difference with the smoke stacks
I'll shut up now let you focus on what he's saying
Well, they we cannot recover any of those materials and use them for anything else because they are now pollution that we must all breathe
If you do not think of them as deadly waste products
It is because you have been conditioned to accept them as a fact of life in a world where people want to fly planes
Drive cars power up the stink boats and watch their big screens in a climate control room
If you did not believe they are deadly waste products
I suggest you consider what will happen if you or anyone else decide she's so not tell pipe or take a couple of deep breaths in a smoke field room
You would never consider such an experiment a new
Neither would most other people you can however find plenty of stories about how the experiment turns out every time it's tried
With combustion deadly waste products humans avoid areas were the concentrations high up to kill them
We also tried to minimize long-term effects
But some of this live in areas where the pollution's bad enough to crush shorter less healthy lives
At some of your tiny chucklets or maybe even some of your older Londoner friends about the deadly small cuts by burning fossil fuel
Do it even I remember what Los Angeles used to be like 15 years ago 20 years ago
And they certainly clean that up the smong has gotten a lot better. You should be just as cloud hanging over LA
So yeah for sure feels new clear vision waste is a good news story because the volume of small
We can isolate materials in containers and put them in type the controlled spaces that most was never had to see
All you have to do is accept the fact that most people are able to follow simple safety rules like stay away from the area and do not eat the leftovers
You and your audience can help us all break through the conditioning that is make people believe that fossil fuel wages
Okay, but fission way to something we will never figure out
routine fossil fuel waste kills people every day
Retain nuclear fission waste from power plant operations has never killed anyone
Take a couple of red pills look around the world today and guess who just might be interested in making sure the
Conditioning remains intact great hair. Hope you went passionate potato feed him and declare your independence from big fossil
Remember in a democracy they are us now. This is true
You work for me and I work for you. I guess in some twisted way atomic rod everybody
That's pretty amazing. I got to get more data on the the volume of waste that doesn't seem like a hell of a lot
Yeah, you know honestly you got a lot more chance of dying by getting hit by a car and traffic
And this is of course the problem is we have been conditioned but in a more overall sense
We've been conditioned that we want it we're supposed to be safe 24 hours a day
You know doctor fucks up supposed to be safe from that
You know that's supposed to happen. This is there's rules regulations
Demit how can we not be safe?
You know fact is we're not safe folks. That's just the bottom line
We're just not safe get over it get used to it
Hey, one other thing. I want to start a topic. So we've got to codex elementarious
How about the something goes along with that fluoride in the water?
I know this is a hot topic because I've been doing a little bit of research and
You know I've been brought up thinking fluoride is in the water to make a teeth healthy
And of course I read the contrarian view saying no, no, no, it makes the population complacent
Which apart which is all of course of that whole conditioning of your supposed to be safe and don't worry
You'll be safe just let the government take care of you you'll be safe which is bullshit
Until I read the legacy of ashes
Which is the book that Uncle Don is mentioned in and in one passage I can't really remember it off the top of my head
But there was some like they were doing all kinds of covert activities and had to go get some cocaine from some camp and
Essentially what they did is they they put fluoride in the water
Of this camp that they were going to go and and grab this coke from and these missiles or weapons or whatever
You know it's one of those convoluted CIA stories another nice piece of American history and it actually said, you know
Oh, we had overflow over fluoridated the water and it gave most of the people in the camp
Diaria and other stomach ills ale ailments and I think in wait a minute if the CIA is using that shit
And you know it really literally spells it out. They you know they use it to you know as a way to
Get into the camp and get what they wanted and you know it seems to me like that's something funky going on there
And this fluoridation of our water. I'm a little bit concerned about it
So let's open up that topic
Keep it along keep it run alongside the red pill that atomic rod keeps shoveling into our mouths and
Let's see if we can meet up again that tomorrow because I'm going to the city Thursday
Thursday and we'll certainly do a food bar Friday
I am definitely looking forward to it before I go the one last comment
Note that everything has happened so far in the week where the hell is Roger Smalls?
See this is the question that's on everybody's mind forget nuclear waste
Forget anything else. Where the hell was Roger Smalls? I can't find it anywhere
I eat really I am actually getting to I am sorry to get it a little bit worried
Not personal is blog. It's not I'm stalking right I can't find what just more than you
Where we even know if you saw a ride for you know you haven't checked in for God knows how long
I mean the you know the inside noise is the email and you're keeping content
No, please let us know could Roger please phone in
You know when it here so we want to get some bot just falls love we haven't heard of them for
God knows how long anyway that that was just a side note that I had to run with poppins my mind anyway
I shall speak you later
I'm
Not saying what knives enough to the question. They were for us
Yeah, you know it's a bit upsetting to me as well and I I do know a couple of people that had a
Recent Skype chat with him and apparently he was in jail when he just got out and you know
I desperately want to help the guy out, but you know if he doesn't contact me there's nothing I can do
So another public call out to Roger Smalls Roger just Skype me or send me an email or
Preferably call in just let us know you're okay, man. That's all I really want to know and if there's anything I can do for you
You're one of the earliest savants one of the earliest and most
Trustworthy and reliable chuckle heads always there and I
Just kind of vanished off the face of the earth. So we're missing you
Anyway everybody I'll talk to you again on Thursday until that time live your life with passion please and as long as it lasts
Enjoy your free another fine
Media old presentation stick it in your ear
You