Delta Sierra Charley, 8-1-1.
There is a wall going on for your mind.
Idiot maintenance mouth surgical strikes from traffic keeper collages in online magazine racks.
Cover girl cut out through a pop-up ad inspecting victims with silicone shredder.
World by past your business point.
Territure was now a rainy pornography lover's cake shelter.
Post-production Debbie Tons pursue you and mask our chariots.
They construct ransom letters from typical packages and bleed mask air into the holy water supply.
There is a war going on to your mind.
Industry inside a slaying test tube babies to poor big crackheads.
They blast logos and blast geto.
They're avoided neck die say stop stitch.
Conscious rappers and whistleblowers get stitches made of acupuncture needles and very in-edge strings.
There is a war going on to your mind.
Professional wrestlers and ice presidents want you to believe that.
The desert sky is their blue screen.
They superimpose explosions.
They shout at you.
Pay no attention to them in behind the mark turn.
You're the greatest beneath the tree flags.
Those who are today we want protection immediately is these days of the size of courtiers.
There is a war going on to your mind.
We are the insurgents.
For $16 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no digging trees in.
I like to think I'm sliding these next year.
Podcasting is a matter of green.
I'll bring your eyes to the millions of lies.
They tell you every day.
I'll bring your mind to the clover disguise.
The advertisement say.
How did they know?
Such good for you.
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Wake up, wake up.
What a hole.
I start to let head.
Then I'll tear it.
Will your wake up, wake up.
What a hole.
Throw it on the land.
And kill what you can't just to make the profit's rise.
I'll say you from her.
From all that you were.
The money spreads like lies.
And how do they know?
What's good for you?
Wake up, wake up.
What a hole.
I start to let head.
Then I'll tear it.
Will your wake up, wake up.
What a hole.
I'll bring your mind to the clover disguise.
Don't wanna hate you.
Don't wanna blame it all on you.
Out of all shame.
If you don't look home for you too.
Wake up, wake up.
What a hole.
I start to let head.
Then I'll tear it.
Will your wake up, wake up.
What a hole.
I'll bring your mind to the clover disguise.
The hole.
It'll be yours.
I'll bring your mind to the clover disguise.
From the affluent suburb of Surrey,
Jonas Kilford in the United Kingdom,
everybody, how you doing?
It's Tuesday, I wanted these days when I stopped apologising for
missing out on shows, which of course I did again last week.
Man, though it's just no way around it. It's too busy. Have you seen this media today stuff? I've been doing this
I got to tell you I'm totally
Vibin on on this video stuff. It's been
Six years, I think since I was messing around with Final Cut Pro actually
It was one of the first versions of the Final Cut Pro. We made our reality show on it
And it's improved quite a bit since then, but just he got it. It's like
I guess like Photoshop, you know, if you're really in a Photoshop, which I have never really been into
You know, you just get into it and hours go by before you know it
And so I'm really trying to come up with the quickest way and I believe me. I've tried everything
I've tried live to take, but at the end of the day, you're setting up some templates and stuff
And yeah, just having a kind of a set systemology and workflow
Yeah, it's a works best and Final Cut Pro and I'm doing all the stuff myself. I'm loving it
Which means I'm getting closer to coming up with the
Some alternative programming that I've been thinking about anyway
So the main thing is I got stacked up because I had to go to the Netherlands on Sunday
I hadn't told you guys about this. This was a request that came in several weeks ago
And it wasn't until they backdored it through my wife
That sounded kind of weird, but
Essentially the public one of the public broadcasters in Holland
So that would be equivalent to BBC, I guess they
They do an annual top 2000
Countdown on New Year's Eve
So not like Dick Clark's New Year's Rock and Eve, but it's in a studio
And it's, you know, it's a really good atmosphere and they're doing things a little bit differently this year
Where just before the top 10 or the top 20, whatever it is, they take about an hour and a half
And they have a smaller setting almost like a living room
With nothing but extremely talented people
And me
So you won't know most of them, although this one guy Tuan
I think he's got a record coming out in England pretty soon
I'll be sure to play that
But Candy Dolphor, you might know Candy, of course, famous for her sex playing
I've known her since she was 14 years old
I've played with Prince, you know, when Prince says when I want sex I call Candy that Candy
Also done a lot of stuff with Dave Stewart, of course
I think it started with Dave Stewart, now they come to think of it
Tuan, you host a house, another famous, I would say, world famous, Dutch singer
It was just, it was just wall to wall really talented people
And the reason they'd asked me to be there is because Madonna, Prince and Michael Jackson are all turning 50
They were all turned 50 this year and so they wanted me to tell a story about it
Not normally, I didn't really feel like doing it, but the producer, you know, worked, producers married to a producer that worked with Patricia
Yeah, I got Shanghai
So anyway, so I wound up doing stuff in hotel rooms
On Final Cut Pro, you dirty bastard, I hear you thinking
Oops, I didn't want that one
Here's what I want
All right, early in the week
Hey Adam, how you doing?
I'm doing good now
I was just hit that number 151, but before we start, I want to take you back to the last week
Okay, this is why
Hi there Adam, this is Barry Apeo, new ring
From the answer number 3
Oh, 19, every three
Ah, very good
Excellent
Ah, it's too bad we missed it, y'all, thanks for putting that
Disappointed in the last week's hit there
But due to some delays, I couldn't get it to you on time
But I didn't want you to miss out on it, so
That's why
This little flashback to last week
It tests number 150
Read all the
All right, enough time for hit test number 151, so here we go
Okay, test
Intro number 1
Uh, flash from the pan
Ah
Got it, now I can recognize
Uh, I don't know the name of the song though
But I intro sometimes you can recognize so easily
Number 2
Adult education, hall another
Hell yeah, on a roll
So definitely two for three, which flash in the pan song was that I can
And number 3
Back to land
Back to reality
Uh, crap, who sings that
And it's time for the answer
And this is answer number 1
Flash in the pan
Nineteen 85
Round midnight
Think
Uh
I don't understand
Can't help
Do you promise man
You don't help me
You midnight man
There you go, midnight man
Answer number 1
And hit test number 1
Five, one
Midnight man, flash and the pan
Ah, I don't know
And this is answer number 2
Adult education
Nineteen 85
And I don't know the name of the song
But I'm not telling you, go, that's why
I don't understand
Oh yeah
What the need of the knowledge
I can't show it
But I'm not telling you, that's why
I don't understand
Oh yeah
All in all
As answer number 2
And this is answer number 3
I don't know
I don't understand
Oh, I don't know
All in all
Ah, prefer don't know
Oh, I don't understand
And so number three, soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to soul to
soul to soul to soul to soul to soul
in
all the stuff. We're also moving by the way in the midst of all this lady Patricia off to the
the Curry Terrace today for flooring. It's going to be a very, very crazy Christmas. We're going
to be sitting in boxes or sitting on boxes with maybe some egg nong. That's what I'll do. I got to
make up some egg nong. Anyway, there's so much has happened. Obviously since we last spoke and
it always, it just seems to continue. It never ceases. The funniest thing which actually I put
in my video today that is airing on today. If you go to my video to Arkham, you'll see it is
the shoe that was thrown at George Bush while he was getting a speech in Iraq. A couple things,
well, actually a speech. It gets a press conference. A couple things that I noticed about that. So
first of all, man, GW got some skills when it comes to ducking the boots. I mean, it's like this,
guys had shit thrown at his head before and no doubt about it. What did the Iraqi journalist,
I guess, actually say, was he just pissed at the TSA for having to take a shoes off every single
frickin' airport in the world or was it something else? Perhaps it's the fact that Iraq has now
authorized, I love this, and the United States subsequently has authorized the purchase by Iraq
of several billion dollars worth of war equipment. Oh, man, this is the economic hitman in
at work. So if you've never read that book, the either confessions of an economic hitman. I've
talked about it many times. You must read that book and you'll see exactly how all of this works
and exactly what went down in Iraq. But I thought it would, you know, thought it was kind of interesting.
And the other thing I noticed about that video is so the guy throws one shoe, then he throws
another shoe and only then in the background do you see like secret service guys running through
a back entrance? What the hell is going on with that? Do they not screen people? Do they feel that
it's all safe? I found that to be highly interesting. It took at least 30 seconds before anyone
responded and did anything. Actually, the other journalists were doing more than then secret
service as far as I could tell was very, very interesting. Financial markets, which I always
keep my eye on for you. I'm sure you've been taking a look at it as well. Of course, up and down,
we're bouncing all over the place mainly because there's so much uncertainty about the
the forthcoming bailout of the auto industry. It's getting really kind of nutty because now,
apparently the treasury is going to just make a decision whether they should give some money to
these guys or not. I mean, what happened to Congress? Is that no longer necessary? And Congress
doesn't have to make any kinds of decisions. Now, Hank Pauls, I could just make that up all by himself.
Oh, yeah, because somehow it fits underneath the tarp bailout bill for troubled asset relief
program. How can that have anything to do with the auto industry?
Unless you, I guess you count them as three of America's troubled assets? Yeah, sure.
And it's horrible, of course, that these companies are going to fail. And I don't think an injection
of cash is going to help at all. It's not even injection. It's a loan that they do have to pay back.
You know, just look at the product. That should tell you enough. I wouldn't invest in it.
Warren Buffett's not stepping up to invest. Why not? Well, because probably people who are
are smart about business look at it and say, nah, not a good idea. You know, kind of like the
way banks aren't giving you a mortgage if you're looking for one. Same thing, but oh, no, we'll just let the
former Goldman Sachs CEO who now runs our money and printing presses make that decision.
And of course, in the meantime, the bailout now really has cost American taxpayers because
you will be paying for it in taxes or indirectly through inflation, which is kind of a hidden tax,
eight trillion dollars, eight trillion. And the Federal Reserve and the Treasury or the Federal Reserve
specifically won't even tell us who they've lent the money to. Go look at the stories. It's on Bloomberg.
And it's all in the show notes of daily source code.com. And most of the stuff, of course, source
from the drop, which is a great place to keep up with what's going on. It's drop.io slash daily source
code. Let's see who do we have here. Hey, Adam, it's Cory from Minnesota. Hey, Cory, how are you doing?
I'm going to go back. Thanks for talking about this stuff. I love this show. I love, uh,
love, no agenda because I love to hear you go back and forth with John Devore Act. I got to tell
we had a pretty good show this weekend. It was a little bit long. It was like an hour and 45 minutes,
but yeah, we were into it. Um, thank you. Appreciate you listen. Lots of people tuning into
Noah agenda. Noah agenda.mevio.com. It's great. Great, great entertainment, great listening. Hey,
I have an idea, or maybe it's a proposal, or maybe it's just, uh, just someone going to throw
out there. Uh, it has to do with dealing with the subject when you're talking to people that
don't necessarily know anything about it, um, or are just don't get that we're getting fucked in the
ass by, uh, Googleful leads. You know, wait. You got a little, uh, cow ball ring for that.
It's just a little too much for them to fathom in one sitting. You know, it's hard to go into
with them right away. And what I was thinking is, uh, instead of sitting there and, and a lot of
us out there can't sit, you know, we can't sit down and explain everything. I mean, there's just too much
to go over. I was wondering if there was something we could do like, is there's some way we could
set up some sort of a page, um, kind of a, kind of a starter kit, a jumping off point, uh, just something,
you know, a little introduction to, uh, you know, what's going on out there? You know, that's a,
that's a good question. And I found that the, well, I'm just kind of searching my own, uh, my own awakening
if you will. I found that looking at one of the hundreds, maybe even thousands by now of videos,
and of course, all of them have varying degrees of quality and accuracy. But there's so many
great videos that really do get into explaining, um, how the world really works, how what I would
call the energy elite control us and have enslaved us to their fossil fuel industry of energy,
of course, being the basis of everything. That seems to be the easiest and, and you've probably
know, you know, many, many different ones. If anything, you'll get people to start thinking,
they may not agree with it. They'll call it total hogwash, but still these videos are,
now getting so well produced, um, that, uh, it just has an impact. It certainly worked for me.
So really sending someone to a site where there's lots of words, it still doesn't have the same type
of impact as, uh, as a, as a well polished documentary online documentary might have. And maybe
even better, just to, you know, um, there's several places we can download them, burn it to a CD.
So it's not even a web experience. All those nuances I find are very, very important. But at the end
of the day, if you want someone just to read mainstream news about what's really happening,
send them to the source code drop. I mean, that's, those are all links to, um,
mainstream or news organizations that are reporting on things really happening. But because it is
not repeated over and over and incessantly repeated over and over again, it just doesn't stick.
It doesn't get to the top of the heap, which is normal in this, uh, info overload society. So
I would say a combination of that, uh, drop.io slash daily source code, uh, as well as, uh, one of
your favorite movies, depending on the situation, depending on the person, you can also, uh, pick any
number of topics that might, uh, that might shake this person up. Uh, I've done it several times,
um, to people who are highly skeptical, uh, but who at least loved me, uh, who are willing to,
willing to watch something and it did work. And it has continued to work. Time and time again.
I mean, it's hard to just send them to your, your site. It's hard to send them to an Alex
Jones site without them being just extremely, extremely cynical about it. It just being completely,
you know, I don't even know what the word is. But uh, just shocked. Yeah, and, and also,
send them to Noah agenda because Noah agenda, I think there's, there's enough balance there
between John and I that that it actually, that that could work. It kind of depends on the episode though,
but, uh, there's something topical going on. It might be interesting for them to listen to it.
It would know agenda. Me vetoed a call. You know, and, or just, it just completely doubt it.
So I was thinking, you know, hey, what if we could all get together, put our heads together,
and come up with something that is, uh, just, you know, what could we throw into this little
starter pack? If they get everybody thinking, you know, like an FAQ kind of a thing,
just something to kind of get them in slowly. So they're not just going to get slammed with all this
information and just being like, oh my god, you know, what's going on? And I don't believe this
is crazy and I leave you alone. You guys are freaks, you know, just something to make it easier
to, uh, to believe. And I think that would help everybody. I'm sure there's tons of people out there
that could probably use something like this. And frankly, we need it. We need for people,
you know, we need it to be easily digested, you know, because there's a lot of people out there that
need to know this obviously. And I think it would just really help the cause and, uh, really helped
the wake people up. So anyway, put it in a ramble too much. Yeah, a little bit at the end, uh,
the gist of when I'm talking about. And, uh, well, they work for us. Yeah. And, um, that's
really easy to, uh, make everybody understand just what that means. Thanks a lot, Adam. And, uh,
hey, I just got to throw one little plug in there. Music. Goat.com. That's where you can find me.
Anyway, yeah, now I may, well, at the end of the day, you know, it's just not easy. You got to work
at it. People don't just wake up from years of hypnotization over night. You know, there is no easy path.
You gotta work at it
You gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you
gotta work at it, you gotta work at it, you gotta work, that's pretty good, that's stuff, that's pretty good, you gotta work tired that this is gonna be P
Baby on your knees
There's a friction
In the kitchen
In the dream
Yeah, I remember
But I know, yeah, I'
Wait, but I know, yeah
But I know, I know, I know, I see
Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I see
But I know, yeah, I know, I, I see
He's right in the end
Look, because you're broken
Is this a joke?
So go by something that you can't afford
Because your road, cause your friends is high
You're such a joke
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
That way it's all created
Even with your heart
Isn't it really, really, really?
Isn't it true?
Isn't it?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Help me make this
Don't make this amazing
I know I'm going to be a lady
I'm going to be so beautiful
It's you, it's you
It's me, it's me, it's me
No, no, no, no
It's me, it's me
No, no, no, no, no, no
I can't just say you're not
What is going to be real
I know I'm going to be a lady
Where is my wife?
Where is she?
Yeah, you're not being Hollywood
Where's my wife?
I'm going to be a lady
Yeah, I'm going to be a lady
And I'm going to be a lady
I'm going to be a lady
My queen Ed Daven
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna go now, man.
There we all be free.
As some disturbing, I'm sitting pretty much in the middle of the news between the United
States and Europe, and I saw something on the news in Amsterdam when I was there, which
I'll get to in a moment.
But I think it relates to this piece, which is from Lou Dobbs.
Let me see.
This was uploaded to YouTube October 29th.
Have a listen to this report.
It's a wrap.
It's a question tonight about an Army combat brigade being trained to deal with civil
disturbances in the United States.
The Posse Comitatis Act of 1878 generally prohibits federal uniform services from carrying
out domestic law enforcement duties, except in cases expressly authorized by the Constitution
or an act of Congress.
Now, you'll hear about this thing called the Posse Comitatis Act a lot.
Let me just repeat that that the US military may not be deployed to American streets against
American civilian citizens unless carrying out domestic law enforcement duties for carrying
out domestic law enforcement duties except in cases expressly authorized by the Constitution
or an act of Congress.
Now, we pretty serious stuff.
That would essentially be an all-out attack.
That's when they can be deployed to carry out domestic law enforcement duties.
But now, listen to what's happening this Christmas season.
Critics say the brigade's training goes against one of the founding principles of our
country, separation of military and civilian government.
Luis Givoni has our report.
They've spent 30 months on the streets of Baghdad.
Now the first brigade combat team of the Army's third infantry division is back in the USA.
The Army times report in quote, they may be called upon to help with civil unrest.
And crowd control or to deal with potentially horrific scenarios and quote, the question arises
why and isn't that what the National Guard does?
Infantry brigade is designed to engage an enemy with maximum amount of this guy is an attorney
Craig Trebilcock, active force and destroy it.
That's not the sort of thing anybody wants to see in the streets of the United States.
Now almost 5,000 strong.
The brigade is based at Fort Stewart Georgia under control of Northern Command, who
tell CNN quote, the primary purpose of this force is to provide help to people in need
in the aftermath of a WMD like event in the homeland so that were they called to support
civil authority, those governors or local state jurisdictions that might need our help,
but they would be responsive and capable in the aftermath of an event like this.
All right.
So, and this is coming from Colonel Michael Boatner, who is interesting title, future operations
Northern Command.
Oh, something that will happen in the future.
So they're training and they're going to be setting up DUI traffic stops, which to me just
seems like it's totally wrong.
Now at the same time, and this is why I'm relating, so the question you got to ask
there is, you know, they're training, do they expect something, do they know that we
don't know, now over to the Netherlands.
I'm watching the news, and this is big bruhaha, that the government had ordered the
production and sale of emergency packs, and the reason why I was in new stories because
they did this huge PR and advertising campaign.
They bought all this ad space, but the packs weren't actually in the stores yet.
Now, so they was some governmental screw up, yeah, go figure.
But then, you know, they're showing these packs, and these packs are, first of all, sponsored
by Varkta batteries, which if you're in any emergency, I hope I don't have to rely on Varkta
batteries, batteries, as we say in the UK.
You know, it was a time of candles, it was like, and they're literally saying, well, just
in case every household should have one of these, and so they did this big push, they
didn't wait for the supply chain to be ready to actually sell these things in stores.
What do they know that we don't?
And by the way, what is the piece of rope in there for?
That's what I'd like to know.
Is that the hang yourself?
I want to probe it.
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel on this week's show, I review Lococo 2 on the PSP,
far cry 2 on the Xbox 360, I round up the latest party games for your Wii, and you can
win copies of Football Manager 2009 for the PC and the PSP.
That's all it gamesweasel.com.
All right, the chuckle head's getting ready to crank it up, I will just pretend it's a little bit
of a footballer crying.
The fight's on.
Hey, you man, it's Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt,
Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt Matt Matt, Matt Matt, Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt Matt
And when we were good, just close your eyes
So when we are bad, we'll scare your mind
We're not as light till we're tired
Telling things, we're not as light
Still around the world, telling you about shit
We said the water's a shadow here
That you're the water's a shadow here
But you're the water's a shadow here
That you're the million shining stars
That you're shining star, we're not as light
Still around the world, telling you about shit
We're not as light till we're tired
Telling things, we're not as light
Still around the world, telling you about shit
We said the water's a shadow here
We're not as light, still around the world, telling you about shit
Yeah, we're not as light, we're not as light
Come on, come on
Say hello to my little friend, Adam Kerry
I'm a really source code
Eduardo, thank you my friend
Excellent
Yeah, fight song
Yeah, oh, one more thing I wanted to mention about my travels
On the way back, going through simple airport
Amsterdam International
They now have, so there's the H.P.R which is where all the easy jets fly from
I couldn't fly myself by the way because we've got horrible weather here in the UK
We've got missed down to the ground
That went like one in the afternoon
So I wasn't taking any risk
I just like let me just take the easy jets
Love the way easy jet works
By the way better than KLM British Airways
When it comes to short haul
Better than anything, I just love the way those guys operate
Anyway, on the way back, you go through the H.P.R you have to go through
They have their own security and they have two lines
One line is the old fashioned x-ray with the metal detectors
The other line is oh yes, it's the new photo scanning device
And this thing is oh man, actually by accident I got on that line
Actually got out of that line
This is the one if you haven't seen the pictures before
It's where they x-ray you
And they can actually see through your clothing
And see if you know what you have in your pockets or what you're wearing
Or should you have anything hidden on your body
And it's so degrading
You have to I was looking at people you have to get in and then put your hands up
All the way if the stretch your hands up while they take this picture of you
And you know and this people looking at you like basically naked
And I find this the perfect opportunity to pester my wife
Because she's the one that says oh you know these cameras
I don't mind about the CCTV cameras because you know hey
Wait until your daughter's missing you know
Then you'll be happy they have CCTV cameras
Yeah darling but at the end of the day you know where does it stop
Well if you have I love this line if you have nothing to hide
If you haven't then you have nothing to worry about
So I said to her yes, I say hey man they got they got that newfangled photo x-ray
Where you know because I've shown her the pictures before
And I remember saying oh my gosh oh my
And she said oh what do you mean so now you have to go through that photo thing
Yeah but I don't know I go through the other one
Chip it eventually they'll have both don't you understand that
She says well I don't like that
I said oh what do you mean if you have nothing to hide
Then what do you have to worry about
But a Bing
Oh it's nasty it's just
I believe when they have that fully
Implemented I think I'm just going to have to ask for a hand search
There surely there must be some legal ground that I can go against that
Oh I feel so violated
You're looking at me naked dude
And as we've established many times before
Naked guys just not a good look
In general
Adam Curry this is Mark from pflying.com
Mark is thankful from the letter pflying.com
I just want to thank you
So much about your show and what you do in your awakening and your message
I listened to your show like twice at least twice each time now days because it's just filled with so much great information
You always mentioned about show length
I really would love three hours shows
If you could do three hours shows that would be amazing
If that's all I did I could certainly do three hours shows
I mean that's the reason why I skip them you know
I do this because I really really really enjoyed and I want to give you guys a good experience
I don't want to put out crap just because I have the word daily in the title of the show
I just don't
So you know if I if I know that it's it's only going to be half a show because I can't prep properly or
I'm not feeling right or I'm going to be stressed for time
I just don't do it so and also I really don't pay attention to the clock
I just keep going until I feel like I'm done
Which is the beauty of this
Let's just call it podcasting because that's what the audio stuff still is as far as I'm concerned
The video stuff that I'm working on is going to be different
We won't call it podcasting we'll call it
We'll call it a revolution
I could even do six hours shows I would follow you
I'm trying to have six hours in your day though
Dude I'm working 18 I just have to spend them on other things
Unfortunately
But I would have wanted to thank you most about is the awakening
And because you without you
I would not be to the point where I am now
I would be believing that
To a kind of took down the Twin Towers
And I would be believing that we need this auto bailout
I would I would believe all this crap that our government has just screwed us over with
There is nothing that I can do at all
That I can pay you back for what you have done back to me
Oh no no no no no never ever ever ever
No no this show was made by you you guys make it you put it together you source it
Almost in its entirety
I'm just kind of the the guy in the middle taking up all the pieces putting together
Spinning it back out no thank you
But having said that next time you're in San Francisco let me know dinner's on me
I'll take you anywhere even though I'm a poor bastard
Oh not a bastard but poor
Anyway, I love you very much
I love you dearly
And of course no homo
Other than that don't know what else to say
Love you show
They work for us is mark from pflying.com
Yeah
Out
pflying.com
All right
Thanks man
I appreciate
There's no money
There's no possessions
Only obsession
I don't need that shit
Take my money
Take my obsession
I just want to be heard
Now that you're all my words
Come into a date man
Tell no what you heard
It's about a revolution
You don't have any desire
To the final conclusion
Let's do an obsession
Come a race, kick your left and put a knife on me
Let's say it's a market for stress
You're mistaken to this system
Why can't you answer to me
For that shit you don't mean
If you bet the world is based on me
Step back and see
Stop thinking about yourself
Stop thinking about
There's no money
There's no possession
Only obsession
I don't need that shit
Take my money
Take my obsession
I don't need that everything is nothing
Everything is nothing
This reality is really just a fucked up dream
With the flesh and the blood
Let you call your son
Step in this eye now
It's a big record
Take your money
Put it up and back in this world
Because I shit
Take your money
Put your money
Take it up
You don't need that shit
There's no money
There's no possession
Only obsession
I don't need that shit
Take my money
Take my possession
Take my obsession
I don't need that shit
Money
Posing shit
I don't need that shit
Take your son
Take your clothes
Come your hand
Come in
You just can't win
Just can't win
And everything's your fault
Only you
Take my money
Take my possession
I don't need that shit
You don't need that shit
Money
Posing shit
I don't need that shit
Is it just me or is it hard rocker today?
I think we can establish that
Pop a roach
Two angels and insects
Daily source code
Episode 8
One
Actually I had the game today
I see it's only 130
I've done just about everything I've got to do
I do want to mention sponsors of the daily source code
Because in these economic times
These are the perfect types of ads
You want to hear about because they're actually products that you want to buy
I'm sure you're going to use these companies or something similar
If you don't already
And we're all looking for a good deal these days
And you just can't get these products
Any cheaper anywhere
Particularly online
We have the best offering
We go out and negotiate with these companies
So that we can give the audience members a great discount
And producers of great programming
Participate in each sale
So let me just run down because it's so much
First of all, eHarmony, this thing
I've never used the dating site obviously
It've been married for over 20 years
But I hear a lot, I really do know
Actually I know a lot of people who have met each other online
And they've had very successful relationships
And they continue to be successful
Of course, I'm sure there's a regular ratio
There of relationships that don't work out
But it's not free to find someone online
In the proper environment
You've got all kinds of
Basically sites that are set up to be for hookers, I guess
Was it adult friend finder
That's my favorite
But eHarmony.com has a great reputation
You know what they do
If you take a three month subscription
The first month is free just use my code
And in fact, all these links are in the
Show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Crosspost at curry.com
For the holidays, for Christmas shopping
Or maybe just for yourself
Finish line 15% off
Any purchase of 60 dollars or more
They've got great sports equipment
Adidas, Puma, Nike, Unayment
And that of course is using my code
MeVODSC
Budget rentacars
Which many of you may be using over
The holiday weekend
30% off
Your weekly rental
Or 10% off any amount
At budget.com slash dsc
Brooksstone.com
Which of course has great Christmas gifts
Kind of the I always view that as the outdoorsy
Sharper image, you know
If a mall didn't have a Sharper image
Which by the way
None of them do anymore
Then
Then I was be happy
There was a Brooksstone 10% off
The Brooksstone using my daily source code
Discount code
30% discount of course
GoDaddy.com with the code
DSC
And we still can get your 35 free songs
At e-newsick.com
No obligation
Absolutely yours to keep
Do with whatever you want
Check them out
Dailysourcecode.com
Crosspost at curry.com
Now this showed up on the drop
And I'm like
Yeah
I kind of dig that
Because I am in love with the 80s
So the song is about
Listen to the lyrics
I think you'll enjoy it
So it was Jeremy in 1983
And as Ocean Pacific team
We got a bloody knee
On a skateboard
In the half-pipe
In the backyard
That Tuesday night
And I'm only gonna kiss my left ear
And I can't work in on this podcast
All summer long
And my favorite bit
All these beats
And I'm gonna wear a pink touch
To the floor
I'm trying to gloss through the first four window
He's gotten fast
Cause I never did a thing so
And I look up to my big
Well cause in the 80s
All the ladies
Grab this hand and cut in like go
And I'm only gonna kiss my left ear
And I can't work in on this podcast
All summer long
And my favorite bit
All these beats
And I'm gonna wear a pink touch
To the floor
I'm trying to gloss through the first window
He's gotten fast
Cause in the half-pipe
And I'm only gonna kiss my left ear
He's gotten fast
I'm trying to gloss through the first window
Cause in the 80s
All these beats
And I'm only gonna kiss my left ear
When you're the president
All the breakfast club
And you're the hesitant
To fall in love
For ladies
Diamonds
I am from Canada
I'm playing thoughts to the floor
Without a year
Who could possibly go wrong
You're not where, I'll take my feet off your head
Cause you're feeling way too far in love
Yeah, I love with the 80s. I've got to mention there was one other guest on that show I did in Amsterdam, Ruby Wax
Who now apparently is doing a Ruby Wax show in the Netherlands as well
She's kind of franchising herself
But it was interesting because you know when people have been in Amsterdam
But in particular for a while at least out of the country she lives in the UK
I don't think she does much in the States anymore at all
You know then there's always a little bit more vocal and think that no one will ever hear what she's saying
And I could tell you know she's like, I don't do this damn promotional thing
I'll go on there, I'll talk some crap and she was talking about her vagina within 30 seconds
I mean it was pretty, pretty wrang, but funny, got to admit very funny
But she started off by saying, fascist Britain, you know this is a horrible
And she kept saying fascist fascist Britain
Which of course I have to agree with her
And she was relating that to not being able to say anything anymore
Because everything is so politically correct
And then she relayed the Russell Brand Jonathan Ross story poorly
I might not, if you can't just explain that in 30 seconds you kind of got to know a little bit of the background
And I thought to myself, wow you know big mouth, Ruby
Why don't you say that over here with your big mouth
Which I don't think she will be doing any time soon
Alright, quick rundown of the drop before we wrap it up for today
Let me see what we've got
Oh and the UK and other dance controversy, strictly come dancing
This is dancing with the stars here in the UK
Oh I heard about this, I didn't see it because it happened Saturday
But apparently this is like banana republic
I can't believe people, you know so
So you already know that the guy who really couldn't dance
But it was very entertaining John Sergeant got thrown off the show
Yeah, he resigned or left or whatever
So they covered that one up
And not that this matters in anyone's life
It's just to show you how complacent the public is
When you're being screwed right before you're very eyes
Or what we actually complain about is opposed to the real crimes that are going down
So now what happened last Saturday is no one got voted off
All three couples went through to the next round the reason why
It was kind of complicated, let me see
I'll read it to you
The problems encountered on Saturday show occurred when there was a tie between dancers
Lisa Snowden and Rachel Stephens following the judges scoring
Okay, so the first was the judges scoring then the audience gets to vote
Because of the way the points were then awarded
Actor Chambers and Partner Camilla Dalarib
Could not have been saved from the dance off
Regardless of how many public votes he had received
And that was considered to be unfair by the show's producers
Unfair
So obviously that's you know there's something going on there
Just like the the X factor the UK version had their finals
They're big finale on
I guess that was was it Saturday night?
Yeah, I think it was Saturday night
And see had three three finalists
You had a group called JLS
You had some young kid
It was kind of cute but very young like 15 years old or whatever
And you had like another with Leona Lewis like clone
And so they got to sing with the superstar of the three sets they each did
And so the kid sang with a crap
I don't remember I don't remember who he sang with
The group sang with boys on and the girls sang with Beyonce
Hello Beyonce a duet with Beyonce
Yeah, do you think that that would be a shoe in for the winner?
I mean come on
And then at this BBC thing
1800 people complained
They felt they were ripped off
Hey, I got news for you
You're getting really ripped off by your government
For hundreds of billions
If not truly
And all people please wake up
Let's see what else we have on the on the drop for today
I'm more about censorship in Australia
Gosh man
And they in the UK they just announced that as well
That they're going ahead
British telecom is going to install that form thing
P-H-O-R-M, pop a hotel Oscar Romeo, Mike form which is
Head-end ISP based filtering and insertion of advertising
It's supposed to be opt-in but
Well, we'll have to see
Have to see what happens with that
I'm getting a BT pipe
Obama still me it's stimulus could reach one trillion dollars
Hmm
Oh, this is a nice one cervical cancer vaccine
Paralyzes 12 year old girl yet no kidding
From the times let's see mystery illness 12 year old school girl has been left paralyzed
From the waist down by a mystery illness
No mystery to the chuckleheads
A mystery illness that came on 30 minutes after she was given the new anti cervical cancer jab
Oh, yes
Ashley Cave suffered
Suffered dizziness and headaches
Soon after the vaccination under school and then deteriorated rapidly collapsing several times over the following days
A week later she was admitted to hospital after losing all strength in her legs
And two months later there's been no improvement
Horrible
Ah, this is so horrible
Please don't just inject your kids with anything
Do a little bit of research
Please please please
Another link about the US Marines to set up sobriety checkpoints in California
There's more about Pasi coming Tata
Of course, let me just check the second page
You guys are still doing about seven pages a day of information
And whoever does the the links with the pictures
I like that very cool highly appreciated
Argentina's coin scarcity leads to elicits
Numerismatic trade
I don't even want to look at that
I can't even pronounce the word while I look at the story
Food banks turn to farmers fishermen and grocers as manufacturers have less surplus to give
Oh, let's see, that's a Yahoo story from associated press
California commercial fishing boats donated 260 pounds of rockfish this month
Food banks running out of food
There's no joke
California running out of money
Peels court case brought in at freedom
Okay, more about the bailouts
Boy, oh boy
And of course, and I did mention this on no agenda
Lisbon Treaty is pretty much adopted now
As the commissioners were essentially handed a bribe by saying, you know what?
If we continue to ram through this Lisbon Treaty, which is all legalese to further the agenda of one world government
And as far as I'm concerned, pretty much set up and orchestrated for the financial new world order
And make no mistake, they're calling it that openly
This is not a, you know, I'm allowed to say this now
Looking at time mags in here all of these links to be found in the show notes
A daily source code dot com crossposts that are curry dot com
Obama's new world order
There it is, that's a title of the article
With him, President elect Barack Obama with his national security team at the news conference in Chicago
The new world order
It's no joke, it's here
And you may think it's great, but I prefer to have some kind of sovereignty across nations
I kind of like different cultures
You know what, it just kind of makes me feel good
All right, everybody, time to get out of here
One more song
To take you into the rest of the week, and I hope to do another show
But you never know
So cherish what you got
To love and love, baby, baby, baby, baby
To love and love, baby, baby, baby
Right, right, right, right, right
When I was here, I played it hard, fast, night, and everything
Walk the way, walk the way, walk the day
I'm lazy, coming, easy, coming, easy, coming away
So I hate, I'm a little, let me go, hate, I'm a bitch, get me go
Let me know, let me know, let me know, let me know
Let me know, let me know
I won't believe what I make, start a full loosen
I got no small screen, I hold you in the bread
Let them print out, no, no
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you
What's your love and love, baby?
Hey, hey, hey, baby, hey, baby
What's your love and love, baby
I need you, hey, hey, hey
I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't I don't open it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, go on
Baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby
Megan on eight one one daily source code that will be it for today. Keep
stuff coming in at the drop please drop.au slash daily source code love
what you're doing there really makes all the difference. Friday I am scheduled
to go to that once again traveling actually carrying the lady Patricia's
baggage as she will be doing her final episode the live the life grand
finale of pop stars in Holland. So that's why I'm not sure if I'm gonna be
doing it a full bar but get the stuff in there anyway I'm track on all the
time I'm saving all the awesome links and so please utilize your freedom to do
that while it's still last and whatever you do live your life with passion.
Another fine media presentation stick it in your ear.