And he's saying that a debate is now needed on how far Britain should go and identifying
potential offenders, given that some experts believe it is possible to identify future
offending traits in children as young as five years old. We have to find who are possibly going
to be the biggest threat to society and kill them and incarcerate them. You have bad DNA,
you five-year-old child.
It's not a new work for us. We can live in our item whenever they're gone, maybe.
So really, so now we can tell the DNA that you're a bad person.
This is spot for us. We know it. They're going to come from your children.
So this of course is my call once again that I think we need to stand up and protest.
Oh wait a minute, you're not allowed to protest without a license in the UK.
Hmm, I'm sorry. No, no one's interested. I'm certainly ready for it.
Catch you, you bloody shit.
Friends, you will prove that in all of a sudden we have hundreds of people up here with these
t-shirts and then we've been five minutes prone. We all dispersed before the cops can do anything.
You will. You won't have to ask.
You want to rock a roll man? You want to have some fun?
We can never do it.
Live your life with passion and whatever you do while it's still less.
Enjoy your freedom.
Oh, $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need lost digging trees in.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Casting is a matter of curry.
You are listening to a man willing to stand up and say, you work for me.
And then sit back down and wait for the TSA to return his pants.
It's Adam Curry in the DSC 736.
Let me sit back and count away.
See the shit.
Three.
I love my bitch.
I love my lady.
I love myjets.
I love my bitch.
I love mykeepers.
Oh, my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my
Dear I, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh, my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, ooh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, Oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh my dear, oh
I'm in the spin I'm seeing
I'm just shaking
I'm just my cheek
I see the sea
I'm like
I'm not gonna let it down
I admittedly I never expected to hear
Martha and the muffins mash up
But there you have a DJ LaClawn
And wearing a big red mashed up nose
With this one mad
Loved this song
It's called Echo Bitch
I made a spell for you
Echo Keato Oscar
Bravo Inia Tango
Charlie Hotel
Makes sense, not met
Wow
That was
Oh man
That was awesome
And I was thinking
Well, I'm listening to the song
How good is it?
These mashups
It's so good
It really belongs in
Opsol
I have to say
It's under the educational auspices
This is
I think it really has to be considered
Fair use at this point
To mash up songs
Because
Look at what we're introducing
People too
So you heard
Buster Rimes of course
My daughter would recognize
Buster Rimes
She know Martha and the muffins
I don't know for sure
Does she know Echo Beach
Of course the
The original that this was based on
Probably not
Although she is in quite an 80s vibe
These days I heard it
Listening to a lot of 80s tracks
Probably source to seekpod.com
Also in this mashup
Emma Peel of course from the Avengers
And I thought I heard some
Uma Thurmond in there as well
Man, fantastic
DJ LaClawn
You rocking and rolling my brother
Hey everybody
Welcome
This was code episode number 736
Coming to you from a rainy
Guilford
We're on the west side of
G-town in the affluent subversory
Up here in
In the attic
At the curry manner
And
Wow big score yesterday
Yesterday show the story
That I shared with you guys
About
The director of
Forensic Sciences for the
Scotland Yard's name is Gary
Well it's
It's built
Pop a uniform golf hotel
So it's either pew
Or
I think I'll keep it
Pa
I just got to read this again
He is the new DNA spokesman
I'm sorry
Along with
The new
My director
No he is the new DNA spokesman
For the Association of Chief Police
Officers
Said that a debate was needed on how far
Britain should go and identifying
Potential offenders
Given that some experts
Believe it is a possibility to
Identify future
Offending traits in children
As young as five years of age
So this of course
In my mind
Is nothing different
From cameras
Looking for suspicious
Behaviour
Or turning each other
Against each other
To seek you out
And make sure that
If you're acting suspicious
That you're reported
And for people like me
Who in general
I'm just not likeable
Guys
This is very scary business
So the whole idea of
Thought crimes
Coming in
Not just a thought crime
But a genetic
Possibility that you will
Actually commit a crime
Is an outrageous thought
Even the lady Patricia went off on this one
And she's all four
Millions of cameras looking at us
Let me just see if I can find
Another one of these nice nuggets
From this article here
Where was it?
A recent report here
From the Think Tank Institute
Public Policy Research
Called for children to be targeted
Between the ages of five and twelve
With cognitive behavioral therapy
Parenting programs
An intensive support
Prevention should start young
It's said
Because prolific offenders
Prolific offenders
Typically began
Offending between the ages of ten and thirteen
So if we identify them young
We can still shape their minds
So you can imagine I got some feedback
On this puppy
Some good ones too
I'm just waiting here
Just a little thought
I told you anything
I was just finally got a little pasted
I mean I should be shutting myself up
But just a little question
Did I have five girls
In terms of the professor really
You know, screaming about four times
I think each other would tend to
Really need to be locked up
We need to do a post five year old
Analysis on your Chris laden
I think you should be eliminated
From society
You are clearly a horrible five year old
Stabbing each other with pencils
Indeed
Showing behavior, refusal, criminal
You must be put to death
That they can't be
Any genetic trait that says
The five year old
Is going to become a criminal
You know, the next adult Hitler
There's nothing they can say
That because surely
And research shows again and again
The game is psychology
And psychiatry
The thing is
It's surrounding the nature of you
I'm not saying you do ethics
I mean, there is something the same
In this case
I don't think Louzo wrote
His arm art and children
But that's fucked up
That's fucked up
That's really fucked up
Thank you
My name
Now I Chris
Chris is a university by the way
Smart kid
Yeah, he's podcasting
His way to university
Apparently
The money we pay him is actually
Helping him out
So proud of that
And I appreciate the feedback
There Chris
Yeah, but you know, this is very much like
Well, life imitates aren't often right
Who sent this to me Mike Felderboro
I said he was listening to the show
Yesterday about the DNA testing of five year olds
And you said it may be think of a couple of movies
In particular
A movie I watched a couple of months back
I guess at some point this is what will happen
To inferior or bad DNA
I've seen this movie
It's called Gatica
Gatica is a very futuristic
It's kind of tough to get through
Unless you're really stone
Or really into it
But it's exactly this man
Because the next piece
It's just like you write
Just like Adolf Hitler
Is to brand people who have
Inferior quality or inferior DNA
He did that of course with the
The star of David
And later in concentration camps with tattooed numbers
Mike also goes on to say it
Reminds me also the beef of endeta movie
Where the government doesn't work for us anymore
Yeah, of course
We've talked about that movie in great detail
You're absolutely right Mike
I'm right there with you
It's life imitating art
That's what's going to happen next
I'm telling you this is just so
This is the cameras
We're so used to it
I guess no one's really jumping up and down
Too much to do something about it
Although do I do have a call
Coming up in a moment
But even James
Who was pretty much
Telling me that I should shut up
No one's watching us
I mean James
If you don't believe the cameras are watching us
And trying to catch us doing bad things
How do you feel about
This DNA testing
And please James
Don't sugar code
Adam, James
Um
I'm cute
We all got you
Logo whatever he is
The DNA
You can fuck right off
He's not a make it stay in it
But not a chance
Um
Sure
The wood is a bad
Get people are pretty supposed to crane
Um
This is mostly I don't know you've listened
And I'll make some red freaking on this
People are pretty supposed to crane
Because they're all free
So nobody's going to be in front of me
Before you completely destroyed barrens
Bangwood
Or did you got his DNA
Or did you got some scruffy little oik
Where next people's bikes
When he's 12
They can fuck right off
Then I might get to the DNA
Show me a spike
Alright James
Well that's
That's my point kind of you know
It's like
What's the difference between the government
Saying that they can actually tell if you're bad
Because of your DNA
Or what's the difference between that
And um
Let's see
Them lying about going to Iraq
They certainly fooled America
Fooled the United Kingdom
Didn't they?
How about global warming
Are you absolutely sure?
Absolutely 100% sure
That what they say is happening is actually taking place
Or is there some ulterior motive behind that
Maybe money
To fund all kinds of green projects
And by the way
You don't hear much about that
These days not the economy is shit
Because the central bankers are tanking everything
Taking money out of your pocket
Saving their own hides at your expense
How about cameras?
Well you know he looked kind of
He had a backpack on you know he looks suspicious
And so we shot the fucker five times
What's the difference?
What is the difference I ask you?
These people work for us in the government
All governments but since I'm here in the UK
Let's talk about the British government
They work for us
They need to listen to us
Look at our neighbors
Across the water
Look at the French
When they don't agree with something
They let it be known
You know
They've taken the violent route
It does seem to work
I don't think we need to do that
I think here in Britain we are
Despite what the French may think
I think we are more sophisticated
But perhaps we've taken it a bit too far
Perhaps we're a little bit too proper
I think we need to make a stand
This is out
Effing Rages
Who is to say that this DNA stuff
Really works that you can really prove
That someone is going to be
Well
I mean
A criminal
Sex Offender
You know
And then they start putting that in your documentation
On your IDs
Right
The National ID card
That is a huge debate here in the United Kingdom
All it takes is just
One little
Checkbox on the paperwork
And it says
Well, it could be a future criminal
In fact, I gave this to put this example to Patricia yesterday
I said
You watch
I guarantee you
In our lifetime
You will see the following happen
You will see
Because when we moved here
I said no credit cards
No mobile
You know
Prepaid only
I want to live off the grid as much as possible
Well
So what does she do?
She goes out she gets a nectar card
Now for those in the UK you know what a nectar card is
A nectar card essentially
Forces you
Into using it
Because they'll give you all kinds of great discounts
As long as you continue to use the nectar card
And what happens is it's a loyalty card right
So upon checkout
And she uses it almost exclusively
It's saying spares
Where we do a lot of our big shopping
And so she'll plunk it down
Just before she pays
And it affects the amount of the bill
And it can be
10, 20
Sometimes it's you know 30 of 40 pounds off of the bill
It's an amazing amount of money
You say
If you don't use it of course
You don't get those discounts
And my wife is fruit
Well she loves discounts
She loves a bargain
But what she's not really
Realizing is it's a trap
It's a system where they continue to look at what you're buying
And they make sure you come back for the best price to buy it
With that
Now that's all fine
So the next step of course
Is that they somehow this data
And I think we have a couple examples
Here in the UK of data getting this place lost
Or just mishandled
Carelessly mishandled
But it could even be an official thing
The government could say
If whatever reason tomorrow
They wake up and say okay
Nector Card owners
We need all of your data
And here's what I guarantee you
We will see happen
In our lifetime
They will say you know what
We've noticed that you've been buying too many fatty foods
So we're going to up the premium on your insurance
Because well Mrs. Curry
We know you have a pre-existing heart condition
And you know the insurance company is not happy
With you not taking care of yourself
So now all you have to do is just start buying some better foods
And then we'll maybe lower the rate again
I guarantee you we're going to see that in our lifetime
My friends you heard it here first
Just like I predicted 100 dollar barrel oil
This is going to happen in our lifetimes
Bob is stepping up
Bob was really the guy who got everything going
What a round episode seven twenty seven twenty one
I think so a couple weeks ago he's back
And he's got some manners mind
He was also by the way responsible for the opening of today's chart
Hey Adam further to our recent conversation
And also the correspondence you've had in from other listeners
You're quite right or they're quite right
It is in fact illegal to protest in this country
So what I suggest we do is we have a fashion awareness campaign
Yes
I think we should have t-shirts
It's really available for people to download and print
In any format they should see fit
And make a contribution to amnesty international
I'm going to set a website up where people can access t-shirt designs
Which our Frankie says you work for us
And I think they should download them
And get them printed as many times they like
And distribute them amongst their friends
For occasional gatherings at well-known places
Such as behind celebrities
Behind politicians during photo sessions
I'd like you to get the message across that way
But as I say only on condition that people make a contribution
To something like amnesty international at a time
Hey hey Bob
Can't we set up a store at like cafe press or something
And then because I saw the designs he made they're really good looking
And although Frankie says it's kind of overplayed
It is a throwback to the 80s
We're all children of the 80s who are actually interested in this I believe
So I think it's appropriate
We could set it up that way
I think you can even set up how money is distributed
So have a look into that
I think it's a great idea
So we don't actually have to go through the hassle of finding a way to print them
But just have that printed on demand
I think cafe press does it
Let's check and see if we have a good supplier for that here in the UK
I think it's an awesome idea and I love your designs man
I'm the apprenticeship
I think that's only fair
Of course they're standing up for our human rights
Which I think is pretty well the only people who are these days
Moving on to your other subject of your accountancy situation and tax
I'm unsure that you're aware of the new law that came in on the 17th of December of last year
Yes, anybody in this country who's self-employed in whatever format
Has to be audited once every three years by their accountant
Now what does that mean?
In real terms the accountant is doing the England revenues job
And they are seeing if you can afford your lifestyle
So wait a minute
That's a hidden tax right there
A hidden tax
Thank you for pointing that out Bob
Yes ladies and gentlemen, all self-employed people listening to this
Once every three years your friend little accountant has always been on your side
Will be asking you to provide your personal statements
Your personal bank balances your personal cards, your points cards
And they will work out whether you can afford to live in that house
Whether you can afford to drive that car
And if you can't they are under law
Required to let the inland revenue know and put you on the naughty list
They course of course can't let you know that you're on the naughty list
But you will be not only that
And this is their good part
They reckon they're going to charge you at the 750 pounds for the privilege
Yes indeed we are going to be paying an additional 750 pounds on top of our normal accounting bill
So that the accountant can look at us in greater detail
And apparently the chartered Institute of Accountants
Recon that the accountancy will make more money out of that charge
Then they will out of the average self-employed or business persons
Accountancy bill
So I'll leave you with that happy thought
And remember Frank he says you work for us
Hell yeah
Get us that up dude
Let me know where we can
Where we can find
Either the downloadable art
Or let's see if we can get a whole t-shirt front to back process going
I'll promote the hell out of it
I promise you
And then of course you need to find a great domain name for that
And I suggest you use my code
DSC3
It'll buy us a year's worth of that domain name
At godaddy.com
You can find the links for that in the show notes at daily source code
Of course
Oh man Bob fantastic
Yes you work for us indeed
I think we need a little breather here from this topic
I got another really good one coming up
And actually I have a real nice gem for you
Once in a while you'll stumble across an old photo album
I mean like really old not like five years old
But really really old
And what I have for you now I think
Is about 30 years old
I don't know the exact release date
But I do remember that
I do remember that
When this song
Not when it was written but when it was recorded
I don't
No, in fact I'm quite sure I was under the age of 16
Now I come from an interesting family
And my two sisters I'm sure they're listening to this now
They'll be laughing when I say that
The musical influences in the early days in the curry household
We're pretty much determined by
Well I've talked to you about the real-to-real tape recorder that we used to have
And what was on that
But my father also played guitar
Six ring guitar, 12 string guitar and mandolin
Not extremely well I'd have to say
And the songs were all kind of like really throwback hippies, tunes
But he wrote this one song
Which he would play over and over and over again
And even when we had friends over to the house
He picked up the guitar and he played the song
Which he wrote himself
And we'd always laugh about it
You know it's
And I think recently it Christmas
We probably even laughed about the song
We all know it front to back
Completely by heart
So this is as I said it's 30 years old
This song I can't remember exactly how it came to pass
But the song that my dad wrote
Did get recorded
And I remember quite distinctly driving
We were on our way back from somewhere
Like maybe a Sunday and there was a program
I think it was either a jazz or a country in western
Kind of like a hybrid radio program
When the Netherlands really only had a couple
Public broadcast stations
And the band performed this live
On one of these shows
And I remember we were in the car on our way back from somewhere
And my dad had timed it out and he turned on the radio
And I think that even mentioned that it was written by him
Quite recall but I remember there was like
Wow man they're playing a fracking song on the radio
And it actually sounds pretty good now that you're not seeing it
So Bob is my mom's second husband
He's at my mom passed away year and a half ago
Yeah, how long ago has it been?
Seems like just recent yet ages ago
That's kind of weird anyway
He was cleaning out some stuff in the house
And he came across the vinyl album
That contains this song
And so he and Bob's got some skills man
He got it
I think he digitized it
I don't know if he did or if Willow did my sister
Anyway, we saw Willow sent it out yesterday
To a family email
And it just cracked me up
And even Patricia you know I was playing it upstairs
And she'd never heard the song
Of course she's heard me referencing or seeing a couple of bars
And she went oh my god
That's the song
So this is a true
A true entry to the soundtrack to my life
And I'll tell you this about the song
It was the first
Although it's real a shit kicker music
The lyrics to this song
It was the first song that made me realize
That a song could also really have an important message
And this one has a great message
Even today when you if you
Listen to Obama speech the other day
This message will hit home for you
It's it's true Americana
It's true shit kicker music
It's titled Blood Brother written by Jay Curry
Performed by Luke warm water
Check it out y'all
Nice transfer
Here we go
We're gonna go
We're gonna go just to Georgia
But daddy hit him on
He had to work for you hard all day
But I never done a song
Like every other country
And it goes every trace
Made them through the word and even the other piece
They're placed
Blood Brother
Now they'll need it some memories
My name is now a part of me
When my family always went to war
When it went to David Cole
Found a 70 and a half years ago last fall
I didn't mind apartheid
And it carried it in the past
But it never could be these tears
So I didn't do this black
Blood Brother
Now they'll need some memories
A morning is not part of me
Blood Brother
A night is not part of me
Hanging behind
Listen, watch me
A day is not part of me
Bulman is no man
Blood Brother
A day is not part of me
F
I'll give up carrot
Blood Brother
Another day is not part of me
Now I'm back here in Georgia and she starts to be here.
But I'm so glad I came tonight to save these words to you.
You can't tell by a skin color if a man is better good.
So everybody get together now and live in Brotherhood.
The world is the most beautiful world.
The war water, blood brother and how man.
Isn't that awesome?
It's not wonderful that unlike a photo album we can actually share that.
And of course what you're hearing here is a clear example of the values that were instilled
me as a young child. And for all of all the things we dislike about our parents, I have to
say this one is high on the list of awesome things. Probably unknowingly, honestly my dad was
probably going for a blockbuster smash in a country music award. But I think what it really
did that are all these years has influenced and absolutely influenced and motivated myself and my
sisters in a certain direction in life and a certain look on life. And I think it's a really
beautiful thing and I'm really happy I was able to play that for you. Now let's talk about some
shit, Charlie. Let me say I get a little bit of music here because it's a rather long comment,
but it'll be worth it. This is, um, hold on. Remember I got an email from, uh, I told you about this,
an email from Libby. I'm just looking for it here in the, uh, in my system working well. Okay, here it is.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, I can't seem to find it. That's kind of weird. Anyway, um,
hold on. This is bumming me out. I'm sorry to be able to find this. Okay, I can't. Anyway,
this was about alcohol and Britain and Libby responded and she is uh,
she's a consultant and she's actually working for the government on coming up with strategies on what we
can do about teenage binge drinking and of course I say it goes all the way back to the core.
We have to find out why people are so incredibly unhappy in doing this and that she sent me
response as requested. So, uh, let me just, uh, let me just set it up here. I did something incredibly
stupid. Well, uh, it will turn that one down a bit. And let's listen to, uh, Libby, hold on. Here's
you come. Hello, Adam. This is Libby Renzetta, calling in to follow up the email that you mentioned,
um, on DSC 724, where I wanted to talk about alcohol and, uh, sorry, it's taking me so long to,
to call in, but I can't keep up with all the shows you're doing this week. Um, yes, I wanted to pick
up on some of the things you've been saying about alcohol recently, but also to ask a favor for me.
So, you've been saying that, um, you don't agree that putting the price up of alcohol is,
it's the way to tackle some of our problems in this country and that we should tackle the root causes.
Uh, and of course, um, that's right, you know, everyone would agree with that, but I think it's,
it's quite difficult to do it because we do have, um, a culture drinking to get drunk in this country.
And we have done for a long time. I think it's not just the UK that I think it's, um,
in common with some of the northern European countries, which is why some funds gets blamed on
the climate. Um, but there's no doubt that we do have particular problems at the moment. Uh, you know,
we've seen death by a liver cirrhosis double in the last 10 years, and, um, the mainstream media
is, is talking every day. It seems about, um, problems with young people drinking and getting into
trouble. Actually, I think young people get, um, I'm fairly picked on and demonised if you like,
because, um, adults are just as bad and I'm sure the young people are taking their cue from the rest of us.
You know, the statistics are just that, um, 30% of adults are drinking more than they should,
and that one in 20 of us is actually dependent on alcohol. So these are huge numbers,
and we're not setting a very good example for young people. But in terms of what we should do about it,
to tackle the root causes, if you like, I think, um, you might not like your price prices,
a factor. Um, but for me, the big factor that's missing at the moment is some kind of credible
health message about alcohol, and what we do to ourselves when we do drink too much, because the
the recommended sense will limit for adults and drinking. It actually quite low, and I think
a lot of people just don't feel incredible. So, um, I don't know if you're familiar with the
concept of units of alcohol, but, um, but the recommended, uh, limits of women are two to three
a day and for men three to four. You know, so if you take, um, a bottle of wine these days,
we've got nine or ten units in it. If a, if a blox is going to drink half a bottle of wine,
he's already exceeded his daily recommended limits. And I think it's a lot of people that just
doesn't seem credible. You know, we need really decent messages about drinking more than
doing to us physically. Um, I'm sure plenty of people out there won't be strangers to
drinking a whole bottle of wine in one go. Uh, we just don't know what damage that does. That's
our other than a mild headache the next day. So this brings me on to the favor I want to ask, Adam,
there's so much going on in alcohol policy at the moment. The government have finally tweaked
that there are probably some votes in trying to do something about alcohol. So I think it's where
we've seen the, the price rise. Uh, the chances to put up the duty on on alcohol, having frozen
the duty on spirits for the last 10 years of this labor government. It seems to be a completely
opportunistic way to, to raise some money rather than a genuine attempt to tackle drinking. But
anyway, that's another matter. The government are doing lots of things, good and bad. And there's
also lots of things happening in the field that are, that are very interesting. And I think what we
could really do with is a good podcast to bring the field together and inform and energise
an exciting people. And if I had to go it doing this, but I realised that I really need a good
producer to help me. And so I wondered if that's something you could help me with, help me find a
producer to do this show. And if anyone out there's interested, I can be contacted on my blog,
WWW, so I'll call policy.net, and it'd be really fantastic to hear from someone. Okay, so that's
it. Adam, thanks very much. Love you, hope you're in, et cetera. Cheers.
Libby, thank you so much. And I did find her email just to complete that. She runs England's
leading consultancy organization advising local government on alcohol harm reduction. She goes on to
say, business is booming, but it isn't bringing about the changes I want to see fast enough. So here's
someone who actually cares and wants to make something happen. And apparently it's making a living
at it as well. So it just goes to show. There is a role for high quality podcasts to update the
field about what's happening, what works and to bring new people on board. I could not agree more.
So there you go, Libby. I hope it works out. Please keep me informed us to, uh,
that's the progress and we'll keep tabs on that as time goes on. He listened to daily source code
episode number 736. I got to stay in kind of the shit kicker mode. This time for the pod save music
network. I really love the lyrics. Billy Burman is the wine of her lips.
She wants to see me one more time. I didn't want her, but I guess I'd have a good life. I
did to do the wine of her lips. Wine of her lips. She's got lips, tastes like wine. She's beautiful.
It'll survive. I want her to be a husband with wine of her lips. The wine of her lips come on.
What is this over? What the hell? I guess it's all just as well.
The members of the major, the force you've had in the wine of her lips. The wine of her lips.
All the violin received again. I wonder what she meant, but there was still a great dance.
Maybe some time before the end, I'll taste the wine of her lips. The wine of her lips. She's got lips,
tastes like wine. She's beautiful. It'll survive. I want her to be a husband with wine of her lips.
The wine of her lips come on.
Whether there is intent or what I do tommorow that doesn't lie.
Maybe some time before the end, but one more time before the end.
That's all has happened, it'll survive. I've got her to be a husband of her lips.
I want her to be a husband with wine of her lips. The shinning is the of her lips.
Just before sheUNFLU, it'll be a pain of her lips of sheUNFLU.
Well, this document is still Toto Mahneve's case, I said I'll be free from roots
and because I have no idea who the person was before the end, it'll be okay for a moment.
Why the lips?
The wine of this
Why the lips
Why never
Feeling burdened for the outside music network you'll find a link to
His music in the show notes a DailySource code calm the wine of her lips
Hey, you know, I want to thank everybody for participating and contributing to the show
You have no idea how incredibly important it is every single morning when I'm doing a program, of course
Of course, when I'm doing the show prep, it's really what you guys send me.
You know, it's the song suggestions.
It's the artists who contribute their music to the positive music network.
It's the master's and the master's doing the mashups.
It's the voicemail comments.
It's the recorded bits.
It's all of that put together.
It's the emails that's everything.
So I really appreciate it.
I'm just driving.
All right.
That's all I'm doing.
You guys are filling this puppy up with fuel, and it is highly appreciated.
So tomorrow, Fubar Friday, you know the drill.
You got to send me all of the tunes.
I really want to rock it out.
I'm going to be home all day.
So I think it's a good Friday tomorrow.
So let's make it a great Friday.
So of course, I would remind you that the most important thing you can do to be happy is to live your
life with passion.
And while it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Thank you.