This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Here's a man whose hair needs more than three ounces of shampoo.
Adam Curry.
Delta Sierra Charley.
726.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I like to think I'd fly into the future.
I have to think I'm flying into the future.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I like to think what I'm flying into the future,
I like to think I'm flying into the future,
I like to think I'm inversing into the future.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
condo in San Francisco, Northern California. It is Wednesday evening 830 p.m. and it's time
once again to roll out daily source code, lots of stuff happen in apologies for kind of a
confused because I did, I did the show Monday night and I carried over into Tuesday of course
that would be a Friday for those of you living in Australia and I wanted to do a show
yesterday and I just came home last actually I had dinner with John Devourack. You know this is my
eating buddy and so we went to it's it's crazy I'll tell you something. We'll probably talk about it
on Friday. We said yeah actually we're walking out of the office together and I said hey man
are you alone here because his wife is up in Seattle and his family is up there during the week.
He said yeah yeah so well have you eaten and let's go eat together so okay so we did actually
pre-plan this time and so we're driving and he says let's go to our place and I was like
holy crap that's kind of scary. We have a place together I don't know if I liked that.
So I was good and we had a real nice talk all kind of in preparation for cranky geeks which was
tape today it's also a stream's live and I thought it was pretty good show actually I enjoyed
myself thoroughly actually what was interesting is the comments already they were like 20 or 25 comments
for the episode and somehow people picked up on you know they think there was some tension
between Leo Leport Leo Leport the chief twit was also on the show with Sebastian Roopley who
of course is the shill of the show and a lot of people thought that the Leo and I didn't get
a long and I was like and I read the comments before I viewed the show and then I just looked
at the whole show and I can see and this is how interesting first of all you know we're on the
show to entertain right so you want to have some kind of fire and some kind of sparks and
one stuff going but there was this one segment where I think just because you know they cut
one camera to me one camera to Leo and just the way it looked and on quite honestly the way I was
looking I think that you could misconstru that as perhaps some kind of bad vibe but nothing could
be further from the truth we love and respect each other and I one day I hope to have a place to go
eat with Leo wouldn't that be lovely not be just fantastic once again we're on the on the live set
up on the live system so this means that I've got my new my new setup completely in place which
I'm quite happy with I really loved in fact he does sent me a note he's pretty much he's pretty much
my my thermometer when it comes to the sound and how everything's working and if the levels are
right on and he's got a great set of ears on his head and he gave me some kudos he said it was
it was pretty much spot on so it was very happy with that all of the crackling and all that crap is
gone and this funny because I showed John DeVore how my setup worked and he said that I have a
patentable process he says you can write a patent for this and I like I don't want to write no
damn patent I got the time for that crap he said no you know what I'll write the patent we'll share it
it's okay don't deal let's share this patent I love it hey by the way those of you who have called
into talk show please don't send me messages on Skype okay if you want to participate in the show
and if you if you have something to say about one of the topics then all I'd like you to do is just
kind of raise your hand and and let me know if you want to come in on one of the topics what you
have to do is you have to call into the talk show system so a lot of you I can see there's tons
of people here right now who are just listening in which is cool not a problem welcome to it but
if you want to say something you got to call in so I follow the instructions you have to call
in you to pin number etc so and if you want to chime in on a topic then just type it into the
chat room say hey I want to talk about something so for example if you want if you saw cranky geeks
and you want to say something about the show now would be a very appropriate time because I'm just
filling up this space waiting for someone to say yeah I got something to say so it's not happening
that's okay so that's how that's how it's going to work and of course we also have
are okay well okay TD enterprises saw cranky geeks TD
TD you there excellent that's exactly how I didn't want it to work
I don't think Skype works too well you got no sound okay good forget about it we're going to
move on to the first pre-taped call hey Adam it's Walt Snyder for a letter Dale I'm the one that
sent you the rubber glove intro that you use the what slide I think so anyway I noticed that
it really sounds like you could use the call stringer to make sure that these guys don't talk
yeah like this just a thought otherwise I like where you're going and maybe if you have a
some sort of schedule we can all show up at the right time and be there otherwise I really don't
know when to show up and be on pop shoe to talk with you all right well what's the show
of you mean it no homo great here and not smoking and there's my phone bye
oh my thanks well yeah of course I'd love to have a call screener but kind of the whole point
and this is part of the whole process is to be able to do it all myself to have basically a
pre-screened process which means you guys are in the chat room you're saying stuff and
and if I think it's interesting or if it's something that you know that belongs in the program
as a part of the topic then I'll just pull you right in obviously it would be great to be able to know
if someone actually has sound if they you know if they can to speak coherently but you know I
just don't have that set up of course we could have here's an idea oh man I just duh I just
came up with it why not um one of you guys be the screener because you're basically all sitting in there
you can all talk to each other right now I have everyone unmuted so we could have a call screener
in the in the chat room and you could send me separate messages through well through different
chat system even you could send me a private message to Skype and say okay you want to talk to
this guy he's got something good to say so this is something we all participated in we obviously
don't have it set up for today but let's work on that in the future let's get a couple of people
in the chat room and on the conference call who can do who can do some call screening and of course
is not just about people who are on the call it's about my savants around the world we love them so much
comic strip no CSB come on in buddy this is really interesting and I do want to talk
about this I love that you know I I really wish we had some people who knew more about this
because cost of oh declared independence and you know now there's the the serves who hate the
I guess the former Bosnians it's very very confusing to me and it's all under this umbrella of
well of course we had a very bloody messy scenario over there not it in just a few years ago really
just recently lots of people died horrible horrible destruction of the countries there and all
within you know my plane could fly there and almost on one tank a gas you know so it ain't all that far
it would be nice to know what's really happening I have a feeling that this is about oil
and it's probably about pipelines running through different geographic regions and I'm sure Russia
has a lot to do with it and I just like to I'd just like to understand more so more on that CSB please
last week I was in Barcelona in doing myself which is located in Catalonia in Spain and on
on license plates in of course I have noticed a C-A-T cat and not E a Catalonia usual in Spain so both
Catalonia and Basque country regions in Spain wants to live Spain so no wonder that six EO countries
are not recognizing cassava so fuck whatever I like you I don't know you see I got some good news
for your comic strip blogger I had a chat today with the illustrious Andrew Grummit and I said hey dude
would you like to be a celebrity in Poland and he said I get laid I said yeah man absolutely all you
got to do all you all you got to do my friend is put an RSS feed into the pod show comments and
you will truly be the hero of comic strip blogger and all that is Polish and all who live in Germany in
one RSS feed for their comments
still lots of people confused about my problems entering the United States
I do not have a TSA problem yes they are part of the homeland security administration
but it is actually the guys with the guns who keep stopping me and give me secondary screenings
those who work for the customs and border patrol so I just want to say one more time because
questions like this although interesting aren't completely relevant you add I'm Christmas
town just heard your first live broadcast is pretty neat and that's right you didn't want to
question for you about the TSA what happens when you try to fly within the United States
like from a US location to a US location the others you get this empty and flag when you come
to customs but what happens if you fly it gets a date it'd be interesting to see if you're
any kind of list that way to see it so that's it is a very good question because I have
absolutely no problem as far as I know and I'm going to be flying to LA I think on Tuesday we've
got a couple meetings in the city of angels which I always look forward to I must say I do
enjoy visiting Los Angeles I'd hate to have to live there and so I don't think I'll have any
probably haven't had any previous problems with flying but if they're truly is and you know of
course now I have the information I know that there is an Adam Curry there looking for with his
birth date similar or exactly the same to mine as mine the evil Adam Curry as it were
you probably wouldn't want that guy flying domestically either so there I think there is a
disconnect between what the customs border protection agency is using as information and what
the TSA uses and of course they are the exact same department or they belong to the exact same
department so I'll let you know flying to Los Angeles I think it's Tuesday so we'll find out
if that works or not thank you all very much by the way for sending in links to what you
think might be the evil Adam Curry we did actually find let me just bring up the browser here
for a second boy do I miss my second screen I gotta get that set um here it is uh pop pop pop
um Eric Elliott one of the people who sent me this uh link you probably already started googling
and found out some info but I found this Adam Curry who lives in Colorado apparently went to
college in Nebraska I look at that guy he's at Adam Curry dot net and I don't think it's him there's
another guy that people found and I can't find the message off hand I know I saved it somewhere
and I gotta say he has a my space page I'll see if I can find the link and if I can't um someone
please post it in the comments um he looks like an evil dude his name his name is Adam Curry
it's from the braska he's got like a go-ty and uh and like a will-knit cap on his head and I can't
actually see his profile on my space because uh you have to friend him first and so he has a private
profile um so uh and of course it'd be kind of weird if uh if I show up you know with my my
spy my space profile which of course is Adam Curry and then all of us you know I just don't want
to do that so let's find that link and let's dig into this little bit deeper because this could
be the guy I mean if they're looking for an Adam Curry he looks about my age and he's from the braska
I mean come on this uh there's just no coincidence like that so uh I'd love uh I'd love some help
uh let me see yeah people asking for the link uh all right nothing quite going on I see Ranger
Craig has showed up in the audience that's good um yeah I got this promo I wanted to play for
this show that we started in the UK uh is now really taken off and I have to say I'm not a gamer
but I uh I really enjoy watching the show because it is the simplest of all formats I can't
believe no one has done this before where basically there's uh it's a new show you here are uh
are savant of gaming, matte cuddle talking about the games and we actually show you all the action
in the video it's been number one on iTunes and it's category for uh for a number of weeks now and
it's even climbing up the top 100 charts.
Hi Adam it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show we've got a review of the new
Castlevania game for the PSP we're also slaying some demons with Devil May Cry 4 on the Xbox 360
and you can win copies of Final Fantasy 12 Revenant Wings for the DS that's all the gamesweasel.btpodshow.com
all right thank you.
love this this one showed up in the top 10 of the week on the podcast music now work for
pod plays it's the dirt white boy remix on the Charlie
white shirt black front white skirt black out coat black front white skirt
we don't顯
oh
What time is it still to your turn now?
Red lip, what time is it still to your turn now?
I'm gonna be there
You're too crazy
Whatever
I'm calling you back
You're too crazy
That's a bear born here, that's a bear
That's a bear
Down here, that's a bear
No hair, down there, no hair
Don't love it, maybe a little hair down there
Swoop
You're too crazy
I'm too funny, I'm too knit
I'm too knit, I'm too knit
I'm too knit
How four is all four?
How four is heart, I'm so new she
I think about you for me
A white shirt, black, a white shirt, black, a white shirt, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black
, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black, black,
We're going to find links to everything and play it on the show.
Of course, at datingsourceco.com.
And if you want to find more cool music, go to podshow.com slash music.
And the pod save music network itself, where you can sign up to get music
for your show under the pod save license, which means you don't have to pay anything.
You just tell, just report back to the network that you played it.
At music.podshow.com.
So we got a pretty full chat room.
We got lots of people calling in.
And Captain Chris from the Plain Madness podcast.
You've got some info on the on the satellite that I guess we're going to shoot it out of the sky.
Yeah, I'm reading it was about 1026 Eastern, which apparently is about an hour and 15 minutes hour.
So I meant to go outside.
Yeah.
And it looks as though they hit it.
They're not sure if it took out the field tank.
Yeah, I know that within about 24 hours.
But they're saying that stuff is supposed to start re-entering in the next one to two days.
That's pretty amazing.
How high up was this thing that they blew it out of the sky with a missile?
Do you know the actual altitude?
Well, I know it was going at about 17,000 miles per hour.
As far as how high it was, I think that's classified.
I don't know.
So that, you know, this is to me is much less about shooting a satellite out of the sky.
And more about, hey, hello, everyone in the world.
We can actually shoot your fucking shit out of the sky at any time we want to.
And it works.
Yeah.
And you know, the Chinese are real tickled.
Why?
Well, they were pretty, I'm excited about the whole thing.
If you gave it, however, they did the same thing with one of their own satellites.
Not too long ago.
And we got a little excited as well.
Now, I read somewhere, Chris, and you're an aviator.
I read somewhere that there was a, a no tan.
There were no tams about this saying, you know, don't fly.
Or maybe even they put up temporary restricted areas.
Or there was a danger area put into place that you're not supposed to fly.
You could hit debris from the plank and to come down.
Do you have any details on that?
Yeah.
I got to be able tonight from a buddy who was, was flying apparently.
And I, I can't remember.
Apparently there wasn't no tams for, for the Pacific Northwest.
And I should just say, I'm sorry.
A no tan is an acronym for notice to airman.
And notoriously, we don't check these things because at the fuck.
You know, we're just going to fly.
But you really should because stuff like this comes up.
So I just want to explain the concept of a no tan.
Yeah.
I see, I can find it as far as, or maybe somebody else is faster access to it than I do.
Apparently, maybe there was one, but it's not, it's not confirmed.
I think it was a NASA originated with NASA.
The no tan, which is, which is, yeah, which is kind of weird.
If you want to understand, well, again, I'm not, I got to figure it out.
Okay.
All right.
So, um, they're expecting if debris would come down to earth, then it would be in the next 24 hours.
24 48, according to the article that I'm looking at right now and everything else should be within the next 40 days.
However, they're anticipating that everything is going to burn up.
So it's right.
I know it's going to reach the ground.
Right. Because it's small pieces.
I also understand, though, that, you know, the real problem is all this debris that's floating around in space.
And if that hits you, even even a, like a, a quarter sized piece of debris.
If you hit that with your spacecraft, uh, that could cause a catastrophe.
Oh, yeah. You have a closer rates of everything in space with, you know, zero drag is, it's unbelievable.
So those, um, there was a, a meteor.
This is another deal that apparently, um, in the last day or two that heard about those a meteor that,
somewhere over Idaho, Montana, and a guy in a light GA aircraft spotted it.
And he spotted the impact as well.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah. I just, I found out about this one today as well.
I, I should've got my, uh, my, uh, ducks in a row for the show here.
But, um, but you'll see, like, they get some more info on that.
They've got, apparently, it's like, five o'clock in the morning.
You guys put them on and it's sesame.
You see the thing and they actually see the hit the ground.
So the, uh, great escape is in the chat room says that, uh, the meteor hit, uh,
Eastern Washington.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Holy crap. So we don't have any reports on that. Yeah, I guess.
And he, anything else that, that, it hit something.
I'll see if you can find something on it.
All right, man. Thank you.
I, uh, I appreciate it.
And you're going to hang around for a while.
If you got anything else, just, uh, just hit me on the chat room and, uh,
I'll bring you in, okay?
Who are you?
Thank you.
All right, buddy. Thank you very much.
I had a nice child who was on London.
I can't be stood outside, uh,
point at MSI, the Astoria, which bet those in London's website.
By the way, this is Charles the, uh,
the Londoner formally known as Charles the drunken Londoner.
Uh, he's not drunk right now, which makes him a lot less funny,
but he's got a lot going on that is pretty smart.
On my way to, uh, go and do my directing day job.
Uh, I've just been into, um,
you know what I don't know what episode.
It is. I'm grateful behind.
Uh, you worked for us.
I mean, you tell me where and when or you want me to get someone to design a
situation, we'll work out how to get him printed.
I'm so in on that.
A lot of flash mobbing.
I get the fan to come this year.
Uh, I think it's an absolute superb idea.
So this is, uh, the idea I had for the UK,
and you're going to hear in the rest of today's show that this is something we should be looking at
worldwide.
Um, that, you know, we need to wake up in the UK and we need to say,
hey, hold on a second, you know, you work for us.
So we need T shirts.
We need to organize flash mobs.
Charles is in.
So he's going to help out with at least part of it.
Uh, I really need someone who's who's good at organizing flash mob to take over that job.
And I'm not going to do any of this.
I'll be happy to propagate and talk about it and promote and take some heat for it,
which I'm sure will come.
Uh, but, you know, the UK residents, UK citizens,
you guys really have to do this.
So Charles is in and he's drunk.
So, uh, help me.
Shake on some of this afternoon.
I feel towards the country.
You have to, you're right.
Uh, the losing is, uh, a symptom of, uh,
the safety of the society.
And, um, yeah, you know, you sort of waking me up a little bit.
I appreciate that.
I don't think you're an asshole, but, uh, I do appreciate all that you do.
Call it a gay guy.
Hey, Charles, man.
I appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
That's for you.
You dick.
Uh, so this is, um,
this awakening from apathy is spreading worldwide.
I can really feel it.
You know, I've got Charles over in the UK, uh,
who pretty much has always despised me and everything I had to say.
And now he's turning around.
He's waking up, which I really appreciate and think is cool.
And now we've got a lot of people think in this way.
And this is a three minute comment,
which actually, I want to play uninterrupted.
I almost considered getting, uh, some God bless America music to play.
I don't need it.
Because, and maybe I'll even look for that while it's playing.
But listen to this because this is, uh,
fellow American citizen who is waking up and is understanding what's going on.
And is seeing the problems and wants to do something about it.
Hey, Adam, hey, this is Mark in Los Angeles.
He called me the Sinnell's Weasel a couple of weeks ago.
Well, that's because you are the sales weasel.
I'm sorry.
I'm free and interrupting.
Look at, you know, I don't want to be long-winded here.
Because I leave you messages, but, uh,
and I know that you get tired of them.
Because a lot of times I'm drunk and I'm talking.
And anyways.
But you know, you know what they say.
Children and drunk people always speak the truth.
One call is correct.
He's absolutely correct.
And I'll even add one more to it.
I've been walking today in Los Angeles.
One of the very few that used the sidewalks.
Here it is, my day off and present this day.
And everybody fucking drives.
The truth of the matter is, and it comes right down to this.
It's oil.
Americans will die for oil.
We prove it over and over again.
That's why we're in the mess we are in right now.
That's why.
We don't ever get away from mental.
And Ron Paul speaks truth.
He asked questions that we need to listen to.
And I don't think most Americans can stomach it.
And I think he's the only only person on the ticket right now for the Republicans
that you have to consider and say why isn't this guy getting a fair shot.
At the end, I hope Obama gets it.
If it's going to not be Ron Paul, but then it just hurts me.
That a man gets up a doctor, a brilliant man who starts speaking something that's precious.
The Constitution.
The reason why we're a country.
Why we have our rights.
And he speaks about it.
And all we're interested in right now is oil.
And it's so sad because at the end of the day, we lost our souls.
We just lost our souls because of this stupid black coal.
And we all want our cars.
We never get to know.
We never walk.
We never get to know our neighbors or friends.
We never get to our roots.
And there's so much more.
I mean, I may be happy too much.
But what can we get to be more?
Why is America settling for 30 years or 31st in education?
Why are we settling for just what we got right now?
You know, healthcare does not have to be a problem.
If we just give our heads out of our asses and start talking to each other.
And now we're going to, yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm just, I do care about this country.
I care about the people that lost their lives over there and overseas.
I care about the best, the patriots.
I mean, but don't they need something more than just a economy that's based on oil?
You know, unfortunately he went past the three-minute mark on the, that's the limitation on the voice mail.
But while man, you really spoke from the heart and I think it really showed and it really,
yeah, that hit me and I really appreciate that.
And you know, those of you who were just listening in right now rewind three minutes.
Listen to that again, listen to what your fellow Americans are saying.
And regarding healthcare, by the way, yeah, of course.
But you know, the problem isn't paying for healthcare.
The problem is the crazy system where it's everything is rigged.
The prices are outrageous.
And you've got, you know, medicare, you've got the government basically doing a no-bid negotiation with the pharmaceutical country companies.
And there's, yeah, oh man, it's, it's messed up.
We got an update, Ranger Craig has more on the, what is it, Craig?
You have information on the satellite or on the media or impact?
I'm in satellite.
I have the satellite hit me man, what's going on?
Well, apparently it was, I'm, and this will launch by the U.S. Navy from the U.S.
Lake Erie, which I grew up on the shores of, we used to call it the great swamp area back in the day.
And it was an EGF satellite and I made a rocket.
And they were concerned about the fuel tank, which apparently contains toxic hydrogen.
They wanted to make sure it didn't come down now.
I can't imagine the fuel tank re-entering in tax, so I wonder about that.
Does the union of concerned scientists group, I generally had some respect for,
and they're a little concerned that this is just basically anti-Satellite test by the defense department?
Yeah, see that? I, I buy that theory.
I, I think it's a, it's a big FU to the rest of the world saying, you know,
and as I just discussed with, with Captain Chris, like, look what we can do.
Hands behind my back and I shot that fuck around this guy.
It's kind of sad to me, too. I grew up with the space program.
I remember watching the first mercury flights on a little black and white TV and stuff and being a big science fiction fan.
You know, you know, we always thought space would be kind of off of limits or help to avoid bad luck.
I guess not. That's made by suppose.
Hey Craig, how's everything going on in the rock man?
Cause you're a range of Craig from, uh, aquatras.
It's great. It's great. Cold and wet here lately.
I'm getting a little break in the names while you were gone.
And now that you're back, it's raining again.
But I know, I see, I seem to be responsible for it.
Holding a cell on the dungeon for you.
So I'll let me know when you get this.
I appreciate, can I, can I, um, do a show from, from the cell in the dungeon?
Do you have any connectivity there?
It can be done.
It's something we have to do officially to our public affairs office.
But yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
What do you call it?
You got connectivity.
Do you have, uh, is there an internet connection?
Um, it's always a government networks.
That's kind of funky because, um, we're not allowed to access things like Skype and stuff.
So that there could be a problem.
But there's ways around that.
We can tap into the phone line raw, um, radio stations and stuff.
I've done it up the media.
Well, theater in the cell house.
We have no theater.
And it was also used as a chapel where it meets, um, went to church and would see a occasional, uh,
uh, very, um, my old movies.
They're very careful about the movies.
They should have had there.
But they should have moved me once a month or so.
All right.
But it's basically a tourist attraction, right?
Yeah.
It's a national park.
So we, uh, I promote it, man.
I do a huge promotion.
You know, we make a big deal out of it.
I think we should stay overnight in the cell.
You know, we'd make something like throw curry in jail or send Adam to get
Mo or something like that.
Uh, and then I'll promote the park.
We'll get lots of people showing up.
If you can work it out, I'll be happy to do it.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
Well, let's talk about it there.
I'll sometimes I get an idea.
Uh, idiotica is, uh, idiotica, you want?
Can you talk?
Have you, uh, you're looking at the evil Adam curry?
Yeah, I am.
And, uh, so, so you just posted a link.
Did you, uh, get into this guy's my space profile?
Yeah.
I think course actually posted that I was just, uh, talking about it.
Okay.
Of course it doesn't have, uh, I can't talk.
So, uh, what does, what does this guy look like?
Doesn't he look like he could be a, a scary terrorist dude?
What is?
Of course there's ages 23 and there's just no way.
He's got a pretty nasty little go-to you going.
I think it's him, man.
That's him.
All right.
Miss something's in Brooklyn.
Welcome.
Good to see you on.
Hi there.
Hey, baby.
How are you doing?
I have some wine tonight.
Oh.
How much wine?
Wait a minute.
How much?
Two glasses?
Two glasses.
That's just a little bit of wine.
That's not so much.
I would just go.
I'm a lightly.
Uh huh.
So you feeling a little woozy right now?
I am.
I wore a fillet.
Are you feeling warm all over?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
How was work today?
How was the advertising business?
Crazyness.
Really?
I was offered a spontaneous promotion and I'm considering it.
Tell me about it.
What's the gig?
Uh a lot to gain a lot to lose.
You know, typical situation.
Okay.
I don't know what to help you talk about.
I find that timing.
What?
Wink or girl is coming to visit tomorrow.
She arrives from Canada.
Oh.
Okay.
I'm excited that my podcasting buddy is in town.
And we'll be cheering up the city and doing our thing.
Well, listen.
Can we do something tomorrow?
If you guys are around, maybe you have some wine together.
And then you call me and then we'll talk about how much fun you're having together.
Sounds like a plan.
And you guys were talking about serious stuff.
And I love that stuff too.
But yeah, we'll be here.
Okay.
I love it.
Women on wine.
There's nothing like it.
You got girls at him.
You got girls.
I wish I had more girls.
I got to tell you.
Um.
I'm not enough.
You know.
The, you know, the data source code survey, which is still up.
I have it permanently in the show note links.
Um.
I got to take that.
Make sure I'm counted.
Well, it seems like there's a 30.
I think it was like 38% or 30% of the women are listeners.
Or the listeners are women.
I'm sorry.
I've had some wine.
Um.
And that's cool.
But, you know, they need to call in.
And.
Preferably.
You have some sexy to say.
You know.
And we will.
Because I'm.
Because you know, I'm your serious.
Yeah, I've been here for a couple days already.
And it's going to be a long couple of weeks.
And I get lonely.
And, you know, when you call up.
You know, you know, I met you in San Francisco.
No, you're kidding.
When?
I did.
We back at a donature gathering probably two years ago.
Oh, the one where the, with the fountain in the, in the lobby is at the place.
I didn't know it was a from far.
I don't remember.
I'm.
My brain is.
My brain is so far.
But I think I accused you of, um, bringing, trying to be into the hood.
And also building up to some bad things.
Uh, I don't remember, darling.
I really don't.
I'm sorry.
That's the right.
Okay.
Oh, hang out for a little bit.
And, uh, we'll definitely talk somewhere tomorrow.
Because like I said, my entertainers.
I'm sorry.
I'm just listening in because this is my entertainment right now.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
Why don't you have another glass of wine.
And, uh, then we'll talk in a couple minutes.
Okay.
Cool baby.
Thank you.
I had a Mr. Dan from Green Rapids, Michigan.
Uh, 41 of the folder.
Um, you mentioned about why don't people get, where's the outrage?
And you mentioned the book in 1984.
Um, in the book in 1984, um, he said the polls.
Which is like the peasants for the people.
We'll never rise up.
And then in the end, um, Winston Smith.
He's, uh, you know, big brother triumphs.
And Winston Smith, the, uh, hero of the story is, uh, he believes he's sitting in a
coffee house, believing all the propaganda.
So that's a bad example.
Um, also as far as a red pill goes.
And then we'll be the matrix.
There's one character, um, who took the red pill.
And then he gets all mad about it.
And says he wishes he had to take in the blue pill.
I think a lot of people are like that.
It's just laziness.
And people just, I'm, I'm part of the problem.
I mean, I mean, I'm in America and it's turned into a police state.
And, um, I'm not doing anything about it.
And I think that's the problem.
Sorry.
Anyway, I love you.
Bye.
You know what, man?
That's not true because you already are doing something about it just by
talking about it.
So don't feel bad.
Awakening takes a little while.
It's not as simple as just taking a red pill.
When you go down the shoot and you pop out the other end.
And now I know what's going on.
Just to let me know.
It's, uh, it takes a little while.
Anyway, man, love you.
Me in at no home.
Hey, Adam.
Just in your hands for you.
I say happy president today.
Oh, sorry.
Obviously, this is a call from a couple days ago.
Yeah.
I got to think in after listen to your last show.
But all the litany of, uh, of, uh, goodbye saying that people haven't.
And it got, the, the, the no-home old thing got me thinking.
And if I was a home of sexual, although I'm not, um, I'm not sure how I feel about that.
I'm not sure that that it would, uh, be,
construed in a positive light or it seems to have a negative connotation.
Like, of course, I'm not, you know.
Guy talk, locker room talk.
I'm sure you got gay listeners, man.
And I'm not sure you want that connotation.
Maybe they, maybe they'd take it differently than I.
But just thought I'd bring that up later.
Well, you know, um, good point.
And now that I've been, actually since I heard this comment and I previewed it before I played it on the air,
uh, you make a good point because if someone was just coming in to, uh,
into the, uh, the chucklehead community.
And you hear that.
And if it's not said in, um, in the right order, if it's not,
love you, no-home, then it's very confusing.
So obviously, it has, uh, it has nothing to do with.
It's, it's a guy thing.
It's for Americans because American guys have problems with telling another man,
they love them without some connotation.
So, you know, we can't, um, hug each other and do what most American males do with
slapping each other really hard on the back.
Yeah, I love your man.
You know, because we got to be a macho.
So this is kind of the virtual version of it is just by saying,
hey, man, love, you know, homo.
But, uh, if you are always not proud, do we have anyone who's gay on the,
in the, um, in the conference call right now?
Can I out anybody?
Okay, that would be a solid no.
And anyone take a fence because it's not mad.
I'll stop doing it and I think you all should stop doing it.
If anyone's taking a fence to it, but I, I don't, I don't think it's a problem.
I hope not.
We can always keep it with great hair.
Love you, mean it, hope you win.
That works for me too.
Hey, miss something.
How you doing?
You done with your next class or wine?
I know I just bored it.
Hmm.
What are you wearing?
I don't know.
You're what?
You're wearing what?
I'm wearing predominant.
Uh-huh.
What kind of pajamas?
Oh, wait, let me guess something.
Are they, um, so you got pajama bottoms and pajama top?
Yeah, I'm simple like that.
I was actually, I will say I was supposed to have a booty call tonight.
And it failed.
You made a booty call and it failed?
It failed.
Boys are so dumb.
You can't get that word.
I said, hey, I got two weeks.
I have a house guest here and you want to meet up?
And there was some work thing.
So who is this guy?
Is he living the city?
Is he living Brooklyn?
Good question.
He lives in Jersey and he contracts.
So he's in the city during the week.
Okay.
And so he did he just say no.
I don't feel like it or he didn't show or how to handle it.
I don't know.
He's strong enough.
You're kidding me.
No.
That's, that is, that is so wrong.
You know, if I were in Brooklyn right now,
I'd be your booty call, baby.
I would hope so.
And the worst part is, I've met him before.
And he's, I thought he was a good guy.
But whatever.
Have you been intimate with him yet?
Or is it?
I've grown ever.
Chissus and tells.
Okay.
So that's a yes.
Yeah.
I have.
Right.
Okay.
So he's a good booty call.
He's, he does it for you.
He takes all the boxes.
He gets for a super short guy.
Yeah.
Hey, we discussed this last time.
I'm sure it.
I'm like five two.
He's not much taller than I am.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
I can understand that.
Because I'm all, you know, Patricia is, well, she says she's five six.
But it's horseshit.
She's five two.
Maybe maybe close to five six.
He knows.
It's really hard because I really miss hugging someone.
My height.
And roll at this point in my life.
Because, you know, the sex for us is just, you know, that pinwheel, right?
That works perfectly.
But okay.
So you're wearing pajamas.
You didn't get a booty call.
So you're drinking a little bit of wine.
And you're listening to the show.
And then you're, are you feeling kind of groovy right now?
A little bit because I have to figure out what I'm going to do to go to bed.
Oh, you need to, you can't sleep yet.
You need to do something to get to sleep, right?
You can sing.
I do everything.
Hmm.
What do you do every night?
Uh, it involves batteries.
If I'm not seeing someone else.
Really?
Of course.
Hmm.
Every night?
Uh, I've become a little, uh, let's start.
Yeah, there's a pattern.
Really?
It's okay, though.
I, I think it's okay to, um, I think it's okay to do that every night.
That's okay.
If you need to go to sleep.
Yeah.
You're going.
Okay.
I, I discovered the solo joys.
A little bit later.
And I discovered, uh, achieving a big go with another person.
Really?
What?
A little backwards.
How old were you when you, uh, first took the hand to yourself?
That's what's very backwards.
I, um, I started in with people of the opposite sex when I was in my young teens.
But I did not discover the ability to do it myself until I was in my 20s.
Really?
But you'd heard about it.
Yeah.
Oh, of course.
Someone told you about it.
But yeah.
I think I might have heard a little bit of a sudden.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
So, um, what kind of vibrator do you have?
Is it, uh, particular collar?
Do you have a favorite one?
Do you have, uh, do you have a couple different ones?
Is it one that you used for talking about?
Period things.
And I'm going to be branded as the girl that derails the serious conversation.
I certainly hope so.
Uh-huh.
It's always the same.
Always the same.
I think I've bought about four or five of them.
And I buy them from my friends as gifts.
Really?
Oh, that's great.
That's the gift that keeps on giving, isn't it?
It is.
Because at the end of the day, always go to the store and buy batteries.
Hmm.
And I always buy a little tiny, uh, purple pocket rocket.
All right.
So, you can take it to work?
No, no, no, no.
You've never done that at work.
You've never thought, oh, man.
I just, I just need to relax.
I just need to get rid of some stress.
I'm just going to go take a couple minutes for myself.
I'm not going to lie.
There have been times when it's in, in really rough.
And I'm like, whoa.
What's this?
When I go into bathroom and I'm like, I am so close.
Yeah.
Oh, I really told it.
Wait till you get home.
Oh, that's the best.
So you're like charged all day.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, this is something I could talk with you about this for hours and hours.
I really could.
And, and I look forward to having more conversations with you and why,
and a wanker girl, uh, when she comes in.
She's coming into tomorrow.
Sure.
Okay.
Excellent, darling.
I really appreciate this, you know,
because I'm an old guy and this makes me feel really hot.
Okay, darling.
Ah, we got our content noise.
Uh, one more song than for today's Charlie.
We're, uh, moving right ahead in the time.
Uh, I found out Rosie who, uh, works at HQ here,
who's really into the, into the music scene.
She told me that one of my favorite bands is performing Friday night in San Francisco.
Of course, now that I'm saying this on the show,
I'm sure they'll know that I'm going to show up because I'm totally planning
on going to see the list of these videos.
They perform here in San Francisco.
I forget what the venue is.
In fact, let me just, uh, let me just look that up.
So I don't have to, I'll probably have to put it in the show.
No, it's right.
Here we go.
Um, the CBS Bities are performing this Friday the 22nd at 9 p.m.
at the House of Shields.
That's a bar located on New Montgomery Street near market.
Not far from my place.
She says an extremely short taxi ride or a long walk.
Well, I just might have a long walk.
I just might have a long walk.
Excuse me, might have a long walk.
And as we're talking about this in the office.
And I can't remember what it, why, but maybe actually
it was reversed.
We were talking about Mr. Rogers.
I don't know.
I don't know what.
I have someone said, it's a lovely day in the neighborhood.
And I said, oh, man, I really miss Mr. Rogers.
You know, what a shame that he passed away.
And then I started singing the song, The La Civius Bities,
wrote about Mr. Rogers.
Of course, those of you who have never seen this,
won't get it, but you'll probably like the song anyway.
It's called neighbor.
It's the La Civius Bities on the daily source code.
When you walk, the door in your change just shows you switch to a sweater
and said, how do you do neighbor?
How do you do?
I remember the look in your sparkle eyes.
Then secondly, I love you.
Don't do all the night.
I love you. Don't do all the night.
It's neighbor.
It's all me looking at you.
I'll pick your picture.
I'll buy the wildly old street.
Standing tall and I'll maybe go round.
Spin it away, Charlie.
Ooh, Charlie.
Where did you go today?
Well, we played with Sandy.
We have for walks in the park.
You were a gentle man.
We were home before dawn.
Neighbors.
Me, delivery.
Make me believe.
Chef Brock gets showed.
It's hard to beg a pie.
Well, lady, Elaine gave him the evil eye neighbor.
You never acted that way.
In the whole world, he said,
There's only one need.
I didn't your world.
I was happy to be your neighbor.
All with the wood with lady,
I've been learning.
Lady, I've been learning.
She was so pretty.
I came home today with our way on my mind.
Life isn't simple anymore.
But I know where I am.
I came home today with our way on my mind.
Life isn't simple anymore.
But I know where I can find you.
You said, there's only one need.
I didn't your world.
I was happy to be your neighbor.
All with the wood with lady, I've been learning.
I know where all you said,
There's only one need in your world.
I was happy to be your neighbor.
All with the wood with lady, I've been learning.
Lady, I've been learning.
She was so pretty.
Thank you, friend.
On episode 726 of the Daily Source Code,
Adam's going Oprah.
He's giving a free iPod Touch
to everyone in the studio audience.
Wait, let me read the fine print here.
Must be present to win.
Well, I didn't go to work.
Here's the DSC 726.
Thanks, buddy.
I came in a little bit late.
Anyway, that's, I think that wraps it up for today's Daily Source Code.
What I didn't get to, let me see some of the topics that, and by the way,
I did post a, a topic list on curry.com,
about 15 minutes before I started the show and that kind of work.
But again, we need more hand raising going on.
But maybe I need to do the show a little bit earlier.
That might help as well.
I didn't get to the northern rock, which I just called a disaster because this is the bank
in the UK that the government bailed out with a total of about 50 billion pounds,
a hundred billion dollars in guarantees and insurance coverage for deposits.
They've nationalized it, which of course screws up a lot of things.
And certainly something I'd like to talk about.
I'm expecting a lot of phone calls from the UK about it in the next day or two,
so we will get to that.
And of course, when I'm back in the UK, it helps me a little bit talking about UK stuff.
And you're being as San Francisco is just not quite the same.
So thank you all very much for participating in today's program.
Miss something when you switch on your love machine.
I hope you think of me tonight.
I think she's already doing it.
Adam and podshow.com.
For all of all of the links with a little bit of luck, a little bit of something
then a little Miss Wanker girl tomorrow on the daily source code.
Be on the lookout.curry.com and on Twitter for the announcement when we record the show.
I'm liking this.
I think this is just my work.
Let's try it again tomorrow.
Thanks again, everybody.
And remember to live your life with passion.
And while it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Yeah.