All right, let's pray.
Let's pray.
Got a rock.
Thank you for this chance to kick us.
Kick us.
We are your humble servants.
Please give us the power to blow people's minds
with our high voltage rock.
This is this.
You think it will be so soon.
And the battery.
One two three,
one two three.
Sixteen million dollars worth of airplay
strapped by us.
To the next generation,
radio content in my ears.
We don't need enough.
Dealing,
breathing,
I like how you think I'm flying
into this jerk.
I guess it is a curry.
It was my teenage night.
My thoughts were short.
My hair was long.
Caught somewhere between it for a man.
She was 17.
She was far from in between.
It was summertime and northern this year.
Splash me through the fan bar.
Talking about the campfire.
It's the simple things in life.
Like when and where.
We didn't have no internet.
Oh man, I never will forget.
Way to move like shine upon her head.
And we were trying different things.
And we were smoking, throwing things.
Making her a lovely, draw me red song.
Look, sit in whiskey out the ground.
Not taking bottom all up.
See the heat, oh man, I'm all summer long.
See the sweet, oh man, I'm all summer long.
Getting all up from the dark.
Watching the waves roll off the rocks.
You'll fall ever, hold a spot inside my soul.
With this thrilling sun.
We couldn't wait for night to come.
To hit that same place, rock your roll.
While we were trying different things.
And we were smoking, throwing things.
Making her a lovely, draw me red song.
Getting all up from the whiskey out the ground.
Not taking bottom all up.
See the sweet, oh man, I'm all summer long.
Looking at the sweet, oh man, I'm all summer long.
Hey kids, there's this kid rock and this whole thing,
and the bait and downloading music.
A legal name stealing that I guess you was just really gone way too far.
I mean, it's like a company swing kids.
The kids are writing something you know, you can only go down low.
My music's still. If you're welcome, you're on a duck, I'm fucking rich.
And so how can I bitch about someone down low in the summer?
I'm just like, you know, we can only go down low in my music.
Fucking rich, and so how can I bitch about someone down low in the song or two?
I really can't, but what I'd like to encourage all of you to do at this point, let's level the playing field.
Still, everything.
Now nothing seems to strange as when the leads begin to change.
Oh, how we thought those things would never end.
Sometimes they hate that song, and I'll start to sing along.
And think man, I'd love to see that girl again.
And we tried different things, and we were smoking on a thing, making all I want to make to believe and so.
Hell yeah.
The whiskey of the bottle, now they get out to my heart, sing it and we all know.
And then you got to love that for a footballer Friday kick off.
Is that right?
What?
Kidrock.
Oh, it's so far along.
Of course, little bit of the leader's skitter in there, with sweet home Alabama.
And of course, you said we could steal the song, so what better way to kick off the
footballer Friday?
Hey, everybody.
It is Daddy Sorskord episode.
First, 771 coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gulford.
This is the footballer Friday music expressed free train blasting through your pots, Jim and
your ear, but it ooze around your brain.
I stop and I'm thinking about the life I can't breathe out, watching another
fall of the other, like faith that's the way it is.
These days I'm feeling good at this morning, and it's mainly crazy, but I was fairly
born, but I have learned to feel alive, but I must be out of my mind, to act this way,
I still feel all the same, and I'm okay, but when you're seen in it, it's one thing
you can expect, and if I can't see it, it'll all be in my mind, and it's all
in my mind, to act this way, but I must be out of my mind, to act this way, but I must be out of
my mind, to act this way, but when you're seen in it, it's all in my mind, to act
this way, but when you're seen in it, it's all in my mind, to act this way, but when you're
seen in it, it's all in my mind, to act this way, but when you're seen in it, it's all in
my mind, to act this way, but when you're seen in it, it's all in my mind, to act
this way, but I still feel all the same, and I'm okay, but when you're seen in it, it's
one thing you can expect, and if I can't see it, it'll all be in my mind, to act
in it, it's all in my mind, to act this way, but when you're seen in it, it's all in my mind, to act
It's not enough for me
All the faces all the pain you want to say
I think you want to say
I think I want to smile
I must be half of my mind
To have this way
I still have all this time
But I'm okay
But will you see me next
Or take your hands with me
I can't see the love me
I love the love I used to be
I love my mind
To have this way
I still have all this time
I'm okay
But will you see me next
I can't see the hell me
Out of my mind
This thing just appeared on the floor
My mind
What is it?
Take a screenshot
I think or a screenshot
Out of my mind
I saw it on the pond
Same music network
I'm like, whoa
After I listen to it
This is awesome
Fantastic stuff
And I've got more like that
For you on today's daily source code
And I was actually going to jam
Right through and play a whole
I'm going to hold a whole bunch of stuff
Line up of course
I've got a hit test to go
Got some soundtracks
From the soundtrack
To my life
Which hopefully will be added to yours today
But then I came across
You know there's a couple of shows
That I subscribe to
You can check out my on the go channel
Which is pretty much the one I listened to
Every day
I just click it in the morning
It's atom.podshow.com
Really easy to figure out
And remember
And one of the shows I have in there
is the BBC Newspot
Which is fantastic
Because it's really
It's like an aggregate
Of all of the best bits
Of all the BBC radio shows
From the previous day
So of course there's a lot of
Radio 4, Radio 5
It's mainly talk stuff and interviews
But the highlights are usually kind of
Pulled right out
And I came across something
I just wanted to share with you guys
Because it'll blow your mind
When you hear it
Hold on a second
Let me just make sure
I've got all
Q to properly hear
Hold on
Now I'm not quite sure
What the show is
Which program it's taken from
Which of course
I'll have to look for later
And put into the show notes
But essentially it's a journalist
Who covers Afghanistan
And I think it's a general
I think
And this is from the
You know the British services
Now you have to understand
Then the past
Was it two weeks or last month
Nine
Nine boys and girls
Actually I think eight boys
And one girl
Come back dead
And from Afghanistan
And I'm really
And they show the coffins
Here on TV by the way
At least I've seen one
Maybe it's just stock footage
Who the hell knows
But it's starting to become a point of discussion here
Obviously as it should be
Because there's a
7 or 8,000 British troops in Afghanistan
And there's a lot of troops
Of countries around the world
Because it's a NATO effort
Now what does that mean?
Exactly
Well listen to this bit
Very surprised
I'll jump in
And point out some of the things that I find interesting from the soundbites
In the last 10 days
Nine British soldiers have died in Afghanistan
Including one woman
Their deaths have prompted yet more questions
About the success of the current military operation
Five lives Stephen Chittendon
Went to the Garrison town of Colchester in England
And spoke to the wife of one serviceman
Who's in Afghanistan
Actually this is
So that's just the beginning of the piece
I want to get to that guy who called
I think he Campbell spoke to them both
And began by asking Colonel Mike Juer
There we go
British forces in Afghanistan
Great question
Why are the forces there?
Here we go
We're not just asking
Of course the fact is NATO was there
There are 47,000 troops there
And 27 nations
That's the point
It's not a matter of Britain being there
It's a matter of the west in general
Being there for its own self interest
That's why we're there
He just said in an article
And there was never said why we're there
Well that's rubbish
I'm close to him
I'm so many times I'm in a sick of you
Notice this tactic
We've said it so many times
Where they're there
So countless number of times
There were sick of telling you why we're there
That's a very interesting tactic
Because I bet you
If I go out on the street
I don't think even half or half of the people you ask
Would actually know the standard answer
Bring it
Why we out there
Where there to prevent Afghanistan
They're coming the base
It was when it night eleven was launched from there
Now
Let's just replay that little bit
Okay
Remember
Britain also went into Iraq
With United States based upon evidence
Of terrorism
Links
And of course the weapons of mass destruction
But
Terrorism
We went into Iraq because that's where all the bad guys were
Right
Isn't that right?
Well nine eleven was launched from Afghanistan
Is what he's saying
Let's just listen to that again
Make sure I heard it right
And they were never said why were there
Well that's rubbish
It's been said simpler times
Some so many times
That one sick of hearing it
Why we out there
Where there to prevent Afghanistan
They're coming the base it
Whilst when it night eleven was launched from there
And when it was a sanctuary for terrorism
And a headquarters for world terrorists
And that's why we're with there
Is it also about
Providing democracy and making sure
And there is a quality of women
As much as it can be
And education
All those things still important
Yeah
What a great question
So of course the guy says
No it's our terrorism
It's not about any pipelines
Don't look at the pipelines
The place
And it's not the pipelines
It's a terrorism
Yeah I'm glad you brought that up about women and children
Well of course
Of course they are
I mean like you go on with a whole range of reasons
I'm trying to be succinct
And give you one main reason
But if you want me to go on for hours
I could go on for hours
Oh I must say there's so many reasons
We are there
I could go on for hours
Of course
Of course there are all those reason
Peter also just manages those reasons
And he's right
They cannot be achieved easily or quickly
And that doesn't mean you shouldn't try
The army is only creating space
You can't win a war
A war like this
Any way you can win some wars
By purely military means
But a war like this
You cannot of course
And Peter and I'm sure we would agree with that
You can only create space
How does that mean?
The final frontier
You're making a fool of yourself Colonel
For other influences to work
And those may take you
You only have to look at all the confidence he was
Since 1945
Okay
Taking up to 30 years
Some of taking 10 years
Some 15, some 20
Oh we could be there forever
Trying to take a long, long time
But we're not
We lost Peter's line
But we've got him on the phone
He was at Peter
Yes I am
So this is about this is getting ugly in a second here
Nothing I'm afraid
But I think I know what it probably was
Now listen to this
This is the reporter right
It's a journalist and he's going to give
His opinion
About eradicating terrorist training camps
And making sure they aren't re-established
And rebuilding society
I'm sorry
But this is completely unrealistic
We have what is it
Eight thousand troops in Afghanistan
And one more province in one part of it
The president of Afghanistan
He was supposed to be supporting barely control
His own bedroom
I like that
The president of Afghanistan
The one that wears a lamb feed
This is on his head
He can barely control his own bedroom
Did I miss something that I missed
I'm kind of scandal somewhere
With Karzai
I must have missed something
I have to look that one out
The country is mainly run by warlords
The various reasons
Which we've been said to be
All actually empty
We are incapable of preventing
The Taliban from operating with Taliban
I've seen most of the best two people
Many people live in Afghanistan
Many guys thanks to a badly drawn border
From 1871
No British or any other part
As ever succeeded in obtaining control
Ever Afghanistan by military means
We would try to act twice in the 19th century
The idea that with our peaceful military results
We can't even afford to protect our soldiers
That idea that with our peaceful military results
We can achieve more than the Russians did
With hundreds of thousands of troops
And to be in charge of getting to the country
It is frankly ridiculous
You really need to hear this whole thing
So I'll put a link in the show
No, so you can listen to it
Meanwhile
Check out
The way you support
The 4th
The 1st
The protest is alive and well my friends
And behind the 4th image of the son of man
It shall stand
And it's in hip hop
Crank this up
Listen to the message
But it's important
And it's about all of us
Of all colors
Yeah
The voice of racism
Region of gospel is devilish
A fake church called the prophet Muhammad terrorist
We're getting call is not religion
But a spiritual bond
And Jesus is the most quoted prophet in the Quran
He bombed innocent people trying to murder the dumb
When you gave them those chemical weapons to go to war
This is the information that they hold back from Peter Jennings
This kind of lease of rice
It's just the new age Sally Hemings
I break it down with critical language
And spiritual anguish
The truth is that hang with the guilt of the train
Christ to murder them stole his religion
And painted them white
Translated and psychologically painted philosophy
Conservative political right wing
Ideology
Clube together
Slappily the blasphemy of a nation
Got my back to the wall
Cause I'm facing assassination
Quantanamo Bay
Federal incarceration
How could it be
The land of the free
The home of the brave
Indigenous holocaust
And the home of the slaves
Corporate America
It's an offbeat to the rhythm
You really think this country
Never sponsor terrorism
Human rights violations
We can sing through the saga
El Salvador
And the country's in Nicaragua
And no one top of that
You still want to take me to prison
Just cause I won't trade humanity
For patriotism
It's like M.K.O.Sra
Controlling your brains
And just thinking
For the new perspective
The change
They want to rearrange
The whole point of view
With a ghetto
The fourth branch of the government
Once to settle
A bent in a full of glittering
General justice
Fightin' for freedom
And fighting terror
For what's reality
No freedom
Not the history
But a place that we live in
Stop letting corporate news
Tell lies to your children
Like the blood of Abraham
Through the truth
And the arrows
Prooking upon
Like a woman's heart
Abused in the marriage
The brink of holy war
Modeled up
Like a miscarriage
And bedded
Correspondent
Don't tell the source of attention
And they refuse
The even mention
You're a peon
Intervention
Or the massacres
And Jeanine
The innocent screams
US manufactured missiles
And M.S.S.T.s
Weapon contracts
And corrupted American dreams
Media censorship
Locking out the video
Screams
A continent of oil
Kingdoms
For Morgan, democracy is just the world
And the people are starving
And average citizens
Made to be blind
To the reason
And deserts full of genocide
What a body is freezing
And the world doesn't believe
That you're fighting for freedom
Because you fought the Middle East
And gave birth to a demon
It's open season
With the CIA
Boking my crib
Trapped in a ghetto region
Like a Palestinian kid
When nobody gives a fuck
Whether you die you live
I'm trying to give the truth
And I know the price is my life
But when I'm gone
No singing song about immortal technique
Who'd be headed to president
And the prince isn't sheaks
You don't give a fuck about us
I can see for your facade
Like a fuller name
You're standing in the presence of God
Bitch, make a scare to the truth
When it looks at you hard
It's like M.K. Oldtrog control
And your brains
Just thinking
For the new perspective
The change
That what a real range
The whole point of view
And it ghetto
The fourth branch
That government
One is to settle
A band in a fuller clittering
Gender rather defighting for freedom
And fighting terror
But what's reality
Much along is coming soon
To the hood
To kill you
While you hang in your flag
Out your project window
Damn
The fourth branch
That government
A.K. The media seems to now
Have a retirement plan
For ex-military officials
As if their opinion
Was at all unbiased
On my sheeps
Should speak for men
So shut the fuck up
Your mindless home
And you know it's serious
When he's saying media outfits
A spending millions of dollars
On a PR campaign
To try to convince you
Their fair and balanced
When there's someone
A most ignorant
And racist people
It's giving that type of mentality
A safe haven
We act like we share
In the spoils of water
They do
We die in the wars
We don't get the contract
To make money
Or for afterwards
We don't get weapons
Contracts nigger
We don't get cheap labour
For companies nigger
We aren't cheap labour
Nigger
Turn off the news
And read nigger
Read
Immortal technique
The fourth branch
And although maybe directed directly
At the ghetto
I sometimes feel in the
Immortal words of Stevie Wonder
We all live in a villa
Village ghetto land
That's uh
That's powerful stuff, man
That of course was found on the source code drop.io
Dash or slash daily source code
Fantastic track
Really really like that
And well just on the topic for another moment here
A couple of people sent this to me including
Parkie
Uh
Exactly according to plan
A rock is preparing to allow
Four of the biggest western oil companies
To renew exploitation of the country's vast
Reserve for the first time in almost four decades
This is exactly what the plan was
I can't remember where it was
I'm sure I can google it and find it for you
But there's a whole plan
This was all set up
This is all dived up
They knew exactly which companies were getting
Which parts of uh
Iraq for oil exploitation
And now they're getting per mission
So here are the companies
Iraq's oil ministry stepped up talks
With BP
That's uh British petroleum
Exxon mobile shell and total
After the US vice president
Mmm
Dick Cheney visited Iraq in March
Where he also pressed the government to revive
Efforts to pass the hydro carbon law
That nationalist MPs were blocking
So the first contracts are expected to be signed later this month
90% of uh Iraq's budget comes from oil revenues
This was exactly the plan
It's happening right under our noses
Exactly as as we knew it would happen
And what do I get?
One news report
This is an outrage
You got it
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
Your honor
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's don't give a nod
To the hardest work
And law here
He's Jersey Ty
Yeah
Oh yeah
Your honor
What do you say?
He might
How's it going Adam?
It's Jersey Ty
The official musical
Just of the
Chacha
So coming out of California
Is one of the greatest band names of all time
The band's name is Candy Graham for Mongo
Which of course comes from my favorite movie
Blazing Saddles
But the song man
The song I wonder
Stands on its own
Is one of the best er guitar songs
I've ever played for Yana Fubar Friday
So get that tennis racket out and get ready to rock
Because this is Candy Graham for Mongo
With eye wonder
Ah
The Delhi source code
Talk to you later buddy
Like it up
I was on a double dating New York City
We took the girls to meet us by the man
And then when you come round the corner
You look so pretty
I'm glad I forgot to get my Tuxedo grip
And I won't know how it is
I won't know how it is
We are now
CBD
My friend
Did like two bells
To me and you
Started kissing
I felt your heart beat
Through your tears
And I won't know how it is
I won't know where it will stay for it
If I can't find this ball
I'll feel something
I won't know how it is
If I can't find this label
I will definitely give you the table
Everything was going perfectly
You can play the tab
You're friendly with a cab
And you roll until it's on night
Out of reach
Cause you're écrit from thekey
Cause you're Wilton Young and somebody
Cause you're Wilton Young and someone
I want you...
Candy Grins from Mongo.
I wonder how it ends.
Well, after about 3 minutes, 48 seconds eventually, it always does.
Thank you very much, sir.
You're as he taught official musicologist of the Daily Source Code, always there on a Friday
when you need him when we have an actual football Friday scheduled planned and executed.
Now, I'm going to do the head test for you, but I've gotten some complaints about the year.
Yes.
Hello?
Hello.
Yeah, I've been in the same lens.
Hmm, mate.
Now, I've got a little bone to pick with you.
I spoke with scoring on the head test.
Now, I think it's about some we introduced some figure into the scoring.
We're taking half a point here and a three-quarters of a point there.
It really isn't on.
What we need to do is we need to implement the following scoring system.
All right.
If you get...
The name of the artist's correct, you get one point.
One point.
You get the name of the track, right?
You get one point.
Okay.
So if you get both right, you get two points.
Right.
And if you get all three right, you get six points.
Right. Got it.
I think that will give us a good baseline for moving forward.
And if anyone wants to go back through the head test,
and do some statistical analysis.
I think that will be fairly splendid.
No, I don't think so.
I'm back to work.
I'm off to Orlando.
I'm Sunday.
The Bahamas on the Wednesday afternoon.
And over to LA at the end of July.
So I'm not traveling too much for the moment.
Take care.
Don't forget.
They work for us.
The official sign off of the chat chat.
Okay. So I've got it.
One point for the artist.
One point for the track.
Six total possible points possible.
Possibility.
Wise.
Okay.
Let's do it.
One point for the casting.
We've had a jury.
This is the hit test.
Hit it.
Young pole.
Hey.
Hey Adam.
This is hit test number 127.
All right.
We're going to start right away with intro.
Number one.
Hit me.
I know that one.
It's the cars and drives.
He's going to drive home.
Tonight. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy.
Feeling good.
Number two.
Cockroven.
That's going to be one star only for that one.
Crap.
And number three.
Madonna.
Express yourself.
Okay.
I think according to the official scoring.
I have five out of six possible.
The answer.
All right.
Yes.
Number one.
The cars.
Ninety four.
Who's going to take win?
It's you.
Just go on.
We're going to take you home.
And we're going to have it tonight.
There we are.
The young pull-up master makes here.
Answer number one.
And hit that number one hundred twenty seven.
The cars and drives.
Answer number two.
Ninety eighty seven.
Cockroven.
Yeah.
This is just the wrong corner.
That's the force.
Oh, man.
I love that cock.
Okay.
One star on that one.
They all sound alike.
Answer number two.
Cockroven and just around the corner.
Oh yeah.
It's the answer number three.
Yeah.
Five out of ten.
This is express yourself.
Hi.
You have done it.
Come on.
Three.
Two.
Eight.
Care it.
Two.
Express yourself.
You've got to make it.
Hey.
So if you want it right now.
Make it show you how.
Express what you've got.
We'll be ready for nothing.
We'll spend it.
But Donna's answer number three.
And that concludes this hit edge.
And it's number one hundred and twenty seven.
Feeling good.
So Adam.
How did you do this?
Well, John.
The point is the new scoring system.
Five out of six points.
You want to check out the info about this and any other hit edge.
You can go through hit edge.
That beefy out.com.
And that's also the place to find links.
One, two.
So we can buy this right.
Future on the hit edge.
All right.
Adam.
Thank you for playing.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
Be back to test at gmail.com.
info.
Youngpool.com.
J-N-P-O-L-E-T-A-S-G-O.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you very much, John.
Hit test number one hundred and twenty seven.
Love it as always, my friend.
Back to the fun.
Save music on the footballer Friday.
Musical Express, freight train addition.
Ugly suit.
Here's your cargo on the Charlie.
I'm going to swing.
You're the rain.
Under me.
And I'm going to be the cross.
Get far and hit and meet.
As I stay.
Further on the beach.
I'm going to stay.
And you won.
Under me.
Don't forget.
Don't rest.
Don't need at all.
Save it all.
Be far.
Come on.
Come.
I took it to the shi-kalu
The temperature struck till I was not in the city
And I can hardly feel my blood
But just as I had almost lost my mind completely
The face had shown the songs in my blood
But without the words of many dead
The sound of whey so many whey
The sound of whey told me
And whewed it all in the game
To just go to the art of the art of the art of the art of the art
The sound of whey so many whey so many whey
The sound of whey food
And whey so many whey so many whey
The sound of whey so many whey so many whey
So many whey so many whey so many whey
And whew so many whey so many whey so many whey
The sound of whey so many whey so many whey so many whey
The sound of whey so many whey so many whey so many whey so Many whey so many whomey
And I'm pretty, that's another one for them.
That is from the Potset music network.
The ugly suit.
I kind of drifted towards the page with that name popped up.
Yeah.
That's got to be something.
I'm just looking, I got a new sponsor here on the Charlie.
The Friday is brought to you by no one less than budget rent to car.
Check that out.
And I got an offer for you guys.
Hold on a second.
So if you're renting a car, this of course only counts for the United States.
If you're planning a renting a car, maybe for the Fourth of July week,
or maybe for the weekend, but particularly a week,
which a lot of people do these days.
And quite honestly, I use our car so infrequently now,
I'd almost consider renting a car.
It's entirely practical because the tree, when I need the car,
it's really not going very far.
But I would definitely consider giving it up,
particularly at today's gas prices.
Anyway, here's the offer for the chuckleheads.
If you're going to rent a car anyway, go check out budget.
Because of course, let me see, what do we have here?
But they got a whole bunch of, it's like 900 locations in the US.
I guess pretty much everybody now is offering GPS.
But they are also offering GPS navigation.
They've added to any rental.
And of course, they've got all the latest Ford vehicles.
And more, including a hummer.
You can rent a hummer from budget.
Is that a contradiction in terms?
I love that.
I guess that's true.
I used to, when we were in, when I still had MTV,
and we go to California, the Los Angeles to do stuff.
And like for the MTV Video Music Awards,
when they were held in LA, you could go to budget luxury rental
on a sunset, I think it was.
I always thought it was so funny because like budget, but they had all the top end cars.
And you know, like a Mercedes 500 SL or something.
Back in the day when budgets were a plenty.
So anyway, you can rent a Hummer H3, a Cadillac CTS.
Even if you want a Prius, awesome.
Okay, so here's the deal.
You can get, if you use the, if you go to website now,
you can get a coupon.
And you've got to go to budget.com slash DSC.
You get $30 off weekly rentals or 10% off any other time period.
So it's a guaranteed 10% off any car you rented budget.
And if you take one of their weekly rentals,
it's $30 off budget.com slash DSC.
All right, some news came in yesterday,
which I find highly interesting.
You've probably heard about this.
A Barack Obama has decided not to make use of the public funds
for his presidential campaign, which, of course,
he still has to be officially chosen as the Democratic candidate.
But let's presume that he's pretty much there.
No reason to pursue him out to pursue him otherwise.
He's decided not to go with, and of course,
this is where all this campaign finance reform.
All this talk has been about this.
I think it's $84 million that you can have direct access
to for your presidential campaign.
If you're, if you're the candidate,
I wonder if that's for, for independence as well.
But anyway, he's declined that.
And he says, no, I don't want to use public money at all.
I'm going to use other forms, which, of course,
is, you know, that can come from a lot of different places.
And I'm, I'm definitely going to look into that.
But I think there's this whole concept of bundling,
sort of one person can collect money from thousands of other people.
And there are some limits here and there,
but still he, the bottom line.
And this was what was interesting.
He said, $84 million is jotted not just not enough
to run a presidential campaign.
And this is what I've always been saying.
It's like he was the most money generally wins.
You know, there's Barack Obama basically saying
it's not enough money to run a presidential campaign.
Not to compete, you know, not to win.
It's not even enough to run one.
Which is just sad.
It's a sad state of affairs.
If that's really true.
But I guess we, I guess we obviously do choose our presidents
the way we choose our, are so powder.
Anyway, so back in the early 80s,
when the thought of a black president of the United States
was just a wish and many and I,
is that the correct expression?
Well, doesn't matter.
I mean, it was, I have to say it was probably that time
unimaginable now.
I was living in Amsterdam with a very different cultural situation.
And this was the early days.
Remember sugar hill gang and Curtis blow.
And it was the very first hip hop slash rap records
and blow fly.
It was kind of like a novelty rap artist at the time.
And he came out with something called
first black president.
And I thought it would be fine to listen to it again
on today's football or Friday.
Just a kind of compare.
If you could even make a song like this today,
I don't you could with all the political correctness.
And obviously, it's humoristic.
It's ironic.
And I think it's hilarious.
But it's really interesting to see how we've changed
culturally and are thinking in 130 years time.
Here is blow fly.
The first black president.
From around, I think 1981 or 82.
Ladies and gentlemen, introduce in the first Nick.
I'm in the first black president of the United States of America.
Present blow fly.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And like I promised y'all when I was running.
I'm going to make sure they are chillins and every pot.
And hooks and every table.
Black control peels and every purse.
And we're going to have a orange and every motherfucking weekend.
Thank you.
Good morning, Mr. President Sir.
Good morning, bit.
I'm at Ms. Clayton.
This shit's going to be easy.
President don't do nothing but sit on his ass all day.
And your ball doesn't even mother fucking way.
It's like getting my hair together here.
Where's my fucking cocaine?
But the bitch doesn't move it again.
Ms. Clayton.
Mr. President Sir?
You get your ass in here, please.
That way, sir.
What did you do in my ship?
Are you constantly at Sir?
Mitch, you know what I'm talking about, my motherfucking Ronald.
How?
I took you down to the vet sir.
Oh, I'm talking about coke, cocaine.
You know that white part of shit that I put on your pussy when I'm getting ready to eat it?
Oh, that's her.
It's right in front of you sir.
Thank you. That'll be all.
Stupid bitch.
If I put it when so good I'll fire.
Let's get over here and get my hair together.
And some good shit.
Mr. President Sir?
Shit.
What the fuck you want now?
Mr. Jackson is here to see you.
Mr. Jackson.
Reggie Jackson and Andrew Jackson are Michael Jackson.
What, which one?
Mr. Superfly Jackson.
Are the United Pimps Association?
Shit. What the fuck you want?
He wants the money you promised him for endorsing you.
I told that dumb motherfucking old assholes that Congress got all the funds frozen.
What the fuck you want from my life?
Well, he stated that payment and coke would be sufficient.
My last coke.
I'll take it. Give it to the motherfucking get rid of me.
Just in and out shit.
I thought that shit was going to be easy.
I got it. I got some weed here somewhere.
Here it is.
I wrote in a couple of jokes.
Mr. President Sir?
Shit.
What you want now, Mr. Clay?
Mr. Paul is here to see you, sir.
Mr. Paul.
Paul Newman, Paul Reveal.
Paul Lanker.
Paul John Paul, sir.
John Paul?
What do you want?
And we each are currently smoking, sir.
Shit, dude.
I can see right now I'm not going to like this motherfucking shit at all.
Give it to the motherfucking.
Can't sniff no coke.
Can't smoke no dope.
Pam, I know what I do.
Fuck this bitch again.
Mr. Clay, what are you coming here, please?
Nightly sir.
Come on over here, leaving, put off your clothes, which is fine, sir.
I'm down.
I don't want to hit a shit this morning.
Can't smoke no dope.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What is the red spots when you're stumbling?
That's what I was trying to tell you, sir.
What are you?
I'm safe.
I went to the doctor, and he says I have hurt me.
The hot piece?
I resigned.
Fucking hungry.
Oh man, blow fly the first black press.
And I probably should point out in case you hadn't guessed blow fly as black.
So, again, the irony, the humor, the unthinkable, and it just may happen.
How about death apples?
What a great country.
This is your source code, the footballer Friday 7-7-1.
We remember the ones that fall in time.
When you were a man, just also fall for the right and new.
I pulled them down for you just when I barely open.
We said that all good things must stay.
Even.
Let's just blow away it is when the red.
Oh, even.
The more heavy the soul looks in.
So open.
Did I should have my chance and the rules?
Feel like I've been used to, will you?
When other night will you spell it out in black and white?
Even.
Let's just blow away it is when the red.
Oh, even.
That's just the way it is, baby
Baby, that's just the way it is, baby
I know about you, but it just lets know this music and all this creativity that's blasting out through the ethernits
It really makes me think, you know, maybe it's just the way it is, baby
It's the Rembrandt's, not pot-sake, but the hell man, it's a full bar Friday, we gotta do something
That's just the way it is, baby
It's Friday
Now I do have one more song to go for it, but I was just thinking about, you know, what if
You know, what if it really is true that there's a whole bunch of elites that are sitting kind of in their evil rooms
stroking their white pussycats, you know, you know, the guys that go moo ha ha
And they really aren't just trying to control us, what if all of this stuff like the price of oil, you know?
What if that's being jacked up, just to put the squeeze on us, because you know when people are depressed and afraid and, you know, look at inflation
It's going up, you know, we've got troubling times ahead, we're perhaps on the brink of a recession
If not depression, certainly some inflation and stagnation
What if it's all part of the plan, you know, part of the idea is just to to wear us down to squashes
It could actually be hamping, and of course, the more we start yelling and the more we start freaking out about stuff
The more we're ground down into oblivion, what if we should really just, I don't know, you should think about this over the weekend
Or if you're not Australia, of course, you're listening to this on next Tuesday, so
What if we should play a little bit more cool, you know, maybe maybe we shouldn't be protesting
Maybe we need to seek other courses of action, maybe
Well, somewhere there's a combination, I'm thinking the power that Ireland showed, show the euro crats, the political elite and in Brussels
Maybe that power, you know, by saying, hey, you know what, we're just not going to let you guys do what you want to do
Because at the end of the day, you gotta go through us first and thank God there was still one country, one member state
It was able to stop the lunacy that is the Lisbon treaty because no one understands what it means
Maybe that's our power
We need to investigate a lot more about this because of course there are 26 other states in the European Union that
Just got the Lisbon treaty rammed down their throat, and how do we apply this to the United States?
How can we actually stop things as citizens?
Is there a referendum law in the US that we can utilize on certain issues?
Maybe there's something there, maybe we just gotta kick back, not get to work up about all this shit that they're trying to throw at
It's trying to make us down, break us down, stomp us to the ground
That my friends is my final thought for the week
Now of course I'm not going to let you go on just that thought we've got to crank up the party a little bit
You know what I mean?
Kick back everybody and let's just enjoy the highlights
Light it up, put it in the air
Light it up, light it up
Can't help but hurt
Can't piss, put a blade, hash, plant, toss, stick, white with a wet the train
It no, I'll do it to the brain, orange, brown, red, head, green
Poach, clown, bones, bloods, zig, zags
Bubbles, bones, blown out of big packs, twist up, roll up, pack up
Hit that sense so strong in the air, where you get that
Can't pack a stand, lamb, sprit, scum
I can't poke, blow, leave, hide, roll, fall
Blue bear, we're finally chocolate, chum
Northern life's bloodless cannabis cut
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Can't hold these musicians actors
Everything wiqi class down the slackers
Lo keep a laser, simpleing point
Because the 1930ship hadzt and I hope gone back
it's a good and kể опис
I hear it while I fall
When you make a live with me
How I walk through the way
Ede
I know there's no light
You just go
All right, I'm going to leave y'all not know my friends, RJ-D2, hi-lites.
I think that's another one I got on the source code drop, which is just a treasure trove information.
I really appreciate everything you guys are dropping in there.
It's Drop.io slash daily source code.
All right, I'm definitely showing out over the weekend.
Big game for Holland playing against Russia, which of course is coached by the former Dutch national coach.
Hitting.
So that's going to be a fantastic game.
We're just on fire here in Europe.
Forget all this Lisbon Treaty stuff.
Boy, we love playing football against each other.
And I have to say it's really been very friendly.
There's been no animosity.
It's just been good.
It's been honest fun.
And it's fantastic to be a part of Europe this time.
Certainly this point in my life.
And let's see if we can, hey, you know what?
Fuck it.
Let's use our power.
Go save the world.
Until we speak again, my friends have yourselves a great weekend.
Please live your life with passion and as long as it lasts.
Enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.