This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
We're listening to a man I identified by the GSA as the spiritual leader of the subversive
cabal known by the code word, Pod Show.
A Dom Curry Delta Characters.
Currently $7.00 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
To the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need nuss.
I like you to be a sign of your signature.
I'm guessing it's sad and correct.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Me now, when I meet now, when I'm down
When I meet you, when I meet you
When I meet you, that's what I meet now
When I meet you, when I meet you, I'm free for you here with me
I'm playing for something free, so I'll be there to make me see
My life feels so good to me
Last year, good to meet you
Wake up and sing in
When there we ended up, that's what I ain't нас
You wanna meet me now
When you should meet up, you wanna meet me now
You wanna meet me now, when I meet you, where you to meet me now
When you should meet, when I meet you, when I meet you
When you should meet, that's what I meet you
One of me now, one of my dreams for you will be with me
I'll play for you, set me free
So I think that you'll make me see
I'll try to get to you
Once again, I'm a sucker for a real nice cookie pot too
And I'll knock
At the girl's stuff, they're from Switzerland
I think every single time they release a new track
I'm right there playing it
Every single one is just walled to wall
Hit me tearfully
Cheer me up
Kicking off episode number 710 of the Daily Source Code
For Thursday
There's early morning Thursday, January 17th, 2008
What the hell happened?
We're almost three quarters of the way through January
Righty
Of course, I'm up here in the attic at the curry manner
And the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford, West Side of Gtown
Representing for you, sorry about yesterday
Got a major league busy, even though I was home
Wait a minute, what was yesterday?
I don't even remember where I was
No, wait a minute
Wednesday, I was in a crap, I don't know
I really don't know
I just don't remember
But we will get three shows in today
Proper footballer, Friday planned for tomorrow
And got a hit test, already lined up for that
Looks like Amy is sent in a new ass
Sur size
So we'll keep all of that for tomorrow's festivities
And I'm not going into the city tomorrow
Unlike today, that's why I'm up pretty early
Getting the show done, I have a meeting with Hayhouse publishers
There of course the publishers
What is that?
I'm sorry
I thought it was on something weird
There are publishers of the books, many, many books
A couple of our stars on the network
Originally from the UK
Gordon Smith, Spirit Messenger
Do you have not seen Spirit Messenger
You owe it to yourself to see this guy
He's the real deal when it comes to medium
Spirit Messenger.podshow.com
I'm also a barefoot doctor
So you can find a barefoot doctor on podshow as well
Then I've got a meeting with the readers
Digest and I've got a meeting with this guy
A new ash bee who was a huge
Record company boss back in the day
And he's trying to change the way music is promoted
And he's caught onto the pod save music revolution
So we'll be meeting with him
Who knows what he's got up his sleeve
Always just kind of interesting here people out
And there's a comment that came in a day or two ago
Which I'd have to say is one of the best comments
About pod safe music
In other words, music that independent producers
Are allowed to use free of charge
Under license but free of charge in their programming
As long as they report it back to the artist or the label in question
And how it's really working and moving product
Okay, it's moving product
This is what these guys aren't looking at
Hello Mr. Hands over at EMI
You should be paying attention dude
Particularly to this comment from one of your customers
Hello Adam
Scott here from Scott podcast.com
I was listening to talking about the
The recording industry and how they're just sliding
Further and further back in the other day
A friend sent me a link to an article on the internet
I don't know if you saw or not
But it was about how the recording industry had brought a bunch of young people
Into interview them to find out what makes them tick
And at the end of it
They offered them a bunch of current CDs of music
And they didn't take any
And they were obviously shocked
And what did that tell us?
That is awesome
You got to send a link to me for that story dude
That's funny
So they offered them free CDs in the alternative culture
Like oh my god
They don't even want to buy the CDs
Now what do we do?
They want to take them for free
You know I guess that's because
MP3 is where it's at
That's what they did not
They want the digital music
And I think they're running scared from that
I read that they're going to have a cell phone
That they're offering and they're making a bundling deal on it
That's going to offer unlimited music
Of course you know that they're going to get a cut
Of the sale of that cell phone
Plus the sale probably of the service of that cell phone
Which will probably be somewhat more expensive
Than a non unlimited music cell phone would be
So nothing's really free
Yeah you see I kind of disagree there
I think that that cartel is being broken open
Very very slowly
There will be new forms of
Kind of cartels
But I saw a Christina
I watched or you know I gave her an iPod touch for Christmas
By the way she's already dropped a million times
Including once in the toilet
I don't know if the things dead are not
If it'll ever come back to life
Teenagers
But I watched her fill it up
You know and she does not have an iTunes account
And she basically was filling it up with independent music
She wasn't going after anything
That's you know that's necessarily legally in license
Not that I could see at least
Or I should say license
Not license for the you know for downloading and putting it onto your iPod
You know she was downloading stuff off of my space players
And I believe she even looked at some
Some pod safe tunes and then search around to find those
I don't think she's purchased anything although she does have room bank card
So it's entirely possible
But I don't think she's pulled it out for that
Yeah it's right you know
The kids want the MP3s
But not necessarily
And not a single I didn't see a RIP a single CD
By the way
Which is another very interesting thing to me
So maybe the offering of these big companies just isn't that interesting anymore
Gee you think
But that's where they're going
You know I got to thinking about this whole idea that it's going to become more and more difficult for them
To get in the middle of a business that's eliminating the middle man
Where bands can sell stuff directly to their customers
What does that say about movies?
Will there come a day when movies will be suffering the same fate?
I think probably so
You know I was watching the Steve Jobs keynote
Even though I'd followed along the live blogging on and gadget.com
And when he first of all Apple TV
I've got a boner over that
That Apple TV thing I think they might have gotten right
I don't know when it'll be available in the UK
But as soon as it is I'm buying one
Because I have the perfect test audience for that
All I have to do is hook it up to our TV
And see if the lady Patricia uses it
And I'm going to set up you know I have a channel that I set up for her on her computer
With fashion shows and stuff
Excuse me
The Frank true
You know a couple of things I know she wants to watch and listen
And once in a while she'll you know
By accident open up iTunes and so
So she'll see a little blue dot there and she'll play something
Anyway I think that it's all about ease
And I think people are perfectly willing to pay a couple dollars for something
If it's easy if it's just easy
That's what it is
It's just got to be easy so Apple moved
Took a significant step in that direction
But you are right I agree with the hypotheses
It's next
You know already we're seeing
Was it a
Vodafone just announced a new USB stick
Which will work on the HSDPCA LMNOP high super
Transmorgified broadband network
It'll do 7.2 megabits on the download
Not quite sure about the upload
But that's what it does in the download
And I have one of there a USB attachments for
For broadband it'll do it does about 1.3 megabits per second
And the connectivity was kind of busted
When I was prepping the show
And I didn't feel like waiting for it to
You know usually comes back in a minute or so
You know just happens
And so I plugged in the USB thingy
And I was off to the race as man
I was just like boom
I was I was downloading an amazing speeds
And it's just going to get better
You know there's just going to be more bandwidth
And it will be easier to transfer entire movie files
With or without bit torrent
You know you'll be able to just drag it into a Skype window
It'll just transfer fast
So yes this is of course what is next for the movie industry
And I guess I'll just quote
The Warner Music
I've got a brain freeze here
Doug Morris from Warner
In that recent wired interview we said look
If Coca Cola came out of the tap at your home
Would you still go out and buy cans
And obviously obviously it's an answer
Is of course no you wouldn't
And that's kind of what's happening
Unless of course there was a different form of packaging
There's many many many opportunities
Not just unexplored at this point in how to package music
So the only you know forms we have
Basically are CD
And iTunes
You know that doesn't really show me that there's a lot of innovative thinking
Going on there
Of course there's lots of other places
The concept of a music store is kind of
You know the one packaging option and buying tracks
Or buy multiple tracks
I mean there's a lot of different things you could do
And I still believe people like physical products
Unless there's some of the rush to the comment
And we're going to find that
The actors and writers and such
How are they going to monetize what they're doing
Directly to the people who they are
You know marketing their product to
Because this is and you know it's quite so simple as the band
Maybe it is I don't know there are fan fiction sites out there
They're doing some wonderful shows one of my favorites is a stock track show
Maybe that's how they'll do it
I don't know how they'll monetize it
But it's going to be very interesting to watch this happen
And I just thought I'd mention that
In case you hadn't heard of it
If you want the link just say so
And I'll send that to you later on
Take care and bye for now
Yeah man, thank you so much
Great comment and send me the link
If you wouldn't mind also put it in the comments
For this show daily source code.com
In case I don't have enough time to put it
Into the show notes
You know me and time right
Excellent
Okay, so great news
If you're follow curry.com
My weblog you probably saw
That the codes are in for the
Nokia N8010
That the pod shown network is now authorized to sell
At a 15% discount
I've been telling you
We're going to do great with a great price
To the market and I have not found anything
Yeah, I've seen people offer it for like
399 and then you click through
When it turns out you get like a
$30
discount if you
Order a credit card
You know, so it will be $30 off your first purchase
If you use the credit card you have to order first
So there's a lot of shielding going on out there
But this 15% discount really is the best price
I've been able to find online
And here's the beauty part of it
If you're in the market for buying one of these
Things anyway
Buy it from someone who show you
Listen to now we we started off with
The reasonably small group of people
Who are selling this with their promo codes
Just like GoDaddy
It's the exact same
Sell our payment concept
But if you if you're listening to
I don't even
Don't even use my code
I've said that about GoDaddy
A million times as well if you listen to someone else
To show
Then I hope those guys up because they get
A nice little piece of
Of the pie
Of the purchase of that device
That you spend money on
So this is one way that we're helping
Shows with smaller yet
Of course, extremely loyal audience is monetized
So
If you want this
Internet tab, which as you know
Completely nuts about it because it fills the void
For me at least between my
Cell phone, which also happens to be a Nokia
The E61I and my MacBook Pro
Because I want I absolutely need to have
An Ajax compatible Mozilla
Based browser web 2.0 thingy
Because that's what makes the Internet work
These days and it's got it in there with the touch screen
It does Google Docs
It does Gmail in its full-blown glory
It's fast
It's stable, it's built on Linux, it's open source
You can run Skype natively right out of the box
A lot of things that I certainly really really need
And it's quite portable
Yeah, I think there's a dent on mine
What is this?
I was just looking at it in the light
That's kind of weird
Maybe there isn't a dent
Maybe the light was falling on it
Shit, I was kind of creepy
This is
I've started another site called
What the hell is it called?
I think it's called Nokia 800
Screenshots.com
Let me just see
Can you remember?
Of course, I purchased that using my GoDaddy code
DSC3
Got it for under seven bucks
Let me see
Where is it?
Where's my screenshots?
I can't wait, let me see
I have a special
Paves that I made here
Yeah, Nokia and 800
And that's n810
Screenshots.com
And what I'm going to do is
Instead of boring you to death about how much I love the device
I'm going to give you a
Great application of this device
Each time I talk about it
And actually took a screenshot of this
Which is on the Nokia n800
Screenshots.com weblog
Of this new service
It's not a new service
But it's a service I found
Yesterday
Called log me in
And so it's L-O-G-M-E-I-N
Log me in.com
Now I love remote computing
I'm a big fan of V-N-C
I adore Apple's desktop sharing
But of course, setting all that stuff up
Although on the Mac is relatively easy
Once you get down to a couple computers in the house
And you've got your router that has to be configured
And you've got a forward port
Who wants to deal with that shit
I guess kind of what Apple was doing
Back to my Mac, which just doesn't work
Yeah, it works if you're on the same network in the house
But once you move outside your router
All kinds of crap starts to happen
And it just becomes incredibly difficult
So this log me in service, which works for Mac or PC
It enables you to do browser-based
Remote desktop viewing
So you can install this thing on any number of computers
It's free by the way
Of course they try to upsell you a
More functionality and more services
And then you can just take your n800
And you go to log me in.com
You log in. You see all of your computers right there
And a handy little list which ones are offline
Which ones are online. You click on it
And it opens up and then you can start controlling
That computer from your tablet
It's all browser-based. It's unbelievable
And there's like four different ways to connect
You can use I think it does active X
Of course that will be for Windows machines
It has a Java version
It has a Mozilla-based version
Even HTML version
And you kind of got a full-around and see which one works best for you
Which circumstance depending also on your bandwidth
But it blew me away
And of course now I have this super-duper information
Gadget in my hand which is really connecting to
To all the stuff going on on my desktop or any machine
How many times have you thought oh man
Well actually here's how I use it
So I've got the via which is pretty much become the studio machine
And it's hooked up to the mixer and everything
And a secondary monitor pretty much all the time
By the way you can switch between monitors or look at all monitors simultaneously
So whenever I'm sitting elsewhere not in the studio position
If I really want something to play over the speakers
It kind of has to run through the via
But that means I have to get up if I want to pause something
Or change a track or if I want to preview something
And now right from my hand I can just click on the screen
And I make shit happen
You know as only right across the room
But of course I can do this from right across the globe
So check that out for sure
I'll put a link in the show notes to the screen shot
Blogs you could take a look at that also
Log me in dot com
Which is a fantastic service
I can't believe I had found that one yet
Ah see what the N800 tended for me
So if you want to get this thing at a 15% discount
All the details are in the show notes
Of course, but it's pretty simple
You go to nokiausa.com slash n810
N80010
And you can buy any extra accessories
You want etc
This is for the USA only by the way
And you use the
What are they calling it?
They call it something different
On the UK site
Let me just see
I think there they call it a promo code
No, hold on one of they call it
Yeah, they call it the coupon code
And you want to fill in daily source code all one word
And for the UK
Just go to btpodshow.com slash n810
And use the promotion code daily source code
All one word daily source code
Of course, link that will explain all of it to you
Is available in the show notes a daily source code.com
All right
It's shit 21 minutes already
We got to move on
Hi there
Maurice sundah here
Host of the Sunday sundah
The podcast with the best easy listening
Patsafe music
To celebrate 30 episodes of the show
We've got a very special guest for you
In the past episodes
I've played so many great artists that we have collected
The best songs played on the Sunday sundah
And put them on a collection CD
Now comes the best part
You can order it for free
That's right
Get the best of the Sunday sundah for free
Just go over to www.sundahsundah.com
And click on the button free CD at the top of the page
You can order milk for copies
You can give away to your friends or family
So they can enjoy the top of the cream
And pop save independent music
Brought to you by Sunday sundah
And sponsored by the interlocks Sunday media network
And who are on the CD
How about Carmen Tyler
The love spirals
Run rather far
Me too evil
The sun can ship irony
It's a theme song of the show reflection at sundah
And just what kidnse
And many more
Some of the songs from hollow horse
From their new album
Wow, how does that sound?
Put it today, your copy of the best of Sunday sundah
Go over to www.sundahsundahsundahsundah.com
Order now
You know, that's what I'm talking about man
That's packaging
Now I'm presuming by the way
That you've cleared all of that with all the artists involved
I think I've seen email about that floating around
So I'm just going to presume that that's taking care of
So what a great idea
In fact, I'm talking with a couple of newspapers here in the UK
Remember when Princeton is album release
In the, what was it?
Was it the sundae mail I believe?
It was
Yeah, I think it was the daily mail on sundae
Or something like that
They're starving for this type of product
So to be able to get this type of distribution
In these innovative new packaging ways
Is fantastic
So yeah, do do
To send me more information on that just email
Or send to another comment
I'd love to know how you cleared that
How the mechanics of it work
I mean that's
We really can do this people
And record companies who have
Shit loads of people and money
They could be doing so much
More
It's so much smarter
If they just change their thinking a little bit
They're going to fire 2,000 people at EMI
You know, you could probably fire 4,000 people
Sorry about those people, but I'm just saying
If you just worked a little bit smarter
Quick run down of the news
Briefly just some stuff that's going on
That caught my eye
Kind of a krefuffle going on
Between
NATO
Or some of the NATO armed forces
And
Why the hell didn't this open up
Hold on a second
And
The US Secretary of Defense Robert Gates
This is interesting
He was quoted
In the Los Angeles Times
By the way, I'll get to the second
He was quoted saying
That
I'm worried we're deploying
Military advisors that are not properly trained
We're worried we have some military forces that don't know how to do counter insurgency operations
And this was about
Basically the only other three countries that are participating
Britain
The Netherlands
And what's the last country
I mean, there's only a couple countries out there
And the Dutch
Freaked out
Particularly because they just lost two of their brave soldiers
Do defundly fire
In Afghanistan
And
So now Gates is saying
Oh, I was misquoted
I didn't mean it that way
Pull shit
I call him big bullshit out
Of course you said that
And of course, they were
Lured into Afghanistan for rebuilding initiatives
Not to be fighting the Taliban as is happening right now
And what the hell are we doing there any
What exactly is going on in Afghanistan
As far as I can tell
All we're doing is making sure that the
Films don't get burned down so that the drug trade can continue because of course
That's what Wall Street actually runs on
Is all of this drug money flowing through the economy
Speaking of
Wall Street
Here's one for you
City group
Posted a fourth quarter net loss of
17.4 billion
Dollars
And they have immediately and this is here we go
This is the wholesale of Wall Street ladies and gentlemen
I'm not going to say America because Wall Street kind of lives in its own
And its own world
Every single time they make a profit
I think the little guy loses that money and gets screwed
I can't quite
Calculated all the way back but it feels that way to me
They are they've taken out a loan
Well, not really alone. They're selling
Preferred stock for 14.5 billion
Dollars basically they're raising money because
They're they would go under
And who are they raising it from?
Ah, well, let me tell you
They're raising it from foreign investors
The Korea Investment Group
Who, by the way, are investing
6.6 billion
Dollars in Merrill Lynch
There's a couple of Middle Eastern groups
These sovereign wealth funds
You've heard me talk about
So basically the tables the way I see it are now being turned
Where's the United States used to hand out money hand over foot
To foreign countries for infrastructure
Which of course went straight back into the coffers
Of the military industrial complex
And and oil companies and energy companies to build infrastructure
And rail and the telecommunications etc
Now it looks like it's the other way around
Now Wall Street is about to become enslaved
By China, by Asia in general, by the Middle East
By the sovereign wealth funds
When you default on one of those payments
What do you think is going to happen, dude?
Very very interesting
I'm sure we have a financial savant
Out there somewhere who can shed some light on it
Hey, where is uh
Where's the nylon
In all this isn't in that racket
We haven't heard from him for a while
Hmm
I wonder if perhaps that's because
Of the credit crunch
Maybe he lost his job
Hopefully he'll check in soon
And uh
Lots of talk over here in the UK
Energy prices are soaring
I'm talking about
60 pounds
Increase per household normal household
Not talking about this this huge
Box of
Energy slurping
Gadgetry that is known as the curry manner
Normal house
120 bucks extra a year
Because of so called green obligations
Or the geo
As they're now abbreviating it in the press
So because of a reduction in carbon emissions etc
Your bill is going up significantly
Ah, sounds a little bit like bullshit here there
But who knows?
I'm sure the energy companies can you know British gas of course can explain it
But it has
Resparked the debate about nuclear in the UK
And I sent a call out to atomic rod
Our atomic energy savant
If he could shed some light on what's going on
With the UK and nuclear power
Because it sounds to me like they are going to approve new plans to come online
Which of course I said the other day will take until 2020
But it is an interesting turn
And of course
For the debate
It is clean energy
There is an issue with the nuclear waste
And of course there is still lingering which I believe
Are incorrect questions about the safety of nuclear
I think I think that comparing a Chernobyl
Like reactor to the types of reactors that are being built today
Is pretty much black and white night and day
Hot and cold
But let's let the truce savant talk about it
Adam, it's atomic rod atmosphere
Your energy savant
Looking through some articles on BBC this morning
Notice that at 1130
Greenwich meantime
John Hutton
The UK business secretary is scheduled to make an announcement
To the House of Commons
That the UK government has decided that
New nuclear power stations might be just the
Answer to high prices of oil and gas
Just wondered if this announcement
Is making any play on television
Since nothing happens
Unless it's on television
Love you Adam
Bye
Yeah man, love you
No homo
Okay, that didn't really answer the question rod
But I know you're listening
So I'm sure it get back to me on that
Yeah, it's getting play
Of course it gets played on the news
It gets a lot of play on the talk radio
Mainly BBC 4
Radio 4
Something just hit me
I started interrupt this flow
About atomic energy
But I was asked specifically
By the producer of the Chris Moile Show
To send her an email
Detailing why I think I should be on the show
On Chris Moile's show
And set him straight
And also just to
Make nice make friends
Because I got nothing against the guy
But he's basically propagating
Disinformation and misinformation
About him I'd like to compare notes
So you know my agent
Super agent Keith called over to the show
And spoke with this
Woman what's her name
Rachel something or other
Hold on
Rachel Rachel Rachel
What's her last name
Let me just check Rachel Jones or something
Anyway, well that's loading up
So I sent her a real nice email
She hasn't even replied back
You know
Okay if you just want to
If you don't want to do anything or whatever
But just you know how the courtesy
At least call me back
Rachel Jones is her name
That's really quite
Quite rude
Okay back to the energy stuff
Actually, no let me stick with Moiles for a second
Nah fuck it
I was gonna say something nasty
I'm not gonna know
Uhh
I would ever
Atomic Rod send in some worrying foe. Let me know what we're gonna do here
Okay, because clearly this is gonna crunch a lot of people if they have to spend that much extra money a year just on
On energy and I'm sure
Wow, man, what a spiral
Hey, there's a lot more going on in the in the UK and in the EU as well
We have a correspondence of on for that. His name is
Comic strip
Hiya, Adam Flericary. Here is CSB your EU correspondent
So European food safety authority agency has just the 30 minutes that food made of clowns
Of clowns animas is not clowns
Okay, it's clones just so you understand it
Yes, clones of clowns animas is healthy for consumption
Yes, eating clowns is healthy
Yummy
But still genetically ordered food is not kosher, so you know watch
I think unlike in USA where biodes are is subsidized very heavily in EU biofuel or biodiesel is text not
Not subsidized and market segmented and generally by of your biodiesel industry in in EU
Dies out in the Europe and in EU and moves to USA
So you
Yeah, I caught that article too that
That the yeah, I guess it's the EU health administration is said hey, you know eating cloned animals is healthy
How do they know that they really know the long-term's effective that it's not
Are we living in a science fiction movie or what it's freaking me out a little bit
All right, I got to get into the city. I'm getting emails now people saying
We're gonna add this meeting subtract that meeting lots of stuff going on
Glad you stuck with me for today. I thought it was gonna be a little shorter than that we're still around our 40 minutes
By the way, the weather today completely crap in the UK the rain is coming down sideways once again
I'll play another song from the pod safe music now
Something I picked up that I really dig the steering can't hear me on the
Right there
So
Can you feel this?
I'm dying for my chance to live till I let go
Let it go, I can't allow
The melody is where you're
Can you give me?
You wasted all this time to fit the balance
You couldn't be yourself in their eyes
Maybe it's easier to be there
And it all will be alright
But think it's all the way you live your life
You wasted all this time to fit the balance
You wasted all this time
In the middle of the clouds you're flying out
Can you hear me?
I'm fighting for my right to break
Can you feel this?
I'm dying for my chance to live till I let go
Let it go, I can't allow
The melody is where you're
Can you give me before the day ends
Before the sunset between the breeze
And hope will come back
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Think you're welcome
Can you hear me?
Can you feel this?
I'm fighting for my right to break
I'm dying for my chance to live till I let go
Let it go, I can't allow
The melody is where you're
Can you hear me?
I've been on the network for a while
They're from Australia, kick ass man
I love that song
Actually they've now based themselves in Brighton
In the UK, interesting
I flew past Brighton the other day
When I did my little wrecky along the south coast
I saw this before I ended up for today
I saw this program
On the
I think it was a channel four
I believe called the Sandbanks
Pierce Morgan goes to the Sandbanks
And I'd never heard of this place before
It's right underneath kind of like west of Barnmouth
Which you may not know has the warm Gulf stream come
Hits that particular part of the south coast
They even have palm trees in Barnmouth
It's really they have a nice weather there
Or nicer weather than the rest of the country
And this place is like they call the monoco of the UK
And I'm looking at that and I'm like, oh man
It's just amazing what's happening there
So a new destination has been found
That I've been studying up on Barnmouth Airport
Which also has big aircraft coming in
So I got a kind of concentrate before I go there
And the lady P is willing to so who knows
Maybe this weekend if the weather clears up a little bit
Because next week I'll probably be off the San Francisco
I think we've got a board of directors meeting
And some other stuff so
And tomorrow I will be here to bring you a proper
Fubar Friday
I'm stacked up, still could use some musical suggestions
But lots of good stuff ready for you
Including the hit test and an exercise for me
So what more could you want?
Until then my friends
Live your life with passion and enjoy your freedom
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Thanks for watching