Delta Shara Charley, 7-7-9-R.
We don't need enough digging trees in.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-7-9-R.
We don't need enough digging trees in.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-7-R.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-R.
We don't need enough digging trees in.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-7-R.
Delta Shara Charley, 9-R.
We don't need enough digging trees in.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-R.
Delta Shara Charley, 9-R.
We don't need enough digging trees in.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-R.
Life's weak, so we live enough in the dead lives
With my dead be a scar, but this town doesn't have to pay him tonight
These dreams start to seem when we have no word
In all my life, I don't know that I ever hurt your life
I don't know that I ever hurt your life
You and your knowledge are falling together
We'll walk again, you and your knowledge has been paid
We'll walk again, we'll walk again
We'll walk again
I want to wake up, you can't scream
I will know I'll wake up, you can't scream
I want to know that my heart will be there
There's a reason, I'm leaving
I want to wake up, you can't scream
I want to live, I can know what I'm leaving
I want to know that my heart will be there
There's a reason, there's a reason
I'm bleeding, here we are now in the forest sky
We'll walk again, you and your knowledge has been paid
We'll walk again, we'll walk again
We'll walk again, you and your knowledge have been paid
It's the daily source code, episode 779, the Charlie's on, and yes, once again, is a
food bar Friday.
Everybody, how you doing?
Coming here from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford in the United Kingdom, from
the Curry Manor.
It's your buddy, Adam.
They chuckle at the time you're doing.
Oh boy, yes, yes, yes.
Time for a food bar Friday, addition of the daily source code, could not be happier.
Although, of course, it's a very typical food bar because the minute I set up the MacBook
Pro to get to work, and all of a sudden, the levels are off, the sound is all funky.
And maybe it could just be my ears.
I don't know, man.
I've been pretty deeply embedded into the sound for the past week or so.
And actually yesterday, I had a whole show prepped ready to go.
And I decided, you know, as is pretty typical after the weekend, and after we've done kind of
a topic based show, then I want to get all your feedback, and I want to put that into
one program.
So I got a whole bunch of voicemail comments, and they really affected me.
And I actually, well, I'll get to that in a second.
First, I have to blow out a huge May, a culpa boy.
I did some really stupid.
A lot of you noticed it.
Yesterday, I got word from the guys over at drop.io, which, of course, we use all the
time here on the charity for sharing files and PDFs and MP3s and embedded videos, all kinds
of stuff.
It's a drop.io slash daily source code.
And they said, hey, we got something really cool set up for you.
You know, you can now add a notification with a link to your Twitter account.
They'd actually set up a separate account, which was Twitter.com slash daily source code.
And I tried it and it worked.
I added something in perfect.
Oh, this is cool, man.
I'm going to put this.
I'm going to link this to to my Adam Curry Twitter account.
And they went something cool as uploaded.
You know, everyone will know about it.
Well, here's the thing I did wrong.
I tested it by sending a test message that said, let's see if this works from drop.io.
That was a big mistake because then immediately people are like, oh, wait a minute.
Here's a way to basically look like Adam and post stuff.
And they were posted notes on the drop.io slash daily source code.
And it just kind of imploded within like 30 seconds.
Everyone was sending messages through my account, which was exactly what I didn't want
to happen.
It's my own stupid fault for sending the kind of hello world test message.
So I guess I got what I deserved.
And it was this is kind of the audio version of the email and the twitters and the tweets.
I should say that I started receiving.
I don't.
Please.
God.
Please turn off that Twitter stream.
You don't mind heading.
I'm sweaty.
Some fucking messages.
In 30 minutes and still going.
I want to subscribe.
I've emailed you.
Please stop.
I can't believe the only one who he is.
Had you doing it.
I'm not going to bother doing all the rest of it.
Cause you.
As I know.
Nah, I totally messed that up.
I am so sorry.
And a lot of people said I would actually break Twitter doing stuff like that.
Which I guess it could happen considering I have.
What is it like?
I had six sixty three hundred followers.
Let me just check for a second.
I'll betcha.
That number's gone down.
Let me see.
Twitter.com slash Adam Curry.
Let's see.
What does it come up with?
I think it was sixty three hundred six thousand three hundred.
Now I have.
Yep.
Six thousand one hundred and twenty.
Or probably about a good two hundred people.
So.
As shipman, I'm sorry.
You guys can come back.
I've turned it all off.
I had really stopped posting.
Anything on Twitter because so often I'd fire up Twitter or
a Faker, one of these other clients and get time out.
It's all kinds of errors.
And then kind of the spontaneous nature of it just.
Kind of dropped away.
Okay, lots of stuff to talk about.
As I said, mainly your phone calls today.
First, the couple things straight out of the news.
Exxon mobile reported their best quarterly profit.
quarterly profit ever for a corporation ever for a corporation. Okay, for any corporation ever
Beating its own record, by the way. With a total of 11.68 billion dollars in the second quarter. That's three months
That's like $90,000 a second. No a minute. I'm sorry. $90,000 a minute during the quarter.
And then of course the Anglo Dutch company shell oil. Ah, they didn't do too bad either. I presume
still partially owned by the by the royal Dutch family or by the queen. Maybe she salais a little bit
left there. She would only need a little bit to be pretty happy. Quarterly profit. 11.56 billion dollars.
And that's up from 8.67 billion dollars in the same period one year ago. This is a lot of money, okay?
And this is a lot of money. Charles Schumer, Chuck, Democrat from New York says inside the
board rooms at all major oil companies. It's Christmas in July. What's shopping? What's shocking?
He says that big oil is plowing these profits into stock buybacks instead of increasing production
or investing in alternative energy. Yeah, it's exactly what my stomach says. Oh, man. Bandits I tell you.
Massive bandits. Then there's another thing. And by the way, this is all coming off. Most of this is
coming off of drop.io slash daily source code, which has just become my total resource for almost
anything. And I will post this link. I think that this link did actually come from
from the drop. It's a list of banks which have failed recently and a lot of them from this past
week or so. It's about 50 banks here. Let me see. We have banks in California, Nevada, Arizona,
Missouri, Florida, Wisconsin, Louisiana, Connecticut, Ohio, Texas, Arkansas, New Hampshire,
Hanalulu, the Bank of Hanalulu and belly up. I went belly up. What is it? Oh, that went belly
up in 2005. But there's a lot of 2008's July 25th. It's coming down. So on the one hand, we've got
the banks failing massively, just kaput running out of money. The federal reserve has opened up
the till, come on through borrow as much as you want. The oil companies are making huge profits.
And I feel like I've just got shafted up the butt. Anyway, so that's just the kind of news
that I'm seeing every single day and boy the quality that you guys are putting on drop.io slash
daily source code is going up. I really love it. And then of course, the phone call. So yesterday,
you know, and I've been doing a lot of stuff for the Dutch radio things in early in the morning.
And so yesterday, I was like, okay, let's do a show. I'm ready to, you know, I'd
already kind of pre-prept a lot of stuff. I started to listen to some more of the phone calls.
Because of course, there was a lot of them from us since past weekend. And in particular, this
next one, which I'm going to play for you, it was a combination of a whole bunch of things.
I guess the process of my own awakening. And I heard this from California Dave. And I had to,
I went for a walk. I had to go for a really long walk. I laid down for an hour or two to go to sleep.
And then by the time I was kind of down from this confusion, it really was.
And there's a lot more, you know, today we're also going to hear a lot of comments
against the conspiracy theories, which I'm very happy with because I've been waiting for people to
come up and, you know, step up and say, hey, wait a minute, this is going too far. I don't believe it.
Or I have a different opinion. So combine with all of that and what California Dave had to say,
it really just blew me away. And, you know, by the time I was kind of back to any, any version of
normal, it was almost too late because we had conference calls coming up with San Francisco, which is
of course, is a part of my third day job.
I think it was happening around me. None of it mattered. I was ignorant and I was happy being
just since your show might have been open. I've totally taken the red bill. I'm totally
earning none of the red of red at all. Things are now making sense to me. And I've seen
I've seen the world in a different life. Now, on top of that, the reason I, like I said,
the reason I called the ones of thank you, while the reason I want to thank you is because
you helped and give me meaning in life. Before the show, before the thing to you, I was just
another, under-cheating connector. So, doing nothing on my life, I had nowhere to go. I was
happy being in a shit job. Now, you have money to rise. Since the BSC and since listening to you
of now back in school, I'm now working my way towards a bachelor's in political science.
I'm officially joined the libertarian party. I want to be part of that revolution.
You know, and on top of all that, because we're on the show, I'm now still thinking it's
making the country of our great again that I plan on running for office once I graduate.
So, thank you out. They give so much of being there for speaking with a little people
and for being that with a voice when we don't have it. So, again, thank you very much.
One of the things we're really quick about, I just want to ask you, because I am very new to this.
And most of my information I get from you, I get from the BSC and I get from other show
kind of similar to your, that I speak in the truth. But what, where should I look? You know,
I want to reset. I'm hungry for nothing. What would you suggest for newspapers?
News program websites, well, good ones for someone like me, who's dying to learn more,
where can I, what would you recommend to me, and anyone else?
So, yeah, again, thank you very much for the bottom of my heart. Thank you for everything.
And, you know, after me, I'm 29. I'm a little clap on a middle lower clap white male, a total folder,
now in the red row and I'm starting to work for you. So, so you hear that, right? And it just blew me away.
I was like, yeah, of course future president of the United States of America. Why not?
California, Dave? Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah. I love that. And for some, whatever reason, just the
the, the planet, the stars, the moon, everything. It just, it, it, it like blew me away. I'm like,
wow, this stupid show has that kind of impact. But to really hear someone wake up like that,
that's significantly, I was like, hell, yeah, I'm digging this, man. California, Dave,
uh, keep in touch with us. Let me give you some advice, because I did think about this during my walk.
You know, where, you know, you're new to this. And so, I would say, you know, listen to, listen to,
shows that they do feel tried a lot of stuff and can, can give you a highlight. I mean, it can be
really, um, energy consuming to follow up conspiracies. And by the way, I'm not going to say
conspiracy theories, because they're all the conspiracy theories. Hey, you know, I have a book here on
the bookshelf, which is, uh, the 911, uh, commissions report. That's a theory. It's a conspiracy theory.
Just a different one. Um, so, you know, listen with caution. And really, the place I could send you,
the best place, if you aspire to be president of the United States, which you've got it all in
you, man, absolutely. Um, this document called the Constitution, go have a look at that and compare
everything that's happening around you right now in the United States, compare that California, Dave,
to what you read in the Constitution. And that should be a great reference manual for you. And
by the way, everybody out there, go ahead and pick up a copy of this thing. The founding fathers
had some pretty good ideas. And, uh, so maybe you listen a bit of the source code. Maybe you should
check out, uh, the, uh, campaign for liberty, uh, which is, uh, Dr. Ron Paul's latest initiative.
And of course, so we'll be talking later on about the rally for, for the Republic, which I'm taking
part in. Um, and, uh, and, and the Constitution, that's really it, man, California, Dave,
will be a great president. I can't wait. Keep us up to speed on what's going on. Will you
please? Oh, I'm proud of you, casting with Adam Curry. Hey, it is a full bar. Hey, Adam,
it's time for hit this number 132. Okay, okay. Hey, we're going to start right away with intro.
Number one. Oh, easy. I got, I know, this one. That would be, uh, ABC, is it, it's either the
look of law, I think it's the look of love ABC. Number two. Oh, no, Torea, Durand, Durand.
Yeah, for these songs from like 89, 91, 91, maybe, 90, and the final one is number three.
Uh, the Peshmode enjoyed the silence. Yes, I think I've made it. I think I got six out of six.
Way too easy, John. I know all of these. And here are the answers.
And this is answer number one.
Uh, one smokey sings. All right, five out of C. That was smokey sing. That was fun.
ABC is answer number one. And this is answer number two.
Durand Durand. Song is also from
the Peshmode. Durand Durand, Torea's answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
This is the Peshmode. This song from
The Peshmode is answer number three. We've enjoyed the silence from 1990.
And this is for hit test number 132. So, Adam,
what are you doing? I'll be honest, I got five out of six. I got ABC's title wrong, but I
knew it after the facts. So, five out of six,
John for this week's 132. All righty, the answers to this hit test. And then the older hit test as well.
And also the links to iTunes, so you can buy the tricks,
feature the hit test online. I'll have to be found at hittest.meepio.com.
Adam, thanks for playing again. Thank you, my friend. Everyone else, again. Thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for another hit test. So, until then, take care. Have fun.
And remember to try to think with your heart. Bye-bye.
Info, y'all, let that come. Jay and P.O.L.V.T.
Honestly, I got to tell you that the sound sounds,
everything sounds off today, but it's just particularly when I play some music,
no, no, whatever. It's football. What can I tell you? As I promised,
going through tons of your phone calls that have come into the voicemail lines,
you can always find those in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com or curry.com,
or on numerous places across the interwebs.
So, some different thoughts coming through the pipeline this time.
And I can tell, you know, we started off with the awakening by switch foot.
We heard California day of awakening. I think this next guy, I forget his name, but we'll
hear in a second. I think he's very close to awakening. And I think he's struggling. I think he's
going through what a lot of people are struggling with right now. Listen to this. This is a comment
on the Lindsey Williams story about how he witnessed how the oil was manipulated in order to save
the US dollar, you know, a quarter of a century ago. I think it was like 20 25 years ago.
And he's back on the scene talking about this very topic. So, here comes some headwind, I guess,
for the direction I'm headed in, but perhaps it's just a tough awakening. Let's check it out.
And I know you're getting this stuff, you know, you're publishing all this crap.
And it's not necessarily fact, and you're just throwing it out there, but there's some big, big
holes. Somebody is either lying out there, their bum hole, or they're just making shit up,
or it's just completely rumored fabricated. Okay, so you got, you got that wind,
you guys, you know, last guy. You see a preacher up there, you worked around the little rigged.
And he says that we have little rigged, oil reserves in the last guy.
Huge oil reserves. He found that out. We can't talk about it. We can't pump it because if we do,
it'll mess up the US dollar. And he said that the Saudi Arabia, we need Saudi Arabia to buy our
oil in dollars. And for each barrel they buy it after buy a little bit of our debt. I don't even
understand that part. Yeah. And I have to admit, it's at the face of it. It's really complicated.
When you start putting dollars down on the table and cups of oil and you start playing the game
and try and see how it works, how the how the trading mechanisms works. I mean, I actually had
bankers show me how swaps and derivatives worked in exactly that same way by giving me a dollar
and then holding on to a pound and then showing what a derivative swap is. You really have to get
down to that basic. So the deal that Henry Kissinger made in the early 70s with the with the
Saudis was, look, we're going to buy your oil. But you're going to only sell it in dollars.
And we're going to pay you a nice amount of money for this oil. But with that, you're going to buy
our national debt. Okay. So that doesn't mean that we're not, you know, that they're reducing the debt
by buying it. They're actually underwriting this debt. They're buying our debt, which is how we've
been able to write up all of these huge deficits. That's the closest and the simplest I can get to
explaining that part. Let's continue. Okay. Maybe that's true. And then he said, I am that's
an oil bank set the price for the oil. So it comes out of the ground. They say $5 a gallon or $150
a barrel. We pay $5 a gallon. Well, hold on. It's not exactly like that. And I agree that he
doesn't explain that how that works. I think what he's trying to tell us is that the world bank
or the IMF tell the Saudis, here's what you're going to ask for it today. And that the price is set
then then and there. And then of course, there is speculation. And there's some real cost. I mean,
refining oil is no joke. I mean, those refineries cost the easily $8 to $10 billion. And we haven't
built enough of them. So there's definitely all kinds of supply and demand issues there.
But if you look at the whole Lindsay story, he also talks about a point and I did go back in
their historical charts. When one of these guys called them up and said, Hey, Lindsay, check this out,
oil is going to go down the 10 bucks watch. And I looked it up and around that period of time,
whether Lindsay made it up or whether it actually did it half in the way he said it did.
Oil and did go down to about $10.5 $11 at one point just around the time period he was talking about.
So I and I'm also not sure how that works. That to me, if there's a hole in the story,
it's right here because I'm not, I just don't understand. I do have a call into my buddy
Captain Dan who, and I actually, I sent him a text message and he did call me earlier. I missed his call.
So we won't know until next week, probably. I want to talk to him. But I said,
you know, based upon some reports I've been seeing, does it really cost $80 to get one barrel of oil out of the
ground? Because that's what these oil companies are saying. You know, the same guys that they're just
posting $10 billion plus profit for three months worth of business. Profit. More than 10,
and more than 11 billion per company. Because I, you know, if you believe the Lindsay
Williams story, it's anywhere between five and eight bucks of a per barrel to get it out of the
ground. So that's the tough one for me as well. But I'm just trying to follow the trail all the way
back. So I, let's just call that a definite black hole that needs to be addressed. So and supposedly
that money is going to pay off our debt. That's why they raised it. Well, our debt isn't going down.
Right. Okay. So that's what I just said. Right is that they buy our debt. They basically
underwrite parts of our debt. That's, that's what the deal is there. So you get the charge
where you want. We'll make you guys wealthy beyond your wildest dreams. But you've got a support
us financially. It's not even a little bit since the spike since I went up to 150. And then he said,
are you said to eat said did another recording? The Indonesia and Russia have these big oil reserves.
They're going to start pumping oil. And that's going to kill the dollar. But then he said,
that that's the ultimate goal is to kill the dollar so that we could merge Canada, Mexico,
and the United States into a big Theresa. Yeah. I believe the merging is part of the, of the
overall plan. I've just been hearing about it too much for too long. About the North American union
that that would be a spin-off or derivative of the North American free trade association.
But yeah, in this corridor that goes from Mexico all the way up to Canada. I'm sure you leave
heard about all this stuff. So I think that that's always been in the planning. But how to put it
together. And even the Canadians are making jokes. Now I saw a TV show. This also was on the drop
drop.io slash daily source code. They're making jokes about about this North American union.
And it actually happening. Although you don't really read any congressional documents about it.
But that I think is really happening. Now the whole thing with the money, you know, it was bound
to happen. I mean, people have been warning against this for a long time. Congresswoman Wrong
Paul has been warning against this bubble that's going to explode. He said, you know, this has been
going for 30 years. This isn't something that just happened. This is essentially what happens when
you just keep printing money. And, you know, have it kind of flimsyly underwritten by oil transactions
that are that are being done in dollars. So everyone needs dollars to buy oil.
That's what's been propping it all up. So this is that's really nothing new. It's just it may be
it's now being used as a great tool to get this North American union together. Because then we
have the North American union. We just recently, the president of the European Union,
Sarcosi announced the Mediterranean Union. And then, of course, we need an Asia-Pacific union.
And then on top of that, oh, we need is one government that kind of deals with everything.
You know, what did I call it? Yeah, new world order. I do think that's for real. And it's not
something that happens overnight. There's North American union. I don't think we're going to wake up one
day. Oh, here it is. But there's a couple more stepping stones to be taken. I think we'll be able
to identify them as they come along. It's the goal is to kill the dollar. Why does it matter who
comes oil where? Why wouldn't it even matter if Iran started selling their oil in your rows?
If the goal is to kill the dollar. In fact, the dollar is already dead. We are heading for the
second depression. Nothing else needs to be done. So, you see, there's someone waking up.
You got that man. You got it. You got it. You're right on the money with that. It's just going to
be used as a tool. So turn it around. And by the way, what we predict today, what we talk about
today could change tomorrow, you know, the way this is being done, this is fluid, you know,
as I said, it's a very long process and the ultimate goal. I do believe that really in my heart,
not just conspiracy theory, but the idea of breaking the world up into unions. I mean, this goes back
to the United Nations. This has always been the idea and then to have a government on top of everything.
Starfleet Command is what it is. These rumors. What do you call them theories? They just don't
make sense. It doesn't add up. Not that. I don't know. I'm so confused. I want to understand this
atom, but it just doesn't make sense. It's hard. It doesn't make sense. At some point, you've got
to protect your family, your country, even a little bit, you know. Oh, man, that time is coming for
sure. In fact, that time is now and what you're going through right now, my friend, that's the awakening.
That is exactly right. And you're going to see that by paying attention and listening closely
and listening to the code words and brushing up on the Constitution, it wouldn't hurt and compared
it to what you're witnessing right now around you. And yeah, check out a couple of sites.
Watch a couple of videos. Google a couple of things. You might even want to go back to,
let's see Google Oklahoma City. See if any information that you thought was true in
95 and 96 and 96, I think. See if that is change. If there's any other differences of opinions,
see how that relates to more recent events. Think the information is out there. The powerful
staff power, the ritual staff bridge, but the spirit of fucking insane insane, they don't make sense.
It's like, I know it's, I know what you mean. And by the way, this guy called it in three or four
times with basically the same message. But, and I picked out what I thought was the best version of it.
I know. It feels really weird because you don't want to, it's like science fiction.
You read stuff. You're like, it's can't be true. It's on the internet. It probably isn't true.
But when you get guys like, uh,
Blorush, Blorush Pack.net, a Lush Pack.com, I think it is.
Linden, Linden, Lorush, L-A-R-O-U-C-H-E, who's an economist who's been predicting all of this,
but this guy went really far. He's like, Barack Obama works for the British and he works for
the British and he's financed by George Soros and, uh, and Barack will never become president,
uh, and he really goes into very calm detail as to why. You know, that's another, and in fact,
I put that on curry.com just the other day. And I said required viewing. You have to check that one out.
All right. Let's move on with the, uh, with the phone calls coming in for this football
Friday, Disney, the Charlie.
Yeah, Adam, it's on the line, the episode, and then he mentioned an illustration podcast about
Hurricane Katrina, uh, I mean, how they spent in various different things.
So I did notice, um, it's not really getting much widespread coverage.
Now, by the way, the truth or the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, let's call it facts or better fact,
are definitely be reported on everything I've been talking about, but
until it's been on the front page of every single newspaper,
until every single news magazine has done a piece on it. Within a certain period of time,
all close together, it just isn't news. There's too many sources. No longer is it that you get something
on CBS evening news, uh, prime time news is they used to call it on the Tiffany network. No longer
does that make it the truth. It has to be in all the papers. It has to be the buzzword of the day.
And it's very, very difficult with just one or two journalists and one or two editors
letting something slip through. But yes, um, things that are not widely reported doesn't mean that
they're not happening. Doesn't mean that they, I mean, look, people have to tow the corporate line.
It's real easy to, uh, to manipulate how a company works because every company is made up of people.
And those people in turn created DNA. And if DNA at the top is, hey, we don't talk about this,
then believe me, that filters down. You don't have to send any memo. Let's just how it works.
Let's see what you were talking about, though. Well, as you know, when they were busy doing all
loosening and all the pillaging and burning shit down, I think I got close to everything got really desperate.
Yes, I do. Well, if it's quite interesting, though, there was a few reports. We, uh, as soon as
they, uh, make up to the rich guess of the places where people are, notably rich in the law that
is around them. As soon as they had the right militias got to write areas, cops have gone through
out with everywhere. Yeah, I'm going to see you. Yeah, I'm going to see you.
I'm going to go for a cup of all I'm going to give you. So, uh, there's a bit, no going on that,
then initially makes the eye. And there was a lot of fucking suppression of,
basically people not were seriously needed help. And they just offered it to the rich.
And, uh, yeah, the thing is, though, got a couple of room. They don't have room for a long time,
I bet. Well, British Empire was built on. Take care. Really more out. Bye.
Yeah. Well, the British Empire is pretty evil as well. If you look at the, the history of it.
But, uh, oh, yeah, when Kanye West went on, it was Kanye West. Wasn't it who went on television
in the States and said George Bush hates black people? He was only half right. George Bush hates
black people and white people. He hates all, he hates all people who are poor. Absolutely.
It's good to see some savants checking in. Here we go.
Yo, yo, hey, hey, come on in. I had an initially prolific program out from San Francisco,
Antonio, went to Lexina. That looks like the EU. The Britain has ratified the Lisbon Treaty.
This is the Lentogas. Time to independent. And therefore, I assumed it. Correct. Um, that's all
Christmas. Yeah, that's pretty unfortunate. That, uh, that millionaire dude who was, uh, suing the
Labor Party for lying about holding a referendum. Um, unfortunately, he lost.
And, uh, there was something I want to tell you about the European Union. But, uh, crap.
I actually had to restart the mac and to have lost the link. Uh, former president of the EU.
I, like, I forget the guy's name. Uh, crap. I forget it. I'll do it on Monday. It was just amazing
something he said about the Lisbon Treaty, uh, which was actually published on the European
Parliament website. I got to find this link. Um, where he said, oh, you know, we just, uh, took the
original tree that was voted down by the Dutch and the French. And we shuffled the round broke it up into
all kinds of amendments and protocols and guidelines. And, uh, and that way, we avoided a, uh,
a referendum in any, in any other country. Except, of course, Ireland who very courageously voted
no. And, uh, it's, it's being shoved down their throats, my friends. You watch. It's really
important for these, uh, for these, you know, these people in power to get this thing, uh, pushed through.
Now, let me just say one thing about the Lisbon Treaty and the UK. The UK has a couple of exceptions.
The main one being that they say they do not, uh, accept the, um, the human rights portion of the
Lisbon Treaty. Oh, I was like, let me just get rid of that. Please. Um, so there's a whole, um,
uh, draft constitution for human rights. It's a part of the Lisbon Treaty. And the UK has a special,
uh, a special little deal in their contract. We actually a couple of them. One is, uh, they don't
have to adhere to that. So they can set their own laws. They don't have to be a part of, um, of the,
of the stuff that I find personally quite scary, you know, for instance, um, uh, there's no, there,
there, there, there, there is no death penalty in the European Union, except there are a couple
of exceptions. Uh, if you're killed while resisting arrest, uh, then that will not be deemed as any,
any legal kill. Uh, of course, the UK has all of their own initiatives and, uh, and plenty of it
going on. Um, but this is done because I, I believe that the, the UK actually, um, want to be
separate from the European Union and want, don't want to be a part of the demise of, uh, or
basically protect their own people on, uh, on the aisles from the demise that is coming. And a part
of that is also, of course, not actually using the euro while still being a part of the European
Union. And this goes back to that story about Soros, who, um, presumably, according to, uh, a linen
lorush. And you got to see this guy talk, um, people are trying to get a hold of me. That's the,
that's the E71 ringing, by the way. Nice little, uh, little, uh, voicemail message. Tone.
So according to Lyndon Lorush, uh, George Soros actually, oh, yeah, you know, when, uh, the story
that he almost broke the Bank of England, well, he was actually apparently working in conjunction
with the Bank of England to set England up to not be a part of the, uh, of the euro. And how that
exactly work, I don't know if I can clue. But I, you know, there's enough pieces on the board there
that I'll follow that trail and find out exactly how it worked. Um, so I think, uh, the UK is actually
trying to steer clear of a lot of the shit that they've now ratified into existence, which still shouldn't
make any difference because remember it has to be all 27 member states that ratified the treaty. And if one
of them isn't ratifying, then it should basically just go away. And we should continue under the
most strict treaty, or the niece treaty, I believe we're under right now. Uh, and that also, yeah,
who the hell knows? I don't understand how it works either. That's that's why we should get rid of it.
If we don't understand it, I, will you know you're being fucked somewhere?
Ah, all right. Let me, uh, let's switch over to something else. I got to give somebody some advice here.
Hi, Adam, my name is Raymond Hauss, a Central email, um, earlier today in regards to the mtv blog.com
The main name dispute I'm having, uh, with mtv, uh, the senior senior council has contacted me
in regards to swimming, if I don't, uh, turn over to domain. Um, um, and, uh,
read that you were in a similar position, uh, a few years ago, and I just wanted to get, uh,
I guess this year, um, feedback or comments, I'm sure, right, busy. Um, but if you did have a minute,
um, that would be great. I'm going to buy back to my email. All right. So, uh, let me help you out here,
buddy. Um, that was a very different circumstance, uh, 15 years ago. I think it was 93, 90, yeah, 93.
And I had actually read just at mtv.com with their permission. Um, now, when I quit,
they then immediately sued me for that name. And if they'd asked for it, the idiots, I would have given
it to them. Just ask that I could keep Adam at mtv.com as an email address, but, uh, that didn't work.
So, uh, they went to court and uh, and I counter sued, uh, because, uh, you know, because they were trying
to strong army and we had certain agreements. Now, of course, we said a lot of court and I'm not
allowed to talk about that anymore. But the, the way they, the procedure they took, which was pretty
fair, you know, all things considered, uh, was, uh, the land amact, which means, uh, consumers could
be confused when they show up at mtv.com. And they see, like an mtv guy, even if he's an xmtv guy,
I'm talking about music entertainment, that could be perceived as confusing. So, of course,
they were right on that. It's just the whole, the way they went about it and the agreements we
had made is where they messed up. And I was able to take it to a press and kind of a David Goliath
type of way, which didn't suit them at all. Now, if you register mtv blog.com, you can understand
that they're going to do the exact same thing. And it's, it can be deemed confusing to consumers.
So, uh, forget about it. Just give it up. You know, uh, maybe a register mtv blog.com,
mpty, something like that. Vee. I don't know. Just forgive it up because they'll suck your
dry and they'll, uh, you just don't want to do it. Please. Oh, boy, I'm only halfway through the list.
Are you still with me? Uh, just a quick plug for rally for the Republic. We're going to get
together with a whole bunch of, uh, whole bunch of folks out in, um, Minneapolis. Parallel convention
to the Republican convention taking place. This is a Dr. Ron Paul's initiative. There's two dates.
There's September 1st and September 2nd. September 2nd is going to be the big who how blow out
in the stadium 15,000 plus people. Uh, but the day before, we're going to have a, we're going to
rock out in some football, uh, on some football field. I'm not quite sure of the details. But if you
go to rally for the Republic.com, uh, that's where you find out all the information tickets are on sale.
Uh, I think it's like $17 and 76 cents, you know, all kind of cool, cool numerology happening.
And I think you'll find a lot of like-minded people there if you happen to be in the neighborhood.
I'm certainly going to be there and I'm looking forward to meeting all kinds of new people and
maybe some, uh, some folks who, uh, um, it will listen to the Charlie. All right. Let's hear
someone happy. Happy, I said. I'm pulled by Johnny from New York. Check it out. And it pulls
out Johnny. Two months and 2000 miles driving the grease car and loving every fucking free
mile of it. Hell yeah. It's not for everybody who said that before. But, uh, just regarding
you're tracking the price of oil, don't be so, uh, don't, don't get all happy when it drops
20 dollars of barrel. Because this is what happens. And it's happening in the past.
First of all, the gas and maybe you'll go down a little bit, you know, let's just take
those down to $4 a gallon. You know what that is? That's the government's way of making us just
we feel good all of sudden because it went from $450 to $4 and they did that for us. That's bullshit.
It's never going to go down below four. It's only going to go up and we'll continue to take it in the
forever. You know, I, I got to agree with you there. Although it has dipped a little bit before
below $4, but yeah, I think you're right. That'll totally agree with. And particularly
looking at these profits that we're just announced today. Yeah, absolutely. They're controlling
that price. And yes, you're right. Ain't no probage. You will continue. So, everyone please choose
your own pill in your own way to fix this thing. You know, mine was a grease car. Somebody else might
be a previous or some other kind of hybrid. Somebody might buy a bicycle, but just do something
for fuck sake. Those are Johnny checking out. Anybody want to know about grease cars, check it out
at the greasebens.wordpress.com. Oh, bulls and John. All right, man. Thank you.
Yeah. So, I'm doing, I'm doing my own thing. I'm testing out these, uh, this hydroxy stuff with
the hydroxy booster. By the way, I won't have time today because and I'm going to do a separate show
on it. Chris from Levittown called in with about, you know, he did two times three minutes on the
voicemail. An excellent, excellent analysis of the hydroxy booster, which by the way, he says,
will not work. But I really like that comment. And as I said, I'm going to roll that out for
your next week on a chuckle on a chuckle. There we go. We've got a new one. Um, because he really
explains how the thing works, even though he says it doesn't work. And let me just say this,
um, based upon the feedback that I'm getting. Look, there's a couple of things about this hydroxy
booster. All right. If you don't know what I'm talking about, just Google it hydroxy booster. I've
got one installed on, uh, on the jack and it works. Uh, if I don't go faster than 110 kilometers per hour,
I've already seen 29% efficiency in my gas usage. And that's just less gas I have to put in.
Now, this could be a combination of things. One, it could be because of all of the tinkering and adding
new fuel source that the onboard computer has actually gotten a little more efficient. That's very
possible. They usually set these things to be efficient for emissions and not necessarily for
how efficient you can be on your engine. Um, and of course, that I using hydrogen or a version of
that being injected in. So it could be that the computer chip is adjusted itself. Um, again, I'm not
not, I'm not getting the data off of the computer chip. I'm looking at how after X amount of kilometers,
I'm seeing how much fuel I have to put into a full tank. That's the simplest way to do it
it's the way I do it in aviation. I, you know, my life depends on it. So that's one. Um, it could
also be that I'm more conscious of how I'm driving and maybe I'm driving in a, uh, a less wasteful
manner, very, very possible. It could be completely, uh, unconscious. It could be happening in my
subconscious. I don't think so, but it's possible. Then there's another option. Shit could actually
work. I've seen a lot of energy going into how many amps, the booster pulls, how much, uh,
hydroxy gas is created, how many liters per minute. It could actually just work. It's a thread
will stay on here. Okay, I promise you. Uh, hold on a second. This next one. Um,
yeah, what the hell is Charles? It's Charles a drunken lunter. Even though it's, it's a little
off topic. Let me bring him in for a second. Adam's, Charles, you know what I'm saying?
I completely, if I go, I was going to tell it. Anyway, um, I'm on your way, which is where
young man called Benville, dad, and killed recently. I've, um, uh, one of my, coming through, uh,
London, I often walk places about five miles, five and up miles, and my home to the very
centre of the boat, where I do Charles is talking on his iPhone and needs a little work on
the acoustic sound when walking down the street. Oh, my word. Oh yeah, I remember I was saying
I was going to be there. So what do you like, home to the 3G? Yeah. You know, it's all right,
half the ball. No great. But, um, what I would really like to see is that the contract,
my GPS movement, so I can see how far I've walked. We'll also be useful for people who know
about it, talking, um, you know, of an app like this. Would you put the word out? Someone
to make an app like this? Oh, just basically instead of tracking, instead of, you know,
me following a route, it will show me the route. I'll, uh, I'll also just enjoy the fact that
I can then do really big pictures. I, you know, I walk in places, I can try and draw or shape
uh, make it and sell out my name across London. You don't mean something like that. Anyway,
if you're ready. Oh, man, Charles. Okay. So what Kurt Charles got his iPhone 3G,
he says it's all right. And boy, I cannot tell you how happy I am. I chose for the Nokia E71.
I'm so happy with that choice. I really, really am. Because here's what I discovered the other
day. I'm a big drive off to, uh, off to Europe. I use something called Wayfinder. And I like Wayfinder
as a GPS device because you can load it onto your Nokia phone. Uh, by the way, the E71,
this, the, the, the, the GPS chips. Man, they come the life so quick. I mean, I, I was going through
tunnels. It would like boom within two seconds of coming out of the tunnel. I've got my GPS
fix in, uh, fantastic. So I use Wayfinder, which is an online service. And what I like about it is you
don't actually have to download any maps. What it does is it downloads maps on the go as you need them.
But it has another feature built into it. This wayfinder. And I think it's only, I think it does
Windows mobile as well, but certainly Nokia phones. You can track it. So because it's already
downloading maps, it knows how to get online and knows how to talk to home base to the server.
But you can also have it track your movement. And every, um, I think it's based on time,
not necessarily on, well, maybe it may be this based on distance. I have to find out, uh,
exactly how it's configured. But, uh, I tried it for this trip. You said on, you said a little,
uh, preference that says turn on a Google Earth tracking. And when I got home loan, behold, I went
to my wayfinder.com. And, uh, there were some, uh, KML files sitting for me. And I double clicked them
and opened up, opened up Google Earth. And there was my entire trips set with intervals. I believe
if it's not that way, it should be something you could set. Um, so I could actually see the software
from time to time saying, hey, I need to connect to the network may I connect. You can make it
connect automatically. But I kind of like knowing when it's connecting, particularly on the road,
when I'm roaming, because that could be pretty devastating, uh, it cost-wise. But every single time
it wants to connect, this basically sending a little ping back to the server and adding an entry
into this KML file. So you could easily take a picture at the same time and you could go back later
and synchronize that. Um, so it exists already. Uh, is there an app for the iPhone that does that?
I doubt it. Again, a reason why I'm really, really happy. And I'm an Apple lover, not a fighter,
but still very happy. I chose for the E71.com extra.com extra.com extra.com extra.com extra.com extra.com extra.com extra.
Time once again for news from our EU correspondent, CSB, take it away. Hello, Adam, I'm on free.
Okay. So your opinion is considering to impose visas on citizens of USA,
where visiting Europe, because USA is fucking up. The Russians in the visa free movement in
very, very serious. So for example, introducing USA is from January 2009,
a requirement to register three days before departure to USA, killing last minute flights.
Oh, dude, tell me about it. I know there were a whole bunch of people who were leaving
people airport in Amsterdam to go to the states and they had their kids,
listed on one of the parents' passports. And a lot of them, like thousands,
has said, you know, you can't fly because you will not be able to enter the United States unless
your kid has their own passport. So you can't get a visa like on a Sunday if you're flying out.
You can't usually can't get a visa over immediately on the spot anyway. So a lot of people
couldn't, and I apologize as an American citizen. I apologize for this idiocy. I really do. Oh, man.
Yes. So now the table is being turned, and I guess all diplomats have to get a visa to come to
Europe. It isn't nuts. Are we crazy in this way? And you say it's using divide and conquer by
not granting visa waiver to all EU countries. So you say it's also a piece of that's a
Poland EU member said we don't feel any danger from Iran and rejected the demands of your
state, locating to several rockets there. So as you see, not always well in USA, EU relations.
Yeah, that's for sure, man. And I'm trying to understand something else. The federal reserve apparently
has a line of credit with the European Central Bank. So now Europe is guaranteeing money for,
I guess indirectly, for banks that have just been going crazy and are failing. And they recently
up that amount from 50 billion to 55 billion dollars. I'm not quite sure why the 10% increase.
I'm thinking maybe it has something to do with how interest rates are determined. That was some
kind of settlement for something, but I'm just not quite sure what it is yet. Oh, boy, boy. How
I yearn for some economics of honest.
Casting from the biggest climate in the world. From London's L's court, it's the great British
beer festival beer cast with 350,000 points of beer, cider and perion offer. There's only one man
for the job. Mark Fitts. Hi, Adam, the 2008 Great British beer festival starts on Tuesday,
the fifth August and once again, RB presenting the GBBF beer cast from the show. The show runs
until Saturday, the 10th and RB going behind the scenes, talking to some of the 2000 volunteers
that set up and run the festival. We'll be checking out the champion beer written competition,
finding out how the campaign for real oil is getting on in the midst of an economic downturn.
And we'll be visiting some of the more unusual areas, like the children's playroom,
because parents are encouraged to bring their kids along too, which is good laugh,
and I'll be tasting a beer or two. If you're going to be at home, we're not jumping
the train from G-town to London, catch the two to old's court, and let me treat you to a beer
or two. It'll be sort of big hair meets large amounts of liquid refreshments. Anyway, to catch the
beer cast and hear last year's editions, head to beercast.btpodshow.com. And remember, I've got a
print glass here with your name on it, so come pick it up. Cheers and fulver.
For more information on the great British beer festival and on joining camera, the campaign for real
oil, check out the website, www.gbbs.org.uk. That's gbbs.org.uk.
You know, you're just no matter what you say, you just can't be free beer.
I'll do my darkness, my friend. I got a small upcoming travel, but it'll be great to hang out with you.
I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to
be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free,
I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free,
I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm going to be free, I'm
I'll be passing, if thanks for all the eggs
And the drums and the nannies and the guns
And the bombs on the kites
Thanks for all the eggs
And the floods and the floods and the drugs
And the ban and all the lights
Thanks for all the eggs
And the eyes and flu
I'm for you, I'm for making our slaves
Thanks for all the eggs
I'll pray for me, my fitness
Cause I've hit a ratchet
Come in, I'd share, like clear patcher
How you can have a capture
The dawn of it's stature
I'm even under my light
My grid, that jerk
Where'd you look, bombs like a nickel true
And then the gas blew up the coordinates
And my man, look
As I see, the sky got once to kill you
If you're queer, I'll review it to you
And I'm mine, I ran a hole
I ran, if you were a dog
Because you haven't got a soul
I ran, if you were a dead baby
You should count your stuns
And see, I'll lock you up
So if you kids run, let it end you up
So I'm time's rest
And the worst cracker
I can say this, cause I'm sure
You ain't shit, we've been advised
Quimbed, we have like a depressed
When we say thanks for all the ice
And the bombs in the guns and the arms
And the bombs on the crimes
Thanks for all the ice
And the lies in the wives and the guys
Who be dying, it's tight
Thanks for all the ice
And the creativity, and for me
I'm bringing on a break
Thanks for all the ice
One, no, fuck it, time
And the bombs in the guns and the guns
And the bomb is on the ice
And the lights are all the ice
And the floods and the bloods
And the drugs in the ban and all the fights
Thanks for all the ice
And the lies in the wives and the wives
And the mic and the sights
Thanks for all the ice
Ever since I played Akira the Don's
The Banks are song
The Banks is against us
Play that uh
We could two ago
Have had a nice little email chat with him
And they said dude, you might want to check out this song
Which
The hell is that?
It's on the track
Let's listen
Let's hear the boy
You can do it all boy
You're the one that bad
You won't step out of the threshold
Because you're a skier
That's freaky
That is really freaky
He said
I think it was on the
Maybe it was in her scope record
I think he said he uh
He played this track for Jimmy Ioveen
Who then freaked out and kicked him off the label
Thanks for all the aids
Yeah
The UK is pretty interesting these days
There was a piece on
It was kind of like a cops show on the
I think it was channel 4
It was ITV channel 4 ITV the other day
It was one of the commercial stations
And it was about drug dogs
And they had these
This is amazing what's going on here
So if you're on the on the subway
Which they call the tube here
In the UK
And so when you come out of the underground
You go up the subway
You go up an escalator
Then to the basic platinum to the station
Right from the platform you write up
And they've got these drug dogs there
And they sniff everybody as they walk by
Now remember this is a subway in London
Okay
And these drug dogs will stand
And they sniff if they smell anything
Then you get pulled aside
And they get a citation
Or we certainly get questions and searched
Because I saw that
And what was amazing to me
Is that these were people who had like a little baggy
of something on them
Just like the minuscule amounts
And at one point this dog is neat
And if you know anything about a tube station
The UK you understand the distance here
So these dogs are right
At where you come off the escalator
And also this dog is like freaking out
And he's trying to find something
And the dog goes
Pass the exit doors outside
On to a part
Was a grading outside
This must have been like 100 feet away at least
And finds a little roach
That had just been put out by someone
That's how sensitive their noses are
And there was also some alluding to
Bees being used you know
Bees as in honey bees
That they're now being trained to find
Just sniff out marijuana and hasheesh
Yeah that'll stop you
If you get a whole bunch of bees circling around your head
Anyway
Thanks for all the aids
Man, talk about some political stuff on the chalk
Huh?
Let's do something else here
And I'm just checking if there's not what side of shiitown
No you'll chuck it
You'll be here you're back from your vague chain
The song I was for
Songs yes
Nice
That's great
Hey let's say just want to say really quick
Listen to your show today and I loved the commentary
You played at CNBC and then you pause it
And then you say what they really mean
That is brilliant
Look at man brilliant
Keep it up
I'm old school here
So we love that
Need it great
I hope you win
And that worked for us
And they worked for us
And I'm wide awake and dreamland
We could add that one as well
Either Adam C Curry
Don't be seen then
You know, it's Mark Sinkle
And a while back of your members
He's really Adam
I think he's had one
He's showing something
Sounds like he's on an eye
Followed 3G
Cut now
Holy herb is cooking to your head
Oh yeah
And all ideas like UFOs and things like that
Now I'd better if you were to ask
You're listening to how many of them have seen UFO
I think you get a pretty big response of people saying
Yeah, it's not something a little weird
Like I certainly have seen something weird
I don't know if you'd call it UFO
I don't know if you'd call it
I don't know what you would call it
But anyways
They work for us not be aliens
But you know what I mean
All right
Love you normal but bye
Well, they may be two sides of the same coin
I don't know
Yeah, it's a good idea
All right, let's find out how many chuckle heads
have seen something they found to be
Strange supernatural or unexplained
Oh, I'm done with that
By the way, another astronaut came out
Today saying that he's supporting the other astronaut
The guy who was the six-man to walk on the moon
That he too saw aliens
And they were in discussion with astronauts
What the hell is going on
Now granted these guys are all 70, 80 years old
But they don't seem like fools to me
You know, there's still that theory going around
That we may be in for a good old fashioned
Scared from the aliens that would be essentially a false flag operation
Who the hell knows?
I'll just believe the dollar is actually going to do a great
Disappearing act
That one I'm done with all the other stuff
Wouldn't surprise me if it happened
Not laying awake about it though
Surprising amount of response that came in
Through my quest for answers
No one is in the DSC audience
As far as I can tell, let's purchase one of these great
Drobot units
If you go to DrobotStore.com
And you use the DSC code you get fifty dollars off
The purchase now it's a high ticket item
But I've got a lot of great response of people saying
Why they will or will not purchase it
And I want to share two of them with you right now
Okay Adam
With from Silicon Valley
Just catching up on your latest podcast
You asked
I think it was Monday about
Drobot and has anyone bought one
I bought the Robo
Storch unit
The day they announced it in
I bought the Robo share
The day they announced that
My assessment is
Well let me just say that
Drobot is like an endless hard drive
It's kind of like a like a disc array or a raid
So it's really safe and even if one of the drives
Crashes you don't lose all your data
You can keep upgrading it with bigger and bigger
Pretty much standard hard drives as far as I understand
Which I think it's just a miracle concept
Now I don't need terabytes of data
Just yet
But for someone using Photoshop or really big music production
I can see where you would need that kind of capability
Is direct attached to Mac or
Windows
They work very well as as a pseudo raid storage device
Much better than raid
Because you can mix and match different size discs
And it's all you know itty approved
Very disappointed with the Robo share
From a Mac
Network perspective
I've had very bad performance
Work with their tech support folks
And they really have not addressed
You know performance problems
So if your users are Mac based and they want the network support
I'd be cautious if you want to direct attach it
Or your Windows only it's probably pretty good
But just announced the new version that has
Firewire 800 for direct attach
And slightly faster processor
And a more quiet fan
So that's probably worth taking a look at also
Anyway, that's my two cents
Thank you very much
I appreciate that so if they have a new version out
Has anyone tried that one yet?
Is the Mac Network support now better?
Because that's pretty critical to know
So I appreciate that report
And I'll also talk to HQ and ask them if they've been more reports
About the network support not being up to par
But it sounds like it's great on Windows
Great with direct connect
Not great for Mac with network support
Now along with that California Dave
Who will become a future president of the United States
Which really sent me off on kind of an emotional spin
This next call also freaked me out
And I didn't hear them in the order that you're hearing now
Beginning of the hour and then you know an hour later
I heard them pretty close together
Because that's how phone calls come in
But this one really sucked
Really really sucked
I'm a Christian Nashville
Listening to DSC 7th set of six
You have to question why no one bought the drill bone
Of course I would love to have one
Perhaps absolutely to have one
Except you know just like a lot of us
I think you know the money crunch
You know or just kind of expect
Kind of expensive right now
I am looking into some
You know storage alternatives
And the drill will be nice
And nice thing that I would love to have
But you know just fill in the pinch
I'm a money thing
Just I let you know
Bye
So that sucks
That really hurt me just I could hear it
And that's the economy we're in
And that's where we're headed
And people got a buy food
As long as there is food
There is a shortage on you know
There are some countries that don't actually have fucking food
So I keep telling my daughter
Can you imagine tomorrow they'd be like
No bread and no milk
Yeah that was suck
Yeah but I mean how much would it really suck if it didn't come back
You know
All right
I had a McDonald's from Chicago
Hey man
I was calling regarding
The
No Kia E71
You mentioned using that product
Do you essentially create a Wi-Fi
Hotspots that you can browse the web
Yeah
You're an iPod touch
I was just wondering why you would use the iPod touch
So that the Nokia N810
Let us know
Okay
Yeah
35 male
Scruncher
Fred Till
Say Work for us
Helia
All right
And wide awake and dreamland
Let me tell you why
Because without a doubt
The iPod touch of the iPhone
It's the same thing
The browser
The Safari browser is very superior
Particularly with the screen real estate
You get to use
And I really use it in three cases
For a quick Gmail
Because I just love the web
I mean on the E71
I can get a mobile version of Gmail
But it's nothing like the mobile
Safari version of Gmail
I mean that's it's beautiful
I wish they would do it
an E71 specific version for Gmail
So it's really really beautiful
The way it works
And it also is autocomplete
Autocomplete
Excuse me
Autocomplete if your email addresses
Right there in the Safari browser
Can't beat it
So when I really want to
You know, scan some email on the go
And I really want to be able to respond
Not just a quick brief little look at something
Then I'll use that
Same goes for Google reader
They have a fantastic Safari mobile version
It's just beautiful
You know, with stuff expanding in place
And it's just so fast
It really saved you so much time
As the same goes for Google
News
That mobile version on Safari
It's also superior to the regular mobile
Mobile version
So that's why I use it
And it's really worth it to me
To carry this really small iPod touch around
For those minutes when I need it
Now of course, most of the time
I'm just using the E71 for everything
And even use the email client
Connected to Gmail
I map and it works great
But at the end of the day
If you use the Opera Mini browser
Which is fantastic
It's fast
I use that for any other website
Except for those
Gmail Safari specifically
Enhanced sites
Hey, I'm getting to the end of the show
Here hanging with me
Because we've got a couple more cool things coming up
Yo, Mr. Curry
I'm John from the Duke
Long time listener
A fan of the DSC and no agenda
Thanks to your work
It's awesome
The Vorac is not
I love them though
Anyway
The calling to see if you heard that Glenn Beck has been using the phrase
It's a tablework for us lately
Maybe Glenn Beck is a fan of your show
Anyways, I love the show
And
Wish I took the blue pill
Scrunchers, run folder, great here
You already won
Love you me in no homo
And they work for us
Yeah
Absolutely
Well, first of all, the only correct thing to say here is
I'm happy
Shit, yeah
This is the word that needs to get out
I think Ron Paul was actually on Glenn Beck the other day
And Glenn Beck seems like he's awakening
He's a little bit behind
But he's getting there
So the more people that use the phrase
They work for us
The better
I don't care who comes up with it
Of course, what you will get
And it's just the way media works
If we just highlight that for a second
Of course, people say
Oh man, you're so lame
Glenn Beck has been doing this for years
And again, all I'll say is
I really don't give a shit
I'm so happy that more people are picking this up
They do work for us
Dammit, they work for us
And if we all wake up
And we start talking this way
We can change things
We really can
Because the people who really own us
The people who really own the countries
The people who own the unions
The people who own the money
And the way the money is printed
And manipulated
They'll never come out of the shadows
They'll continue their plan
And they'll continue to try
But they only have certain control
They only have control over people
With money
And we have control over
Who actually
Does anything in government
It is completely within our grasp
And if we're just all awake
And we're standing there awake
Then these guys and gals
They won't be able to do anything
But what we tell them to
Because they work for us
And of story
Hey, I don't know
This turns
I was just going from Texas
And that's the state
That T-Boom
Pickens is from
Yeah, you know
I've heard a lot of
A lot of people have been sending me messages
About T-Boom pickens
And I've not paid attention to
Of course not having been in the
States for a while
I haven't seen any of the commercials
That I keep hearing people refer
To
And I'm not quite sure
I don't have an opinion on the guy yet
But he's definitely
Wait, first of all
Guys got a cool name
Nothing wrong with the name
Like T-Boom
That rocks
He has proposed his new energy plan
For building wind centers in Texas
In order to power the electricity
Here and there around
This around the area
He's saying that it'll cost up
From $7 to $10 billion
Which is of course
Is peanuts these days
And I guess the main reason
He's doing that
Because he's saying that
Well, I guess the statistics
Is that $7 billion
That $700 billion
It's spent
On that note
We can take the profits from
Shell oil alone
For one quarter
They could take their profits
They could invest
In his plan
If it's for real
And I'll take that
There's a new report
To MIT is figured out
Some way to store solar energy
Much more efficiently
I'm starting to believe this is a real
Viable alternative
And it seems like there's
Enough companies and corporations
Out there
Or enough money floating around
Dollars or euros
While it lasts
While stocks last
To get this funded
To Tom's pay
I'm not a guy
I don't know how many windmills
It means
I don't know if it means that Texas
Will be the known as the windmills state
But
In tough times
You've got to make tough decisions
Environment
That we pretty much
I mean you kind of wonder
How much is that
It's just to protect the places
That we get the oil from
But I'm kind of curious
Know what people are
So against the officer
We're dealing
It's because of pollution
Or
Now I think the people are against
The offshore drilling
Because of
Mainly this has always been Florida
Because it ruins your view
And if you've ever been on a beach
Where you're seeing all you see
Out there is
Oil rigs
It's not nice to look at
I think that's really
Pretty much the only reason why
It's because they don't like bush
Or I really don't know
But I thought it was a pretty cool idea
And I'm seeing it's commercial
It's on television
Talking about how he wants to build wind farms
Around the United States
And saying that it will
They'll meet the restructure
The power of grade
And all kinds of neat stuff like that
So maybe you could
Say a little something about that
On your show
Haven't seen your show
Haven't popped up in a while
As far as
New one
We've got a couple days
I mean come on
Anyway
Have a great day
And
Holder
Love you
Take care
Bye
Alright man
Thank you
Yep
Tea boon
Piggins
Like that name
Wow
This show is long
I hope it's making up for
Actually
I gotta tell you that
Doing two or three shows a week
It suits me just fine
Certainly if I can make them a little bit longer
I haven't heard any complaints
So I guess you guys are okay with it as well
The final one kind of starting off
Or ending up or we started off with
With
What was it
Um
Uh
Lindsey Williams being full of holes
Here is
The last one for the day
For this footballer Friday
And this is about 9-11
And well listen to your listen for yourself
I'm Chris Conquer here from Seattle
I'm just listening to the latest daily source code
And you're talking at the very beginning of the show
About the press
And kind of how there's different layers
And how they like to report on what's safe
And maybe I misunderstood
And you, but I think you're completely full of crap
There's no way on earth
There's absolutely no way on earth
But if there was a giant conspiracy cover up
Over 9-11
Now I'm not a bluetooth guy
I mean let me say
But there's no way on earth
There's a giant conspiracy cover up
The event is 9-11
And the press had this information on their hands
And they wouldn't report it
I'll tell you why
Because the agency that breaks about
If it's true
Become the number one news organization
All time
Oh oh oh oh oh
Yeah
Okay here's someone coming out of his cocoon
Unfortunately that's just not the way it works
And there's been plenty of individual reports
Lots of them
Lots of little documentaries
And I'm talking about mainstream stuff
Real mainstream reporting
But it's not enough
It doesn't get the traction
And you know
If it, if what you're saying really is true
Then I mean there's enough sensational stuff
And YouTube clips that
Any network could buy that
And a heartbeat
Clear it, put it up and broadcast it
And it would be sensational right
Well how come they don't do that
I mean is there any difference between a Britney Spears story
Of her shaving her head
And some of the out there
Like there were no plain theories of 9-11
I mean come on
Like the BBC recently
Did kind of a half debunking half leaving in the middle
Type of story about about 9-11
You know no one really talked about it
It kind of came and went
Because it's not on the agenda
It's not being hammered home
The way media is set up
The way it works
As free as I was at MTV
Or thought I was
And there was no rule book
Stuff came down from the top
It was the DNA of the company
The DNA of Viacom
That steered us in certain directions
And away from others
It's just the way it works
And stuff gets killed all the time
Stories are made
They don't necessarily make it on the air
The stories that aren't are completely safe
Don't make it on the air
Or stay on the shelf for years
But it's not true what you're saying
Because again
Look at anything out there
Anything that's being discussed
And there are plenty of examples
Of real mainstream reporting
Including the BBC by the way
Financial times
Does it all the time
So real good solid reporting
That is outrageous
When you read it
Or when you watch it
Or when you listen to it
But it just doesn't gather the traction
And mainly it's because people think
Now that's too crazy
That's crazy
Pretty spears
Shaving her head
Showing her beaver
That's real
This stuff that's crazy
That just can't be
We've you know
We've been educated that way
The people are calling me crazy
Now that shit my wife from time to time
Is calling me nuts now
You're going off the deep end
She says
And maybe she's right
But it's not true that these coverups
Just by reporting on them that all
You know that all of a sudden
It's going to be the richest news
Organization in the world
If it truly were that way
They could do it
They could do it today
They could do it any second
You're not going to tell me
That there aren't questions
That are unanswered
I mean there has been no
There was nothing
In the 911 Commission report
About building seven
Nothing
Not a single thing
Could we at least have that explained
Or please
How about a little more on
United Flight 93
Do some research on that
That's where you'll find some real coverup
There's no reporting on that
And it's not because
The journalists don't want to
It's because of the way the media
Has been consolidated
Consolidate up
Consolidated up to owners with corporate
Initiatives and corporate
Again, issues that have to be protected
And of course
You can also say that there's government
Involvement or aluminum
Involvement or whatever
But I haven't been in media for all
It's like the music business
The music business
If what you're saying is true
Then all the best acts
Would have number one hits
But they don't now do they
The best acts
Are performing around the corner
Or at your college
Who'd nanny
Those are the guys who rock the most
But never get an album out there
Do they?
And that's easy to understand
Because just like the media
The record business
Well, until their product
Of course became worthless
Because it's now
Copyable within an instant
And distributable across the world
In the same small amount of time
They had a lock on it
Just create anything you want
That's halfway decent
Repeat it over and over and over again
That's our new stories
Become true
Repeat it over and over and over again
Play it on the radio
Over and over and over again
That's a fix by the way
It's not coincidental
The record companies have budgets
And they know what songs they
And what artists they think are viable
And they make their choices
And they have a deal with the radio stations
Which have also been consolidated
Into huge corporations
Think of the clear channel
And they decide what's going to be played
So if it really was true
What you're saying
That all these great news stories
That news organizations
If they really were true
That they would pick them up
And they would be the richest news organizations
In the world
It's not true
They're going to report on what they think is important to report on
Just like the music business
They're going to give you the music
That they feel is important for you
But it's really important for them
That's how it works
I don't want to worry about so
And advertise anymore
Does that make sense?
There's a long way on earth
But they're going to sit on information
Like this
It was a government
There's two people who hate the Bush administration
To allow them to continue what they're doing
Oh, please
Our own Congress, which is democratic
Won't even try and get rid of Bush and Cheney
Please
The media is not going to do that
People are afraid for their jobs
That's why they don't do this shit
They're afraid for their lives
Maybe
There's some kind of trouble
What you say is so true
And all these people who think of 9-11
Never happened the way they did
But you said it had to whatever
And I'm going to even honor this issue
What I'm saying is your premise is flawed
There's no way that the mainstream media would sit on a story
Like that
And not reported
Well, they're sitting on a right now
And I'm reporting it
The story is there
There's a million different theories
No different from the theories reported in the 9-11 Commission report
And the media sitting on
We're all sitting on it
You've seen the videos
You're sitting on it
How come they're not reporting that
It's what?
Because it's not true
What?
That makes the 9-11 Commission report true
They reported it on that
No, no, no, no, no
That's just unfortunately
It's just not the way it works
Simply because they make way to what's freaking money
No, no, no, no, no
I'll be dead
I love you
Don't worry about it
I really do
And you'll get there
We're still awakening
Did by bit
Play one more for you
Because we're rocking out for the weekend
This is from the drop
Delirious
Bliss
I feel lonely when it's you I miss
I feel crazy when I dream I miss
I've tried all of this way
For just one kiss
Is it bliss?
Rock and roll is everything
Everything's so lonely
And never will I be there for you
I love you
I feel like I'm home to the place
Where it goes
I where my love for you
I've never traveled
If I'm right, then you won't
If I'm wrong, then I will live
If I die with no reward
And I know I have peace
To the carrot the soul
I try to get to my heart
I don't know if I can get to my heart
If I'm wrong, then you won't live
It's a simple thing
The saddest fight Keep my feet on the ground
And my head in the sky All of you more
Then I can't say And I won't change my mind
All the choices I've made
Nigel Bye-bye, L-bye-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-Bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, Hail-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-bye, L-
I had a final fun phone to read.
Well, there you go.
Final thought of the week.
I've really enjoyed what we just went through.
I hope you liked as well.
It's only an hour and a half, so crap.
That was a lot, but it was also good.
I almost didn't want to leave anything out.
So I don't hear people who are anti-conspiracy theorists.
I don't hear people who are totally outrageously opposed to the ideas.
I hear people who are slowly awakening,
and that's what I really appreciate.
All the way from my friend who said that not on news organizations would have brought this
to light if it really was any truth to the matter.
That's someone who's coming out of it.
That's someone who's coming very, very slowly, and all the way through to the Lindsay Williams
stories full of crap.
It's frustration.
I can hear it.
You guys are awakening, and I love it.
So that's what I'm hearing.
And if you got some thoughts, please call it into the voicemail line.
You'll find those on the show notes at dailysourceco.com, or of course, at curie.com, or
for time to time, I post them on yourself, so that would be my final thought of the
week.
Look around you, pay attention, listen to the codes, listen to the messages, and welcome
to the awakening.
So have yourselves a great weekend, live your life with passion, please.
I'll at last enjoy your freedom, another fine, medial presentation, stick it in your
ear.