Delta Shared Charly 7-7-4
I need to spend the night with you, girl
To give me a reason for today
Release the tension when you play
Let it go, let it go, let it go, go all the way
Hear it on the radio, what more exciting
Let's see who the video is on real light
Give me something safe, drink for my mind
Tell me in the meantime
I just want to spend the night back in time
Bring the cells to life from my mind
Let it go, let it go, let it go, go all the way
Hear it on the radio, what more exciting
Let's see who the video is on real light
Give me something safe, drink for my mind
Tell me in the meantime
Let's see who the video is on real light
Give me something safe, drink for my mind
Tell me in the meantime
Hear it on the radio, what more exciting
Let's see who the video is on real light
Give me something safe, drink for my mind
Let it go, let it go, go all the way
Tell me in the meantime
Let's see who the video is on real light
Give me something safe, drink for my mind
Hey, everybody. Welcome to the Daily Source Code episode number 774 as always or at least
has it's been for the past eight weeks brought to you almost directly from the curry
manner in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Guilford. Hey, it's the prize nice
scene each other today. I actually had a couple of meetings scheduled in town. They got
canceled or actually postponed, I should say. And not too bound about it because today once
again protest in and around London as the holliers, let's just call them the truckers,
our staging a protest rally. So they're driving on the I think it's the A40 which goes
into London. Some of them are actually parking on the A40 and then they're driving through
Westminster and of course they're protesting the fuel prices and they're saying that
the government really needs to do something about this very very quickly. And they're actually
calling for some kind of anti-competitive behavior compared to Europe. And I guess what they're
saying is because you have truckers coming in from from the continent where there's less
taxes on fuel that the British truckers just can't compete. And they're saying hey man, even
these one or two pennies a pound, it's making a difference and we can't keep our heads
above water. It's the second time they've done a protest like this. And interestingly enough,
yesterday I was up in a wadford. Remember the last time I was in a wadford when they had
the previous protest is almost timed with my I should probably not go to wadford because
then we know when I go to wadford to visit my friends at newsquest up there, there'll
be another trucker protest within 24 hours. Anyway, I can of course totally understand and I
got to tell you, I don't think I don't think this is going to let up. And man, I don't see
how any of government including the UK government, they can't let up. They can't let
go these billions of pounds at these guys want relief for because the country's broke. You
know, it's like we got no money. And it's kind of the story everywhere across Europe.
Now the Lisbon Treaty seems to be falling apart because Germany has not ratified the
proposal yet. Of course Ireland has not the United Kingdom as far as I know, the law still
suits still continues. So even though they have royal ascension still no ratification
and now Poland saying, hey, look, if Ireland is not in, we don't even have to ratify
it. Oh, man, that's pissing off the brand new president of the EU, Mr. Sarcosi. He was
ready, man. He was ready for a real six months of pure presidential pleasure. He got his
babe on his side. He's all trim and fit and he was thinking, I'm just going to be the
root of the roost. And now he's got crap. Let's see how he solves that because I think
there's a lot of questions. And it seems to politicians have questions. Oh, gosh, I'll
go into a head on the hand basket in the world. Anyway, plenty to talk about and I'm glad
that I have some extra time to talk to you guys. Starting off with a couple of comments.
And this is based upon Monday's Charlie, we talked about the reasoning behind the price
of oil. Actually, let me do a quick little check here on the futures prices of Brent
crude. Hold on, I had it all cute up. Here we go. As of, I'll refresh here. So this is
as of 824 AM today, August prices. So this is a future. So basically, someone is willing
to pay $141.15 per barrel as of August, 2008. Kind of cool, because you can see the whole
chain of these options. And you'll see that February 09 prices 143.37. So obviously whoever
has this out there is expecting that if someone's going to buy it at this price, they're
obviously expecting it to be higher than that. So that seems to be about the highest one.
It's cool. These futures go all the way through, when we have here 1314, all the way
through December 2016, where the future price is still at 139, of course, with eight years of
inflation that may be cheap at that point in time. No, no, it's still trying to feed and find
out more about how the world bank works. And I went back and re-read a confessions of an economic
hitman. John Perkins has a new book out, actually. See, where does it go? It's a history
of the American Empire or something like that, which seems to be pretty good. I've only just started
it. And what this guy says is true is just amazing. He's alive. And I hope you guys did
your homework. I hope you checked out that Lindsey Williams video that I have on Curried.com.
It'll blow your mind when you see what the guy has to say. That's where I got a lot of my theory
from. And of course, I expect this some of the U.S. Check-all heads to check in, including some
savons. Here's a topic, Rod. Hey, Adam. It's a topic, Rod. I'm here. I'm a topic about gas
network.com. Just listen to Monday's DSC about your theories on world oil prices. And I think
you're close. There's no doubt that there's lots of very powerful people that like the oil market
just the way it is. Yeah, and I would say it's not really, I don't even think it's a few people.
I think in general, it's the whole system has become corrupted by this dependence upon
oil being traded in U.S. dollars and the deficit being financed that way. Because of course,
the deficit is created. Unfortunately, not through a great health care or fantastic social security.
I think the deficit is pretty much created by war. So that's the military industrial complex
that we were forewarned about. Now, $9 trillion of federal debt, that's what the U.S. owes
other countries. That's just a sad state of affairs. And of course, it's for building all kinds of
you know, war, war crap. Most of it is at least I presume. So yeah, it's a lot of people. It's not
just the happy few as far as I'm concerned. Which is why you really can't pin down to one single conspiracy.
But everyone's kind of being on this game. It's just we've been asleep at the wheel. Because
they worked for us. Remember, they're the drivers, but we pay their tickets.
But we're not going to beat those people by installing little plastic devices.
Also SEO, most of the little marketing sites websites.
Tom McRod. I didn't say we're going to beat anyone with that. I mean, I don't think we're going to
beat the big oil companies by propagating biodiesel either, you know, but it's just maybe a way
a personal way to get a little bit of relief. It sounds like he's not a big believer. Our
savanda, Tom McRod here. No, we're going to beat those people by having a better energy source.
That's available to more and more people. All of them, yes.
Iran was a independent nuclear power source. It scares the heck out of the powers that be
the establishment that likes the oil market controlled the way it is. That's why they're afraid.
Anyway, there's no doubt in my military mind that we've got to stop this. We've got to pay attention.
And we've got to tell our representatives that we like expanding nuclear power to avoid the
continued addiction to oil. That's all for now. I work for you.
Thank you. Thank you, Tom McRod.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't know. Sometimes something just may need some form of a revolution. I don't know.
But I mean, like a loud one. Because you know, I don't think we're going to get very far just
by saying, you know, we want a atomic energy. First of all, it's pretty difficult to rally everyone
around the atomic energy. I don't know. I'm just stuck on this topic. I wish I could,
you know, the best thing to do is just to propagate the information and tell everyone as much as
as I know about it. In fact, that even seems to be dangerous. I got an email from someone who
shall go unnamed, who says he has it on a reliable source, that somewhere in September is when the
war will start involving the United States, Iran, Israel, and Pakistan. Sounds feasible to me.
And if this does happen, please, you know, if we really get any kind of, we get this
kind of watch it. You know, let's just learn. Let's just presume that the 911 truthers are right.
Let's just presume that for a moment. We know what to look out for, right? So we know we want to look
out for, let's see, what was Gulf War 1 when the George Bush's dad went into Iraq. It was, oh,
yes, it was kids, yeah, unplugging incubators, killing children and incubators. I think that was the
main driver behind, you know, going to war. This guy is a horrible man. Let's go and take his oil.
And then, of course, we know weapons of mass destruction was used next. So what will it be for Iran?
I don't think the weapons of mass destruction thing is really working so now it's like, you know,
they got a nuclear bomb. I think they'll come up with something more innovative. I think they're
still with a couple months left in the presidency. I think they'll come up with something really
good, something that'll just, outrageous about how horrible Iran is. By the way, if you're a
Iranian, would you please call in? Because I'd like to speak to someone from Iran. And I know that,
you know, there's a huge proliferation on the internet. Although the language that is used by the
Iranians is not pretty universally understood by the rest of the world. I'm understood, but I'm
led to believe that they speak English as a second language quite well. And just looking at pictures
and videos and stuff on even on Facebook, you know, I'm seeing like this is like a young thriving
population, the 70% of that country is 30 years or younger. When I go bomb him, he's fucking crazy.
We all know what it's about. So let's just be on the watch. Let's keep our eyes wide open.
Anyway, go back to the hydroxy booster. Yeah, of course, you know, yes, there's MLM websites.
But I think the principle is kind of there. And I've spoke to a couple of people who say to me,
oh, we're no, we're going to, how them shit really does work. It does work. And they've built on
themselves. They haven't bought anything from an SEO, LMM, MLM type websites that just tried it out.
Now, maybe it's perception or maybe it changes your driving habits. But hey, if it, no matter
what it's doing, if it's working right now, 25% reduction in your gasoline usage could be about
a buck a gallon. So I think it's worth the experiment. Some more calls about that.
I do. Don't call a gas gob. Hey, John. Hi, drugs are based. Yeah. Back away, sorry.
Every time it's a little bit of a feel Christ, it's all these sort of gadgets pop up out of the wood
magnets. Yes, you put a current through water. You break it down into hydrogen and oxygen.
Which you can re-combine to get water back. When it's a energy company, let the current.
Well, a whole second. I'm not saying it's it's efficient for the actual energy produced. I'm
saying the efficiency is co and I do believe this is true. I mean, if you can get it right,
it seems apparent to me that the the efficiency is in your pocketbook, not in the the
power output. And I don't want to get into the argument because I've got lots of physicists
or telling telling me it's impossible. It doesn't work. The numbers don't add up. All I know is that
I know people who are spending about $40 or $50 less a month on gas since they installed
the hydroxy booster. Again, it's not about putting your entire automobile on hydrogen, but also
that whole idea of on the go hydrogen. I'm still into that. I think this possibility is in it.
Of course, once the engine is combusting and driving, it should output more power to charge your
battery or provide an off answer whatever you need to the to the setup. Look, I don't know. I've ordered
one. I'm going to put it on the jag. I don't know what they have I'm talking about, but I will do
a real conclusive study for myself and I'll let you guys in on it, okay? If you're doing it on board
in the car, it's been generated by the engine. There's no such thing as a free lunch. And then you
feel economy gains. What you always get that when you try and you get, you're looking for an
bird to say, come and drive a little lighter wondering whether it's working. That's a few
tank flows, the driving reserves are normal and the economy returns normal. It happens every time
there's a two crisis. It happens in 73. It happens subsequently and it'll probably happen again.
Just walk away. Nothing to it. John, you're telling me that you were aware of hydroxy
boosters in the 70s? How old are you? I was pretty young in the 70s. I wasn't even thinking
about cars, little-own hydroxy boosters, but I'd be curious to know. If anyone who says this won't
work, have you tried it? That's what I'd like to know. And I'd like to hear from some people who've
tried it and like to hear their results. We've got phone numbers for you to call you know,
it's been so long that I've played one of those jingles. I don't even know the, uh, I don't even
know the numbers by heart anymore, hold on. Plus one, 201, 625, 6357. Of course, I could know the
jingles plus and 201, 625, 6357. I came and singing anymore. Anyway, if you're calling from
Europe or from the UK, it's plus four four and the plus of course is handy if you put that into
your mobile phone so you can dial it from any country without having to do any pre-codes. Plus
for 4200, 768, 13753. If you've used a hydroxy booster, let me know. Did it work for you?
Did you get any results? Do you feel stupid? Do you feel really great? I mean, you got to tell me?
I thought I had to say something as well. Anyway, I'm 27, I want to be a accountant,
I don't know, I'll come to me living in London. Keep all the good work. Thanks. Bye.
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel. On this week's show, we review enemy territory quick,
wars on the Xbox 360. I get a quizzical with the new buzz on the PlayStation 3.
The 3G-8 tells us about the new 90-game and you can win special preview copies of Final Fantasy
7 Crisis Core for the PlayStation, portable, complete without books. That's all it gamesweasel.com.
I had the latest and nothing to me. I've been trolling. I've been so transparable.
I couldn't have seen. I asked if you liked our new wild, drunken comedies.
But were you like as a child? Did you feel the green?
But was you made your college major? Did you have enough of the same?
You're the little green. You're still waiting for the world. What a win!
The music notes it through the air, along the chattering of all the other people there.
It wasn't that green. The sound is just too exist. We're all equipped for me and you.
That's not true. Yes, I can't turn the world anymore. I don't know. So unique. I know it happens.
Every day, when you be fully, you say it's never been that way, never the right.
Even besides, I can't see that photo here. I believe it's true.
It's never been that way, it's never been that way.
You know, there's a ranking on the Podship Music Network. You can see what's getting the most
play per day, per week, per month, and all time. This was on the charts all of a sudden.
I know I've played it before Andy Stone in the coffee shop. But I like it as obviously a very
beat-less feel to it. Nice for kind of a rainy Wednesday. Even though the temperature's nice
today in the United Kingdom, man, we got some storms going on. It's just outrageous. Especially
over the North Sea or looking at thunderstorms, hail, real, very typical, typical English weather
in a way. Of course, nearing the finals of Wimbledon, which is about the only thing going on in
the news now, it's just boring. Wow. Oh, here's something I want to tell you about.
It actually comes from the Lady Patricia and the Pod daughter, Christina.
Now, those of you living in the United Kingdom will know about this, but I'm so happy to say
that in a way my dream has come true. The whole thought of branding, we were talking about the
creating the wrong brand and just avoiding brands all together. Obviously, it's such a hypnotization
that's going on. You have to wear, you have to have the right sneakers, you have to have the right
shirt, the right watch, the right car, et cetera, and I'm like, well, why don't we just have the wrong
stuff? You know, that's much better. And let's have it not come per se from China. Although
that part I don't think actually was successful with this latest venture, but there's a company now,
which has opened up stores in, well, I know there's one in London, and I think they're opening
up all over Europe, and it's called Primark, and I really love this store. And I can just see
Brits rolling their eyes. But what they do is they have, now I'm, I'm no fashionista, but my girls
are. And they had, it's like a huge clothing store. You know, it's like clothing. It's, you know,
but everything from, you know, dresses, slacks, shirts, shorts, belts, bags, shoes, you name it,
you know, real apparel type store. And they sell everything, which as far as I can tell, pretty much
at the price for which it should be sold at. Now, of course, it doesn't have a label on it.
It doesn't say, you know, Gucci, doesn't say Ralph Lauren, it doesn't even say,
well, it doesn't even say H&M. Although I wouldn't put H&M in a real high-class category.
And it costs next to nothing. And the, and the girls like freaking out, like, look at all this
great stuff we found. And you know, this is like a whole pile of things with bags and shoes and
sunglasses and skirts and socks and bikinis for like 60 or 70 pounds. And like, yeah, and I think
these guys at Primark, Primark, or as I've heard women here call it, Primar Shay.
You know, kind of like a tarjay thing. It's Primar Shay. I think they're going to be very,
very successful. Maybe finally we're starting to break this very vicious circle. You know,
now that people are looking at their pocketbooks and saying crap, I don't have any money left
at the end of the month, mainly because of the price of fuel and food. And maybe we're just all
getting over ourselves here. And I'm really liking it. Look at a Primark, or as we say,
Primar Shay, hello, at a Market here. You might remember about two weeks ago I called
us for Got Your Flight from UK to runner who was, runner, byboard them. Yes, or
a kind of mountain. Anyway, so I recorded a flight with my motorcycle rider, I allowed to
backpack then. It's about 36 minutes. You can get it via a
nip url.com slash audio flight and nip url is s and i t url.com slash a u d i o flight all one
word. Yeah, I would be glad to get your feedback. I also also tested a couple of new
recording equipment doing it. So probably quite a lot of quality. Anyway, thanks
yeah, Marcus, absolutely. Now, I did check it out. And if you like the kind of stuff that
we do with the Delta Sheriff from time to time, this is a great sound seeing tour. Actually,
Marcus did a really fantastic job. He really edited this together. He said it all up. He tells
you each step of the way, he'll break in and you know, before you. So it's not really like a beginning
to end flight like I've done, but he's really taking you through the steps and I played it on the
speakers here upstairs in the attic and it sounded really nice. Particularly when it turns the
engine off, because it's a it's a sailplane. It's a motorglider. So once he's up at altitude, it turns
that off and it's like, wow, that's a nice, that's a very quiet ride. So you should check it out
if you're new to that kind of stuff. Absolutely, Marcus, I really appreciate you checking in.
One more comment for today. Hi, I'm Susan from Whistland in here.
I'm Dr. Veckel in the month. Um, I'm fortunate to have been on BBC News 24, uh, last time
from heart talk. And he sets an interesting thing. He said that a lot about your list of
three things. They agreed with everything. You said so quite rightly. Um, he also talked about
IT cards. And he mentioned the interesting thing. He said that time is positive agreement. We have
with the US for data sharing. Any information, the, uh, you take up my collection systems would
be automatically shared with the US government. Yeah, you know, it's, I don't know if you're referring
to this report that came out to with the New York Times uncovered, uh, beginning of the week,
um, where they're apparently that, I mean, the US have already signed on the dotted line from,
from what I understand, I actually spoke to a minister of parliament today, uh, who said as much.
And the idea is that there would be, um, you know, a full agreement between the US and the European
Union, um, to really transfer any and all data when requested from either side. Of course,
all of this will keep us safe from terrorists if you surely understand what it's all for. It's
very important. We just comply with this and lie down and take it up the ass. Um, but, um, that could
include, uh, indeed, uh, all kinds of records. And the EU is, well, and basically, the United States and
the EU are now pretty much on par with phone taps and, and of course, this, uh, this horrible, horrible
bill, uh, which forces US credit card companies and other, uh, online transactional outfits such
as eBay and Amazon to hand over all of the transaction details to the government so they can scan
it for, um, oh, terrorism, of course. Yes, it's all for your protection. So it has, it's not
done yet. It's not a done deal, but man, we get those ID cards. I mean, is it just me? It feels like
we're into the final stage. If there really is such an evil plan as the new world order, then man,
we're getting really close to, to the final phase with oil prices up, food prices up, um, inflation
up, uh, economy stagnating, all kinds of invasions into our lives, uh, from all different angles
for all different reasons. I mean, the only thing that has to happen, now is martial law. That's all,
I mean, that's the only thing that has to happen and we're done, right? So I don't think it's quite
there yet, but certainly something that warrants fighting, and, um, I have spoken to, uh, minister
of European Parliament, Sophie Innitfeld. You might want to check her out, I'll put a link in the
show notes. She's actually suing the US government with the electronic frontier foundation.
She has pretty much the same problem I have when she enters the US, and she did the, you know,
where they stop you and give you secondary screening, but they can't really tell you what it's about,
and they need to do a freedom of information act, which they never respond to. So she's actually
gotten the EFF involved, and we'll see what comes out of it. I doubt very much, uh, but, you know,
she says, look, just tell me what you've gotten the database. How the hell can we start to
exchange information with you? If you don't even know what's in the database or how to get a
perfectly harmless people on person off of the list. So there are people fighting this, and I encourage
you to do the same. And, uh, unfortunately, you know, the only means we have really are
whatever political processes that are at our, uh, at our fingertips. You know, I might give
Sophie a call, and an interviewer on the Charlie about this issue. Let me just see how the
plays out. Uh, there's a, there's a, there's a, there's a story on her in the Washington post,
and uh, she's Dutch, so I, you know, I have a kind of shorter lines of communication. We speak the same
language, uh, but she's, uh, also very fluid and English. So we'll, uh, maybe we'll give that a try.
Oh, and see what else you got here on your message, man. Um, this is apparently, uh,
according to any pen on, um, TV, um, to do with the, to agreement that we had,
or because we could, do what we had. So, oh, that's interesting. So it might be part of a
different agreement, a nuclear agreement, hmm. Yeah, I'll check that out for sure.
Just making a note of that. What do you think of that? Um, I'll also, um, on the news recently,
classic. I think this, uh, you can then just learn some of the
single aspects and says it's flying cars on the horizon. So, uh, they, they may be, uh,
it may be here, but it's a quick and, uh, we hope that doesn't see them yet. Um, all
usual stuff, uh, solar and, uh, anything else like that. And then that, they
work for us, right? I don't have any of them because, uh, a lot of people still
learn to realize it. Yeah, don't forget it. Absolutely. I love
Clive Sinclair. He seems like a really cool guy and, uh, and my first computer
actually was the Sinclair ZX 80 for those of you nerds out there. That was my very,
very first, uh, Nax, he wasn't the first one. Yeah, it was one of the first computers
that I've ever had, um, along with like, um, a big 20 came after that. Anyway,
doesn't matter. Uh, big fan of the guy. I always thought his, uh, you know,
his electric cart or a bicycle thing, uh, never thought that was really appealing.
It looked pretty frightening because he was so tiny and driving and traffic just didn't
look right. And the flying car, but now it's just not going to happen. And this is coming
from a guy who actually will believe in a hydroxy booster, okay? But the flying car is not going
to happen. It, in fact, it already exists. It's called the airplane. Private aviation
certainly is there for anyone who wants a flying car. You know, we already have the flying
parking lots where you can fly your flying car to, you know, you just have to take a different
car from the airport from the flying car parking lot. Do whatever you want to go.
It's just not going to happen, okay? There's too many reasons why it won't. Yeah, it's, it's
it's, it's, it's, it's, you know, yes, I totally believe that new engines and electric engines
and new types of engine management, et cetera, that there'll be lots of exciting new flying
aircraft. But it's not going to be for someone who hasn't trained. I mean, it's just not as simple
as, uh, okay, auto navigation zipping me away. Take me wherever I need to go. I mean,
you're talking about mother earth, you know, there's conditions that, uh, that warrant all kinds
of adjustments. And it's just not going to be, you know, it's just not going to be done completely
electronically. Certainly not for any type of, uh, affordable price. Just not going to happen.
Even though I know we all love one, wouldn't we? I'm going to play one more song for you
before I get out today. This is brand new, uh, Lisa was brand new to my ears from the pod
save music network. Blake Morgan featuring no one less than letting crabots.
Now a big fan of all, so to have this pod safe is truly a gift. Why don't you see on the
Charlie seven seven four.
You're one more side. Let's see who the hell is on this line.
Can't miss something safe trip from my mind to help me in the meantime.
I just want to spend the night back in time
and bring the cells to life from my mind to give me a reason for today.
Blow it up and drive away. Let it blow, let it come, let it go, go all the way.
Here in all the radio, one more side, let's see who the hell is on this line.
Can't miss something safe trip from my mind to help me in the meantime.
Now the radio, one more side, let's see who the hell is on this line.
Can't miss something safe trip from my mind to give me a reason for today.
Can't miss anything safe trip from my mind to give me a reason for today.
Oh. Now the radio!
I wonder if there are little minny suns and wateride in there?
Can't miss something safe trip from my mind to give me a reason for today.
Let me prove it, why don't you say it is?
Pods, safe.
Find that at music.podshow.com, which is,
as far as I know, I know, still the address for the
pod save music now. We're going to, of course,
pod save music now, work.com.
I'm pretty sure you can get to it from
pah music.mevio.com as well.
Okay. Um, so I'm not quite sure how the rest of the week is going to look
since stuff has been moved around, um,
but if I'm here another day, you know, I'll do another show for you.
And of course, I am going out to San Francisco,
probably by the end of the month.
Excuse me. Oh, and guess what's going to take place?
Oh, yes.
Excuse me. Finally, a full blown
turn it off unplugged jackout
vacation for the curry clan.
That's right, uh, from the 11th, so they'll be next Friday.
We're taking off. We're going to the south of
France to San Rafael, which is somewhere in between
con and central pay and we've got a pad all lined up there.
We're going to have seven days of nothing but, uh,
hopefully sunshine and that over. I'm really hoping for, um,
this is swimming pool. Of course, with the ocean is nearby.
I'm so looking forward to it. And that means that I will be completely
unjacking from the cha cha.
Unless someone wants to take over and do a couple of best
or, um, or any other ideas, which, of course,
I'm completely open to just to keep him's content.
Some continuity going, I gladly hand over the rains to any
chuckleheads, uh, and or savants who would like to, uh,
take a crack at it. So let me know what you think about that.
Adam at mevio.com. And I'll, uh, I'll check you guys.
Hopefully tomorrow, if not, certainly for a food bar Friday until then,
give your life with passion. And as long as it lasts in this,
what feels like a final stage, enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, mevio presentation. Stick it in your ear.
Are you ready? I'm going to lay it down for you.
You'll never lose five again. No, no, no, no, no,
with a judge on a dead road.
But it's just, this is Angie B of a chill cast.
And I can save you $50 on your ultra-cooled
Durobo storage unit. Just use coupon code chill.
When you check out at DuroboStore.com,
don't delay your data's at stake.