Delta Shared Charlie, 8-0-1.
And during the few moments that we have left, we're running tall, right down to that, in a language that everybody here can answer the undistinguishable.
The $60 million worth of airplane straps by aspirin.
For the next generation, bring you caught any mightors.
We don't need a deep interest in it.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Augustine is an angry.
The Kingma!
What do you say?
The concept of the reality.
I know you're ready.
I know you're dreams.
I've been a friend in one of me.
Oh, I'm a self-generationality.
I like most of me.
And can I be?
I'm a self-generationality.
A self-generationality.
Me and life,
Love and pride,
But I miss me,
To the next generation.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Only you can set me free.
So thin, you need to be.
I'm a slime, I'm a semi-auty baby.
Oh, I'm a self-generationality.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Only you can set me free.
I'm a self-generationality.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Me and life,
Love and pride,
But I miss me,
To the next generation.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Only you can set me free.
Sergeant.
GO!
Copima.
My partner.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm thinking that's 1989, maybe 1990, oh man those guys were way far ahead of their time.
Hey everybody, Daily Source Code episode number 801 coming to you from the Curry Manor once again.
I'm back in Blighty for just a little bit after more or less five weeks on the road three
weeks in San Francisco, quick trip back to the Netherlands for the surprise party for Bob,
then back for another full week in San Francisco and Los Angeles and I arrived yesterday.
I was supposed to arrive a lot earlier and I would have maybe even have tried to e-cotta
show yesterday, but got in, really didn't get in the house until about 4, 4, 30.
So, took a little bit longer than usual, also coming in from LAX, there's different thing.
In a Virgin Atlantic uses different planes, they use the Airbus instead of the 747, so it's
a bit.
It's an uncomfortable kind of, honestly it reminds me, you know those diagrams of slave ships,
where we have all the bodies laid out in rows, that's kind of what the Airbus Virgin Atlantic
experience is like, it's just one long container, one long tube filled with people lay
down in almost that exact same position, it's kind of scary, you should look at the diagram
of the Airbus, what is it, the AS340, 600 I think is the model, it's the elongated one.
Anyway, it doesn't matter, I'm back here, I'm a kind of trip and out from the jet lag,
it's, you know, going back and forth and a week and it's just kind of weird, both the
lady Patricia and Christina have, oops, am I getting a hair cell phone signal coming through
here, which what where is it, ah, you know what that is, it's here, see if you can identify
this sound, can you identify that, let me try it again, that's closed and now open, that
my friends is the G1 Google phone, which we'll be giving you a review of later on in this
very program.
Anyway, both the girls are out, they left this morning, late this morning to the Netherlands
Patricia has her first of the series of live shows for pop stars, the show she's judging
right now in the Netherlands.
Number one, it's time to slide on Fridays, a huge audience market share, and a show with
actual losers, which, you know, I enjoy very much, it's good to have a show with people
who compete and people who think a lot of themselves and then lose, and of course, it's
great to see winners as well, man, it's, and it's, that show, when it comes to entertainment
because that's all it is, that show is well put together.
Anyway, so Patricia is off, and Dexter is along with them, Dexter, now officially being
Christina's boyfriend, how do I know it's official, well, well, they went through the
official boyfriend girlfriend ceremony of stating so on their Facebook by setting their
in a relationship with flag to each other, so this is a big deal, is another man in my
house.
I woke up this morning, there he was, as Dexter, so they took along some camera equipment,
they're starting the Chrissy and Dexter show, a video short episodic, and Dexter has
a little production company, he does lots of video work, and I can't wait to see what
these kids come up with, they were outside this morning early, getting, getting footage,
I guess they're doing this first episode, which their pilot episode will be about their
trip, you know, they had the wireless mic with a cute little mic flag with a Mivio
on it and Dexter and Chrissy, oh boy, so that means I'm all alone here, just me and the animals,
and you chuckle heads along for the ride, it is Thursday, it's about five o'clock in the
afternoon, I've been trying to catch up a little bit on stuff on the drop and things in general,
and they're just really four main topics that I want to run through with you today, one of
them will be just the general economy, of course, the bailout, I won't dwell on that too long,
I do want to talk about some of the feedback I've been getting about from Obama supporters.
As promised, a review of the G1 Google phone, which have now had my possession for almost
36 hours, and of course some of us, I'm going to use it along the way, I'm not going to make this a
super, super long show, it shouldn't turn into the hour and a half we've been doing,
because I am saving things for tomorrow for an official food war Friday, since I'll also be here
by myself and let's plenty of time without distraction to eat out a food war Friday edition.
Saturday, of course, no agenda, Patricia is coming back on Saturday, the kids, as we call them,
the childrens, will be coming back on Sunday, so that's my life, how you doing?
Hey, so I start off with cult of personality, and a couple of reasons for that to start it off with,
I came back and I had already seen this, I think on my way to the airport, I was scanning through
some news, trying to get back into the UK news loop, and it's really amazing.
At the top of all news today, front page of most newspapers, if not all, top of the news,
and I'm not just talking top of the news, I'm talking like 10 minutes top of the news,
more important than anything else, lead story, lead story is about a radio show hosted by Russell
Brand. Now, he works for, he does a show, I think it's only a weekend show, I don't know if it's
a daily or a weekly show for the BBC for Radio 2. Russell Brand, of course, he hosted the MTV
Music Awards, he's in that movie, something forget about Sarah, I saw it on the plane actually,
it's cute, it's a fun little movie. He has a radio show, and the guy is absolutely insane,
and I usually like the stuff he says, he makes me laugh, he's very quick, very witty, very abrasive,
you know what you get with this guy, and certainly the radio 2 knows what they got with this guy,
and along with him on this controversial, or this, it is, of course, the big Russell Brand,
Jonathan Ross controversy, so in this controversy, Jonathan Ross, who is arguably the number one
TV talk show host in Britain, he has this show on Friday nights, it's the show to be in,
it's all the superstar foreign guests come to see his show, I mean, it is the place to be, and he
makes an enormous amount of money by UK standards, I believe it's 6 million pounds a year, he also
does a once a week radio show on Saturdays, which is usually, it's okay, it's kind of fun, I like
his Friday night TV, his talk show better, and then he does, he's a major film buff, his wife also
writes movies, I believe, writes scripts, many, some big movies, and so he does like a movie
preview or review show, so they were on together, and they decided to call up Andrew Sachs,
he played Manuel on faulty towers, which of course is John Cleese produced the vehicle, I think
was a, I'd call it a Monte Python spin-off, and so whatever transpired in this, so they called
him, I believe he was supposed to be on for an interview, I'm not quite sure, but they called
them, they got his answering machine, and then they started goofing around leaving stupid messages
on his answering machine, and what they said, which I'm happy to let you hear if you can actually
sit through it, because it's actually it's boring, what they said has become the outrage to such an
extent that Russell brand has now quit his radio show, he resigned, and Jonathan Ross has been
placed on the inactive list, so normally he tapes his show on Wednesday, his television show,
he didn't tape it on Wednesday, we'll not air on Friday, even though they've both publicly stated
apologies, the director general of the BBC is investigating until further notice, Jonathan Ross will be
will be kept inactive, will be, what is the word I'm looking for? He gets pushed to the
bench, he's on the bench, what he is, he's benched, and there are 20 or 30,000 complaints that
came into the BBC, and this is a gross misuse of taxpayer funding, or actually it's licensed
fee funding, because you pay it independently of the tax system, like 151 pounds a year, and people are
just in arms, and this is like the biggest news, and I said to Patricia, how can this be? I mean,
there are other things going on in the world, yeah, sure, this is interesting,
and it's fun, and you know, they basically insulted the guy, so big deal, you know, if anything,
it was a non-funny bit, they should be benched or fired for being not funny, not for some
outrageous, you know, supposed outrageous candor, and who cares? Move on, no, you can't move on because
and Patricia made a very valuable point about this, you can't move on because people are so
sick and tired of hearing about Gordon Brown and about the crisis and how the house prices are
crashing and how people are going bankrupt and being kicked out of their homes, they're so tired
of hearing about it that they latched onto this, and they're just going nuts with it, and if I,
I will play just a little bit, and might as well, just so you can get a general idea of what this is,
it's nothing, it's, you know, it starts off with, you know, what the hell is this? Why is my,
yeah, no, now of course everything is slow to load. I'm back in the UK with zero bandwidth
opportunity, here we go. It's uh, there's a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com. I'll just
leave you here a little bit because actually, let me just explain that nowhere, does anyone quote
in these new stories, what actually, and you know, was said, and it was kind of hard to find audio,
I left a note on the drop, and immediately some folks sent me some links, but it's not like the
new stories are actually reporting what they said, but you know, whatever, was it was scandalous,
it was horrible. What is that just, she's also found right on the phone, but this is
a conventional upload something out. No, no, it's like, no, it's a family, it's a common sort of
moment that somebody's calling again, or either message, speak off the turn, thank you. So lonely,
when you've missed your message, enough or for more options, press one at any time, uh,
oh, hello, and this is Russell Brandt. I'm a great appreciate it, uh, if you'll work over
the decades, you're going to be on the Michelle now. Uh, I don't know why you're not
answering the phone, it's a bit difficult for me, we've drawn it from Russell.
Hello, Andrew. That's true. Basically, they're calling up to insulting about, uh,
about being on some show of, uh, uh, stars who used to be on the bill, which is a cop show here,
and that, you know, whether they did or did not have success after that, it's, it's a, it's a,
it's a very infantile, not funny, gag, not funny, you know, joke that they're going into.
Speaking now, uh, we understand, anyway, well, I can still do the interview to be honest with you.
Let's do it, let's do it. I think, uh, I've drawn this. I mean, Andrew Sachs,
do you will be appearing in a documentary, the bill might be famous with a Martin Camperon's
Dolchry Paula Grady Paul in Cook. Yes, they've been building my cool, those people,
find my Sandra Sachs. I'm a tiny, didn't I, Andrew Sachs. Well, that's Jonathan's big.
I'm a tiny, you, you woe to find with you, I'm telling other performances. Yes, love.
Guess the appearance on the bloody bill. We've, for you, it's better than for you,
towers than ever, and be been in the bill. I didn't know you was in here and all pulling.
I know very fully towers. I remember your singles. I've got all four of them. Well, they were
four great singles now. You know what I'm saying? It's boring, right?
Man Andrew Sachs. Don't call him, man. Well, that's really bad.
Oh, I apologize. Oh, you're sad. He's an idiot.
Look, Andrew Sachs, I've got respect for you and your lineage and progeny.
We never let that only question to hint. Oh, what do you mean? Why did that come
because you know what you're doing? It's fun to grind it up.
So that was the genesis of the whole thing. Russell Brand, who is a known, I think it actually
was a sex addict. He went to a clinic for it. He had sex with a guy's granddaughter,
whatever. And so from there, it just goes downhill. It's just dumb. It's like,
so it's total cult of personality, the society of the spectacle. And it makes total sense.
And I would say, let's begin to look out for this happening in the States pretty soon.
People, you know, there's a need for some different news and need to switch away.
And but it just kind of the fact that it's been going on for three days, just kind of amazed me.
You know, people are sticking their hands even deeper in the sand. At a moment when we actually
have to be kind of paying attention. So you can listen to the whole interview if you're so inclined
by checking out the show notes, links there at datasourcecode.com.
One other thing, there is obviously, I got to go through some bummer news. I can't help it.
I did what I just want to pay homage to and Presley. This is the news reporter who was beaten
in her home and apparently robbed. Now, this happened in, I believe, Arkansas.
And it's just really, really weird. The whole story is weird. How it happened, you know,
it doesn't, it's just like no information. There's no news, but she passed away, you know,
beaten the death. And I'm sure that there's been some stories here and there, but, oh, man,
it's beautiful. How did this happen? And why did this happen? And, you know, just, I don't know,
there's something about it. I have no basis what's of all other than I got a hunch that there's
a lot more behind this that went out hearing about. If it really is just a robbery, then,
you know, violent robbery, it just doesn't feel right. And it's a horrible shame.
All right. So I was in Los Angeles for, let me see, I was at them two, three days, two days,
three days for digital Hollywood, which was kind of interesting. It was good to be in Los Angeles.
We also have a new sales guy, Paul Mendoza, who's in charge of the Southwestern region.
And he's part of the Mendoza crime family, I hear. But he has a very interesting way of selling.
And, of course, I'm talking about ad sales. So we, you know, we hit all the media agencies and
it was, it's kind of vibrant in Los Angeles. A lot is happening. It feels a lot more alive when it
comes to digital and online media. Like a lot more is happening in Los Angeles than,
well, certainly than San Francisco. But even New York in a way, LA just seems, I have to say,
it seems to get it a little bit more. So I'm very bullish and very happy about that. It was also
kind of cool to hang out at Digital Hollywood. I'm not one who likes to do a lot of, you know,
conferences at all. I'm not really comfortable doing keynote speeches. I like, I do, I do
one every single, every single time I do a daily source code, I feel like I'm doing a keynote.
You know, I'm tired. I'm tired of talking. And nothing to say. And the things that I want to say,
people at a conference don't want to hear me talk about. But I did do this one panel, which was,
it was kind of interesting. It was about, basically, called the personality online Hollywood
gossip. I'm not, well, I was asked to be on this panel. And for a number of reasons, but just to
give you an idea was on the panel, it was Axis Hollywood, the entertainment section of Yahoo fan
cast, people magazine I think was, was represented. And the village voice, actually,
a bill from the village voice, it was kind of fun hanging out with him. We pretty much agreed
a lot of things. But it was just amazing, you know, how seriously people take that stuff,
that there's a whole panel about it, essentially. I just, after about a half an hour, it's like,
I just got started messing with this. I just got so tired of it. You know, what are the,
what are the boundaries and how far should we go? Like, what are you talking about?
So, there was no one, no one has any scruples. You know, these, these children who are
celebrities are being misused. And nothing new, by the way, Judy Garland was given pills by the
studio, pills to go to bed, pills to get up and make another movie, shut up, bitch and work.
You know, this is nothing new, surprise surprise. Hollywood is fake. The movies are fake.
Television is fake, duh. Please. It was fun. I ran into people who hadn't seen it like
14 or 15 years, including Daniel Paul, who worked at Apple way back in the day. And he
hooked me up with the first Apple had a program where they'd hand out loaner computers to people
of immediate influence. And that's when I got my first Apple, too. That's how far back we go.
And actually had to send it back. That was, it was the program. You get your Apple, too. And then
after, you know, like two years, you had to send it back to them, which I diligently did by then,
you know, I had already, I was already in a buying like power book, one, 40, or the, the duo,
doc, 230. Remember that one? I'm a Mac with a gigantic, like a big floppy drive. Oh boy, good times.
So that was, that was okay. And there were some people who actually had some pretty interesting
content that they were trying to get distributed. So yeah, all in all, not too bad. And
the end of, as I said, even the sales calls. Because, you know, we got to, we got to really
move it. We made a very conscious decision. Of course, we were, we had some foresight about the economic
downturn, duh. You listen to this show. You know, we had some foresight. And that's why we,
we were reorganized early on several months ago. You remember that? We changed, you know,
that's around the time we changed our name from Pod Show to me, Vio. And we also raised the
additional money. We knew that this was coming. We knew what would be necessary. And so,
you know, we're in a reasonably good spot to really put the, the pedal to the metal. And hammer
the acceleration, you know, while other people are, and other companies are having issues and
having trouble. Now, we might be able to pull ahead. And we're all working very, very hard. And of
course, that includes the entrance of the new member of our management team, Jeff Carp, who joined
us from Electronic Arts. We haven't done an official press release about it yet. I have quite
honestly just going to be a bit of crazy busy. And, you know, we were just working.
Jeff, we recruited him right out of Electronic Arts. He was for eight years. He's been there. He was
the head of all North American marketing for all their games. So, if you ever saw commercial,
or, or we're turned on to any EA game, Jeff Carp was responsible for it. Well, let's call it
accountable. He uses words like that. So, we are getting our shit together. I'm very happy about it.
That's, that's basically that. So, I quite sure when I'm going back, but we'll probably hit New York,
you know, as again, you know, just out there, drawing up sales, got to make it work. We,
we have a small company, challenging times, but got to push forward, got to move forward, got to work
really hard. And again, it's, you can see that it's tough out there. There's a lot of, a lot of
companies running into trouble, which is unfortunate, but it's the reality. Call it a version of
main street. You're witnessing it before your very eyes. Okay. Some feedback coming in through the
drop. Remember, you can leave your voicemail comments there. There is a voicemail number with,
you can always find that in the, in the show notes, curie.com, or crossposts at DennySourceco.com.
If you use a paid number, but then you can leave a voicemail on the drop. Or you can upload an MP3 file.
That's fine, too. I'm, I'm, I'm going to be kidding me, PSC and Hammer Smith. The secret, you want to know
what the secret is. The secret is, they got suckers like you to buy that book. Oh, man, come on.
That's the problem with the world today. People expect to get everything just by thinking
about it and not working for it. Now, I got a number of comments about this. This, of course,
referring to the last portion of Daily Source Code episode 800, the previous show, where I discussed
the book, The Secret. And a lot of people really misinterpreted what I was saying about that.
Of course, it's ludicrous to think that you can just think happy thoughts and be positive.
And then have the world be your oyster and everything show up exactly when you need it, how you
need it and exactly get to your specifications. Obviously not. And I only,
really highlighted this book because it does pull together a number of things that I've come to learn
throughout life and do believe, absolutely, if influenced the course of my life. I didn't
come from money. I didn't come from success. I didn't come from, in fact, my family of anything
are a bunch of robots for the government. We're all government issue, worked in various levels
of the military and politics. You know, absolutely assimilated. I've never been a part of that.
I've broken free of that very early on. And I've lived the life that has my own life,
which is taken its own course, but by focusing, by thinking about things, is usually when you start
driving towards them and make them happen. And I disagree. The book does not tell you that you
can get whatever you want just by thinking about it. It doesn't sound like a lot of people actually
read the book. But again, it's not a solution. It is just a part of a toolkit that you do need to
become successful. And it's worked for me. That was my point. Man, people really took it the wrong way.
I'm surprised, honestly. I had a work. Which, of course, means I didn't communicate it properly.
What we want, we have to say. And I think it's quite obvious. I work very hard for what I want.
And what I want is not just from me. It's for all the people in my companies and it's for the
community of listeners and it's for my child and all the children of the world. That's what I want.
Not from me. I don't give a shit about me. I really don't. And of course, you got to work. That's
the whole point. But focus and it all comes a lot easier. You get perspective. It all makes logical sense.
For what we want. Don't save up any money to buy that book. Don't save up people. Don't waste any
money to buy that. Don't watch the DVD. Oh, man. What a waste. Love date, hundred. Love to show.
Keep it going, man. You almost had it up until the end. That's not a secret, dude.
That's the power of. I don't want to work for what I want. I just want to think about it and get it.
No, no, no. That would be what we're about to receive from our new president. That's what
that's all about. That's the big secret there. We'll be talking about that more without a doubt
because there was lots of feedback from, I guess about how much supporters, but maybe just
people who misunderstand my position on that as well. I'm all about work. I'm all about creating
opportunity, creating jobs, creating wealth, not for myself, but wealth among a smaller
community. We got 50, 60 employees and providing them with things like, oh, crazy shit.
What is it? Oh, yeah. Health benefits. Yeah. That kind of stuff. I'm not doing it because
I get nothing better to do. It's what I do. It's what I enjoy doing.
Then when I put my mind to it and when everyone in the company is aligned, things really accelerate.
Things start to happen. Good things start to happen. That's why the whole title of the book,
the secret is kind of a farce to start with. It's no secret. It's logical.
But to take it like, I haven't seen a DVD. Maybe the DVD puts it in a wrong perspective,
but reading the book. I was like, didn't seem like it was telling me all I had to do was
did it home and dream. Although we can hope for change. That's the big secret, I guess.
That's a problem. That's the whole problem with the world today. Everybody just wants it. They
don't want to work for it. They don't want to have to save up for it. They just want it now.
I loved everything about the show up until the end. I got to say that was a real disappointment.
I see where the oil is going. I see where the cold is going. Maybe they're trying to bankrupt the
Saudis now. That'd be an interesting thing. The first time. Get the Saudis all worried. If you
noticed on the news, they're pumping 2.5 billion into their banks today.
And still going the way of the corporation. It's still going the way of the big brother. We got to
look at that and we got to analyze how do you fight a corporation? When the only way you can
make money is through the corporation, the only way you can survive is to make money. We can't
buy our own food. They're outlawing that with one cento. Tell the show, keep them talking.
Do you see an hammer's mess? Hopefully he had him back to Oregon this week.
Take it easy. I'm in. Thank you, he's. I really think you misunderstood me. I really think you did.
Although listening to your comment and just thinking about the words hope and change, it does
really seem like there is a mass mania of food where we're just hoping stuff will get better and
we think we deserve change. But yeah, again, you're right in that regard. We absolutely don't
seem to want to work for it because it's being spoon fed to us. And that's not just in the states.
That's that's global. That's absolutely worldwide. And I've and I look and I live in a society where
it takes place right now in the United Kingdom. So there's no escaping it. But I'm also,
I'm I'm planning a melody out of it. I'm getting I'm I just have to become a little more
laid back about all of this. There's not much that can be done. We'll have four years now. And this
absolutely one of the reasons why I hope Barack Obama is elected president so that we can follow
along. And I can continue to say, oh, well, gee, is that really unexpected or is this what you
really wanted? Is this what you voted for? Is this what you think was the promise? Because that is my
feeling. You know, we're we're really being lied to and we're being snow jobbed into this.
Yeah, I'm more about that in a bit. So anyway, the secret itself, the book is more about positive
thinking, the power of the of the conscious and unconscious mind about focus, about how you can
change your inner feelings and an instant. And yes, indeed, about the things that have not been
proven and almost go against all laws of physics, you know, energy, magnetism, amongst beings.
You know, I believe in a lot of that stuff. But I never intended anyone to believe that they
can just sit there and hope for good things and the change will come. Oops, I'm sorry. That is
there you go. It doesn't actually work that way. You just said it. Okay. So there's not much to say,
you know, there's not a lot of news about the general finances that I want to get, you know, the
bailout and everything that that is going on right now, other than holy crap. It's all over the
math and it just seems like all of the predictions are coming true. You know, the dollar will eventually
get hammered. It can't stop. You know, the banks have taken our money, are 700 billion,
another 150 billion went to other stuff. That nothing to do with the bailout, but that's how they got
it passed. And so they're going to use that money to acquire other banks and not actually pass it on.
You know, the now the the borrowing rate for banks is, you know, the the the the primary
rate was just caught. It's 1% now. I still if you go into a bank and you want a mortgage,
you're looking at seven or eight percent. I don't see any really cheap. If you're talking
a long term, not an adjustable rate mortgage or a long term mortgage is incredibly high.
Interbank lending, that means the the banks lending to each other is three and a half times the
going rate. It just makes no sense. I'm not an economist, but when you understand the very basic
principles and if you don't, you need to need to learn about it. You need to pick up a book.
You should be able to pick up a junior high school book and learn about it. You'll see that
what they're doing just makes no sense. And whatever they think it's doing,
it's definitely not getting money moving in the economy. Other than we're being encouraged to
shop more and buy stuff on credit cards. And I saw a report on CNBC this morning that
people are now using credit cards in more places than they used to. The the in fact the number one
check this out. The number one use of credit cards today, the retail level, is it McDonald's.
People are buying the McDonald's with credit cards. I can't tell you that that's just scary.
You have to believe it. No, so I would guess people don't actually have the money.
So they're buying their McDonald's, which is not exactly the healthiest food to be eaten too much.
They're buying it on credit. So it seems to me like we're in a pretty dire straight right now.
So the European Union has been looking at E money as we call it because of course
that's the next step is you know take it from credit cards into
really electronic wallets, you know money that they you load up onto a card or
very much like the the transport cards. Now the European Union is doing a lot with this. They
have an E money directive and there was a whole review process of what industry fell to the
banks felt and there's a PDF you might want to peruse that of course also in the show notes linked
through. It's really quite interesting because essentially when everything is E money and there's no
more paper this is the move from paper to plastic. You're going to hear you're going to hear a lot of
that paper to plastic which of course is kind of a play on the whole plastic or paper or what
kind of bagged you want it when you're checking out the supermarket. You can hear this term
moving from paper to plastic meaning moving from money that's printed into the easiest form of
money creation stuff that just exists in a spreadsheet and it looks like the European Union is pretty
set up. They have four what do they call them? Let me see. Electronic money institutions they call them
EMDs and electronic money institution ELMIs and these are these are companies that essentially
will be keeping the money in a database on a spreadsheet. I mean the implications of this are pretty
big because you know then it becomes so much easier just to say okay if you have X amount on deposit
you can lend out 10 times that it's the same thing it's it's just a continuation of the problem
we have with central banking only it feels well more like we would be bringing it or reserve lending
I should say we'll be bringing it one step closer to to infinity MPH had all coordinated that
trying to do this across Europe. It's pretty crazy. Let me see you got another phone call here
I want to share with you. This was funny. Hello Mr. Curry it's Brent from Tampa Florida you know
every day I turn on the news with an unsfox MSNBC CNN local affiliates whatever they're always
talking about how terrible things are. I hate to break the news to you but there's probably 75 to 80
percent of us out here in United States they're doing just fine. We're not behind in our house payments
we're not behind in our car payments we're still spending lots of money. I go out once you twice a week
I spend 75 to 100 bucks every time I go out I just bought a brand new motorcycle I'm not behind
on any payments at all and paying my credit cards off and I'd say for the most part most of us out
there are probably in that same seat so when you talk about how terrible things are you're actually
brainwarsing a lot of people into failure. I mean look at kids in school when they go to school
and they're surrounded by people that give them a lot of good feedback they tend to do better in
school but if you're in a bad school and people say oh you'll never make it you'll never make it in
life you're just doomed for failure chances are you're gonna fail so how about every once in a while
in the DSC putting out a good story putting out something that talks about the good things that are
happening in life because there's more of us out there than not that are doing just fine take care
my phone or see you later you think that do you speak about all that who am I kidding we're just as
screwed as the next guy hey that's what's that YouTube video what do you think uh then this goes in this
whole whole thing about death collectors yeah it's kind of funny yeah yeah it's you know I just keep
your eye on it as a DSC in Oregon said currently and wherever the hell he was you know we
we got to take care of our own and just keep your eye on the ball and follow the money
because it's your money it's being taken away it's being uh now we're gonna give it to
um oh we're gonna give it to we're gonna give it to the auto industry but instead of doing something
well so here's it just one quick thing about this and all and I'll move on is it amazing that the
US auto industry is collapsing they're a standing at the government store saying you have to give
us money we're too big to fail wherever that before we're too big to fail because we've got uh hundreds
of thousands of jobs that depend upon the auto industry for what I understand almost 17% of
all retail purchases in the United States is based on the the car industry so it's not just uh
the manufacturers but it's the parts it's the the showrooms sales etc so these guys are dying on the
vine uh looking for billions of dollars from the government that's your money in my money and if it's
not then it's being printed which which which really takes away from the value of your money in mine
if you if you have US dollars um and the oil companies the drug dealers the true drug dealers of
of the of the universe are posting record profits uh exon mobile today 16 billion in profits for
the quarter so why don't we you know considering that one billion dollars of bailout money for the
auto industry equals 30,000 jobs what why doesn't exon mobile step up to the plate you know make
them give those guys 10 billion make all the top three oil companies give them 10 billions they
got 30 billion that would create a nice hunk of jobs or maintain them save them and the caveat
is that this is only for uh new technologies uh like the plug-in hybrid electric and I'm not talking
about you know the 150 miles per gallon which is crazy I was looking at the Obama campaign uh
uh they talk about a plug-in hybrid that gets 150 miles to the gallon well if it's a plug-in what
is it have to be a hybrid and you know 150 miles to the gallon gallon of what it's a plug-in
you know it should it should be plug-in or a hybrid I think there's two different things there
because if it's a hybrid then doesn't necessarily plug-in it can recharge from from the motion of the engine
that's what the uh what the preest does anyway I'm moving off topic why don't we have the oil
companies who are you know always oh yes we're investing in future energy and future technologies
having really stuff up to the plate haven't given 10 you know have exon mobile give away 10
billion of the 16 billion uh to the car companies um to new subsidiaries so that they can go and
create you know real new cars or you could consider not bailing out the oldest establishment
but growing a new one you know these new companies like Tesla even though they you know they're
making a stupid car it's you know it's a sports car it's like not meant that's not that's a niche market
you know make something useful and you and make it as cheap as possible and uh incentivize those
exhaust guys new new people new entrepreneurs new companies do that you know so now the incentive is no no
we're just going to continue making what we were making we're going to try and bail out and be
get the bail out and continue along the status quo these are the things that just don't make sense
to me and what will be next what will the next industry be that is too big to fail because of the
jobs meanwhile the true R&D the true entrepreneurialism in the United States which a lot of that
I feel is in uh in uh in uh high technology uh they're laying off left and right big companies
laying off uh 10,000 people at a time so if three companies lay off 10,000 people that's 30,000
that's a billion dollars that they should be whining at the government force saying oh please help
bail us out this has always been my problem chucklehead this is not the way the United States is
supposed to work it really isn't it's not a big business is 25% of what goes on in the
States business wise the rest is small and medium business we're helping the wrong people we're
giving them our money and if we're not giving them our money then we're printing it which is
devaluing our current money this is what's so wrong and both candidates voted for it
Barack Obama and John McCain both skewges for Wall Street voted for the bailout
shopping every Sunday at the moment oh everyone's more I love more than we have it all
so take me to the new show you can you hear the rain and make sure you want to see
it's such a show beautiful day yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
we got
And make sure you want to see
It's such a beautiful day
But yeah
Yeah, I'm so tired of the wings
But I have been missing wings
You little like a king
Well, lots of money and things
Let's wear
Baby burn your pocket
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah
Deep deeper in your wallet
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah
So take me to the new store
You can't you hear the rain
It makes you want to see
It's such a beautiful day
I'm so tired of the wings
But I have been missing wings
You little like a king
Shinaya Twain
I gotta tell you, I kind of
Didn't follow Shinaya Twain since I feel like a woman
This was left on the drop of drop.au slash daily source code
And it made total sense
That's right
So the change
The way the system works
Just change it at the bottom
That's how we got to do
Save your money
Keep it in cash
I know right now
It feels crazy
If you're looking at your retirement plans
If you're in the United States
You have a 401k perhaps
It works different in many different countries
But in the States, it's very cultural
To look at what your 401k is invested in
My personal recommendation would not be to sell
Leave it in there
If you can, which means you basically have to leave it in there
For the next 10 years
But that will improve you
If you're retiring now
You're getting screwed
Hate that's hate to say it
And I know plenty of people who are
See if you can only take out a little bit of your 401k
See if you can
See what you can change
Because you're going to have to do it
Because it's going to be quite a while before the value was back
But selling getting out now
Trying to reinvest in something not a good idea
I can't believe it's already like 50 minutes
I got a boogie along with a couple things here
God bless Ireland, man
They were so right when they voted
I was the only country in the European Union
Allowed a referendum
Permitted a referendum about the Lisbon Treaty
Because now, as we see in these Sunday times
Here in the United Kingdom, John Hutton, the minister of defense
Or the United K
United of K
He's the Secretary
Secretary defense
He's backing a French plan for a European army
Branding those who dismiss it as pathetic
In a wide ranging interview with the Sunday Times
He said, I think we've got to be pragmatic about those things
Where it can help we should be part of it
His support goes beyond the public position of Gordon Brown
The prime minister and will antagonize those who believe that
Further European cooperation will undermine NATO by excluding the United
States
Yet bloody, bloody, blah, the whole point was
Why do we need a European army now?
Nicholas Sarkozy, the French president, has sought to develop
Europe's military structures with new headquarters and rapid reaction forces
Each consisting of 1,500 troops from member countries
It's not a big military, but it's a start
And Hutton, the defense secretary of the UK, said
France is one of our closest allies militarily
The French believe very strongly in this type of role
If we can support it, we should
Any added that working with the EU allies
And military missions was perfectly sensible
I think we need less army, I'm all for less military
And why now do we have to sit like schmocks in between the United States and Russia
Essentially, and we'll have our own little army
Oh man, that's exactly what the Irish word about
They word about the tax situation, but they primarily word about a global European army
I said, no, no, no, it's not going to happen and here it is
Well, this is a good idea, let's go and do it
It's being driven by Sarkozy, European army, what's next?
Hi, Adam, it's Matt from Game's Weasel on this week's show
We Review Pro Evolution Soccer 2009
Give Spore a quick spin on the PC
Some free runners tell us about the new parkour action game Mirrors Edge
And you can win a copy of Fallout 3 and the Shining New Playstation 3
To play it on, that's all against Weasel.com
Yeah, gamesweasel.com
That show kicks ass, I love what Matt Cuttle does on that show
And I've never been a gamer, I don't own a game console
But I really don't enjoy what I'm seeing
Then some of these things look really awesome
And you know, Jeff Carpin, we've got an injection of
Game culture into the company, it's kind of exciting
I guess we'll have to break down in the new pad
By the way, we are moving, we got a new place
Haven't named it yet
I don't know if it's going to be like the Curry Terrace
Because it is on it is a terrace house
It's on a square, maybe called the Curry Square
Haven't quite figured that one out
I don't think there's any curry corner
There is somewhat a little iteration to be had
The Curry Corner
The Curry Corner Casa
Anyway, yeah, before like some before the end of the year
We'll be moved out so
Holy crap
Got a lot to do, a lot to pack
Going down under for a couple of stories
You know, Australia, this guy has been around before
And I believe this, I don't know how old this news piece is
I'll fire it up here
Maybe I can see when it was posted on YouTube
But there is some very, yeah, 13th of February, 2008
Very encouraging
Very encouraging news about energy
And I've been following these guys
People who make generators
With magnetic pole
So they're using the attractiveness
And the rejection of magnets
Depending on if you have the north
The south pole of the magnet
Focus on each other or north north or south south
There could be a pole or a rejection
A force
And just in a nutshell
I'm going to play a little piece of this
This news piece from Sky News in Australia
The whole concept is you get the generator going
By using a very low power source like a battery
And then once it's running
I've seen in some cases people actually disconnect the original power source
And then it becomes something that I've grown up to know
As impossible it becomes a virtually a
Was that calling San Francisco office
A perpetual motion machine
Which is highly unbelievable as is for many
But also if you keep the battery connected
It outputs five times the power that you're putting in
Which is also said to be impossible
And these guys, it seems like they really got the real deal
I mean this is a mainstream news report
It's not bullshit
So I'm presuming they're reporting to some degree in a proper manner
And everyone seems to agree these guys have it
And it can power a whole house
So I'll play a little bit of the clip you like it
I dare and imagine a machine that could power your house for free
Well, that's exactly what two Australian inventors claim they've developed
Using magnets and a battery
Their new generator has been described as revolutionary
And find investors aligning up for a piece of the action
Chris Allen reports
So John, this is the machine
Yes, this is it Chris
What's the capable of?
A little power house, this will the machine will provide sufficient electricity
To run a house and have power doing
It sounds good to be true
But inventor John Christie is convinced his machine will change the world
So John, basically you're saying this machine can produce five times as much power as it can see it
Yes, it does
This one is exactly as we see it
It does and in fact it can produce more than that
Once Kickstarter from a battery John and his partner Lou Brits say this prototype will run for years without stopping
Generating 24 kilowatts of power a day
You don't get more revolutionary
I think I mean we've talking about something that has the capacity to change the way that the world produces its electric power
There's a capacity to change the way that motors cars are propelled
You can replace the combustion engine impact
John, these are big claims that you sure you can live up to them
We don't really need to live up to them, Chris
What the technology speaks for itself
I mean a household could buy one of these machines and install it in his garage
And power is house forever, they're buying another kilowatt from a retailer
I mean that's how serious it is
Steve Bratsington is an interesting choice of words
That's how serious it is
It's almost as if it's a bad thing
So you could buy this, it'll run for a couple of years
It'll power your whole house, you don't have to buy energy from an outside supplier
That's how serious this is
Well, isn't that like a good thing?
You would depend on electrical engineer
He's seen the machine and backs up everything John says
It's revolutionary
That's the only way to describe it
I think the technology
It's not bending physics, it's just using principles
That I guess are commonly used in power generation today
In a different way
These guys have thought outside of this way
Basically it's magnetic attraction and magnetic repulsion
That provide the movement or the moment of the motor
Can you understand why some scientists are skeptical about it?
There is no physicist or engineer
Who is looked at our motor or has looked at our figures
Who says it doesn't work
Yeah
So take a look at the whole video, it's pretty amazing
The thing absolutely looks cool
But I wouldn't mind filling up the drop with some information
On this technology, other people into it
And let's try and keep these guys alive
They're clearly under some things
We should at least give them that
We should protect them
If this stuff really works
Because man, there's going to be a lot of people really pissed off
As this catches on
Hey Adam, this is a former calling from Brisbane in Australia
I just wanted to call and let you
And the idea is, listen, there's no bad in the vent
Coming up soon called
My Vemba
Basically, we went around Australia
In the world of growing pistaches
During our Vemba to raise money to help raise awareness
Okay, it took me a little while
The tune into the accent
But so this is a plea
To support MoVend
No Vemba with a mic
MoVemba during the month of November
By growing a moustache
Perfect for the chakra heads out there
Upload your pictures to the drop
All the men's health issues
In Australia, the money will be donated
To the post-ite cancer foundation
All the Australia
And a company called Beyond Blue
Which is Australia's national depression
Initiatives
The funds will be used for the research
And increase support networks
For those men who suffer from prostate cancer
And depression
The sponsor, people can donate
Paypal, credit card or a checkfire
Slowmail
I guess paypal is probably the easiest for most people
I would appreciate any support
The chuckle heads can give in the form of sponsorships
We've also sent you an email with URL link
To help my moust
I don't have any pictures posted yet
As it does follow me
First of November
My current aim is to grow a nice clean little
80s porn star
I'll see how that plays
May it's thanks for Charlie
I normally listen to while driving towards the morning
And I think your recent long-shows are great
All right, thank you
All right, good luck with that
Yeah, the call is out all the chuckle heads
There's a lot of stuff going on in Australia actually
I've mentioned before that they're talking about some pretty
Strange and internet filtering
And it looks like it's like it's really happening
This is from the Harold Sun
Which is mainstream publication in Australia
Australia, I'm reading verbatim
Australia will join China
In implementing mandatory censoring of the internet
Under plans put forward by the federal government
The revelations emerge as US tech giants
Google Microsoft and Yahoo
And a coalition of human rights and other groups
Unveiled a code of conduct aimed at safeguarding online
Freedom of speech and privacy
Well, we know that that only comes down to whatever they
Broker with the government
I mean they all have deals with the Chinese government
But it seems to be pretty far reaching
And of course this is to quote, protect the freedom and expression
And privacy rights of users
Yet they're talking about mandatory blocking
Where possible of illegal material
And this is where it gets kind of tricky
And I'm not quite sure what is legal and illegal in Australia
But they're classified here
Okay, if a board member Colin Jacob said it would have little effect
On illegal internet content
And here's the description of it including child pornography
Of course, you don't want child pornography
But they're expanding it now
And I'll tell you exactly
I can't find it now
Somewhere in this article
They actually talk about hardcore pornography
So they're taking it from child pornography to hardcore
And you could tell me it's just that it's semantics
But it's not, you know there is a difference
There's an absolute difference between those two
And so you know what is next
What kind of pornography will be illegal
Not now we're determining
Down to that level
It seems a little bit scary to me
And they're going to do this with filtering at the head end
And once the filter is in
Oh, here we go
The plan was first created as a way to combat child pornography
And and adult content
Okay, so what does that mean?
If we want adult content we have to buy it
It could be extended to include controversial websites
On youth in Asia or anorexia
Now of course, I'm not for a lot of what is going on
And these areas but this is really going to shut down free speech
And if the government can determine what is illegal
Then you know, when is the show becoming illegal
It won't take that long, believe me
Because it'll be negative sentiment
Or maybe because I'm depressing people or whatever it is
So Australia keeps sending in information
Drop that stuff at drop.io slash daily source code
We got to stay up to speed on what's happening
Because it looks like it's going to take place down under first and foremost
And if there are other countries around the world where this is happening
Which by the way, probably includes the United Kingdom
But not to this extent
Stay in touch
The great wall, the great firewall of China extending now to down under
And Australia
All goes to prove the point Jarvis Galker needs to make
You want to know who really wants the world
Jarvis has the answer
Would you hear?
Listen, not true, don't
Those was decided
We'll end up with the most
That the cream cannot help
But always rise up to the top
But I say
Shit flow
If something's too much
Friends, you're the same again
But we're not, we're the fewest ever
Comes us to world in the world
Now we work in classes
All the soly
They are so close to society as they can see
So let them all kill each other
And get a baby
We see
That's the way, don't you know
From the guys that's run into the show
Let's be mad, like my head wants to kill
Come on, come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on come on
Come on, come on
I'll figure feeling alone
Three facial hopes to change them
I'm not afraid to touch how I believe
I'll feel it, I will always stress
Feel lies
Too many things
Now it's just, how I feel Yeah
Look you mirror how neck's your lingering
If you're lucky it's perfect for the natural
Do you think that I'm so kind of dumb?
It's the ideal way to order the world
For those who make it in my name
If you don't like it, then leave
I'll use your right to protest on the streets
If you're right, we're talking about you
No, no, no, no, no, no
It's just how you love it more
It's just how you love it
It's just how you love
Jarvis Cocker, you can only say it in the UK.
Cuts are still running the world.
Hell yeah.
You know that.
It's wanna make my position clear once again that when it comes to the two leading candidates,
the only ones allowed in the debates, the only ones really allowed into the election race,
which is the nominee from the Democratic Party,
nominee from the Republican Party.
Because there are other independence
who, in many cases, are on the ballot everywhere,
not everywhere, but in most states, Cynthia McKinney,
Chuck Baldwin, Bob Barr, and Ralph Nader.
There may even be more, but those are the four independent time Canadian right off the top of my head.
They're not invited to the debates.
Why? Because it's a messed up system.
But at the end of the day, it is the same people running these two candidates,
the four runners, Barack Obama and John McCain.
And just to give you some proof,
it's a big new Brazinski.
He was the guy that was running Jimmy Carter,
and he's written books, and he's self-proclaimed Marxist.
His sons are now both advising each of the candidates.
So his son, Mark Brazinski, is a foreign policy advisor to the Obama campaign to Obama,
and I'm sure we'll be in this cabinet.
And Ian Brazinski is advisor to John McCain.
So the control is there through the lineage.
And these two guys, they are merely actors.
That's really what they are. They are actors.
And they're good ones.
Although it seems like Obama gets all the good lines, all the good jokes.
And the writers are really playing up his character, the true writers.
And McCain has been reduced to a bit player.
You know, it's like a soap opera.
And it's the way it feels, and it's the way I would produce it,
if I were running it, because it gets great ratings.
And all of this money that they raise essentially goes right into the media
to buy airtime, Obama just bought a half hour commercial.
All these ads, it's hundreds and hundreds of millions.
So it's a closed loop system, and it works very well, and they don't want to change that.
But the way I express this has resulted in some pretty aggressive feedback.
Now, this can also be from conversation I've had with John C. Dvorak on Noah Genda.
But I did want to share two emails.
Unfortunately, they didn't come through.
I'd love to have these in audio.
Even if you're pissed at me, please, leave a voice mail.
The email is kind of boring, and I did ask these people independently.
And you know, send this to me in a voice mail, man.
This is good stuff, because you know, this is a dialogue I want to have.
This first one coming from Kim Costello.
You are entitled to your opinion, but have you ever tried to do real research on Obama?
So whenever someone starts with that, I'm like, wow, you have not been listening to me,
and to this show for a long time at all, because I do nothing else.
I spend a lot of my time researching, and mainly on the stuff that people make public themselves.
And yes, I'm very familiar with the Obama's policies, because it's all right there on Barakobama.com.
I can continue.
It's all right not to like the guy, which I've never said.
I like the guys.
He seems perfectly okay.
He's a great candidate.
I wish we could be programming him.
And we could be giving him the right things to say and to do and to promise.
Anyway, says it's all right not to like the guy, but your reasoning is just crazy.
You keep stating that you know what he is going to do as president and it scares you.
My question is, where did you get this mysterious knowledge of Obama?
You sound like a fox news pundit.
Well, yeah.
And when I talk about McCain, I sound like a CNN pundit.
And have you ever played the CNN Fox game?
It's best after debate, which of course we don't have right now.
But even if you just from time to time, put, you know, use the last channel, the flashback,
whatever the button is called on your remote control, and go flip back and forth between Fox and CNN.
And Fox will be, you know, all four McCain against Obama.
And CNN will be all four Obama against McCain.
It's a setup.
You know, is that obvious?
And it's just obvious.
This is, it's all part of the game.
Now, here's the thing that a lot of people responded to that I've received several emails.
And it really surprises me when I get this.
Also, Kim says, you always state that you are not a racist.
Yet you also say, you are afraid what will happen if Obama is not elected.
Oh, no, riots.
That is pretty fucking racist.
Black people can't contain their militant anger.
Now, here's what's interesting.
Whenever I say, hey, man, I really hope Obama wins because there's going to be riots if he does it.
I'm thinking about the neighbor I have in San Francisco who's working two hours a day in her spare time.
For the campaign going to Obama camp and has completely been assimilated by the process.
And it's thinking this way.
Is she's a woman?
She's white and she's Jewish.
I see her writing.
I see yuppies writing.
But the true racist, sir, is you.
I presume, I'm presuming Kim is a him.
Could be heard, doesn't matter.
You're, you're the racist.
You're the one that thinks riots.
Oh, black people.
I never said that.
Never have never even entered my head.
And I get a lot of that.
So those of you who imply or think that I imply that black people would be writing, you're the racist.
You're thinking that.
Not me.
And you're reflecting it in your emails.
Crazy.
No, no, I'm thinking yuppies.
You know, I'm thinking people who are totally, totally, totally assimilated into this process.
And they're going to be angry.
But I don't think we have to worry about it.
Honestly, I think the playbook is pretty clear.
So here's the second type of feedback that I've received.
She's also quite misunderstood.
Adam, I really enjoyed the podcast.
The quote of yours from the recent show.
And I think this is an accurate quote.
I hear what Obama is going to do.
Running companies and countries that are socialist, which is the direction the US has had.
Our company is the one that's going to get screwed.
We're going to get all the tax crap.
All that shit's going to come down on us.
We're the ones that are actually working in people who are lazy bitchers are going to be sitting around taking handouts and not wanting to do anything.
This is not what America is about.
Absolutely.
I totally agree.
And when I look at the economic plan.
In this case, Obama doesn't matter.
McCain has as the same stupid ideas.
It's just packaged a different way in the less compelling way to the majority of voters.
And so Matt goes on to say, you are an insulated coddled out of touch ignorant fuck.
Obama raising the top tax rate for percent with the scary socialist Ronald Reagan had it.
So that the other 96% of Americans can actually have a bit of a tax cut after being screwed over the past eight years.
And this isn't going to turn us into Sweden, let alone the UK.
You come off as such an elitist trick talking about the poor people sitting around taking handouts.
Most people with an average income are working their asses off,
often without health care to try to get their businesses going or just trying to get fed to get by and feed their kids.
And you're talking about how you're a real patriot.
Take your thought policing false nationalism and shove it up your ass you fraud.
So I'm amazed at these types of comments if you actually understand what is being proposed.
And you're incorrect in saying that there's only talk of a tax cut.
It is refundable tax credits.
And it will go to people who don't pay taxes at all.
There is very little, in fact, there's only one line in the whole Obama plan about what is going to do for small business.
And that is making loans available.
Well, I haven't seen that.
I don't see any information.
I don't see any expansion.
And when I say we, I'm not talking about rich people.
I'm talking about people running businesses, small businesses.
I'm running a small business.
And Obama and McCain voted to give our money to the rich guys.
And but you're not outraged about that.
You just sit back and go, okay.
I'm sure that they're doing the right thing.
You know, Obama voted for it.
McCain voted for it.
Do you know that Hillary Clinton's health care plan?
That or indifferent was going to cost 110 billion dollars a year for universal health care.
And it got beaten down primarily, I think, on cost.
So we could have had, you know, in this bailout, of course, is eventually going to cost much more than 700 billion.
That was just the cold hard beginnings of the cash.
But take that and compound the value of that over 10 years.
You know, it's going to be trillions.
So we could have had, we could have fixed health care.
We tried to fix the financial industry.
None of that money went into your house or mine.
None of that money went into my business.
None of that money went anywhere except to the same people who created the problems.
And it was just printed so we're paying for it.
Where's the outrage?
That's what you should be outraged about.
That that is by definition wrong.
And the creating jobs is what we need to do.
So, you know, poor people who can't afford health care, what we could have fixed that.
We could have fixed that in a month's time.
Boom, the money was clearly there.
We had the money to bail out the financial industry.
You're buying those lies, I guess.
So why couldn't we just fix that?
We could have used any health care plan that was on the table.
But we didn't.
And people who don't have a job should not be receiving a refundable tax credit,
they should be receiving the opportunity to work with a job.
I mean, actually, I'd rather bail out the auto industry,
which, you know, they're asking for such a small amount of,
comparatively speaking, you know, 30, 30 or 50 billion, I think.
That's a small amount of money.
And one billion goes a long way.
I mean, that's what's being officially reported.
And it's been in, creates 30,000 jobs.
So take, if we're going to, and I'll pay for it.
I don't mind.
You can take more of my taxes.
That's fine.
But, you know, I'm, what I'm seeing is a whole lot of stuff.
I'm not seeing, I'm actually not seeing money going to create jobs.
I'm just not seeing it.
And I'm sorry that you think that I'm talking about me.
Like, I'm, like, I'm really super rich.
And by the way, part of the American dream used to be that you could make it,
and that you could be proud of that.
And other people would be happy for you and aspire to that.
That's one of the things that was always very different about America.
That's now gone.
It's now a dirty.
It's now dirty to have money.
Apparently.
And what I've seen from my experience,
and I've lived in the couple countries where this exact system is in place,
is you get a complacent culture.
And you get all kinds of screwed up things where people are just kind of working.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, okay.
So, then we'll probably get job credits and stuff like that.
And people will be working in places that don't really want to work.
And just more slavery is the way I see it.
And by the way, I work my ass off too to feed my family.
And to help feed 60 other families.
That's what America's about.
And I think that is very patriotic.
And I'm wondering how I can miscommunicate so grossly that people respond in this manner.
And I truly believe that you're just really not reading the facts as they're stated.
It shows becoming longer than I wanted it to be.
But, you know, have you actually gone to Barackobama.com?
And by the way, again, I'm not saying this to defunct anyone, debunk or talk down.
It doesn't matter.
I haven't even looked at McCain.
I'm so uninterested in what he's doing.
And I'm sure he's not going anywhere.
He certainly won't be president.
But, you know, when I see what Obama's doing on defense,
he's doubling up, doubling up on troops,
doubling up on rapid response teams.
It's all right here in the actual documentation.
He's going to find, disrupt, and destroy Al Qaeda.
Yeah, so we're just going to be in more places.
Staying in Afghanistan, sending more to Afghanistan.
It says it right here on the website.
This is probably my favorite.
This is a crazy one about the avian bird flu.
Let me just, avian, here we go.
Barackobama and Joe Biden pledged to lead an international effort
to diminish impact of major infectious disease epidemics.
Senator Obama was one of the first legislators to recognize
the dangers of a potential avian influenza pandemic
and was successful in securing 25 million for US agencies
to combat and contain widespread outbreaks of avian flu
and work to provide $4 billion in funding
for the Centers for Disease Control to combat avian flu.
What do you think that money's going?
It's going right into the big pharmaceuticals
for a non-existent virus.
So far, there is no version that goes from bird to human.
Yet there's $4 billion waiting for this to happen.
And we've gone over this so many times.
How many people have died of the bird flu?
In 15 years, doubtful 150.
And we don't even know if they really died from, you know,
we know that they didn't die from a bird to human version.
They died from a bird version.
And there's a lot of other issues out there
that could deserve $4 billion in funding.
Barackobama will continue to promote international efforts
to develop new diagnostics vaccines
and medicines that will be available in affordable
in all parts of the world.
Maybe I just read this differently.
But have a look at our information networks.
That's a different section.
Protect our information networks.
Everywhere I look, I see a new database being built.
I see secondary internet being built.
Barackobama will work with industry and academia
to develop and deploy a new generation of secure hardware
and software for our nation's critical cyber infrastructure.
I don't know.
Everywhere I look under any section.
And it's quite detailed.
These plans are very, very detailed.
Doubling the Homeland Security, doubling border protection.
Locking everything down, creating civilian forces,
forth there's some event.
Here on taxes, this is the one I was actually looking for.
For corporate tax.
Kind of interesting, by the way, that on the website,
the tax cut comes above $250,000,
but in the half hour information that he did,
that price has not been lowered,
or that level has been lowered to $200,000.
I don't know which one is right now.
If that was the updated amount,
they might want to update the website.
So giving you a credit, seven, up to $7,000
for the right car.
Well, damn.
I'll take that.
I don't think it's right.
But, you know, we're bailing out the car companies,
and we're giving money to people to buy cars.
Okay, where's the thing about small businesses?
Eliminate capital gains taxes for small businesses,
cut corporate taxes for firms that invest and create jobs in the United States,
and provide tax credits to reduce the cost of health care,
and to reward investments and innovation.
Like all of that.
But there's no expansion.
It's just everything else is very detailed down to the dollar.
When it comes to what you, what's going to be given to small businesses,
it doesn't say it anywhere.
There's no further information,
which makes me suspicious.
And that's what I mean.
Why I say that, you know,
it's turning into,
it's turning into a,
do a system of the government takes care of everything.
And it's just not the way it's always worked.
And it's not the way the Constitution stipulates it,
and that's so air-go,
not what America should be.
If America wants to be different,
then we should change the Constitution.
But, but not this way.
So anyway,
I'm going to try to do better on the communication of these issues,
and I'm not,
I'm not on any way think that I can change anyone's mind,
on what they want to vote,
and moreover it doesn't matter.
This is being run by people behind the scenes.
And if you're so ignorant to think,
that when you have two parties that these,
and fundraising that is undefined, rampant,
and you can do whatever you want to do,
and take from wherever you want to take from pretty much,
you know,
if you think there isn't a price to be paid,
and if that isn't to buy influence,
will you're crazy?
You're absolutely crazy.
Of course that's being done.
And what I recognize or come to recognize,
is this has been going on for a long time,
and maybe now I'm just a little bit more awake,
but it seems like it's so much more blatant.
And I've done it.
I've tried to build business in other countries,
where it is the direction that this ticket will take us,
and I've failed at it.
It's impossible to do.
You get all kinds of rules and regulations,
and we're going to get carbon credits and taxes,
and it's just slavery, complete slavery.
Speaking of enslavement,
and I don't have much more to do.
I do want to get to that review of the G1 Google phone.
This was just kind of scary.
It was a piece in the New York Times
that I just wanted to share with you.
It's called the California Prison Disaster.
Now, if you don't know in the United States,
and by the way,
we're going to get more of this under either McCain or Obama.
The prison systems are being privatized and commercialized.
So there is, although they say there isn't,
there is of course an incentive to have more inmates,
or at least a quota,
because that's how you make money.
It's a profitable system.
Each inmate has a profit associated with it.
But then when you really look at the statistics,
it's frightening.
The mass imprisonment philosophy that has packed prisons
and sent correction costs through the roof
around the country is hit,
especially card in California,
which has the largest prison population,
the highest recidivism.
I knew I was going to stumble on that.
recidivism rate,
and a prison budget raging out of control.
Now.
Here we go.
You know,
this isn't crap.
This isn't the one I wanted to read to you.
Oh, shit. This is the wrong article.
Oh, man.
Well, the whole, it is an article about marijuana, essentially,
and how million people are in jail on marijuana,
marijuana usage charges,
not on, not on distribution,
but on,
on being users of this plant.
And the crazy thing is,
and how, man,
now I'm pissed off.
I have the wrong article.
Okay, so roughly the statistics that I found,
which just freaked me out,
was that it's roughly equal men and women
who smoke marijuana,
although more white people smoke marijuana,
86% of people in jail,
for smoking marijuana are black.
And it's tripping me out
that that's what's going on in the United States.
And it may be going on just about everywhere else,
and it's messed up.
All right.
Time for a commercial break,
and a fun manner?
Hey Adam, Chris here from Seattle.
I wanted to tell you what happened to me the other day.
Since I never got to quit my day job,
a couple of years ago,
I ended up getting a job in IT.
One of my clients is a advertising
and communications firm,
and specializes in non-profit organizations
that are making a difference.
Why am I calling and telling you about it?
Because I had to say this.
The client said they wanted to register
a whole bunch of domain names.
And I said, well wait,
we're going to register them
with, of course, they said go daddy.
I said, well before you do that,
let me get you a code.
It will actually help you save some money on doing so.
And they said, oh, that's a great idea.
No way he says, where did you get this code from?
I said, well, have you ever heard of a guy named Adam Curry?
She says, do I know what fucking Adam Curry is?
That's her law for me.
She goes, this company,
that can she go with a company for 17 years now.
This company back in one of its iterations,
used to be owned, I think, new ideas.
Yeah.
And we sat and talked and she knew about you
and she didn't know anything about what you were doing
but turned around on the website.
And back, what I said was,
I said do I'll be honest,
if you guys, if I was doing what you were doing,
I'd be looking very strongly into media
and what they can do for your clients.
That's how it's podcasting goes
into independent media distribution all of those.
That's the only way.
I had to share that with you.
I'm sure by now you know exactly
which company it's an advertising firm in Seattle.
17 years.
You got to know something.
Anyway, I had to share that with you
and let you know that we're using the DSC codes
for GoDaddy in unique ways.
How do we do Adam?
No, man.
Chris, I really appreciate it.
First of all, for the, you know,
the blast from the past there.
Yep.
That's the company that's a run and I started,
I was at 94 and took public wound up selling it 99
when everyone said we were nuts.
And you know,
I know the company still exists.
Today is still profitable.
I think they're still listed as I think
it's the Hackett group now.
They did change their name.
And it wouldn't surprise me if the Seattle office
is still the member of the company.
And it's very cool.
And I appreciate you turn them on to that.
Of course, that's the whole system with this,
these sponsors of many shows,
including the daily source code.
You can find all different links in the show notes,
daily source code.com or crossposts at a curie.com.
You'll see the same type of great deals for a budget
rent to car for e-music.
We can get, was it 35 free songs, 25, 25 free songs.
What else do we have?
Brooks Stone.
And what we do is we actually go out.
We negotiate these great deals with these companies.
And then we only,
the producers only get paid on a success basis.
So if you buy something and you use one of
the mevio producers codes,
then that's when they actually get paid.
And so it incentivizes them to,
you know, to talk about it,
to motivate their audience.
If they're going to buy it anyway,
if you're going to rent a car as an example anyway,
or get domain names,
you might as well get the best deal anywhere
and support your favorite show.
It's that simple.
All right.
Enough with all that.
So we switched our phone providers from AT&T to T-Mobile in San Francisco
at the head office.
And that gave us the opportunity as part of the deal
to get new phones.
And so first, and I hadn't even done a review of it.
It was such a horrible experience.
I could, well, obviously I wanted the Google
phone because I wanted to try it out and share the experience
with you guys with the chuckle heads.
They didn't have it yet.
So first I got the Windows Mobile
Christ, now I forget which model it was.
I mean, I had it for literally one day.
And I gave it back crying to Chris and David and IT.
It was like Windows only a small.
And you need to stylists to operate it.
And it was all clunky feeling.
And it was just horrible.
You know, stuff that would take me one finger move
or maybe two actions on the Nokia,
on the E71 would take five steps on this.
It was just completely uselessness, completely worthless,
really unbelievably bad experience.
And then finally they switched it out.
And I was given the new G1 Google phone.
And very, very interesting device.
Now the hardware itself is made by I believe HTC.
And of course it contains the Android,
I guess we'll call it operating system.
I'm not sure if it's a layer on top of Linux or if it is a full OS,
it doesn't matter.
You know, and apparently it's all open.
So you can write applications and change stuff.
And it's the whole idea of this is an open source phone
that you can then customize and make better or run as you want to run it,
which is what the whole Linux vibe is about.
And that is very much Google strategy with all of their tools
and all of their services.
So let me start first by saying I'm not a big fan of a phone
that doesn't have at least some exposed keys on the front.
I really love the E71 for that very reason
that the keys are right there and no flipping anything open.
You don't have to turn it sideways, slide something out.
It's just there.
And they're manageable.
You can actually, they're usable.
So to access the keypad on the G1, you have to flip it open,
which, interestingly enough, is done in a kind of a sexy way.
It's almost like, where's the, where they call them,
the hip tops or all the kids are using them.
I can't remember the name of the device.
But you, you kind of flip it open and then you turn it 90 degrees
and then you had this.
So the screen also flips 90 degrees beautiful screen.
Touch, but you can also, there's a little track ball
that you have as a mouse.
The browser is quite nice.
Of course, it, it never does, you know, all the stuff
the traditional browser does like flash videos as an example
or any type of flash functionality.
Keyboard, not bad.
But it's really, it's almost unimportant
as to what is happening and what this device is all about.
Just a couple more hard work bits.
Three megapixel camera is nice.
It's got built in Bluetooth, although I,
but don't think it's for transferring a files
only for a headset or other external audio device
has Wi-Fi built into it.
It switches seamlessly back and forth between
3G network and Wi-Fi.
If it finds an access point that is defined.
So very much, a lot of the, the iPhone experience
in a way, also, the screen size and the feel of the unit,
although it feels really robust, it feels like
a good drop this and, you know, it wouldn't hurt it.
It actually feels like a good drive over it
and it wouldn't hurt it.
The screen is not multi-touch.
So that's kind of a bummer, you know,
I'm immediately going, oh, I want to, you know,
want to zoom in on that.
It had, it's zoom functions work very differently
from the iPhone.
It's just, it's a whole different concept, really.
But the luminance of the screen and what you can read
is beautiful.
But what really got me is you start this thing up for the first time
and it says, okay, do you have a Google account
or do you want to use your existing one?
And you use your existing, yeah,
so you, you enter your Google account information
or presumably you set up a new account
and it immediately starts to come alive.
And I really like this because I use a lot of Google products.
I use, well, I actually use Google apps,
but now for predominantly the mail,
I use Google Calendar.
I do not use Google address book,
which is, of course, one of the flaws.
You know, how do I get my stuff into the address book?
I would have to go suck it out somehow and suck it
into my Google account.
But really the phone comes alive.
The services become activated with all your info.
And it integrates some of your multimedia.
You know, that is what really, really struck me is,
these guys now have an operating system
that goes along with their software services.
And that integration is on par with what Apple
has always been thinking about,
but Apple really started from the reverse
and said, okay, here's these devices.
Now we're going to kind of all sync it together
with mobile me and I think it's pretty well
know that mobile me didn't turn out quite the way
they expected it to.
And it hasn't really lived up to the performance.
I think that a lot of other cloud-like services have.
But Google so many people use it already
that it makes sense.
Now granted this still, I mean,
this is still very much an engineering release
is what I'd call this.
You know, everything works and everything fits together
but they're missing a lot of the little bits of finesse
like how, for instance, do I send a web page to someone?
Can I, it seems hard to copy
the link of a page that I'm on and put that somewhere?
They haven't quite integrated the Google Notebook.
Docs is not fully integrated,
but they're getting there.
And I think that this is much less about
it being a phone where it kind of fails
on battery life alone like three hours
and the thing is empty.
So that's no good.
It's much more about this is what Google's plan
and strategy is for all devices.
So this would, I can see this work perfectly well on net books.
I can see it working perfectly well on PDAs.
And the cell phone is just, it's just kind of a way to,
you know, to get their foot in the door.
I would not advise anyone who's used
to some pretty normal common functionality
of a regular mobile phone.
Like what I get on my Nokia,
I wouldn't advise anyone to buy this
if that's what you're looking for because you're just not going to get it.
Besides excellent email,
if you're using Gmail and there is an email client
to add other email accounts as well.
But if you're using Gmail,
I mean, right down to the key shortcut commands,
it's fabulous.
Just phenomenal.
Being able to customize your desktop,
let's see.
Of course, adding applications,
there's a marketplace where pretty much,
you know, anyone can build something
and get onto your store.
The scrolling is nice.
I'm doing it right now.
You know, clicking on little stars to star and email.
It all that makes sense.
And, you know, it's, it works.
The whole, it truly is the Google phone.
I mean, it's really,
it's Googleized,
and then Googleized experience
writing your hand.
Maps with the GPS, you know,
phenomenal.
I haven't tried the instructions
in the turn by turns,
but I'm sure that's fine.
I mean, I'm actually using Google Maps
on my Nokia GPS now,
even for directions,
because it's much easier to find stuff.
You can just say, oh, you know,
like nearest, you know, nearest airport
or maybe a particular store
in a particular neighborhood
and Google Maps finds that
much better than any other software.
But, you know, of course,
it's lacking.
There's, I haven't seen a VoIP client for it yet.
I mean, there's all kinds of stuff
that still has to come online.
But it really, truly,
is about the integration of the Google services,
which so many people use already,
far and wide,
and an operating system,
which I believe will export to many devices.
And they'll get it right.
They will get it right.
And I can easily see a whole new generation
of computer users using this,
this combination of operating system and service.
And if anyone can do that,
it is clearly Google.
And their mission is so clear.
You know, just use the services.
They'll figure out where to put the ads
and where to market,
and where to make money from you.
I mean, I'm now using Google checkout.
It uses, you know,
data from my, from my Google account.
You know,
and you don't have to enter all this information.
And yeah, you know,
it means I trust Google a lot.
And I guess doesn't matter
because, you know,
once your data is online,
it's online.
And if anyone wants to get to it,
they'll just tap in it.
And there's not much you can do.
But as it goes,
these guys are doing a pretty damn good job.
And I think their,
their record is a little bit better than the government owning my data.
And,
yeah,
I mean,
I'm trying to think how to wrap this up.
I really would say,
as a geek gadget to,
really hold in your hands the future,
what Google is going to bring you.
Excellent choice.
And it's probably cheap enough to go out and buy that.
I don't know if it's actually similar and locked or not.
It may be tied into a team mobile.
I have to,
I do have another,
a SIM card.
I'll see if that actually makes a difference or not.
If you can use it.
But as a phone,
you'll get very frustrated because it's just not there.
Battery life alone forget about it.
Now,
I do appreciate that it uses standard USB connectors.
So,
on the one hand,
I appreciate it.
So if you want to charge it,
you use a standard USB connector that's adapter that comes with it.
You can also just plug that into your computer.
So you don't need to slip another adapter along with you.
Love that.
Unfortunately,
the same USB connector is used for the headphones,
which is a Collane Capital L.
You know,
how about a standard jack-out?
That would be nice.
For those of you,
like most of you probably,
you might have multiple Gmail accounts.
Forget about it.
You can only have one.
And that's a bummer for me because I have my email on Google apps.
And I'm using a different account from my calendar,
which multiple people have access to.
And so I can't just say,
oh, well, why don't you use this,
this calendar account from,
or use this data from my calendar from this account,
and use email from a different account.
So that's,
that's a massive bummer.
Again,
I wouldn't even know how to get my contacts in.
My contacts sink beautifully
between my address book on the Mac and my,
and my Nokia,
that's all fine.
And this is basically my email contact.
So, you know,
how do I merge that?
I mean,
it doesn't seem to be any path to get there.
That's a, that's a pain.
And of course,
I'm not a big fan of,
of on on screen key watch.
Yeah,
I don't know.
Maybe this ain't too bad.
I'm looking at the dialing pad right now.
And this screen works well enough.
Works a hell of a lot better than the on screen
on the Windows mobile.
I'll tell you that.
Man, that was really bad.
Let me see,
just erase those numbers there.
So,
yeah,
you know,
I'm working with a couple different apps
that I've loaded,
which is pretty much the most interesting thing.
And these are not necessarily web services,
or the Twitter,
Twitter,
which is a Twitter client.
That's basically an app that does a web service.
But there's an interesting GPS tracking device,
which, of course,
integrates beautifully with Google Maps,
but you know,
I'm always looking to track my flights.
And I'd like to look at that on Google Maps or Google Earth.
And so, you know,
people have already gotten into that and done that kind of stuff.
And, you know,
it looks like it's going to be a very interesting,
a very, very interesting platform.
We'll see what develops.
But let's wait for G2.
I guess that would be the final message.
Until there's G2,
you definitely have no business using the G1,
because it'll just frustrate you.
It's 75 bucks to play around with.
I just want to be okay.
Be okay.
I just want to feel the day.
Feel the day.
I just want to feel something.
I just want to feel the day.
Feel the day.
I just want to feel something.
I just wanna be okay, be okay, be okay, I just wanna be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, I just wanna be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, I just wanna be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be
okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, be okay, not on the kinda,
Our new album called BOK, which contains live recordings,
B-Sides covers, and it's now available on iTunes as well.
And a portion of the proceeds from the sale on iTunes
will go to support stand-up to cancer
and intimate online community for those
who are touched by cancer, stand-up to number two,
stand-up to cancer.org.
Thank you Neil Beer's chuckle head, massive chuckle head,
actually, for sending that in.
All right, I don't know how it happened,
but I've gone, this seems like the longer show
we've ever done all of a sudden.
It's the new call me, which doesn't get me
through the top expast enough.
Anyway, tomorrow I'll be back with a football Friday
edition, get your songs in,
load them up onto the drop.io slash daily source code
because I do need some help in putting
the kick-ass show.
And we'll just go rocking and merrily into the weekend.
I hope you'll join me for that until then,
be respectful, mindful, and very happy
and careful what you do with your freedom
and live your life with passion.
Another fine, medial presentation, stick it in your ear.