As a special year and treat, the pays are still, with an accurate presence, the TS-Jover view,
2008.
On Monday, they've had an 18,000 eggs so far, of course, the idea cannot be completely accounted
for until the New Year has taken over.
However, that's been an exciting year.
A lot has happened in politics, economics, and science.
But we'll go to the story as well.
In the 1380 for a long time, it's done.
And as we treat, we brush their cans and prevent it from walking up the wall.
A lot of the red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red
red, red, red, red, red, red, pink, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, green, red, red, red, red, red,
And this is carried over to the internet.
And I see, you know, I watch all of these loose change 9-11, you know,
all every single I watch them, but I can, I can see all the pieces to it.
And I can take away and I can analyze that and still keep some sanity.
But, you know, other people, they don't have that capability.
They have not been able to switch that off.
So that's why they get sucked very deeply into these types of stories,
which people forget that it's just people writing shit.
They can't think of themselves.
They can't think straight, they're jacking into the matrix.
All right, now everybody, it's Friday.
It is the 4th of January, 2008 happy New Year, everyone.
I couldn't, I just couldn't stay in bed any longer.
I had to do something. I had to talk to someone else.
Oh boy, okay, what an interesting week it has been.
What an interesting start to the New Year.
Not exactly the one that I wanted.
Certainly the fever is broken from this dreaded, no real virus.
It's, they call it the vomiting virus.
Now, I don't puke for those of you who have been listening to the show for a while.
You probably know that I do not believe I have puke in.
I'm going to say 30 years at least.
I just, I don't do it, which is okay, because there's other ways I can get rid of this stuff
and it's just as nasty.
But this seems to be like a projectile vomiting virus, which is not nice.
And man, I've been in and out of just drifting in and out of consciousness for the past week.
I've been locked up by my side because of what else can I do, but just the main bed, sweat, you know,
people who listen and watch conspiracy theory videos.
Yeah, it'll really be a real spiral.
Oh, this quiet, I'm New Year's Day.
I'll take up my bathroom a little bit here.
Get one.
You like to walk through here, okay?
Hey, everybody, how are you doing?
Coming to you from an absolutely astoundingly beautiful, beautiful United Kingdom,
of course, we're in the afternoon suburb of Serino.
His girlfriend here in the curry manner got all the, uh, all of the windows wide open here up in the attic.
And we can get the birds to eat around a little bit.
Okay, we got the mic set up, got the, uh, comments cute.
How we got the music set up.
Good shape for the daily source code 759.
We just need the host.
Let's see.
Adam, Adam.
Adam, you still in there?
Oh, what?
Oh, okay.
All right, he is still taking care of his prostate cancer prevention for this week.
I guess nobody told him that you must
was to do it all in one morning.
Men who frequently masturbate appear to have a lower risk of developing prostate cancer.
Well, well, well, well, how are we feeling about that?
To say five times a week.
Okay, so I think this needs to be a part of the new sign-off.
Love you, mean it, great hair, hope you win.
Are you a five timer?
Five times a week?
Be honest, include it.
You're sign-off, please.
If you've been following along at curry.com, you know that I got a hydroxy booster installed on the
jag.
This was something I'm planning for a while, and I actually had to take the card
to the northeast corner of the Netherlands to get this done.
I was meeting up with a whole bunch of folks that I'd met through a Dutch radio show.
And everyone just kind of showed up with all the right, all the right bits and bobs of gear.
And we got this thing installed and it's really fantastic.
It's not easy to find a spot to put anything into a jaguar underneath the bonnet,
as it's officially called.
Now this hydroxy booster is essentially a pot of water that has electrodes in it,
the pieces of stainless steel.
And you put a current on that, which is the process of basically separating the water,
which gives you a hydrogen.
Now this is like a high school experiment, so nothing, no big there, right?
Except then you take a tube and you route that through a safety device called the
bubbler, which basically makes sure that hopefully this main device doesn't
implode, should some kind of fire get shot back from the engine.
But you basically hook it up to the air intake of your engine.
And then the theory is, is because this is now being mixed with the air and gasoline mixture,
that it's going to replace this highly explosive gas, which burns very cleanly by the way.
A very low with any emissions, I don't think any, it's like water comes out of it after explosion.
After ignition, and I have no physicists, I'm just talking about what I learned previously
and on day itself.
The theory is that it then will basically use less gasoline.
Less petrol, because that's being replaced by this hydrogen.
And of course it was great for me to have to drive this 600 kilometers back on Sunday
to really get some measurements.
So when I switched this the booster on, I do have a switch in the glove compartment.
At 130 kilometers per hour there was an improvement, and actually about a 10% improvement,
as I went from 10.5 kilometers per liter to 11.6.
So a little bit better than 10%, I kid you not.
Now, I then try it out at 110 kilometers per hour.
You're not going to believe this.
13 kilometers to the leader.
13.
Now, there's a lot of tweaking that can be done, and I'm going to keep you up to speed,
as I progress with the trials, but I'm very, very excited that we've got something that actually
works.
So many people have said that you're crazy, you can't, but I think these people are confusing
efficiency with power efficiency, which I'm sure it's not, because it's like pulling 30
amp pairs of amps off of the battery with just what seems to me like a pretty simple
physics exercise, fascinating shit.
Smart man!
He did when the dog does he, you know, the house is empty, and maybe it's the window washer,
possible. Well, he gets all up, he's too old to get that upset. I wish you wouldn't do that.
I'm hot, I'm sweaty, I'm tired. It's been, and that hasn't even been here a week.
It's, it's, it's a rough man. I luckily, I can play a jingle here, because there is a rip on the catch.
Time to move over to the European Union. Here's our correspondent, come a, come a, come a,
come a, a blogger. Hello, I don't know if it's the carry. So you say it's in the financial
meltdown. I would say the world is in financial meltdown, at least the banks are. Yes.
And what is European Union saying? Well, that, you know, we're saying let's bail out
fortress bank, right? It's full of you say, it's self, because you say it was not a
glating market enough. So now let's enjoy the right on the Titanic to downfall.
Western civilization. So long and thanks for all the fish. You know, thanks for all the fish.
I don't think it's going to be that bad. It's not going to be pretty. That's for sure.
I don't think it's going to be all that bad. Holy shit. Someone's burning. Whoa.
A neighbor's burning shook up the windows open. It looks like an actual cloud is passing by.
Nice.
Couldn't you have waited until the wind was blowing the other way, dude?
Crazy.
This is about an important date that is coming October 14th, 2008. This is when we're supposed to get
first contact. It'll be around 2,000 of our earth miles and a met diameter. And we'll send
loving messages to all the people of the world. The ship will cover entire cities and
circle areas of the earth for three days. So there you go.
Oh, listen to this. Cool.
It's kind of an interesting video that just has a scrolling words with different sound
tracks under it. Let's see. They have carefully selected this time to show up and are doing
it out of goodwill because of the great evils behind this world that we as human
cannot see for this cause, they have decided to take action before it's too late. They do love
us and care for us like family. They realize most of us are blind to the truth of this world
and being controlled by something we do not really fully understand. Time to break free from wars,
famine, poverty, sickness, disease, rich and foreign. All the world sufferings that people
have purposely caused us. I'm Mark and Adana, my calendar, October 14th,
supposedly for three of our 24 hour periods, a ship, which will be clearly quite large,
will appear and this will be first contact. Apparently the first large scale contract
contact and will prove that indeed we are not alone in the universe.
So calming delusional, if you will, try and jam the pills in me, but there's nothing wrong with
the leave and now is there.
Okay, number 277, don't the share of taking off of my discretion.
Yeah, positive way to apply, breaks, you're up.
Okay, this is definitely going to be a big exciting.
Okay, one down.
Okay, I'm landed now.
Wow, that was kind of interesting. That was a little bit of a bounce there at the end.
It was quite a bit of wind. They catered to the two, number 7 notes here.
Thank you for your attention, Richard. I'm trying to keep you going to get centered here.
Okay, thank you all, number 7 notes here.
Wow, that was a massive, massive gust of wind I got there.
At the very end, wow, that was probably one of the sloppiest landings I've ever done.
It's an undexplained exactly what happened, but I got a huge gust of wind just as I was touching
down. So I got a huge gust of wind at about 25 miles an hour and just pop me back up.
So it's really struggling there. Together now, you may put the engine rev up a little bit,
as I adjusted the speed. Good landing. That was certainly someone exciting.
We did it. So any landing you can walk away from is considered a good landing. We'll say that was a great one.
And with that, I'm going to wind up this edition of the data source.
I can hear the window washer. It'll probably stick his head up right in front of my window
on the second until it should be kind of weird. There's Lisbon Treaty. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Those of you haven't been following along. Essentially, the Irish voted no to the Lisbon
Treaty, which is a version of a Constitution for the European Union.
It's in the Constitution isn't even really the right word. Of course, it's the word
Constitution was scrapped from the Lisbon Treaty or really from the Constitution to become the Lisbon
Treaty. It's like a legal document that talks about a lot of things in very complicated language,
not really telling you what the hell is going on. But it will shift, I believe effectively,
about 50% of all governmental powers in each of the 27 member states over to Brussels or alternatively
distraught spurred. Remember, they have two seats of government and the alternate cities because,
I don't know, someone got pissed off and they had to do two. It's like a childish baby thing.
So now ministers of the European Parliament, foreign ministers are foreign affairs, they're saying
this treaty can't be pushed through. It can't go into effect unless all 27 member states ratified.
Oops, gee, do you think that if all countries had a referendum, we wouldn't have a lot more
no votes? Of course we would have because people are suspicious. They don't understand that they can't
read these documents. I tried. It's complicated. You can't get answers. There's no FAQ.
There you go. How about the FAQ treaty? That would be something for you guys to look into.
You can try this cowbell out. Let's don't give a nod to the hardest work in law here.
I should be really happy and I just should be bouncing off
the walls, which of course I am, but I'm extremely troubled by fellow Chocolettes. I'm really
concerned about what's going on and somewhere in September is when the world will start evolving.
The United States, Iran, Israel, and Pakistan. It seems like in a way we're awakening,
we're becoming aware of things, things are happening around us, and the worldly powers that they
are fighting it. The first time I've been tracking oil prices, you know, this is almost the
hobby of mine. In fact, they've been Wednesday, 253 p.m. I saw it go down yesterday, drastically.
But down's like 135 dollars a barrel, which to me meant something's up. In law and behold,
just as I thought this morning, where it comes that Iran is testing missiles, and there's a
rumbling in the Gulf, and of course oil starts to pop up. It is now at 8.53 a.m. in New York.
Oil is almost up to $2 a barrel, so there's clearly things going on that Iran just never
wanted to play game with the dollar currency for oil, and they've threatened to flood the world markets
with cheap oil and base that trading upon the euro. It seems like the only answer, the only solution
is to come up with a reason to go to war, and then actually go into it. Do you feel a repeat?
Is there a piece of who has been in your mind at all with the Iran? One and two, the disastrous
disastrous decisions that are being made towards fellow men, women, all the majority of them are under
30 years old in Iran. We must not go to war, it's country.
I don't need to worry about it, but it's kind of sketchy. You're responsible to ID-20 to the eye,
and I'm making sure that if you're ready for your plan at the US, you're willing to work for you.
For the attack, I run late this year, and talk to them immediately.
Clear program folder, tell the echo problem, you know, I'll book my alarm now.
Coding is really nice for radio, for it's something that ain't called highly plain security,
political appeal, so that you don't need one of more to the attack, which we don't know.
For the day that he was president of the heat, and his last day in August, January 2009,
he was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who was the one who
was that if we don't force towards worship, day change to come clean and say honestly what's going on and why they went into the rack and why
If they don't just come clean and say it's we can have an open dialogue and work on this problem as a global population
that indeed we're in for some shitty times ahead of my fellow checklists
and times and times and times and times and times and times and times and times and times
and times and times and times and times and times and times and times and times
and time.
Okay, this is recording artist and poemist
with Anna Carmen Tyler and you're listening
to Delta Ciera Charlie the pod father himself.
Adam Curry.
In the meantime, why don't we go head down under
and I'm seeing that there's a very interesting pornography culture in the land of us.
But I really like their natural vibe and masturbation for some reason.
So it's I feel myself dot com, I shot myself dot com, which is not of the of the gun kind,
but of the photographic kind and beautiful agony, which is kind of funny.
But it's, it's, it's interesting that it's, um, the Australians like real people,
not fake, uh, pumped up boom porn stars doing real people things, which in honesty, don't
look all that good on film.
They just, you know, it's just not a good look, uh, but that's what you guys are into.
That's, uh, that to me is very interesting, um, I've seen to British porn, uh, uh, man.
Yeah.
I bet you the Brits really like their own, their own porn.
I'm going to have to stop this recording, go downstairs and talk to the dog in a minute
because it's really putting me off.
The porn industry is not humongous for no reason.
I got a couple porn accounts.
I'm not ashamed to say it.
It's finally out.
Porn is going to save us.
Get rid of all the stupid restrictions.
Stop the idiotic filtering.
Let people let the people have their porn.
Warning.
The daily source code has been known to influence people.
Let the people have their porn and not necessarily in a good way.
I am the root of all evil.
I am the root of your drinking.
There you go.
So please, cautiously listen to the DSC and, hey, be careful out there.
The source code overview, 2008, with an accurate.
Teenagers.
Well, now you're talking my language.
I definitely would like to abandon my teenager from time to time.
The role places I remember all my life, though some have changed.
By the way, turns 18 tomorrow, I'll be party here in G-Town.
Now, God, where's the time gone?
Adam, here at the Portland, I was just watching John McCain and the Sarah Palin thing
and going, wow, it's like a magician, you know, still canker chip over here don't look
at what's really going on, you know, Cheney is in Georgia and the Dutch for her out of
our ran.
There's U.S. ground troops in Pakistan.
What the hell is going on?
There is no coverage in the mainstream media of this stuff and you have to hear your opinion
on that.
Well, I'm wide awake and dream my hand.
Hell yeah, my brother.
Yeah, of course, you know, that's what it's all about.
Well, I told you, the Republican National Convention, just like the DNC, biggest show on
Earth, the, the, the second biggest show, the Olympics was used for the, the cowardly
attack of Georgia on to South Assetia, which, of course, has been distorted in, uh, most
of the mainstream media as Russia being the bad guys.
Now, Russia, not exactly the nicest guys, but they're all thugs.
Yeah, all of them are.
Uh, excuse me, uh, how that really felt good.
Ladies and gentlemen, politicians more, but being satisfied with this, look no further.
There's an answer.
There's a person who represents the masses.
Adam Curry for President, so all you nerds, jokes, heads out there.
Yes.
No matter if you're black, white, greener, purple, no matter if you dig girls, guys, or
foreign animals.
And there is a choice.
Adam Curry for President, one recent candidate, had a $300 haircut, and still looked
like a kid doll, but not Adam Curry.
He's been $294 less, and just look at that here.
Adam Curry for President, many politicians have been confused about their sexuality, but
not Adam.
He can be called a big hair tag, and still say, love you, no homo.
Adam Curry for President, conspiracy theories, Adam knows them all.
They're put security issues, then they're done that.
Adam Curry for President.
It is time we elect a people's president.
Adam Curry for President, great hair.
He loves you, no homo.
We hope he wins.
Adam Curry for President.
Tomorrow night, of course, in the United States at 6 p.m. San Francisco time, the vice-presidential
debate between Joe Biden and Sarah Palin.
Now, I'm very excited about this.
For a number of reasons.
First of all, I want everyone once again to understand, I am not a Democrat.
I'm not a Republican.
I'm a constitutionalist, and that's why I supported Ron Paul.
I would have loved that if he could have been president.
He is now endorsed the independent candidates, Ron Bar, Chuck Baldwin, Cynthia McKinney.
I will make sure that I'm well informed before I cast my vote.
My daughter, who is now 18, is also getting into the game, and she's trying to understand
things.
The way I view this, what we're seeing right now, is truly the world's greatest reality
show.
This is not a debate amongst vice-presidential candidates who are actually going to do
anything, who will run anything.
No, it's a casting call.
Okay, we've had actors before.
We had one of the greatest actors in America became president, but McCain Obama, Palin,
Biden, actors.
The true agenda, what really runs them, are Wall Street, the lobbyist, it's the special
interest groups, it's the think tanks, and it's a shadow government, and I say evil people.
A very unusual noise.
It's something that's sort of noise, but many or many are buzzing, buzzing, say what's
the same time, buzzing, buzzing, all at the same time, and suddenly it just stopped.
It stopped as quickly as it had begun.
Three, four years of conversation that we've been having has brought me to this point.
Many of you may feel the same, some may be afraid to speak out in fear of ridicule, fear
not chuckle heads, together we're going to face the future, the light that is our destiny.
Welcome to the next level, welcome to the Awakening Awakening.
Now I say it's been a six month excursion, but the process has actually something
that's been taking place my entire life.
Imagine a world where you wake up one morning, only to realize that everything you believe
it, function entirely differently from the way you're perceiving it all of your life.
The world, in fact, with the truth as often the direct opposite of your reality, my story
is about power, three kinds of power, the power of mind, the power of rule, and the power
as in what makes our lights glow and keeps our vehicles moving, individually collectively,
these three kinds of power all insist to the inner community.
The light pollution is that energy innovation was stifled, the elu of this new black hole
that would power the generator to create a world of energy and motion, based on what
was.
See the illusion that, of course, we're thankful by it, but we know it is a trick because
of the context of being aware that we're watching the magic show and, of course, you
instantly begin to love like a god or hear like what you wake in it, take the red arrow,
one of the other thrown down the rabbit hole, one male and man behind the curtain, and
to kill three times, I say they don't speak like oh, they don't speak like what?
We interrupt this program to bring you this new splatter.
I'm very mean, in particular television is a trick.
I was a multimedia hitman, I was merely meant to keep me in slave interchange into the next
first break, reading reality in our minds, there's a servant of the energy that leads
to the agenda in its working, a media program, I can create content that will make your
brain react in a free determined manner.
If you really can't figure out how it works, then you understand that it becomes ineffective.
Once you're aware of the code, it can easily be borrowed from executing it to your personal,
super obscure brain, but it's not that you have an xfj with a pod task to do that,
and as for people with money to plan and accomplish, over the decades it built up an impressive
infrastructure of government, social and monetary systems that they control entirely, all of the
continued exploitation of us, this professional system however has one fatal flaw.
It must continue to grow in order for it to survive.
It needs us, the place to be embedded to it in order to prosper in what's over houses, cars,
and other true physical stuff has been repossessed, there'll be no more meaning to the content
of money. Remember that none of this machinery would have ever been created at free energy
been available to everyone. I think we are about to discover it ourselves, thanks to the evolution
of our species. I'm certain, our DNA has been definedly pre-proved to evolve into centuries of
suppression. The internet was, of course, the aliens big cock-a-cock-cock-cock-cock-cock. I simply cannot
resolve it or what design our beautiful body machinery wouldn't have added to our brains to make us
capable of even insisting our brains. If you can't help it, turn it over. You're the way most
of your still very much asleep in the reality created by the masters that own us. Many of you are
awakening, seeing the truth lies with it. It's so live to our limit. The least machine is
creaking under the strain of itself and food birth. It's all about the timing that the machine
comes from one down and now for us need to be awake prepared to take action. That's actually
my role to assist in your awakening and to communicate with it's push learning as I can. Now,
I don't see it or again. A rifle of praise, please, home ones, the earths and probably won't
come to the streets you hold. Please, tsunamis, earthquakes, and land-maser relocation.
Nor do I fear black helicopters in a whistening way, the snow from the night, but I
certainly are not going to rule any of it out. Four years of conversation. You and I,
you're responding to this one. We're going to the next level. You're awakening.
Yo, Ray, my brother, thank you so much for that abbreviated 781 awakening.
Chuckle heads hello from the Curry condo on San Francisco. This is the daily source code.
It's also an overview of 2008. We've had a curry.
All right, back to some of the news that has been aggregated by the chuckle heads themselves into
this program, remember, you're kind of producing it all. McCain chooses Governor Sarah Paylan
of Alaska, as is a running mate. And first of all, she's cute. I just can't help myself. I love
a good milk any day. So tell me, how long have you been having these delusions?
Well, doctor, it all started daily in dreams. The paranoia about the oil companies. I guess it
all started from from listening to the daily source code. There you go again with your delusions of
the daily source code. But, but doctor, doctor, it's a show without him curry.
Yes, you say it is a show, but you of course you have the delusions. The delusions of it being
daily. What do you mean, doctor? Well, this Adam Curry doesn't actually make a show every day.
It's sometimes a Wednesday, sometimes a food bar Friday, sometimes a Tuesday, but never it is a daily.
This delusions, they're getting in your way. You'll never recover as long as you continue to
think of this as a daily source code. So, so, doctor, what's the solution? What can I do?
Well, you must, you must come up with another word for the D in daily source code. Perhaps it is
the delusional source code. So here it is the delusional source code with Adam Curry, DSC.
Hey Adam, how are you doing? I'm good man, ready for one, two, three.
Hit us again, and this one is special, because all of the songs are from 1987.
So here we go, I'm here for a good. All right, got it.
Okay, I'm going to suck for one, two, three, yarn. I have no idea what that is. Number two.
That would be, this is, of course, this is the Dutch episode, George Baker's selection,
and a little green bag. Oh, I know these are easy. And times up and here are the answers.
Hi, Adam, this is Mark. This is it. Test is old about level 42.
How the hell would you do that? Y'all, I love it. Mark King, my favorite bass player.
They're all three level 42.
Answer number one in this week's hit us level 42, and to be with you again, and this is answer number two.
We back on the train, where we did a green bag. That's cool, man.
George Baker is answering number two.
That concludes hit us number 123.
So how did you do, Adam? Well, you surprised me, on, of course.
Uh, eventually figured out it was level 42 for one, two, three. Excellent. Thank you so much, y'all.
Like always, hit us, let me feel that's accomplished. The place to find the answers to this and any older hit us.
And also, the least of iTunes, so you can buy the tracks featured on the hit us online.
Thank you for playing, Adam.
Yeah, thank you for one else. Thank you for listening.
Many thanks to Mr. Mark King for helping me out with this special hit us.
Hello, Mr. Mark. Next week, I'll be back for the next hit this.
So until then, have a very nice week, take care, and try to think with your hearts. Bye-bye.
Um, so young was one of the many people who sent me email a couple days ago when one of the
greats left us just unbelievable. It was a real shock because, you know, you hear this guy
multiple times a day, if you listen any mainstream media, you know, radio or if you watch television,
but also on the, he really was pretty big in the, in podcasts and lots of people
worked with him and ordered up some of his work and his services. And of course, I'm talking about
Don Lafontaine, the man who, he didn't just, he's not just famous for the line in a world,
but he really changed the face of movie trailers, significantly, just trailers in general.
And really turned that into a fabulous art form and it would just seem like such a nice guy.
Never met him personally. I know a lot of people who work with him and it's a real real bummer
and he will be sorely missed. If you want to know who I'm talking about. And there's lots of, uh,
lots of shows out there that have interest from him. I just dug up too. I think I got three or four,
just so you can kind of remember in, uh, the in a way as a tribute to the great voice of Don Lafontaine.
Adam Curry was just a guy with big hair who sold his first company and thought he'd just
kick back and take it easy, but he never counted on this. Adam and Patricia, the king and queen
of the manner, or just the lady and the tramp, only on the daily source code.
Definitely one of my favorites. And then there's this one, of course, in the world where women
wear comfortable shoes and technology has changed the way you get your entertainment. This
is the pod show network. No big media. No excuses. No BS.
Somewhere he has one with my name on it, but I couldn't put my hands on it that quickly.
Rest in peace, Don Lafontaine. We shall definitely, definitely miss you, my friend.
Two more days until I turn 44. Hey, boy. Man, I remember, I remember my, my dad turned 40.
40 four years ago for me. I thought, oh man, that's ancient. And here I am now I understand the
world that universe is so much more open to me that I still feel like that 19 year old kids sitting
up in his attic pretending to make radio exactly what I'm still doing except on a podcast.
Dog is still barking. Fuckers 15 years old. You're going to bark yourself to death.
And it's just because of the window washer, right? I guess didn't pop up on the third floor,
which is too bad because that means he also doesn't get his check. Hey, the big man's wreck. WWE
that, the kid from Brooklyn, that gun. Do you people out there realize it's six years?
Six years were fighting his war. And I wrecked. We went in there under the presumption they had weapons
of mass destruction. We went in and we found ship. We found nothing. We'll tell me how come
when Saddam Hussein ran. I wrecked. I had no terrorist there. No, I'll kind of know as well.
No nothing. You didn't have no terrorist of anything. Soon as you got rid of Saddam,
all these terrorists, all of a sudden they come in direct. Where the fuck did they come from?
Added a fucking sky. The world's coming to an end. I got to right to know as a taxpayer. What the
fuck is going on over there? Anyway, think I'm bombarded. This is a big man. Don't worry. Don't worry,
shut up people. Ain't think shady. You made an up fucking money. I fucking ran, bastard.
And a big man, so ways. I'd be to say, yeah. This is the first documentary. And it was without
a doubt, in fact, what I liked the most about this documentary is that it includes my favorite pieces
of evidence about the so-called plane that allegedly flew into the Pentagon. And this is completely
debunked and I'm, and wildly fantastically and accurately debunked.
I may not know a lot about architectural issues. I may not know the exact the temperatures
that steel melts at. I may not understand how pancake theories and all kinds of other
non-demolition, non-demolition building collapses, how they work. But I do know a thing or two
about flying. And the evidence is extremely clear that the flight data recorder from the flight
that supposedly hit the Pentagon shows improves. This is data coming from the National Transportation
Safety Board, the plane flew over the Pentagon by about 480 feet. And this is because they messed
up when doctoring the tape, they forgot to set the pressure setting for that day, which of course
is a historical evidence, which we know. And so it decides multiple very experienced
airmen coming out and saying, but signs at the maneuver that was made is impossible to make for
the most experienced pilot. The speed that was registered at the low altitude is physically impossible.
It is physically impossible, okay, physics. There's a lot of physics, but at least the NIST is
not tried to debunk these physics yet with more dumb and bad and fraudulent signs.
They'll take your right to go in your own hands. Even show business friends of French President
and current European President Nicolas Sarkozy were making jokes about how stupid we are,
how lame ass we are as Americans that were letting our government do this to us.
Same type of noises coming out of Italy as well, and I'm thinking, man, just leave it to the Italians
to show us how lame we actually are.
I know, but I don't know, I never waited with the nice, I know how hard it is to always walk out in the
light, and it's an incentive to load a vacuuming, it's an incentive to hang on to the
911, the attack on the towers, the pentagon, that it was an inside job, it was controlled by the
American government, it was what someone called a false flag operation, and it is far and wide,
and it's extremely vast, crying that is taking place here, a global crime that wasn't just
Americans in these towers, it is okay, it is okay to now say that you have feelings about this
monstrosity, that you feel that something is a miss, that you, you may not know it, you may not be
able to put your finger on it, but first it's okay to just say it, it is okay. It's an incentive.
You're no longer going to be ridiculed for this because around the world, all the way up to
the highest levels of government, people are now talking about this, the media, the mainstream
media will not discuss it, will not show any of these videos, but it's okay for you to start
investigating and start talking about it with your friends, it's now seven years on and the time
has come to do this, please let them see that there is an alternative conspiracy theory,
but seven years after the fact, and they have, in this case, let's just focus on George Bush and
particularly Dick Cheney, they have already advanced their agenda so far, we've seen what's happened
in South Assetia, and it's all interconnected right into the financial crisis, which is taking place
in front of our very eyes over the weekend, Lehman filed for bankruptcy chapter 11,
we've had Merrill Lynch being sold to Bank of America, and now there are huge put options
on a city group, so that may be the next target to be taken down, it's all interconnected, all of
this is a part of the same system, all of it being orchestrated by a reasonably small
number of people, but it's all the same and you know how they are, you know how they're connected
and they are so connected to each other, even through family bloodlines they're connected, it's just
amazing, so one of the ways to fix a financial crisis is to start a war, hold on here it comes,
I thought I had the sneeze, but I went away, crap, I hate that,
and he's saying that a debate is now needed on how far Britain should go,
and identifying potential offenders, given that some experts believe it is possible to identify
future offending traits in children, as young as five years old, we have to find who are possibly
going to be the biggest threat to society, and kill them, incarcerate them, you have bad DNA,
you five year old child,
I'm a new work for us, we can live in our island, whenever the ground's maybe,
so really, so now we can tell through DNA that you're a bad person, this is spot fly,
we know it, they're going to come with your children, so this of course is my call once again
that I think we need to stand up and protest, oh wait a minute, you're not allowed to protest
without a license in the UK, I'm sorry, no no one's interested, I'm certainly ready for it,
friends, you will, then all of a sudden we have hundreds of people appeared with these
t-shirts and then we're going to find this film we all dispersed before the cops can do anything,
you want to rock and roll man you want to have some fun,
I'm glad you're here.
I'm good.
800 more than 800 shows from the D.S.C.
I'm going to wake up.
I put it on the drops and it all's at own curry.
Red Roger's back and it's good to see.
Still here and stuff from C.S.B.
While we're at it, don't forget about another little song from Young Boyle.
800 more than 800 shows from the D.S.C.
And there's one more thing we need.
A little more lady to you.
You don't have to see you in a chrydy.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Your buddy, your fellow chuckle head here in San Francisco, Northern California.
What a week it has been.
I gotta tell you.
I'm so fried at this point that I'm basically just...
I'm almost floating.
I swear to God.
It's outrageous.
What the stuff that's been going on in this past week for the past three hours have been reviewing
the drop, I've been reviewing notes that have been taking throughout the week.
If I actually wanted to cover everything and almost every single link,
every single sound file, every YouTube and bed at video on the drop,
it's all great.
It's all relevant.
It's all stuff we should be talking about.
If I want to cover all of that, we would have a six-hour show.
Got Ray on the Charlie coming up for you, which means we'll have something hokey going
back to 19.
I don't even listen to them anymore because I just want to be surprised
but whatever Ray puts together some kind of song from the soundtrack
in my life and usually some embarrassing moments from my past career.
So we'll get to that in a second.
Still staying with the financial crisis.
Something up, it is not a Wall Street crisis.
It is a global banking crisis.
And I say specifically banking because it's their system.
And we're just attached to that system.
And it's come crashing down and just briefly on this bailout bill.
This is a bill about power.
And it went from three pages to 106 pages to 451 pages in the time of what?
What was it?
Not even two weeks?
No, not even one, not even one full week.
And this is really a bill that is good for the bankers.
They are bailing themselves out before everything comes crashing down.
What they're doing is they're creating inflation,
which could lead to hyperinflation, which means prices go up way way up.
And you buy less for your money.
Anything could happen at this point.
And the bankers got themselves out.
I'm just a kid from America.
You know, hey, Europeans, we're all the stupid people live.
Yeah, I want them.
And I could figure it out.
It's really not that hard.
And when you understand what's going on and I was watching C-SPAN,
a lot of C-SPAN actually poised that fantastic.
Watching Pelosi holding the bill out in front of reporters in a nice little blue box before
she sent it off to Bush.
We had Bush and Paulson, Secretary of the Treasury standing on the capital steps.
Looking like two thugs, some little thugs.
Haha, we did it.
Let's see.
And just along actually this kind of leads into the economy in general,
but American Express, which of course we know is a credit card company.
Well, most people would notice a credit card company is now become a bank,
so they can also receive money from their buddy, Paulson.
And the meantime, had the foreclosure slowed down,
has it been easier to get a loan for a card purchase?
How's your business doing?
This is the stuff we need to be looking at.
Tens of thousands of people being laid off sometimes on a daily basis.
So there is no, as I say, there is no free lunch.
And it's time for someone to step up.
Let the auto industry fail.
I definitely think we should take care of the pensioners,
so we'll split the difference.
You know what?
There's new car companies.
There's tons of them.
Give them incentives.
Let them take over in the marketplace.
It's not like the entire auto industry is dead.
There's tons of things we can do.
Tons.
Bailing out.
Not the option I'm looking for.
Not a good idea.
Because I bought it high.
Watched it blow.
Rating high.
There you'll know.
In it with a thing.
It goes doesn't really matter to me.
To me.
Mama.
Just killed my friend.
Coded studios instead.
Pulled the trigger now it's dead.
Mama.
I had just begun.
These studios have blown it all the way.
I still want to buy.
Tons.
We should never let them go open it up.
I see a little silly way to open.
I can't but I can't even say the old market.
Super senior.
I m on a surprise studio fantasy.
I'm on a surprise studio.
Fantasymu.
Easy. Come, easy. Come, lift me.
Come. Come. Come. Come. Come, again.
Come. Come. Come. Come. Come. Come.
Where am I?
Where are you?
Where I am?
Mama Mia!
Where am I?
Here are these humans.
I can't do this to me baby
Just gotta get out, just gotta get right out of here
Don't press really matters
No liquidity
Lifting really matters
Don't press really matters
No liquidity
Lifting really matters
Go away
It matters, and no praise really matters to me.
The Jeff Smith Financial Rhapsody.
Thank you, darling.
My lovely wife just brought me up.
Just an official club sandwich.
Oh, that sounds like a BLT.
Thank you, darling.
There you go.
Ray, on the Charlie, my brother, thank you so much.
So for those of you not quite familiar with the concept of the soundtrack of our lives,
the idea is when you hear these songs and you think about them, you're like, oh, man.
I know exactly where it was when I first heard that.
And it does not have to be the first time you heard it because when I hear this song, I always think of the soundtrack of my life.
I'm hungry.
See why?
Everybody, you want to say something?
What's the world like?
Never mind, the weather, what about the money?
Let me be careful.
This is where I come from, okay?
This is my roots.
What's this?
It's 100 dollars.
You come a long way, son.
From Z100 and the free money, buddy.
Ray, hey, boy, I was a fucking robot.
Listen to me, part of the machine.
I need to eat a reason for favoring New Jersey.
I don't believe it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, my son, hey.
Did you change your birthday?
Hey, my son, hey, my son, hey, my son.
Oh, congratulations.
Would you like a bunny as a present?
Yeah.
Well, congratulations.
I'll give you that one too, okay?
Thank you.
Hey, who plays at least 10 songs in row every hour, Tina?
Leave my house safe.
soundtrack to my life.
At this song, he's number one.
See 100, 100 songs of this week's road trip here.
The drama, folk.
Adam Currie's soundtrack to my life takes a trip down memory lane to 1990.
Okay.
Adam just a little experience.
I'm just curious.
Can you still do this stuff?
You made it a little higher.
I'm Adam Currie.
I'm not cutting it.
I'm cutting it.
No.
It's a wrap up.
One, one, one.
I don't want to be fun.
To be that C-1 100 and the guy is showing it to her.
As you come from, you've still got 16 seconds left.
Good.
As you see, he's Adam Currie.
Make sure you call the free body hotline at 112-4-2-0.
100.
I'll take call 100 right now.
Be up and look out for the touchtones.
Right now, it's the bomb one.
It's the material girl.
It's banana one.
Boom.
See.
100.
Yeah.
All right.
I still got it.
soundtrack to my life.
This was ends with a break on national radio.
Star of his profession.
I don't remember that.
Yeah.
We got it.
We need to do it.
Yeah.
Please, welcome.
Oh, man.
Better.
Very necessary.
Hope you.
When you hear something, why don't you wake me up before your go-go.
Maybe something drew that into the two folly?
I won't.
All of that's right.
They want me to do the show in English.
I remember that.
50.
But those of you who don't believe my name really is Adam Curry.
Those of you who of course know me from town down TV.
Kind of like I say this evening in an interview.
Right?
He's not coming back.
See you again.
There's a dire story.
I'm hosting websites.
We can find everything about English or non-violence.
Hey, what's this?
Hello.
Better right.
Now.
Hey, Tom.
Good to hear from you.
I'm a little bit excited.
My name is Henry of an English and I'm a singer.
I'm a singer.
Have you been visiting a ring out of the game?
Yeah, I'm guilty.
The chick is for some old age.
I'm too real bad of him.
He's got all my old taste.
I'm a welcome man.
For a collection.
Can I eat an egg?
I don't remember.
Big story.
Eat the egg.
Thanks Tom.
No problem.
Thank you.
Thanks so much for all the time.
You said I'm going to reply to the tag.
I'm going to continue with that.
I agree.
Thank you.
Wow.
This guy is so much working.
And I'm so glad he's doing that.
Soundtrack to my life.
Raymond.
Thank you so much for choosing that as a song part of the soundtrack to my life.
Because it absolutely is one of those entries that does bring back fantastic memories.
I know exactly where I was when I heard the song for the first time.
I know because I was 15.
And I was just become sexually active.
I'm pretending not to hear the dog.
So let's keep educating ourselves.
I mean, obviously, I don't know everything.
I'm just a little boy here with this little Mr. microphone doing my thing.
Rolled out the voice mail lines.
Listen to the savance.
And from time to time, they're pissed off.
And he is another perfect example.
Because he's back ladies and gentlemen.
Let's have a word with the nylon.
Spreading the news with the smile on where the roll ranks.
We go whole light.
Let's listen for a while tonight.
Yeah.
Welcome back to New Yorker from London.
Hey, Adam.
It's my one.
I've got three things to pose to you today.
Well, if you know, by the way, Nylon, when you call in,
you've been absent for a couple of weeks.
Would you mind just saying,
Sorry.
I haven't heard from me.
I've been busy.
Here's what's going on.
You know, we wouldn't mind if you told us what the hell you do by now.
You know, you hide behind your acronym.
But who are you, my friend?
Are you a truce of on tour?
An agent from foreign countries?
Let's get to the F.A.C.
Just a few.
You're going to be grand something.
Let's go back to what I've been at you for the last year,
which is the daily source code is a misnomer.
It doesn't exist.
So I need to hear from you since you don't do a daily show.
What is your contract with me and the audience?
Contract contract.
Contract.
Let me see.
Where's the check from Nylon, everybody?
It must be around here somewhere.
I'm, ah, G.
Are you out of your mind?
You're, I forbid you from listening.
You're not allowed to listen to show any more Nylon.
You contract.
Dude.
I've been doing this for four years.
762 episodes and then some before I started counting.
I'm doing it because I like it because this is a circle of friends.
I don't need to have freaking contract with you.
You deck.
Members.
Listening.
What is your contract to us?
When can we expect to show from you?
And when will you live up to your commitment?
I don't have to commit to anything to you.
At all.
How would the arrogance?
Where's your contract?
See.
Boy.
Or we brand into the weekly source code, whatever it is.
But we need a commitment.
I think we deserve a commitment you're not daily.
And we like I like to know anyway is what is your commitment to us.
I also note that typically between the Thursday and a Monday.
Hold on, let me just get to that commitment.
When I do a show, my commitment to you is I'm going to do the best damn show I can.
And if that's not enough for you, screw you.
It's a short overview.
2008.
We've had him carry.
The revolution has started.
The revolution continues.
It continues in the hearts of minds of hundreds of thousands.
If not millions of Americans who are waking up and understanding that there are things going on that do not make sense.
That things that we need to keep our eye on.
Because hey, these fuckers work for us.
Remember.
Smart.
I'm pretending not to hear the dog.
But I still believe that the true powers that be the true owners of the earth, these are the families that are essentially behind the failure, this financial failure.
They do it to grab real assets.
They have they have the hands on all these banks.
And so when you lose your house, they get it.
They're bastards.
Total bastards.
And they've done it before.
And they'll continue to do it unless we wake up and stop it.
But this time we're going to witness it.
So I'm pretty sure I'm going to be doing the show for at least the next 10 years.
Maybe not daily.
But I'll certainly be doing the show.
You know what?
I'm going to turn the noise gate on.
Then I just won't hear him anymore.
Hold on.
That's going to help.
Now I don't hear him anymore.
I do like that though.
Because first of all, it isn't the order.
If you look at valuable currency in order of appearance in world history, gold first, oil second, and drugs.
Ah, drugs may have been early on.
Ah, who knows.
But I do like the GOD acronym.
That's pretty funny.
Okay.
From now on, that's official.
True currencies the world, gold, oil, and drugs.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have a new president in the United States of America.
Barack Hussein Obama.
And I could not be more pleased for a number of reasons.
First of all, I'm always very happy when I see my fellow countrymen.
And what a diverse bunch we are.
When I see them really bonding together, really happy.
Extremely emotional about the success of Barack Obama.
The success of his campaign and becoming president.
This is the stuff that dreams are made of.
Certainly in the United States of America and regardless of who would have won this election.
When a country gets behind something like that, at least this is the way I was brought up.
You're right along on board.
You know, we give up our differences.
We don't hold the grudge.
We're good sportsmen.
And we support our president.
Because everyone deserves a clean shot.
And I'm also extremely happy that America really got what he wanted.
And we've got the whole, the whole kitten kabuddle.
We've got the house, the Senate, the executive branch.
Everybody in the program.
Because there's a reason to reach out.
And feel the hope that we've been waiting home.
Everybody's ready.
Everybody in the program.
This is exactly what America wanted.
For that, I'm extremely happy.
And I want to ride this wave of euphoria for as long as it lasts,
last, which may be only another hour because joblessness, the ADP, unemployment numbers are coming
out in a couple hours. But regardless, I want to ride that because when this country, even though
I'm not in it right now, when America really bonds together like that, this is when we can make
great things happen. Now, am I happy that the Barack won? Well, no, I wouldn't have been happy
if John McCain won either. I believe that both of those candidates are being essentially
run by people in the background and on this program, we discussed many of those names. So,
I'm digging it. I really am. And this may sound weird to a lot of Europeans, but this is exactly
the way we respond to America after a presidential election. Hey, that guy won the one that you
were for. I was against, doesn't matter. He's our president. We're going to support him. We're going
to let him take the shot and do the best he can. Now, of course, sounds a lot like what we've had
for the past couple of years, but it could change. That's what has been promised us above all,
change and hope. Well, that part we've got down Pat. We're good to go. So, we'll just launch
right into it. There's still a lot of things not going well in the world. And these are the things
that we hope will change. And I think we should be right there. Hounding our incumbent
representatives and the new ones coming in. And it is quite spectacular that it will be completely
democratically run now. Is it all really one party, other different fractions within the party?
Who's a good guy? Who's not a good guy? Because I think there's good guys and girls and bad guys
and girls and we'll see how the puppet masters continue to tug at the strings in the background
and if we really get what we want. So far so good. Step one has been taken again. I could not be happy
if we're good.
Dear Mr. Cart. Yes. I have listened to several episodes of your podcast
No Agenda. Yes. I must commend Devorek on his excellent work. From what I've heard thus far,
I must say that you often come across as an egocentric asshole. You seem to think you are American
Dutch and British. Yes. I understand you have lived in each of those countries. Yes. However,
you will not British in the slightest sense. Oh. And it's insulting that you would ever try to
insinuate that you are. Okay. Just listen to yourself. Yes. And that's so good English that's
abused from your mouth. You talk utter rubbish. You are an idiot. Yes. You are disgusting. Yes.
I hope one day you can see how much of a scumbag you really are. You know what? You really tell
you really made my day. Hey Adam, how you doing? This is David Rhode Island and just
want to give you an update. Yeah. The bank and end of it. Yeah. Hell yeah. Good work Adam.
I was waiting for that. Yank the bank. It's the central banks and the federal reserve.
Federal reserve now. Ben Bernanke, he's saying. Oh, we can't do it on a motive bailout.
Yo, this is only for my banker buddies. This is not actually to improve the world or help the
United States populist. No, no. Fuck you if you're going to be out of a job. We don't want you to have
our money. It's ours. That's what's going on. You watch. Poor old schmucks there in capital hill
thinking they're going to do some good. They're getting yanked on both ends of it.
First of all, by the auto makers. And then by the fed who does not want to give our money to
anyone but themselves. It's so blatant, so clear. Wake up people. The new world order is forming.
And we've got to stop them. Yank the bank and the fed. And take back the power of your own
government wherever you are.
I've always loved the Matrix soundtrack. The wake-up.
Oh, man. Great song that is. Well, what's been going on is it's just been crazy busy. Of course,
the move is starting to spin up. We got the keys to the new concept, which I think indeed is going to
be named the Curry Terrace. It just has a nice ring to it. I got a great office. I cannot wait. So this is
of course, as a terrace house in London. Very typical. And so you have a, you walk up a short
flight of steps to walk into the house. And then that's where you have the living room. And we've got
an overhang and conservatory at the back. And you know, it's, it's really fantastic. You can also walk
down the steps from the front or internally, of course. And on the, I guess that would be the Sutara
is at the back is a huge kitchen with another aga, which I'm very happy about. Of course,
we've got the teenager apartment out back, which is right outside of the kitchen. So, you know,
she can come in and get a midnight snacks. And we have the whole house to ourselves. Now,
on the front of that is where I get my new office. It has very high ceilings, which I desperately
need because I've been doing. Finally, I'm getting into video production. It has taken me several
years. So finally, I can get into some production. You've probably seen at mevio.com every single
day. There's a new, uh, uh, new little, uh, these days. It's like three minutes, three, four minutes,
highlighting stuff that's new on the across our four networks for that day. So that's,
men, women, music, and tech. You can play those channels. They, they roll out one after another.
It's, um, you know, it is literally in one of our channel systems. So one, one show play one at one
episode plays after another. I'm very happy with it. Advertisers are happy with it. And it's looking
cool. And it's just given me so many ideas of things I want to do. I'm thinking of two shows
that I want to put together. One is tentatively titled My Gear, the other one. They work for us.
That's the tentative title of the show. And so it's that kind of stuff that I'm working on. What
better way to start your day than with a hot cup of coffee with financial times? A little DSC.
Well, you might want to go to the bathroom first. Here's Adam Curry.
The part of the plan that is to get all of our information control us, give us ID cards,
keep us as hot little fucking slaves. Keep working, keep paying your taxes.
And present electobama is just as bad when it comes to that. Because we're going to have one
million soldiers working to secure the homeland. One million soldiers and already they have
five battalions just in case there's any unrest during the credit crisis. And all they're doing
now is keeping the shit afloat until Obama is president. The minute he's president and he knows
it's coming. He's part of the plan. That's when it ruled. That's when the wheels come off this thing.
I'm talking global meltdown. The minute, maybe a minute, maybe two minutes after he's
president. Dog is still barking. You're going to bark yourself to death.
And now the song that I've been waiting for to play for you for at least four years. I was unable
to find it in the iTunes music store. Unable to find it anywhere online even at cpo.com,
which is where I rip all the best stuff. Finally, I found out through a message on drop.io slash
daily source code that it is available for sale at emusic.com. And of course, I'm signed up.
emusic.com slash daily source code. I got 35 free songs. This was one of them. The LSE brothers.
I'd like to stay in love with you all summer and after fall I'll keep you on through the
window. I've knitted one way. There's no more play.
I'd like to write my heart should go with you on the end of the fall. You'll have to run away.
Do all that chase it through the matter. Wish you all without a few more times.
It's never covered.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no,
Oh yeah, I think it must have been the summer of 75. I was a wee boy, maybe 11, 12, maybe 13 years old,
all the madly in love with a girl at school and just thinking about right with her and my handlebars
through the middle and really didn't mean it.
That's from the soundtrack to my lives, how to share with you on the source code.
Oh man, perfect way to finish off the week as if we're from our Friday maximum music
free training spirit and the Alessi brothers of Lauren.
You're Adam, you're my Eduardo, where are we going from Seattle?
Yeah, long time listening to her first shine dropper and I wanted to drop you a message.
By the way, that is now official Charlie vernacular.
First time call or long time dropper.
Just as long as you're dropping, that's good.
Because during your past show, you keep complaining about hearing the dog
and you play around with your nice kid and I couldn't tell the difference.
I didn't hear your dog and I wasn't sure if you're just...
I love the way you say that.
I didn't hear your dog.
I didn't hear your dog, man.
I couldn't hear your dog.
At least the stuff I will talk about with you guys.
I got plenty of things.
I'm so flushing out.
There's a lot of improvement that I like to make in life.
But the core of my existence, I'm just professionally with a person.
Well, what is the data source code?
Is the relationship that I have with you guys with Charlie heads out there?
As it congealed and comes together on the source code drop.
So here's the thinking that I have for this show and where I like to take it.
I would like to commit a minimum of an hour, five days a week.
If I started re-blocking the afternoon, you came time.
Everyone has a possibility to check out life.
But I really want to do it the right way.
And I have a little better chance to really do something top of the whole day.
Because we need to do...
I can't know.
I can no longer wait a day to talk about something because then it's five other things
that it pile on top.
And I'll just run now to what I've got for today.
And this is all of the most that I've taken from the drop.
Actually...
Let me see.
I see, actually.
But I want to say, I don't know where to start.
That's what I'm saying.
So I'm gonna start sneaking stuff in, bit by bit.
We've got to get to a larger, wider audience.
Welcome in.
Wake up, help understand what's going on.
And tell a friend.
He really needs to tell a friend.
And my friends, that's it for this episode.
So until we speak again, you got your freedom.
Spread that.
Let people know about it and let's maintain it.
Let's keep that freedom.
And above all, I don't know what you do about how you do it.
Leave your life with passion.
Let's keep that freedom.
Let's keep that freedom with passion.