Delta Shared Charlie, eight one two.
It's the financial rescue bill, fails in Congress yet again.
The value of your home could plummet.
Families looking for a new home will be unable to get a loan.
It's going to be harder for you to get a mortgage for your home.
New car sales will come to a halt.
Or the loans you need to buy a car.
It would be more difficult for you to get the loans you need to buy a car.
Or send your children to the college.
No longer be able to get loans for college.
What businesses would close their doors may be unable to pay employees.
Thousands of businesses could call.
In millions of Americans could lose their job.
Millions of jobs could be lost.
We failed to act.
And ultimately, our country could experience a long and painful recession.
We're 60 million dollars worth of airplanes trapped by us.
To the next generation, we need to count any of my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I guess it's a new curry.
I like to think that I'm flying into the future.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
We're shrieks for which you are
I'm getting out with each other's mail
You're heading around
You get from out
That doesn't help you
You're the better man
The crazy's on you
That's not me
So what do you do
That can't be
Hey you, you're the best now
Yeah, I told you
Just me for myself
I'm counting on you
Let me hold you
That's not me
So you're the better man
The crazy's on you
Let me hold you
That's not me
So you're the better man
The crazy's on you
Let me hold you
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
G-town probably the last time we'll be doing the show from this location.
In fact, I'm 100% sure of it.
This will be the last show before Christmas.
It is the 23rd of December 2008, Merry Christmas.
Or as we say in the United Kingdom, happy Christmas.
Happy Hanukkah.
Happy Quanza.
Happy Winter Solstice.
Anything you celebrate as long as you're hanging out
with your family for the next couple of days.
Enjoy it.
So yeah, between the move, which has been,
this is actually, I don't know if I really like this process
of having the house for a month
and then slowly bring in stuff over
because you've also made some adjustments
and not want to change this floor
and all kinds of stuff going on between that and my job,
which these days consists pretty much of creating
the Mivio today, four minute video show,
which runs when you hit Mivio.com,
it gives you an overview of what's playing across the four networks,
which I do in its entirety, all of myself.
It's kind of, it's like master-batory almost.
It's really weird.
You know, because I got the camera set up,
got the light set up, got the blue screen set up,
I make sure I'm positioned, I got a white balance
and focus myself, record everything.
I would much, much rather,
actually be doing some kind of master-batory function.
And then, of course, I edited it together.
It takes a long time, man, to do four to five minutes a day.
Crap, Ola.
Then, of course, I, as you know,
I don't want to just rush through it Charlie,
so I spent a couple hours preparing.
Actually, I've been saving links throughout the week
as usual so much happening,
but I'll never get to every single bit of it.
And also, I don't want to go to two negative,
and during these happy times,
we were all getting together.
We really should just be getting together
with our families, just to get together
with our families, and I forget about gift-giving.
It makes not make a card, but that'll be sufficient.
Get into the habit of it, because money talks,
and money is changing right before our very eyes.
A lot of weird links popped up in the source code
drop over the past week, drop.io slash daily source code.
I just want to share a couple of them with you
as we get into the, the meat of what's happening in the world.
Of course, there are no secrets only information
you don't yet have.
A lot of that information is on drop.io slash daily source code,
mainstream news articles, stuff that you just had never heard of,
but was reported on, but because we're so inundated
with information at this absolutely no way
that it can bubble to the top with one or two stories.
This is from a new vision, which builds itself
as Uganda's leading website.
And it's just a weird link that I think is worth discussing.
All boys and men in Uganda will be mobilized
for free circumcision, beginning next year.
This is according to the Commissioner
for the Assistant Commissioner for National Disease Control,
in Uganda, the government plans to introduce
free mass circumcision before the end of 2009
and get this as one of the ways to reduce the spread
of HIV AIDS.
Now this, this is obviously it caught my eye.
And there's some facts in here.
75% of Uganda and men are not circumcised
according to the 2006 National Zero Survey.
But here it comes.
They expect 50% less AIDS contracted by men
if they're circumcised.
That is HIV from women to men.
And I've never heard of this.
But apparently, let me see if I can get the exact part.
The World Health Organization, who I must say,
I kind of distrust, estimated that implementation
of mass circumcision could have hurt up to 5.7 million HIV
infections and 3 million AIDS death worldwide by 2026.
Based on that, World Health Organization
and you need, I guess, that's a UN body charge
with HIV matters, issued a set of recommendations last year
for the use of medical male circumcision,
circumcision, HIV prevention efforts.
This is interesting.
But apparently, the foreskin is,
I'm looking for the, let me just search.
Ah, Safari is so good at that for me.
Four skin.
There we go.
The foreskin is vulnerable to tears and ulcers.
Oh, this is not a happy Christmas story.
That provide an entry point for HIV.
The inner skin is very soft and allows HIV
to easily penetrate.
When this is cut off, the tip of the penis hardens
making it difficult for HIV to penetrate.
Wow, man.
I'd love to hear some doctors weigh in on this.
They really believe that 50% less AIDS,
now they're saying sexual transmission,
although 50% reduction from transmission from women
to men, which I thought was pretty low anyway.
But just in general, it seems like a pretty drastic move.
Nothing I would have to worry myself about
to that spread worldwide since I am circumcised.
Wow, did I just share too much information with you?
Okay, let's move on to something else.
Shall we?
Hey Adam.
Yeah, it's Wardo.
Can you do it?
In terms of Wonderland's of Seattle.
Yeah, my little friend.
Want to drop you a quick message to give you feedback.
Your comments regarding for my changes to the DSC.
I have been addicted to tank shifting for the past three years.
First with the dictionary for DVR.
And the last year using a mini with IDV.
Yeah, so I Eduardo, of course, is responding to the fact
that I really desperately want to go live on a very regular basis.
Even if it's shorter, just to get some feedback.
So I'm not living in this vacuum with MP3 feedback in comments.
So I guess he has a problem with connected to my SDTV.
And I have to say that I barely watch any live TV anymore.
There's a lot of people I know that don't watch any television anymore.
They're watching video tons of video, but very little actual television.
And honestly, now that I have the all these swing boxes,
I can watch television on cable in Detroit.
I can watch television on cable television in Hawaii.
You just sat by the channel's man.
It's all commercial.
It's literally as the boss saying, 57 channels, nothing else.
I can see how a live show will be better for you.
I may improve the content of the DSC.
I will not listen to the show live,
but I will definitely continue to listen to the recordings of the live show.
I would only suggest that you still provide some time in the show for recorded comments.
So we times she's certain droppers can still have a voice in the show.
Of course.
Droppers always welcome here on the Charlie.
By the way, that gear show that you are planning is long overdue,
and I can't wait to watch it.
They work for us.
Elliot?
They may have forgotten, but they sure do.
But before I forget, Ray has put together a year-end daily source code
that will blow your socks off.
It is a compilation of a year-worth of episodes,
which used to be a lot, like 200 or something.
Now it's significantly less.
So he didn't have to work that hard.
Now seriously, it took him days
if not weeks to put this thing together.
I'm going to run that just before new years,
between Christmas and New Years,
as I said, you probably won't get another show out of me.
Until 2009, a fresh new show.
And yes, Eduardo, no worries.
Always room for droppers in the show.
Wouldn't want to change a thing.
Some good links and kind of wacky ones,
which of course you couldn't see in the show.
No, it's a daily source code.com.
Crossposts that at curie.com.
This is just something that I picked up.
I think it was, gee, it's so, I think it was several months ago,
maybe even, from Project Camelot.net,
which I don't talk about a lot because of a lot of their stuff
is way out there.
But I do keep up with them.
This is a translated Google page,
or a page translated by Google.
And it talks about, and this is the story,
here's the story in short,
and it's kind of a crude translation,
but worth the read, you'll see the link in there.
That a prominent Norwegian politician has apparently
blown the whistle on this entire underground complex
of tunnels and trains that go with the speed of light
and flash you from one side of the country,
or Lord knows the continent to another,
and that this is where the elite plan to live
with stored food and seeds, apparently.
Bill Gates is mixed up in this,
and there's been a lot of talk about the seed vault.
But this story is, well, you have to read through it,
and you really got to focus,
again, the translation isn't super,
but there's probably another version of it
over a Project Camelot.net.
Again, it's massive tin foil hat time,
but take a look at it, it definitely boads a read.
And just when you thought that you heard everything,
you know, we talked a lot about the government wanting
to chip its citizens, put RFID chips in us,
to track us and eventually be able to control us
through our money or Lord knows,
maybe even implanted in your brain.
Well, now there's an actual reason
to want one of these, or want some form of chip,
because Viagra may soon be history.
Scientists at Oxford University are working
on an electronic sex chip that can stimulate
pleasure centers in the brain.
I think this is how they do it.
They give you something like some fantastic device
that, of course, particularly if it's embedded in near
or in connection with the brain,
could probably do a lot of different things,
maybe not all good, but they give it to you to get a heart on.
It's like, yeah, give me that chip, boy.
I could use that.
It's a great story, and it comes from the times of India,
which I'll just consider to be mainstream as well.
Something I talked about with the John C. Devorek
on Noah Gendo over the weekend.
The NASA has, well, not just NASA,
but the number of scientists have discovered
this breach in the Earth's magnetic field.
And it's funny because this is a lot of the stuff
with the north and the south pole and magnetic pole.
A lot of that is prophesized and talked about
in the 2012 circles of people who either believe
that the dawning of the age of Aquarius is coming
and we're all going to be saved,
or exactly the opposite as many compared
to the Book of Revelation,
where the Obama is the antichrist and we're all going to die.
I don't know, but it certainly is a discovery.
And in fact, it's really, I think somewhere in the article
it says it's of tsunami-like proportions
when you, oh, what does this?
Oh, man, I can't do a conference call right now.
I'm in the middle of my charting.
See, even on our week off,
and, of course, Tom Vilsack announced
as Secretary of Agriculture meeting that Moncanto,
whether they are in the hidden tunnels of Norway
or not in the hills there, near the fjords in Norway,
I think so.
There's certainly going to be in the White House,
Tom Vilsack, who at one point campaigned
using the Moncanto corporate jet Moncanto, of course,
owner of food.
They literally have patents and trademarks
on seeds of a particular corn, mice,
that are genetically modified,
as far as I'm concerned, not healthy for you.
And so this guy is not going to be in charge
of agriculture.
Yeah, that's the change that we were looking for.
And there's some weird story,
which I want you to take a look at about Hillary Clinton
dating to repay him or help him,
recoup the $400,000 he used as a campaign debt
for, I don't know, and maybe he's,
what was he campaigning for?
I don't know, but then he, maybe he was campaigning
for president.
Let me see if it says it here.
Yeah, democratic, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
one time candidate who endorsed him,
I guess he was a one time candidate.
Interesting.
It's all connected, it really is.
And of course, the ongoing story about this IT guy,
doesn't sound very respectful.
Does it, I'm looking for the, here it is, here's the link.
This thing's to high hell, Michael Connell,
if you recall, there was a whole slew of emails
that were held or kept confidential
because they were off the grid, so to speak,
off of the White House grid, 2004.
Actually, this may have even been earlier.
It was a GWB43.com and the emails
between George W. Bush and Carl Rove were,
were supposedly deleted, but, you know,
there's a lot of probably incriminating evidence
containing those emails about a lot of things.
And this guy, Michael Connell, is the guy
who set it up and apparently were supposedly
erased everything, but he was actually, as far as I understand,
there's very little detailed information.
Was flying himself back from Washington, DC,
where a lot of people speculate that he was blowing
the whistle on what actually went down
and what was in those emails, maybe even had copies made
available.
And of course, his single engine plane crashed,
not a shitty plane, by the way, a pipe or serotoga.
I read a report that, oh, he probably hit an ice patch,
which is just about the most unaviation-minded comment
you can make.
This aircraft, by the way, is able to handle ice.
Certainly, if you're more or less on a downwind leg,
as far as I could see from the airfield,
just looking at Google Earth and where the crashed occurred,
versus proximity of the airfield, direction he was coming
from, I didn't get an actual weather report
to see what the icing conditions were.
But I'm even reading a report
that he did not fly his plane two other times
because of tips he got that the plane could have been
to sabotage.
I mean, it's just a big mess.
The body count goes up by one, nasty.
Oh, let me see.
Well, let's do we have here.
Oh, yeah, this one I liked.
This is, you might have seen this post that on Curie.com.
It's a project called the Global Consciousness Project Dot.
And it's essentially, you can embed this on your,
on a web page anywhere.
And this dot has, what does it's six different color phases,
ranging from blue to kind of like turquoise to green
to, or a yellow to orange to red?
And the history of this thing is there are,
I think it's like 15 or 1600 people globally
who have probes inserted into their brains.
They had some kind of unrelated brain surgery
and agreed to have one of these detectors,
one of these probes inserted into their brain.
There's a whole website about it, a lot of information.
And they, I don't know if it's a real time or if they have to connect
and upload their brain data, but they send it all back to home base.
And based upon that information,
you can see what the global consciousness of these,
you know, the sample group is,
well, not really what they're thinking,
but how what their anxiety level is.
And this boils back to the fact that your brain
actually receives information and dishes it out to your limbs
and to your body with up to a half second
or sometimes even longer delay.
However, your timing isn't off
because it turns out people can actually anticipate
something that is about to happen.
And it's this anticipation, this global consciousness project
is built upon.
So for an example, if someone throws you a ball,
you're even though your brain is sending you signals
and this is scientifically proven,
that take half a second to make your body react,
to catch the ball, as an example.
Your brain is, or something within the human psyche,
is anticipating this projectile coming at you.
And therefore moves you and synchronizes you
so that you actually kept the ball on time
and not half a second later.
So what they found is that on up to four hours
before the World Trade Center attack,
the charts went literally off the charts,
that people worldwide could feel some kind of anxiousness.
Something was about to happen.
And there's several other examples.
You can drill down deep into it.
A lot of people call this crap.
I find it highly interesting.
And so what entertaining to you?
So what entertaining just to watch a little dot
and see if it changes color from the time, time, time.
I heard this on the radio the other day, I thought,
man, this is timely once again.
Oh, now it's the day to come.
Because there's something in the air,
we got to get them together,
so the whole day to come.
Because from where the moon shines in,
I don't know what's right.
I don't know what it's like.
We have come to get it together.
No, no, no.
I don't know what it's like.
Because there's something in the air,
we got to get them together,
so the whole day to come.
Because from where the moon shines in,
I don't know what it's like.
We have come to get it together.
We have come to get it.
and I think it's gonna happen there's a lot going on around the world this
is stuff you definitely will not read about in your local newspaper you're
not going to hear about it on the news on the six o'clock evening news
because nobody wants you to know that what's really happening in the world
because people are writing they are extremely pissed with what's happening
uh... let me just uh... here this is a great headline from the international
harrel tribune very reputable source french politicians fear youth violence
along the Greek pattern you barely hear anything about grease
but uh... there's writing going on uh... in fact here it is fire bombs breaking
glass tear gas burning cars
the images from grease this month were enough to put the fear of youth into the
hearts of european leaders particularly fron's
and uh... when you look at the numbers you can really understand why this is
happening now yes
in uh... grease the police shot and killed a fifteen-year-old boy
and that was the spark but it's really it's a tender box worldwide the rapid
rise and unemployment amongst young people under age of twenty five particularly
in southern europe
is a very big concern in spain for instance youth unemployment
shot up from eighteen point four percent in august of two thousand seven to twenty eight
point one percent in october
of two thousand eight
almost doubling
yes certainly uh...
sixty percent there the average jobless rate for young people and italy grease and
fron says well above the average for the european union
according to your stats the uh... luxembourg agency that collects e-use statistics
and uh... they're doing this uh... how many should have pulled this song out
uh... in grease there uh... the their plans songs on the radio like another brick
and the wall by pink floyd
which of course controls the leg contains the lyric we don't need no education we don't
need no thought control known dark sarcasm in the classroom
hey teacher leave those kids alone
oh man
island where of course uh... the ship first really hit the fan
this is from bloomberg
towards the week before christmas and rike vick and all through the town evahodok stir
but a band of sixty whistling blowing pan banging shouting demonstrators saying pay
your own debts
as they went from one bank to the other this is this is a civilized culture by the way
you know he's like people who have cell phones and iPads and uh... and uh... go to the
you know they watch football
and they got screwed they got screwed by their banks in the government but because
it only a three hundred twenty thousand uh...
head population
it happened a lot quicker and uh... and the news
the true news spread throughout the population much quicker of course than it'll
ever take us to
help people understand and and i've i'm coming back from this awakening idea i i really
think we should just say there are no secrets only information you don't yet have
as much more provocative
and this awakening
uh... because people who are asleep and sheep
don't like it you know you know you don't like to know likes being woken up for one and
whatever reason even if you're actually sleeping
you know i don't like the awoken up
and doesn't help but why here do i hear
mm
interesting i don't have the noise gate on today so i'm hearing all kinds of
extraneous stuff
uh... riots and grease this month sparked by the police shooting of a teenager became
tensed with economic dissension
a group of quady equity traders marched on the emir's office in october to demand
the closing of the stock exchange to stem losses even in u.s. city civil disorder is
conceivable
if unemployment rises above ten percent from november six point seven percent
so this uh... this lady eve uh... hoax dotter
uh... she said we will use our voices
if we have to will use our hands
or maybe even access
so
are these people just smarter are they further along have been they have been hurt more than
we have
like and tell you this all this money that's being thrown away literally
is m and it's just it's being thrown away general motors cheap executive rick whagnor
says hey we got we asked for nine point four billion dollars in loans over the next
twenty four days however investors
are betting against the company
they're taking all kinds of position saying even with that money they'll never make it
and of course when you think about it this plenty of money out there to be
invested in companies certainly in the automobile industry but why is it not happening
why is it no private money going into them because
in private investors they can read this balance sheet which apparently the federal
reserve and certainly are treasury cannot
the uh... united uh... nations
it's actually it sounds like my oh there you go now i was really crap and out
the other nations uh... general assembly held a vote
you like this
uh... over the draft resolution
it's kind of like a human rights uh...
article
draft law resolution
of the right to food
saying that every person has the basic human right to food
one hundred and eighty four nations voted in favor
i'll just uh... plot a couple of gunna stand and gold uh... Bangladesh
Costa Rica Egypt Japan Jamaica Madagascar Mexico Mozambique
Canada chili the Philippines Poland Rwanda San Lucia Saudi Arabia Switzerland
Sweden Netherlands United Arab Emirates United Kingdom
there was only one vote against
one vote
yeah you guessed it united states
i'm coming
take a sauce car
we're going to get that car
i'm going
all right
i've succumb
time for a little bit of Christmas cheer on the charlie
uh... to classic
charlie before it's the night sent out crazy on the charlie
down in the workshop all the else making boys
well the good channel girls and the good channel boys
but the boss busted him
nearly scared him half the day
that arrived a little hands
cheap whiskey on his bread
from his beer to his boots
he was covered with ammo
like a big bad drunk disgruntled
you'll not ramble
and it smiled at the sand
with a twinkle in his eye
merry Christmas to all
now you're all going to die
the night sent out crazy
it went insane
realize he couldn't get the wrong heel
some fine apples who stepped in his grave
well the workshop is gone now
he decided to bump in
everywhere you'll find the easiest
a few but a comment
anytime up his helpers
and he held the elf hostage
and he ground up a road up into
rain this on pitch
he got anger in France sir
with an old German lougars
and it's last time fashion just like
ready prudent
and he picked up a plane throwing
headed by the few places
he took a big bite and said
he's just like he can
a 9th and a weight crazy
a 9th is free
the way it's done
can't hardly walk
ram a normal
with us them and it rained
here good
the national garden in the
and beyond
there's a man from
me I wouldn't lose
and I've got to serve me
round in the sky
and the ball is alive
and the body can thrive
and in every one night
and then don't
close it away
mama mama mama
used to be such a jolly guy
oh
yes but genius
now sand is doing time
and a federal prison
or is it full of crime
made it a friend
who tried no more tears
he'll be out with good behavior
and seven hundred more years
but now makes it very
silver
and the owner
got job
for the whole
for
and the same
this is why she's on the
whole
every night
with a lawyer
not to be able
move
the right thing about
the 9th
and a weight crazy
make a little spin
from his back
for some
mountain girl
some of me
like he would find a new
people
the 9th
and a weight crazy
make it
when it's in
realize
he can get the run
some finally
most you've never been
you've been
more
some finally
most you've been
he is brain
tell you
some finally
most you've been
in his brain
Yeah, I got to tell you, I'm so excited about the move to the new Casa, the Curry Terrace,
which many of written in and said, oh, what a horrible name, because it sounds like you're
talking about the Curry Terrace or the Terrace house, but no, it's the Terrace house,
end of Terrace to be exact.
I am truly, really excited about getting the new studio set up.
I've ordered this beautiful 19-inch rack, which I'm only going to put the gear into,
that I know that I want, that I know they want to keep.
I probably don't even use that much since everything is pretty much 100% digital at this
point.
The only thing I'm actually using is external gear that I'm using is the, the maybe controller,
the, what is it, the fader fox.
And everything else is internal.
So I, I just want to have some stuff around, you know, so I can, I can produce different
sounds.
I got a big honk and Mac, xenon, dual, multi-quad, whatever processor thingy to really
crunch the video, looking forward to that.
Oh, before I forget, and it, it's probably too late by the time you're hearing this, but
you can always get an after Christmas gift for somebody.
We've got a lot of excellent deals, we've got fantastic sponsors of this program and
others across the media on that work.
Let me give you a quick rundown, finish line, which sells athletic clothing, Nike, Puma,
Didas, and more.
You can get 15% off a purchase of $60 or more, and let's face it, $60 is, that's probably
just one item, maybe two.
If you use the code, mevio, dsc, guaranteed 50% off, can't get a cheaper online anywhere
in the world.
If you sign up for e-harmonie, and this is a reputable dating site, I think they're probably
one of the largest, not the largest.
It's not one of those porn hookers sites, like the ones I always get sucked into.
Oh, look at how hot she is, maybe she'll want to date.
If you sign up for three months, you get one month, three, if you use my code, which is, of
course, daily source code, there's links all throughout the show notes, daily source code.com,
across posted at curie.com.
Also if you are renting a car, maybe between Christmas and New Year's, and get your $30 off
a weekly budget car rental, or 10% off any other amount with my DSE code, 10% off at brookstones.com
with my code, my code, my code, my code, my code, and of course, the Mac daddy of them all
go daddy, 30% discount on everything you buy, go daddy.com, using my checkout code, dsc,
free, and of course, 35 free songs at emusic.com.
For all those links, so you don't have to remember the codes, you can just click on them,
the codes are already embedded in the link, go to the show notes, daily source code.com.
And as I said, cross posted at curie.com.
All right, let's take another call here, because I also have young, pled standing by
with a special Christmas edition of the Hit Test.
So let's move.
Hey, Adam has a go in there.
That's a time listener.
Okay.
Sounds like someone from Ireland.
E-mailer and yeah, first time dropper, first time dropper.
I love it.
So anytime before, when I got in contact, you never saw any reason to use anything I said
in the show.
And that's fair enough, because I never really had anything worthwhile to say.
Ah, let me just say that it's sometimes I missed stuff sometimes.
Well, if you had nothing worthwhile to say and you said it anyway, that would probably
be your reason.
Most of the time though, the stuff is just too long.
It's like five, six minutes, you know, not from you, but from lots of people.
It's just there's no way I can play that.
And nothing is that interesting.
I'm not interesting for what do you think I play songs?
I'm just thinking for five or six minutes.
But right now, I've got a few views on this whole Lisbon treaty issue.
All right, this is the Lisbon treaty.
For those of you just tuning into this program, this thing was essentially the
derivative of the European Constitution, which circulated a number of years ago.
The French and the Dutch voted it down in public referenda.
And what the, and this is by their own admission, this is stated, you know, we're going
to do what just going to pull it all out, turn it into three different documents, remove
the word constitution.
And then we'll put it out there.
And then we won't let any countries hold the referendum, we'll just ram it through
all the individual governments.
Except for one country, the shining shamrock, Ireland said, no, no, no, no, this is
important stuff.
We want to have a referendum.
We want the people to actually vote.
They said, no, wait, don't want it.
Don't like it.
Not that anyone could actually understand the document, but we've delved into a very deep
on this program.
Horrible things when it comes to human rights.
Such as, yeah, you have a right to live and no one can kill you legally unless you're
running away from the police.
It doesn't say unless you're a murderer running away from the police, no, unless you
are running away from the police.
If you are hooked on drugs, alcohol, mentally unstable, which let's face it, I could be classified
as that.
If you have a communicable disease, you can be arrested and thrown in jail, children can
be taken away from their parents.
And all of this was said, oh, no, and I've talked to all of the euro parliamentarians.
I've talked to a minister of parliament in the Netherlands.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, those are just guidelines, you know, each country can do its own
thing.
Yeah, bullshit.
So now, of course, it turns out they really needed this, Lisbon Treaty, all of its
legalese ramp through and ratified so that they could form the new world financial government
and subsequent, I guess the world government is what they're working on.
The new world order, you're hearing politicians openly say it now.
And they don't say it the way I say it.
Because when I say it, I get a nasty aftertaste, you know, kind of like you just threw
up in your mouth.
When they say it's like, it's like gold, I love it.
So of course, they're operating now under something they call operating, operating under
the Lisbon principles.
And I have no, I just don't have the time with a desire to do it, but I'm sure if you
really went delve deep down to the legalese of Lisbon Treaty, you'd see this whole financial
thing all tied up in with it.
So they're going back again because, of course, when the Irish said, no, well, yeah, that's
not acceptable.
Let's do another referendum, but see, if we can get them to say, yes, this time, they'll
keep going back until they get what they want.
That's what this is about.
I'm sorry, my friend, continue.
Or as the European Union likes to call it the Irish problem.
Yeah, the Irish problem.
Yeah.
Well, recently our wonderful new T-shirt Mr. Biffel Count went over and had a little chat with
all of them over there and decided that he would come back here.
And completely ignore the results of the last referendum and, you know, go and have a
whole new one.
Yeah.
First.
And for me.
This is how they do it, by the way.
It's the same thing with the bailout, the people of America, a thousand to one, maybe
even more, we're calling in, calls being rejected, by the way, by the White House Switch
Board.
Websites taken down emails taken offline so that we could not communicate to our legally
chosen representatives, whether they're scum or not, because they'll just take whatever
they want.
And so Congress said, no, go back and we'll just ram it through the Senate until Congress
has to say yes.
I mean, it's that simple.
That's how politics is done.
Yeah, that's just disgusting and really odd.
There's no real words to express, you know, how I feel about this.
Listen to that.
This isn't Irishman, okay?
And when I think Irish, I think Jack Nicholson, right, Jack Nicholson, that's how he
has that Irish blood in him that can just explode.
And you can hear, here's a chucklehead at arms.
He is frustrated, angry doesn't know what to say.
His voice is not heard.
It's very obvious what comes next.
This is so stupid, so counterproductive.
But we have to fight it.
So we'll fight it however we have to.
And I stand proudly side by side with the Irish on this.
It's just, well, look, yeah, see, for the last referendum, we only really had two main
groups opposing it.
We had one political party, which was shinfane, which is really nothing more than the
redneck mafia of Irish politics.
So in all honesty, most people really really don't care what they have to say.
And then there was another group, and just a group of business people called Libertas.
And of course, since the referendum, the government and the national television station,
have been a little go at him and they've pounded him, they've gone after his past, all sorts
of stuff.
Sure, the EU themselves said to do a whole big bit of research on him and figure out
what's going on with him.
The guy had Declan Gannley, the main man of Libertas, to be honest, he's been made to look
like the kind of guy who'd be down on some street corner telling you to find the ace
in his three cards and there's only, maybe, two or five in a queen, so I don't know.
I think they really didn't touch on the right issues either, because most of the stuff was
going and looking at traditional Irish issues like, actually, EU stands on abortion and stuff
like that, and tax cuts and all sorts of things like that, and just general things that
people might worry about.
Yeah, you know, the kind of stuff that you should worry about in your own country.
I'm all for trading amongst nations and even the euro itself, although I'm completely against
central banking and which, of course, is the route of all of the problems that we have right now
and why billions and hunt actually trillions of dollars, euros, and pounds are being pumped
through the banking system, none of it actually, you know, they're just using it as an excuse,
but the jig is up, the game is over, that just stop working.
So yeah, but that's of concern, that is the main concern.
Same thing that you don't want to central banking your own country, your own state or even your own
it's crap, it's a stupid lame system designed to protect the banks, not to help you whatsoever.
I mean, for the longest period they were saying, oh, if this comes in, the French are just
going to raise our corporation tax in line with the rest of Europe, and that really didn't sit well
with people, especially known that, you know, the recession was coming on and we need as many companies
coming in as possible. So, so this leads me to believe that if the business leaders were protesting
against this, that they actually did have a good look at this Lisbon Treaty and said, hey,
wait a minute, this is a unification of everything. We don't want to be what those guys want to be.
We want to be Irish and have our own corporate taxes. Now, by the way, I can just hear
comic strip blogger yelling into his iPod there, or he probably uses a zoom saying, well, they took
billions of euros in subsidies from the European Union. Yep, that, of course, is also true.
But still, that was all before this Lisbon Treaty came to bear. So, I'd say,
fair and square, no, is no, no, is no. I don't know, but they really didn't touch on any of the
whole structural issues on it. You know, like how the EU will be structured and managed and
the simple fact that we don't even have, we don't even have a chance to vote in the people and
power over there anymore. And they don't seem to realize that by letting it into the constitution,
when these unelected assholes get in, you know, they can make up whatever crazy rules they want,
and we have to follow them. Yeah, oh, yeah. All kinds of crazy rules coming down the pike.
And it's going to start with the internet very, very soon. Even this program, I guarantee you
will be violating laws within the next 24 months. There will be laws that will be violated on this
program. And guess what, the violating will continue. And I don't know, personally, I think people
should look more into that side of things. And sure, I'm going to be working on that myself.
I'm going to get out and start telling people, no, to this in Lisbon thing. I mean,
I voted no, and I want my vote to count. And right now, it doesn't. So I'm going to make sure that
next time around, it does. Anyway, love the hair. I think mine's better. See you around.
That's probably ginger top, huh? All right. Well, if it does come around, if they do set up another
referendum, we'll just go through the whole thing again. We'll dissect the Lisbon Treaty once again,
explain to the Europeans. And obviously to the Irish exactly what it means. And we will continue to
fight that. Because it's, it's necessary. We got to stand up. All right. Uh, it's the 23rd.
Uh, the Eve before Christmas Eve. I need a little bit of Christmas music. It's titled the Christmas
edition. I'm hoping it contains some. Hey, Adam, how you doing? I'm good man, Merry Christmas.
This is the Christmas edition of the hit-est. Yep. Have we got to start right away with intro?
Number one. Oh, yes. One of my favorite Christmas songs.
That's uh, Chris Ria. I'll be driving home for Christmas. Oh, cool, man. I like this.
Number two.
It'll be lonely this Christmas. Oh, I don't think Americans know that one at all. And number three.
It's the most expensive. And it really is, I guess.
Truly a, uh, some Christmas here there, y'all. And it's time for the answers.
Yeah, this is answer number one in this Christmas edition of the hit-est.
This is Chris Ria. And he's driving home for Christmas.
Oh, I can't wait to see those faces.
Driving home for Christmas. Yeah.
Come up, we don't hold the ground.
All right, nice.
This Ria's answer number one.
Yeah. This is answer number two. I love this. This is mud.
I'm trying to imagine a, I'm a Christmas all alone.
It'll be lonely in this Christmas, without you, it's too hot.
It'll be cold, it's so cold without you, it's too hot.
Oh, this Christmas.
It'll be lovely. This Christmas is answer number two.
Mud. And this is indeed free.
This is as you will.
We're going one love once a year. It's the most wonderful time of the year. And it will be us.
As answer number three. And that concludes this Christmas edition of the hit-est.
So Adam. Yes, y'all. How did you do this week?
Well, if I hadn't gotten six out of six on that one, I would have been pretty pathetic.
But Mud was a curveball I liked it. Thanks, Y'all, and Merry Christmas.
Once again, to you and your family.
Like always, the answers to this and any other hit-est.
And also the links to iTunes, you can buy this tracks featured on the hit-est online.
Not to be found at hittest.mefio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam. Thank you, Y'all.
Everyone else. Thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll turn me back for another hit-est. So, one till then.
Have fun. Take care. Think with your hearts.
And Merry Christmas, everybody. Bye-bye.
Wow. 152 episodes. Holy moly. Merry Christmas, Y'all.
I like that one, dude. It's cool.
Actually, I was thinking of playing a couple of those songs.
And then I saw that you had a Christmas edition.
Like, no, I'm going to hold off. I'm happy.
I definitely would have played Chris Rhea. That's for sure.
So, I've been talking about setting up a live call-in system.
Something that I can actually manage myself.
And I've been looking in two different directions.
Actually, three different directions.
One is some form of a conference calling system,
which we have tried before with Talks Show.
But it doesn't really allow you to talk to people,
stack up calls, put them on hold, keep them waiting,
then bring them in one by one.
I have considered actually doing that with a hosted conference calling service.
So, you've called in and you talked to the operator, the operator.
And there are lots of companies around there that will actually do this.
It says, it's not all that expensive.
And all they have to do is write down your name,
where you're from, as an example, and what you want to talk about.
And they could even IM me that while I'm doing the show.
And then, but then still, they would be adding that person into the queue.
So, I have to say, okay, you know, Pete from Portland.
And then the operator would have to be on the ball listening and plug the person in.
And, of course, I can't cut the person.
I need to hold a bunch of different things.
I wouldn't want to be able to do that way.
The most obvious route is to get some kind of
virtual switchboard.
And so, I've been looking around.
There are tons of companies that do kind of kind of what I need,
but not everything.
There's certainly nothing that I've really been able to find that,
well, there's systems that will stack up calls,
but then they take them in order, and you can't talk to people
while they're on hold, and you can't plug the show's audio back into what they're listening while they're on hold.
And my old friend, PC from Down Under, he's been working on this.
He's, we've been trading emails, and he has an idea as to how he wants to set this up.
And he's even set up a website because he believes that this is a technology that
once developed would have greater good for the rest of the world.
Well, there you go.
And he sent me a comment as requested to explain a little bit deeper about what
what track he's on and how we're going to solve this problem.
Mr. Gary, part master, Phil from Sydney.
Yep.
I just wanted to discuss with you the possible options for your
live call for them with call queueing, and how it can actually be done.
I think you're going to have to use Skype as the main call and method.
By the way, I'm really happy with using Skype.
I have lots of VoIP systems. I use Gizmo Skype.
Barnon just performs best gives you the best quality, certainly over time.
But of course, as far as I know, it's only one, in fact, here's a question.
How many incoming Skype calls can I actually handle?
Um, I know that if one person calls another person calls, I can answer it
then the original person goes on hold.
I'm presuming what Phil means here is I use my Skype to call into some form of
a phone bank and that that's where I make my connection to multiple phone.
Because you can get Skype at numbers for the countries that you need to participate.
Yeah, I got those.
Got a lot of course, people can just call them, you know, Skype off their desktop.
So I think what you need at your end is going to, you want to need a Skype gateway,
something like a skip to PBX, which is going to be able to convert the Skype callers
into SIP at the back end and you're going to need something like an Asterix VoIP system.
Yeah, see, this is where my eyes start to glaze over.
I actually, I, there's an Asterix, which is kind of a software based phone
switcher PBX, they call it.
There's one for Mac OS 10 and I installed it and I was like, okay, I just installed it and they're like,
now what? I couldn't get into work.
Yeah, I did that amongst all the other things. I, I took about an hour and a half of looking at
Asterix, big mistake, not a place I should venture to any more IPPBX that's going to be
able to take the feed from the gateway and filter into Asterix and then provide some sort of
callcuring or with some sort of Asterix, third party add-on. They're okay, hold on a second.
So what Phil is saying is we reverse it and have the Skype in numbers going to a PBX and then
the PBX apparently, I guess I'll just jack right into my sound system. I think there are
quite how you're going to jack it into your sound system. Yeah, I can use a jack router for that,
which is what I use in my mouth. I'll use jack router. So I think you're probably, that's jack
router and OS X on the Apple. I think you're probably going to have to switch to using
jack router on Linux because I know they've got native support for sippin asterix.
Yeah, that's, that's, that's going to be a non-starter, my friend. I'm definitely tied into the Apple
platform with all of my recording gear. So that's, that's my suggestion. I've actually set up a
website to just the discussion forum to try and figure out how you can do this. It's quite an
interesting problem and one that has quite a global reach. So it seems like a good idea to have a
central point where we're, where people can suggest perhaps all the ways to do it,
best or worse in mind. The website is www.makingcarry.tv. That would be Mike,
Alpha, Kilo, India, November, Golf, Charlie, uniform, Romeo, Romeo, Yankee.tv. Yeah, let me know
what you think. Chocolate, take a visit. I'll suggest some ways to do this if you're sound engineer
or if you're a voice engineer. Let's discuss it. Great here. Hope you win. They work for us.
Yo, well, there's one thing is for sure, whether we solve the problem or not,
that makingcarry.tv, I guarantee you at some point in the future there's going to be a television
program about making curry dishes and they'll want to buy that off you. So it's going to be
worth something. And I hope you used my discount code DSC3 at godaddy.com for that. This is something
that showed up on the source code drop. Drop.io slash daily source code. We're truly there
are no secrets only information you don't yet have. This is a mix of three, well, at one point
they were all three candidates, but it is President Bush. Presidential candidate John McCain
and President elect Barack Obama. Over the course of the past few months talking about the
economy, please pay very close attention to the similarity in what they're saying. The words,
the rhythm, the speeches, almost all identical. These are not three people working for individual
parties or different agendas or competing with each other. These are three people working for the
same master. Listen, if the financial rescue bill fails in Congress yet again, the value of your home
could plummet. Families looking for a new home will be unable to get a loan. It's going to be harder
for you to get a mortgage for your home. New car sales will come to a halt or the loans you need to buy a
car. It would be more difficult for you to get the loans you need to buy a car or send your
children to college. No longer be able to get loans for college. My businesses would close
their doors, maybe unable to pay employee. Thousands of businesses could call. In millions of
Americans could lose their job. Millions of jobs could be lost. We failed to act. And ultimately
our country could experience a long and painful recession. It reminds me of if you are not with
them, then you are with the terrorists. It's just terror. That's what they're doing. Because what
is this money actually done this 700 billion in hard cash? And then the 8.8.6 now I think
trillion dollars that the federal reserve has loaned out given away guaranteed bought assets with
which they won't even tell us what they've spent it on. This is the outrageous part from the
associated press. In fact, the title of this, I like what the AP is doing here, the title of
this article, where the bailout money goes. It's a secret. That's literally the headline.
So they went around since the need of the treasury nor the federal reserve
will which is the American Central Bank bad news folks. Since they won't tell us or anyone
including apparently associated press or Bloomberg, we've mentioned those articles many, many times.
They went around to the banks and they said, hey, what are you doing with the money that you receive?
Well, here are some of the answers. Bank of New York, Melon, which received $3 billion says
spokesman Kevin Heiney or Heine. We're choosing not to disclose that. Thomas Kelly spokesman for
JP Morgan Chase, which received $25 billion in emergency bailout money, said that while some
of the money was lent, some was not and the bank has not given any accounting of exactly how the
money is being used. Kelly said, we have not disclosed that to the public. We're declining to
associated press contacted 21 banks that received at least $1 billion in government money,
my money, your money, and asked for questions. How much has been spent? What was it spent on?
How much is being held in savings and what is the plan for the rest? Not a single one of these 21
banks provided any specific answers. Here's another one. Barry Coulding spokesman for
Leonard Georgia based Sun Trust banks. They got $3.5 billion in taxpayer money. We're not providing
dollar in dollar outtracking. We manage our capital in its aggregate said Regions Financial
Court spokesman Tim Dayton, another $3.5 billion recipient. This is unbelievable. Unbelievable.
That these questions aren't they're just refusing to answer the questions. They got this money
for free from us. Not entirely correct, but they got his money to help them. We know that billions
have gone to bonuses, but for them to not even tell us what they're using it for. How much longer can
this idiocy continue? Well, quite some while apparently. Dr. Ron Paul, who now of course
is a favorite on Fox News, he used to be called a cook. Now that Fox has turned around and of course
Fox hates Obama. They can have him on all the time. Here he is once again talking about
exactly this issue. Or they just simply refuse to disclose it. Texas Republican Ron Paul, he joins
me now on the phone. Congressman, what do you make of all of this? Well, it looks like it's more of the
thing. Same old story. The taxpayer coughs up. The money's passed out. Nobody knows what
happens to it. But even sometimes we don't even appropriate the money. There's two trillion dollars.
The sad has issues and they tell us that it would be counterproductive to tell us where it's going.
So we don't have any oversight to down the banks' status, but just not too long ago we had a report
that we passed out $23 billion in Iraq for rebuilding in its total loss. They can account for it.
I don't know how long this could last. And here that $23 billion in Iraq that is just
unaccounted for. It's just gone. This is a congressman of the United States and elected representative
he's been a congressman for over a decade. And he's on the banking committee and he can't get
the answers. And like any sense at all. And yet we limp along, but nobody should be surprised
that we're in financial difficulty when we run our fears the way we do. Yes sir, I understand that,
but your congressman, don't you guys have the power to enforce some accountability here?
You would think so. And I'm on the banking committee. Every year I've been in congress. I've been
on the banking committee. I've always been interested in monetary policy. I'm on the domestic monetary
policy subcommittee. But I have no authority whatsoever to look at what the federal reserve does.
And that's, of course, there's a big culprit. But the question you asked earlier about
are the tarp money? That's money appropriate by congress. But they rushed it through to the
river of the panics. They were here in the land. So there were no restrictions placed on the legislation.
And now the congressman, to come up late, say hey, why don't you tell us what you're doing?
And they either don't know or don't want us to know and don't feel compelled to tell us.
But you know, that is that is. The real problem is, is why are we in the business of taking money
one group and handing it out to another group? That's the question. What is that all about?
Keep your eye on the ball because at the end of the day money doesn't matter tonight.
Never, ever has enough to treat as late as right. He does pushes away in a hug.
Says, money don't matter tonight. Mine don't matter tonight. Show it, man. Yes, indeed.
Just when you think you got all that in love, swear it all up and fly the way.
Then when you find out that you're better, I'm thinking sure you're so all right.
Because money didn't matter, he has the day. And a show don't matter tonight.
If they could invest, they'd tell him he just can't lose. So we go out and try to find a bond.
But all it finds are users. All it finds are snakes in every kind of a nationality at size.
Seems like the only thing that he can do is just go to his eye.
Says, money don't matter tonight. Show it, man. Yes, indeed.
Just when you think you got all that in love, swear it all up and fly the way.
Then when you find out that you're better, I'm thinking sure you're so all right.
Because money didn't matter, he has the day. And a show don't matter tonight.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, baby, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, have you, your nonsense, I're ok, pk, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Tell me, do you think you got all that in love?
That's you, where did all of it get lost?
I don't wait, I don't wait
I don't, when you find out that you better love
Think to show your soul, boy
I said, that you saw me home
Money paid, money is the day
The show don't matter tonight
I don't matter tonight
It's show it man
Ah, the man is such a genius
Friends, money don't matter tonight
Sure, that matter yesterday
That depends on how you keep score, I guess
But it is really true, just doesn't matter
And it has a funny way of flying away from you
Just when you think you have enough
To take it from the voice of experience
Up and up and down that roller coaster
Let's see
Oh yes, it is
We do get triple witching just before Christmas
Which is the expiration of all kinds of options
Usually Wall Street looking for what they call the Santa Claus
Rally where stocks go up
I can actually, I can take a quick little look for you
See how the markets are doing at this very moment
Again, this is being recorded on the 23rd of December 2008
Where we see Dow is down 50 points
At the moment it's been down a little bit more than that
So probably not a lot happening today
Over in the advanced police state of the United Kingdom
But in all this get-mownation, these things are heating up
And getting pretty freaking wacky
They talk about bailiffs here
Which I guess you'd almost call that the repo man
In the US
They've been given new powers
Or apparently powers they already had
But they're now being formalized
Where they can break down your door
If you have an overdue debt
An overdue debt like unpaid credit card
Which could happen maybe a car payment
But they will now break down your door
Many examples is reported by the Times of London
As a fact, this is an elderly couple
Which was really a horrible story
Let me see if I can find that
All of these links of course in the show
Know to dailysourcego.com
We're crossposted to curry.com
It's from the Daily Mail
But it's not an elderly couple
Anyway, the Debra missed a payment
Missed one payment
Boom
Bailiff knocks down the door
So they're now allowed to just break in
In the Netherlands, I learned
While I was there over
Over the weekend with the Lady Patricia
I learned that they're now proposing new legislation
Which I'm sure will pass
And if it's happening in one country these days
With the way everything's going
With this one financial and new world government order
It's going to happen everywhere
The IRS will actually be allowed to take money
From your bank account if you are in a rears
So if you owe them money and by the way
The tax guys do mess up a lot
In fact nine out of ten times
That I've been torn apart
Investigated turned upside down inside out
There was no change whatsoever
In one instance there was
There was like a $27,000 difference
But that had to do with an intercontinental exchange of money
And I was wrong they were right
According to their illegal taking of my money
But there you go
It's not constitutional
So now in the it'll start in the Netherlands
If you own the money and if they think they're right
They'll just take it from you
This is impossible anywhere else
In any other form of transaction
Except with the government they'll just take your money
Take it
But thank you very much
And they have all kinds of laws where they can freeze bank accounts
That's one thing because possession
You know as they say is still nine ten to the law
But to actually take that money from your account is pretty disgusting
And headed your way
I found a YouTube clip
It's a Diane Sawyer talking with
Jim Carrey and
Two people with a passion
And Jenny McCarthy
Talking and I just want you to hear this
Because you can hear from someone else from besides me
Their son was born with autism
And it's not very clear how autism
Or where it originates from
If it's genetic, hereditary
You know there's all kinds of theories out there
And they totally believe that it has to do with a combination of things
Including too many vaccinations
And the shit that's in these vaccination shots
And I just want you to listen to a little bit of what Jenny McCarthy says
Because she's saying pretty much exactly what I've been saying
Only she's a little
Well she makes more sense perhaps
And she's a hell of a lot cuter
Listen to this
So it's really good
Cause that has been provocative bringing her praise
Controversy and a higher calling
Three and a half years ago Jenny McCarthy began
What she calls the search for her son's life
I found Evan Seizing his crib
And he was filming at the mouth and his eyes roll back
Doctors first said Evan had epilepsy
But she says her maternal instincts told her something more
A second opinion, the devastating diagnosis
He said
I'm sorry your son has autism
I died
I crumbled
She immediately went online looking for ways to help
Finding a website offering hope with something called
Biomedical intervention
Controversial diet many parents claim was helping their autistic children
Many doctors still skeptical
But she forced ahead putting him on a wheat and dairy-free diet
And two weeks later
Just listen to this
So we changed his diet
Cute kid, by the way
Change his diet
Took him off wheat
Which I'm sure
I'm sure is directly related to genetic
Genetically modified organisms in the food
And dairy
And gosh there's a lot in the dairy products
And miraculous, miraculous change in just two weeks time
He doubled his language
He stopped tantruming, his eye contact got better
And he slept for the night
Through laying in bed and watching a cartoon
He laughed at the abstract joke
And I remember going
Oh my god
I literally start jumping on my bad screaming
I'm pulling out of the window
I'm pulling him out of the window
I see
Judy says
Evan's new diet combined with therapy
And medications allowed him to make a recovery
But doctors now say he was likely never autistic to begin with
That's the way it is
Oh no that was a misdiagnosis
I'm sorry
No no no
All the shit the word ministering your kid
That can't be to blame
And in fact you never had that in the first place
You get your dream in it
And don't it?
She remains an advocate fighting for evidence
Other children
Along the side of the man she calls the autism
Whisperer
And now we are joined by Jenny McCarthy and her partner
The Whisperer himself
I just know play a little bit more of this
Because she really is quite eloquent
And what she says
And listen, particularly to the facts about mercury
That take a harder look
As some tougher questions about the way children are vaccinated
In this country, good morning to both
Good morning, thank you so much for having us
Jenny, I want to get this clear right at the outset
You are not against vaccinations
You want to stress the importance of vaccinations
But you want to walk
My self and the autism community
Really have been saying we are not an anti-vaccine group
We believe that vaccines need to take a closer look at what the ingredients are
And that the schedule is too many, too soon
A lot of people aren't aware that mercury is still in the shots
You'll see report if the report of people saying they have been removed
And it truly hasn't
The FDA still has 11 shots
Still contain mercury
And other ingredients like ether and antifreeze
That we believe
Really played a role in our child's autism
And for a
You a pharmaceutical nuts out there
Chocolate heads of the medical profession
Please explain
What does antifreeze have any business doing
In vaccines
And ammonia and mercury
Why is it in there?
No wonder our kids are for our refer
Screwed in the head
But you know we also believe it's not the sole reason for autism
But it does vaccines do play a major role
Now
Yeah, okay, she's being political there
But it's good, it's good the way she's putting it
You know that they've done a lot in saving lives
But we do know for many children
They are causing damage
People to take a closer look at them
Destroyed a vaccine program
We're here to lend our voices to
The millions of people who are calling for balance
And moderation
When it comes to the substance as we give our children
They're not bottomless pissed
That you can endlessly pour these substances
Absolutely
You have to consider the cumulative effect
Not only that
But the possible interaction
Every other drug has interactions with other drugs
And yet they assume that vaccines won't
I can't appalling
You know there was shoes administered
Eight shots and one visit
And you know part of this rally is just
It's interesting because I'm looking at Diane
So her she's almost looking annoyed
While they're talking
It's on a split screen
And she really is making annoyed face
You know speak up parents
Space the shots out
We're not saying get rid of them
Slow down
Yeah, we'll get rid of a couple of them
Absolutely
There's a lot of stuff
Like the anti-servical
Cancer drug which doesn't actually
Solve or fix or prevent against cancer
And contains all this crap heavy metals mercury
And right as you can
Killing and paralyzing young girls
The scientific community has said
In many cases there isn't
No chemical of any kind in the vaccine
But also if it's there it's in a modified or very small dose
That's exactly right
That's what they say
It's not there
And if it is it's modified or it's a very small dose
It's like the melamine in your milk
It's okay
The FDA has approved 2.25 parts per million
It's a little bit is okay
You're not going to die from that
Just a little bit
What is it doing there in the first place
What a point out something Jenny
That I read is this right
That in the 1980s
Little children were given only ten vaccines at a time
And now they're given 36
Man 36 vaccines
If they're not out to kill us
They're certainly making a killing off of us
Off of our kids
36 vaccines
Nuts
All right
One more link I'd like you to take a look at
Which I'm not going to read through right now
But is a very interesting read from Voltairenet.org
Which I'd never visited before
The title of it is called Operation Sarcosi
This is about the French president
Who was up until the middle of this month
Also the president of the European Union
That has now been transferred over to the Czech Republic
Which is by self is interesting
Operation Sarcosi
How the CIA placed one of its agents
At the presidency of the French Republic
And it's a fascinating, fascinating article
About Sarcosi
His connections to the mob
How the mob
Operated with
These are how we're going back to Charles the Gaul time now
The CIA integrated with NATO
I mean you know how Sarcosi used funds from
Multiple sources including from the elf group
Which today is known as total big oil
And
And how Sarcosi is consistently used
The gossip press to cover up big issues
That we're going on around him
And they've really said this article
Really says that his whole marriage to Carla
Bruni is a complete scam
And look at pictures of that girl
Will ya?
Take a look at some pictures
And tell me she isn't like a bit glossy eyed
Let's play a song of hope
A song with a message
From a man I miss very, very dearly
To a Frederick Mercury
Listen to the lyrics Chuckleheads or Google him
In you window
The unimitable queen on the chart
While the sun hangs in the sky
And the desert has set
While the waves crashing the sea
We can land
While the wind in the stars
And the rainbow
Till the mountains grow up
And it's late
Oh
Yes
We'll keep on crying
Spread them behind
Oh
We'll keep on crying
Yeah
Just lost in us
Oh
While we live and calling to race
Cut our creed
While we rule my life
And there's no creed
I like dictated by tradition
Superstition
More brilliant
A brilliant young man
And our
Oh
Yes
We'll keep on crying
Oh
So the end of time
Till the end of time
Until the end of time
You can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't be anything you want to do, you can't
to be just a yours of adventure and you need to get up, free free maltempt free free free reerventa yo na ready free free free be your son
This is a God already kind of justice under the sky
If there's a voice, if there's a reason to live under
If there's an answer to the question, if there's a word to ask
So yes, this drop is, please, you may ask
Oh yes, you keep on trying
Hey, let's run from the valley
We'll be
Please
If you went down
Reven up
Did the source code 812
Save her your freedom, my friends
There are no secrets, only information you don't yet have
And whatever you do, live your life with passion
There is a war going on for your mind
Idiom, mavens, mouth surgical strikes from tropicalisis and online magazine racks
Cover girl cutouts through a pop-a-beds infecting victims with silicone shredder
World by past, your business, the point territory is now its rainy pornography lovers take shelter
Post production, every time to pursue you and mask our chariot
They construct ransom letters from typical taxes and bleed mask air into the holy water supply
There is a war going on to your mind
Industry inside a slaying test to babies to quote me crack hits
They clash logos and blast getoes
They're avoided neck die say stop situation
Conscious rappers and whistleblowers get stitches made of actu function
Heels and Mary and Ed Strings
There is a war going on to your mind
Professional wrestlers and ice presidents want you to believe
The desert sky is their blue screen. They superimpose explosions. They shout at you
Pay no attention to the main behind the mark turn
You're the greatest beneath the tree flag
Those who are today we are protection immediately say to the size of corpses
There is a war going on to your mind
We are the insurgents
Remember to listen to the best of year and 2008 Charlie brought to you by a ray
That will be on the feed between Christmas and New Year's
And I wish you a Merry Christmas
Another fine, medium presentation
Stick it in your ear