The 60 million dollars worth of their plan strapped by us, 3 meters to the next generation
we do content in my ears.
We don't need no speaking friends, me and I like to think I'm flying into this church.
Augusti!
This man!
Don't the Cherichardly 790, a milestone program in the common collective of the chuckleheads.
I won't say anything.
It came that took it all away,
the main highlight of all day and night.
I'll always listen before you stop to revenge.
That seemed to be something, but the way I was and before me,
You're a bit of grotesque
So many mistakes
You're the man that's trying to jump
Like it always is in me
Talking about you, this is you
While you're on dreaming
That's a little I love to see you
While you're on dreaming the other way
They'll take your light to all you're on, I'll hear
Because I'm inside of you
Maybe you'll never hear
Your touch makes the heart
Everything you want to do
When I'm inside of you
Like it always is in me
Just talking about you, this is you
You're a bit of your summer
But you don't care about me
I don't care about you
I do what I need you
I don't keep doing
Doing it, doing it, doing it, doing it
Doing it, doing it, doing it until we're gone
We're going, we're going, we're going
I know what I'm doing, I never waited with the night
I know how it is to always walk out in the night
And it's an answer jump, turn out of that book again
It's an answer jump, hang on to my dear eye
You don't know what I'm doing, I know what I'm doing
I know what you're doing, I never waited with the night
And it's an answer jump, turn out of that book again
It's an answer jump, hang on to my dear eye
You don't know what I'm doing, I never waited with the night
And it's an answer jump, turn out of that book again
And it's an answer jump
You don't know what I'm doing, I never waited with the night
And it's an answer jump, turn out of that book again
It's an answer jump, turn out of that book again
You don't know what I'm doing, another beauty full day today
We had a great weekend, a great Monday
And typically I don't do a show on Mondays
But I really felt compelled to talk with you guys
Because I had some interesting things happen over the weekend
Not just interesting, really important milestones
The first one, really took place just before the weekend
I got a link, which I believe was on the source code drop.
Drop.io slash daily source code
That pointed to a new story about documentary
An Italian documentary about 911
And this thing is called zero
An investigation into 911
Of course a link and a bedded link in the show notes
A daily source code dot com and curry dot com
As far and wide as I can spread this
This is the first documentary that I really
When I looked at this and I've seen a lot of these individual bits
It was done in Italian, which is interesting
Because they have a number of Italian experts
And they have an England in this version that I've posted for you
There's an England English British narrative voiceover
That does the voiceover for the Italian bits
But it's a lot of stuff that I've already seen
And it was without a doubt
In fact, I sent this to a couple of people who I've never sent
Any 911 truth videos to at all
Because it has a number of experts
Many of whom I've already seen in different material
Available online
That really debunks the official conspiracy theory
Because that's what it is
The 911 Commission report is a conspiracy theory
It's the official one
Of course does not drive at all with the alternative theories that are out there
And what I like the most about this documentary
Is that it includes my favorite pieces of evidence about
The so-called plain that allegedly flew into the Pentagon
And this is completely debunked
And wildly fantastically and accurately debunked
That conspiracy theory, the official version
By the pilots for 911 Truth.org
Which as I was telling John C. Devorek on Saturdays
We were recording no agenda episode 47
I may not know a lot about architectural issues
I may not know the exact temperatures
The steel melts at
I may not understand how pancake theories
And all kinds of other
Non-demolition
Non-demolition building collapses
How they work
But I do know a thing or two about flying
And the evidence is extremely clear
That the flight data recorder from the flight that supposedly hit the Pentagon shows
And proves this is data coming from the National Transportation Safety Board
Which by the way, I'm fairly convinced it's Dr. Devon
And that's how stupid they are
But it shows that the plane flew over
The Pentagon by about 480 feet
And this is because they messed up when doctoring the tape
They forgot to set the pressure setting for that day
Which of course is historical evidence which we know
And so it decides multiple very experienced airmen coming out
And saying, besides that the maneuver that was made
Is impossible to make for the most experienced pilot
The speed that was registered at the low altitude
Is physically impossible
It is physically impossible, okay?
Physics, there's a lot of physics
But at least the NIST is not trying to debunk these physics yet
With more dumb and bad and fraudulent signs
So this documentary really got me excited
Because this is now something I'm going to show to my wife
To my daughter, this is something I would not be ashamed
To show at a gathering at a party
And when I say ashamed with that I mean that
It is so non-refutable
And the experts that talk about what is going on
And what has happened and what really happened
Is so strong and so convincing
That there would be no discussion
Based on fuzzy shaky video footage
You know all of these documentaries
Although good in their own right
There's a high amount of drama
And it gets people very confused
When you see professionals lecturing
And showing empirical evidence
It really changes the game
So I'm loving this documentary
The new story by the way
And obviously I'm going to see if I couldn't find it
Before I take the report of the show today
The new story that I picked up
Was saying how even show business friends
Of French president and current European president
Nicholas Sarcosi were making jokes
About how stupid we are
How lame ass we are as Americans
That we're letting our government do this to us
Same type of noises coming out of Italy as well
And I'm thinking man just leave it to the Italians
To show us how lame actually are
Then I hadn't seen the documentary
I'd only read this link
And I was planning on taking a look at it
And then I did no agenda
Number 47 with John C. Dvorak
And at a certain point
The conversation turned to him
Quaring me
For the first time I believe he actually asked me
Outright if I was a so-called
Truther
A 911 Truther
And I said yes I am absolutely a Truther
And he started his normal
Scoff and guffying
And the typical ridicule
Which is okay because
We have a lot of respect for each other
And that's just his opinion
But then I started to lay some facts on him
Some facts which are particularly from
Pilots for 911 Truth.org
Which
Really turned him not around
But I could hear it got him thinking
And John is an arrogant old bastard
And very set in his ways
And very opinionated
And it was quite a personal
I don't want to say it was a victory
But it was so extremely satisfying
To finally have used some of the evidence
That millions of people at this point
Worldwide are now becoming aware of
And for him to actually start thinking it over
And of course I sent him a link
He hasn't commented on the documentary
But after the show I sent him a link
But it was so spectacular
And it was really kind of towards the end of the show
That I got really excited about
And like man if I can turn this guy around
If I can wake him up
Because he sees all the evil ways
Of the thugs that run the world
The true owners of the earth
And a lot of that is
We cover in financial news
But I really got to him
And I got me extremely excited
And really made me want to pass on this
Particularly this information
This evidence and this documentary is far
And why it is possible
And then something else happened
On Sunday
My true friends
A comic strip blogger
And the candy man who do an answer
Show to know a gender
Which you may have heard of
I know I've talked about it
Before on the daily source code
It's called Yo Agenda
And typically this show is
They just kind of refute everything
And I listen to it religiously
And here's the reason why
Because it really helps me understand
How to communicate better
Because so often I'll hear them pick up
On something that was said
And pick up a totally incorrect
And sometimes 180 degree opposite
Meaning of what was said on the show
That it's very important for me
To learn how to communicate better
Essentially
And I wish I had an answer
Show for the daily source code
I mean wow it's so helpful
Now
I don't talk about it
About that program typically
Because it's
Now they say a lot of
Mean, often hateful, personal things
I know they don't mean it
I know it's all taken in just
And
And obviously a lot of things
They say are just completely incorrect
And not at all what
What was discussed
Or what the intent of a discussion was
And you know
John and I have both been called
Pretty nasty names by these guys
But they are my true friends
Because they are saying
What they truly believe is right
And what was interesting about this
Most recent episode
Now the no agenda
Number 47 was about
Almost two hours this week
It was a long one
But it was jam packed
And that show was meant to be long
And no agenda
A yoga agenda
Was longer than usual
As well
In fact it was about
They had minutes typically
They do around 30
And they even play a song
And those 30 minutes
And what blew me away
Is that they were talking about
All kinds of stuff
Particularly about me
And about me, and about me,
And how I'm distracted
And how I'm not
And I'm crazy
But they didn't for one second
Talk at all
About this evidence that I laid down
And what I was hearing
Was listening to the show
Was my God
I got to them
And they are so
Conflicted internally
They can't actually bring themselves
To speak about
This empirical evidence
That 911
The attack on the towers
The Pentagon
That it was an inside job
It was controlled
By the American government
It was what someone called
A false flag operation
And it is far and wide
And it is extremely vast
What a crime
That has taken place here
A global crime
It wasn't just Americans in these towers
And they couldn't bring themselves
To discuss the topic
Even though that was
Without a doubt
The climax
And the most important part of the program
I'm presuming they heard the whole thing
And it's funny
Because
They had sent me a promo
And I said
Getting to the week
Or maybe even last week
I said, hey
People drop a promo
That hasn't happened in a while
People aren't sending me promo
It hasn't, of course, promo
Start showing up
And so they sent me a promo
For yo agenda
Which I didn't listen to
Until the
This morning
Because I got it late
And we don't play promos
I know agenda
And I think I got to put that in the next
Daily source code
And then I hear the actual promo
And I want you to take a listen to this
Because
It's just
It's amazing
Listen to this
So you love
No agenda
Podcast
Or maybe you hate it
People are afraid of their feelings
And feelings are disturbing and painful
But how can you deal with love
If you are afraid to feel
Pain is meant to wake us up
So don't be ashamed
Stand up for your rights
To feel your pain
And visit your agenda
And listen to it
Put us about an agenda
Yo
So normally I would not even
Play that promo
After the show they put out this week
Because it had nothing to do with
A comment or a bottle
To anything discussed on no agenda
I mean almost nothing
It was just all personal bashing stuff
Which is okay again
I don't mind
And normally they do
As I said they do have a good
You know
A good show that sticks to the topic
If you listen to that promo
I mean that is the actual
Projection of what they're feeling
And I'm here to say to my real friends
So Candyman comic string blogger
But really all chuckle heads
It is okay
It is okay to now say
That you have
Feelings about this monstrosity
That you feel that something is a miss
That you
You may not know it
You may not be able to put your finger on it
But firstly it's okay to just say it
It is okay
You're no longer going to be ridiculed for this
Because around the world
All the way up to
The highest levels of government
People are now talking about this
The mainstream media
We'll not discuss it
We'll not show any of these videos
But it's okay for you to start
Investigating and start talking about it with your friends
It's now seven years on
And the time has come to do this
Please
If you can download this documentary
Burn it to a DVD
Let people see this
Send them the links from YouTube
And Google video
Let them see that there is
An alternative conspiracy theory
To the official conspiracy theory
And if you want
You can just point them to me and say
Here's someone else who thinks there's something going on
You can point them to thousands of places online
Thousands literally
So
This is really this is really fantastic
I'm just getting reports from around the globe
The people are waking up
More and more people are saying
Wait a minute this can't be right
There's now book in the top ten of the New York Times
Best Seller List by a very accomplished prosecutor
The United States
I believe the title is
Prosecuting George Bush for murder
Not a single bit of exposure on television
Anywhere still top ten New York Times Best Seller List
All the polls that are being taken now
80 sometimes 90% people are saying
Yes, I believe that there was something wrong
About the explanation of 911
And it's okay to come out and say it now
Of course this happened seven years ago
And it's taken us seven years for this collective awakening
Which is now taking place and it's really running quite fast
And I believe you are going to see more and more show up
In mainstream media
Certainly in newspapers
That's probably what you'll see a lot of this come first
But you're still going to have to be a part of the alternative media distribution
Network which goes beyond the internet
And the best way is I love giving out DVDs
It's really cheap to make
You can buy a whole stack of CDs for empty DVDs
For a pretty low cost
And you can just hand them out to people
And it's okay all of these truth videos
911 truth or videos are okay with you handing it out
You might want to check the copyright notice
Just to make sure but as far as I can tell everyone is on board with that
No one's making money with this
People just doing it to get the information out
Get the word out and start waking people up
But seven years after the fact and they have
Advait they
Okay in this case let's just focus on George Bush and particularly Dick Cheney
They have already advanced their agenda so far
We've seen what's happened in South Assetia
With the Americans
Basically train the Georgians
Gave them weapons, gave them security consultants
Which is another term for mercenaries
They attack South Assetia
Georgia retaliated
That was not part of the plan now they're getting ready for a war in Iran
Which looks like this going to be a ground war as well
Now as tanks are being moved into Afghanistan
Where there have no use the only use for them would be
Indeed to drive up the road across the border into Iran
And it's all interconnected right into the financial crisis
Which is taking place in front of our very eyes over the weekend
Filed for bankruptcy chapter 11
We've had Merrill Lynch being sold to Bank of America
And now there are huge put options on city group
So that may be the next target to be taken down
It's all interconnected all of this is a part of the same system all of it being orchestrated by a reasonably small
Number of people
But it's all the same and you know who they are you know how they're connected and they are so connected
To each other even through family bloodlines they're connected
It's just amazing
So one of the ways to fix a financial crisis is to start a war
This has been done over and over again
The true owners of the earth love starting wars because they make money on both sides by lending money
Which subsequently is make to use to make weaponry and sell weaponry
And another way of course is
Through drug trade you'll see that to start to rise again
As it's just another form of currency that is used
And I don't want to get into deep everything because I'm already so excited
That we can lift the veil on lift the veil just a little bit on this horrible event
That took place seven years ago
And there's so much has happened in between so much that we have to combat so much that we have to
Open up our eyes to and it's not just my responsibility
It's all of our responsibilities to help wake people up
So go get the go get this documentary again
It's embedded in the link to links are all in the show notes at dailysourceco.com
As well as at curry.com
You can show this
It's it's low on drama
Well, there is some drama in there obviously for effect
But still it's really easy to understand it's empirical evidence
It's evidence that everyone just cannot avoid
And I really urge you really really urge you now that you're starting to wake up to get other people on board as well
It's absolutely essential that we do this
Alright, so that was the message for this Monday September 5th 2008
And I'll leave you now with a message from the musical genius himself as Eddie Murphy once said
Stevie Wonder loves a need of love today
This has to
Could change your joy and laughter
To tears and may
It's that love
And need
Of love today
Don't delay
I'll send yours in right away
Hey
For now
We can many homes
Stop
Bit me
Before it's gone too long
Oh
The boss of evil land
To make you its possession
And it will if we met it
Run, bring in many hearts
No, nothing to be
Oh, it's gone
Stop till you cross, love
In me, oh, love, pain
Oh, it's gone today
So it wasn't right away
You know that hate
It's going wrong
Breaking, it's tried to break my heart
No, no, no
You've got a strategy
It's gone before we both
We both
Oh, it's gone today
So it wasn't right away
You know that hate
It's gone right
It's gone right away
You know that hate
It's gone
You've got a strategy
It's gone before we both
We both
Oh, it's gone
So it wasn't right away
You know that hate
It's gone
Oh, it's gone
So it wasn't right away
Breaking, it's gone
Oh, it's gone
So it wasn't right away
You know that hate
It's gone
So it wasn't right away
You know that hate
It's gone
So it wasn't right away
You know that hate
It's gone
Yeah, yeah, yeah
No, no, no, no
Yeah, yeah
That's enough
No, no, no, no
Oh, it's gone
That's right
That's what we need
Oh, it's gone
Download that documentary
My friends chuckle heads spread it far and wide
Send links out
Let everyone know
Help your friends, neighbors
And family wake up to the truth
And as always
Why still have your freedom
Enjoy it
And please live your life with passion
Another fine, medial presentation
Stick it in your ear
Oh, it's gone