ONE FRrode
$16 million worth of airplane straps by S
And the next generation radio content in my ears
No, I said that I can't fix it
I'd like to think I'm shring into the future
Since taking pity this now
ительно, the sheer chart is a size
but I'm 27 to 9 humanity
Oh
give them a b****
Finally lies from the other side
Power into the darkness
Stand up and fight with your eyes
Freedom
We're talking about your freedom
Freedom to choose what you do with your body
Freedom to believe what you like
Freedom for brothers to love one another
Freedom for black and white
Freedom from elitism, male from nation
Freedom for the mother and wife
Freedom for big brothers, in segregation
Freedom to live your own life
Power into the darkness
Fire in lies from the other side
Stand up and fight with your eyes
Freedom for black and white
Freedom and wife
ina
Freedom for black and white
Freedom for white
The Holy Institute of Marriage, even our magnificent police force,
a no longer safe from those who would undermine our society.
And it's about time we said enough is enough.
It's all return to the traditional British values of discipline,
obedience, morality and freedom.
Freedom, the reds and the blacks and the criminals,
prostitutes, pansies and punks,
football, who ligands, juvenile delinquents,
lesbians and left-wing scum.
Freedom's from the niggers and the precies and the unions,
freedom's from the gypsies and the Jews.
Freedom's from the long-hand, lay about some students,
freedom's from the likes of you.
Freedom, the reds and the blacks,
freedom's from the gypsies,
freedom's from the gypsy,
The affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Bielford, and still funky weather with those Atlantic
storms going on here, which of course with Hurricane Ike now nearing the Gulf Coast
of Texas, we're getting more of those Atlantic storms.
And of course my thoughts are going out to everyone on the Gulf Coast seems, of course,
this is rarely, rarely getting the attention that I forgot even the name of Moza, well,
I don't even remember the name of the hurricane that was going to hit Louisiana.
See how fast it goes?
It seems like it's just not getting the same amount of attention, you know, it's like
the news media say, oh, well, you know, it could probably slow down or I guess until
they get really the photos, you know, if it bleeds it leads, that's when it'll really spark
off.
Anyway, it is Friday.
It's the Fubar Friday where fucked up beyond all repair or recognition as you prefer.
I want to say hi to everyone in the Netherlands listening, the former arrowheads, now
chuckleheads, who are joining our family, our community, which of course helps me aggregate
every single, each and every single show by throwing it into the drop drop.io slash daily
source code.
Man, you guys put together a doozy for me once again.
And by the way, I apologize, this is only the second show of the week, but man, it's just,
you know, I stopped doing this morning radio show in the Netherlands, and it really didn't
buy me that much extra production time because typically, I mean, it just, I get to sleep
a little bit longer.
I'd be getting up at 4am, do the show from 5 until 9am, and, you know, then chill out
for an hour or so.
And then I'd start working on the, you know, the regular day stuff, and of course, the
biggest problem was in the evening hours when San Francisco was up and up and about.
That starts around 430 p.m. London time, which is 830 a.m. San Francisco.
You know, and that could go to 910, 1030 11, and of course, that's really where I was
cutting into the lifestyle because I was just wasn't getting enough sleep, but it's not
like I actually have, you know, all that much more time on my hands during the waking
hours, and actually been spending a lot of time with me via, we got a lot of new stuff
that were actually Monday, we're coming out, I think, with a new version of the site,
Monday, maybe Monday, evening, Pacific Standard Time, so it's been busy, it really has
end the lady Patricia is off on one of her johns, she's a judge on another fabulous show.
This one's called pop stars. So you made maybe, I don't know if the show was in America,
it was a big hit in the UK, many countries in the world where it's done quite quite well.
And this is all about singing, so it's a little bit, you know, it's actually 100% up
or alley, and she's enjoying it. And that's the most important thing. But of course,
she's gone for a week, so I'm taking care of the, the Moranic teenager.
Every single night, I'm going to go out now. Are we going to go, I'm going to go to the pub.
She doesn't really drink, you know, she'll have like half a, a Cardi Briser, maybe.
But, uh, uh, she says, yeah, because I'm legal now, I can do whatever I want. I'm legal.
Oh, kids, I tell you, but she's been good. She's been there. She's really been helping
out this time around, uh, with some of the chores around the house. Man, the house is just too big.
And the lady piece looking for a place in London, which I'm looking forward to, because hopefully
it'll be something a little bit smaller. We really don't need all that much room now that, uh,
the teenagers legal and, you know, just kind of basically hangs out to eat my food,
I sleep in, uh, in my house, and invite all our friends over to do the same. Anyway,
it's been, uh, it's really been a fantastic week. Um, and I've been, uh, doing a lot of research, uh,
in the evening hours, you know, watching a lot of Fox News, CNN, Russia today, uh,
CNBC, CNBC is, it's just fantastic. And of course, uh, the show, the closing bell with Maria
Bartiromo comes on around, I think you're not six or seven, 30. Maybe even 8 or 8, 30. Anyway,
it's in the evening hours. I always seem to catch it. And you can just see the dismay on everybody's face.
And they have nothing to say. They absolutely, you know, no one has any insights, no one knows
what to do, what to say, because they're all seeing it crumbling before they're very eyes. Obviously,
this all started with the, well, it started a long time ago, but, uh, the effective nationalization
of a phanny may and Freddie Mac, which I did want to mention, by the way, uh, for the UK folks,
you must be snickering every single time you hear that on the news, phanny may. You know, when I grew,
uh, a phanny was your backside was your butt. And my mom was, I'm, I'm going to spank your phanny.
In the UK, however, I learned, uh, well, only a couple of years ago, we moved here that phanny,
is actually, uh, it's a slang word for vagina. Uh, probably, it's probably more
equatable to pussy. Because I have heard them say it on television, you know, oh, well,
something happened with my phanny. I just, this is so weird. Uh, really, uh,
common, uh, two two countries they're separated by a common language, huh? Anyway, so, um,
you probably heard about Lehman Brothers. Now, this is one of the true old, uh, I'd almost call them
a Luminati firm, um, who, uh, had this huge, real estate portfolio, huge portfolio of mortgage
back to assets. There you go. Uh, and, you know, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, when you really follow
the money, it's so easy to see why all of this is falling apart. Because basically no one's lending,
no one has any. And now shareholders, they are kind of tapped out as well. Even the sovereign wealth funds,
you know, the only way they can put more money into the kitty is by printing it. That's just,
uh, in China. And Lehman Brothers dropped significantly. They're kind of in that same spiral that
Bear Stearns was in. Once, you know, once the rumor gets out and once people start talking, I mean,
that's basically the end of it. And, uh, we'll see maybe to, maybe even today after the, this show
goes up or maybe next week, I think Lehman, uh, they'll be bought for, uh, for a couple of pennies.
Now, Merrill Lynch, another one of the big, the big boys, their shares fell 17% on Thursday.
Same, uh, same type of thing that, uh, that Lehman Brothers is going through. These, these are big
firms. These are the, the, the, the, the, the monoliths. In fact, they're not the only monolith. And again,
I'm, uh, I'm just taking mainstream news reports. This is from Reuters. Uh, this next one is, uh,
from Motley Fool. All the links in the show notes. I mean, I'm not making it up. This is not,
wacky conspiracy stuff. It's just news that is reported on by some really good reporters,
but the trick is is to aggregate all these stories together so you can connect the dots because
mainstream media, particularly the news media is not going to put this up there for you. Then
not going to lay it all out because it's, it's not in the interest of the corporations. Of course,
only a few corporations really own the media. As we all know, it's, it's, and I'm not just saying
it, it's the truth. Go look it up. Do some research. So this independent media is extremely
important. Next one to go, uh, could possibly be Washington, Mutual. Uh, this is, uh, this is,
this is pretty scary because this is, in fact, I'm reading an article here from Motley Fool.
Uh, an ill-timed venture into subprime has left Washington, uh, Mutual's books looking like
they just got hit by a nuclear bomb. How's that for an analogy? Last quarter,
net charge offs came in and more than three and a half percent escorted by a $3.3 billion loss
and a supernova. I'd love this. It's not the full guys. A supernova of loan loss provisions
to nearly $6 billion. At the end of last quarter, Washington, Mutual, uh, held more than 60,
$6 billion in home equity loans and lines of credit. And if you think that, uh, this takeover,
this, uh, nationalization, this, uh, basically socialist, if not communist move, completely
on American, if you think that's going to save anything or anybody, um, briefly, only so that
everyone could bail out. And we're going to talk about that a little bit, uh, a little bit later
because, uh, well, I, I think there's, uh, I think there's, uh, I think there's a few things that, um,
that need to be, uh, linked together. One more story here from blue bloomberg.com.
Uh, this is the true cost of this, uh, phanny may Freddie Mac or, I like to call them fraughty and phony.
What the true cost will be. And this is because the oversight, uh, is the oversight board, which is an
independent, uh, uh, the organization. It's not a part of the government. They're basically,
say, hey, you know, um, you guys, you, when you take over these companies, you actually have to put
that, you know, the debt of those two companies onto the books of the United States. So the United
States now has, I believe, nine or $10 trillion in debt, which we owe to foreign, uh, countries mainly,
and some big ones like China. And, uh, that just might be opt significantly by, uh,
well, at least 50% because the oversight board says, you know what, um, that's 5.2 trillion in debt
on phanny may and Freddie Mac's books. They need to be on the United States's books as well. And, uh,
for, you know, there's, there's not a lot of news about this. I'm trying to find it here and
their Bloomberg is the one that's really, uh, following the story and reporting on link in the
show notes, of course, a daily source code.com. But their, a Bloomberg is saying, you know, this
actually could be true. It may have to go on to the, onto the books, which means we now have
14 or 15 trillion dollars worth of debt. Um, and, uh, and, and these, and it's, it's, it's interesting to
watch, uh, they have, um, you know, if you buy government or treasury bonds, and now phanny may
in Freddie Mac are essentially exactly the same. They're priced the same. They're, they're valued
the same way. Uh, but there's a spread, which you have to pay to ensure we don't have to ensure,
but which most, uh, good investors do, and certainly the banks, is they want to ensure that, you know,
so they have this debt. So let's say $10 million worth of debt from phanny may Freddie Mac,
and you can sure against it. And at one point, it was, I believe around $70,000 to ensure $10 million
of debt. Now that has popped up to, uh, essentially $700,000 to ensure $10 million worth of debt,
because the, uh, United States is not seen as credit worthy anymore. We don't have the goal to back
it up. And we could certainly do fine on our own, but this system has to end. You know, we need
a massive reboot. And the big question is, who's going to control the reboot? Because it's
going to happen. You know, when you have your computer and whether it's Windows, even a Mac, you know,
sometimes you can say, oh, shit, man, I know it's going to happen. It's going to freeze. And then it
does. And then there's only one of two things that can happen either. You're going to do a control
all delete or you're going to hold down the power button on the Mac, which is the way it works on
the Mac. You know, we lead one finger, one finger operation to make my Mac come back to life.
Or you'll know sometimes what it's just like, explodes almost and it reboots by itself. So what's
going to happen? And who's going to be in charge of it? Because we have a presidential election coming
up very, very soon. Or as many have often said, do you think that George W Bush and the Bush administration
might actually use this to postpone the elections under Marshall Law? There's a lot of talk about it.
I have no proof that it's going to happen that way. But oh, man, it's an interesting thought.
So again, these, this bailout of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, you know, as far as I'm concerned,
it really was, well, obviously it had to be done because the whole system was going to come down
worldwide. And there's just too much pressure. Although I think that probably would have been a
reasonable alternative because we just got to go through it. We're going to have to go through the
pain. There's no two ways about it. But people are trying to save themselves and better yet
they're trying to save their own hides or their interest or corporate interest. And there's one
guy who I often bring into the show, not really by invitation, but I do pay to get his video.
So I don't feel too bad about playing the audio from one. It's the kid from Brooklyn who has a
very unique take on exactly what's going on in the United States of America and the world
when it comes to finances. Hey, the big man's back. WWE that the kid from Brooklyn that
got. I keep telling you the world's coming to an end. I mean, come on, give me a break, George Bush.
He bailed out Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, but truly isn't out. Is that me? Come on,
would he bail out George Bush's shop if Joe went broke and bankrupt and had three kids in a
wife and couldn't pay the mortgage on his house? No, we wouldn't. But he bailed out all these
billion dollar companies. Not only that, the head CEO's that he's companies are getting compensation pay
over 40 million dollars a piece. Let me come on. The world's coming to an end. Why don't the
people in this country say something? Nobody says nothing. The rules really. I mean, I'd be out there
writing it in a streets now. Don't show people understand. The United States of America is broke
with Brooklyn busted. We all want three dollars. We can borrow no more. You know the dollars
work today in a farm and country. Don't eat sense. The American currency ain't worth nothing
no more. But nobody. Nobody says anything. I'd be out there now and Washington DC. The true
home of all guys crying. Ryan would mean some people had to come on. What's going on here in the
world. The government won't work for the people. The government works for all these special
interests and corporations. They don't work for me and you, the people. They work for these
rent passes. They run people for three years of dollars. I'm tired of this fucking shit. I want
to eat people say something. I want the whole world on a revolution here. We can't let this
go on. This is the device. What do you raise space? What do you weigh? Think about it. This is
the big man. The voice. The voice of people that's right. Twenty cents on a fucking dollar
and a big man's always happy to see. I love anger. What a beautiful emotion. The kid from
Brooklyn tells it and tells it straight. But yeah, that's right. We're not out there writing.
We're not outrage because it's not being told. We don't know the story. If you know someone who's not
awake yet, hand them a copy of this show. Turn them on to one of the many other shows that talk
about what's really going on in the world. The true reality, the real truth. And I know it's weird
to understand and weird to even comprehend because you think to yourself, no one could really be
that evil. Unfortunately, it's just the way it is. Now, it doesn't matter. I'm not here to
bum you out to bring you into put you into bad mood, particularly for the weekend because this is
all good. It's all good. The direction we're headed because we're waking up. We're understanding
what's happening. We're talking about it amongst ourselves with our friends, our family,
our colleagues, it's school. I hear Christina talk about it with her friends all the time. That's
specifically to this detail that we're talking about here on the show. But she's not oblivious
and she doesn't watch television. And that's really, really important. And we have to protect our
internet's at all cost because that's what they're coming for. I don't think they actually can come
for it. But you watch when I've all kinds of tracking installed. It's going to start in the United
Kingdom first. In fact, it has already started. You know about all the cameras. You know about
the random searches on the street in the subways, the tubes. And I saw someone get in search
randomly at Waterloo Station just yesterday. And it was interesting because after my trip into town
had a couple meetings, I was walking up the back steps to Waterloo Station. Actually, it's the
front steps, but it's not where the taxi cabs are. So you come in like a track 16 or whatever.
And there was, I don't know if there was two guys fighting on the street. And they weren't fighting
there. We're yelling at each other. And just as I was crossing the street, so I'm aware of what's
going on. Like, okay, I'm just going to keep walking and see what's going and see if anyone needs
some help. So I did turn around and stood for a second and looked like these guys. I don't know if
they're going to go out at or not, but they were yelling shouting then within seconds. Like a police
bus, a patty wagon. Like screeches to a halt. Three cops jump out. They jump on these guys and they're
kicking them. Like I see them being this guy in the back. And for what? You know, so they were
yelling at each other. You could have just calm down the situation. It was a real face-to-face
reality check for me for a moment there. Anyway, it's as I'm saying, it's this is good because
we're waking up and once enough people are awake, then we can actually start changing things. And we
will, but still a lot of crap to go through first. And you know what? Just by exposing you to the
real truth and to the information that's out there being reported by mainstream media. This is
not just stuff out there that's on the internet. Yeah, these are by real reporters doing real reporting
work. Just back to the Fannie Mae Freddie Mac bailout for a second. So I'm pretty sure on Tuesday
we talked about this that the London Stock Exchange suffered a computer bug, which they still
have not actually told anyone about, identified what exactly the problem was. You know, something
that couldn't have been for seeing, but now that we fix it, it'll never happen again. So I've seen
some blogs out there saying, well, you know, this thing was running on Microsoft.net, that's why,
you know, it should have been on Linux servers, then it wouldn't have been okay. Let me tell you,
I've been around a lot of trading systems. And yeah, a lot of it's built on on some off the shelf
quote, off the shelf stuff like Microsoft SQL Server, but also Oracle. And these guys are not stupid.
Okay, shit like this does not go down for seven hours. Unless there's as far as I'm concerned,
unless there's sabotage involved. So I wanted to add one extra thing to this story,
because I found this only after I'd done Tuesday show that the, and I saw it in a very small
mention about some, you know, because of course, everyone over in the UK was like freaking out,
because this was their opportunity to make a lot of money. Some people made a billion dollars on
Monday because they knew all the financial stocks would be a huge bump. Everyone's getting out
personally. That's exactly what that was all about. And I believe that they sabotage the London
Stock Exchange, except there was one trading system under new regulation, go figure out. New regulation
has allowed private trading systems or black hole pools as they're also known. As long as there's no
more than 500 people connected to the trading system. So I read this, I was reading this article
about the London Stock Exchange, and that, you know, I was really pissed off that couldn't trade,
except some trades are being executed on turquoise. And turquoise is a trading system, which was
just set up by here comes, Maryland, Lehman, all the big boys. It's their own private trading
system. And that was working just fine. Thank you very much. Not only that, it was the first official
launch day, the first official launch day. And then I found another story. So that was the ninth
on September's second. That was one week before. I'll just read from this. This is from financialnews.com.
Turquoise, the European equity trading system set for launch next week suffered. It's first
technical glitch. Well, testing yesterday as a firewall crash, leaving some brokers,
unable to trade for a few minutes. So they had a little problem. They fixed it. And they probably
took that little problem and spewed it onto the London Stock Exchange, because believe me, these guys
made a killing. They were the only ones able to trade. Links in the show now to DaddySourceco.com.
I know you're going to appreciate reading this whole story because it just shows you more of what's
really going on now. You know, these guys, they can't, they're fighting each other. This is how
bad it's gotten. Like they're stealing from each other. Everyone's trying to bail out themselves.
First above anything else. And I found an awesome song on the drop, which comes from the mad
money machine, which I want to play for you right now. It's so in line with all this. It's called
The Dead Prison Blues. It's here on Daily Sourceco 788.
Well, it's just a baby. I'm on this city. Always be a good boy. Don't play with activities,
but I bought some shares of fannings. Just to watch them slide.
When night flows and bells starts ringing, I might head in a grime.
I've met the politicians and the bankers and the fair. Got out of the market before
everything went red. Well, I know I had a comment. I know I can't be free.
Cause those people took my money. And that's what torture is mean.
Well, if they freed him from this prison, if that portfolio was mine,
I bet I'd buy some index funds and everything would be fine. And bought from Daily's prison
as well. I won't do it. And I'd let that closing bell bring my blues away.
The Dead Prison Blues has sourced from the mad money machine. Check it out mad money machine.com
and hopefully that song will be released somewhere because it should get out, man. It's cool.
You'll notice I'm not going to talk about Kanye West assaulting a photographer.
I can't believe what passes for news these days. It's just unbelievable. It really is.
And watching Fox News and CNN too, CNN is clearly now the Obama news station. Fox
obviously the McCain palean station. Both of those both the Democrats and the Republicans,
it's just a show. Okay. See it as a show because they are not actually going to run or control anything.
And speaking of running and controlling ever since Lindsey Williams came out,
or since I was exposed to his story, Lindsey Williams probably recall is the pastor who worked for
oil companies up in Alaska in the 70s. And he became an insider literally and has come out
multiple times about how it works and how they control the oil. And he said, look, oil's going down
to $60 a barrel. No matter what happens. And you can even see it now. So here comes Hurricane Ike.
What happens oil goes down? Oh, because we're using less. Is sure we're using somewhat less. But this
is horseshit. You don't go from a 147 to below 100 with a hurricane headed right towards the
Gulf. You just don't. The whole reason the oil is being pressed down is because they want to
bankrupt the Arabs. They want to bankrupt them and then start drilling and be the sole supplier.
We've got plenty of oil in the United States. That's clearly the plan. You know, calling for drilling
and now, and this is from, where did I get this from? This from MSN money? I'm sure that they just
bought this probably. Maybe not. Douglas Mac and Tire. And this is yesterday, so September 11th,
you probably recall that so, you know, the OPEC, the oil-producing economic community countries,
sorry, who desperately wanted to push back on, you know, them being bankrupted essentially,
they see the oil. They see what's happening. They see it being brought down.
And then the OPEC said, well, you know, we're just going to lower production a little bit,
which is the game they always play. So that's there into the equation, because if they lower production
less supply, supply and demand, you know, less supply, same demand, price will go up.
And how Saudi Arabia walked away? Walked out of OPEC yesterday. This is big.
This is really, really big. And they say that they were tired of the rants from Hugo Chavez
of Venezuela, as well as the oil minister from Iran. So again, it's all about the three major
currencies, gold, which you can't get anymore. You could get you could buy paper that says you
you will own some gold, but it's actually, it takes two months now to get just some gold,
physical gold drugs. And I'm not talking about marijuana. I'm talking about cocaine heroin
mainly, because that's the stuff that's coming out of Afghanistan. You know, the poppy fields
were down to zero. And the Taliban forced everyone to grow new crops. You know, the kind you could
eat. And then we show up with a coalition. And now they're back in their producing again. I'm sure
please Google CIA Jets smuggle cocaine. Because that is a huge currency. One of these days
I'll really get into it. I'm not quite affluent enough in it to really let it all flow out as,
you know, here's how the story sits, but I'm getting pretty close. But the US government certainly
is involved in drug smuggling. It's proven if you read Legacy of Ashes, the history of the CIA,
which my uncle Don, who lived most of that story and was a Bush senior's personal advisor.
He was there during a ran concert. That's what it was all about. He says it's true. It's exactly
the way it happened. And it hasn't stopped. Drugs for weapons, drugs for money. That's how money
comes into Wall Street. And so now they're all fighting amongst the third real true currency, which is oil.
And then I'm sure, hopefully you heard about this. But again, being buried under the
under our VP, Elf, our VILF, Sarah Paylon. And by the way, I still think she's kind of hard. There's
nothing wrong with that. But I hope that you heard about the investigation and interior department
investigation of the mineral management agency, I think it is. These are the people who actually
determine inside the government what licenses are given out for drilling, mainly offshore drilling.
And the oil companies, clearly they go and try and get better contracts. And they're always trying
to get what they want. And the way they've been getting it is, of course, a fine American tradition.
By bribery, not just bribery with money. It's the mineral management service, actually.
This is the one in Denver. They were hanging out, doing drugs, having sex, going on ski trips,
golf outings, with energy company representatives in our very own government.
So this is a pretty big investigation. And I really wish this is on the front page every single
day here. I'm quoting from Yahoo. So these are probably an AP story. Yeah, associated press.
It's funny where was it? Yeah, employees frequently consumed alcohol and industry functions.
Had used cocaine in marijuana and had sexual relations with oil and natural gas company representatives.
Who are these people? I want names. I want pictures. And we put on the news where,
you set up horny guys with an IQ of 65 saying, hey, I'm a hot teenager. I want to come over and
have some sex. And then you got the news crews sitting there waiting to hijack the guy.
Why don't we do it with these freaking people? By the way, that is a show. I think that we get
huge ratings. I'm more than willing to finance that program with what a great idea.
Excellent. If you want to do the work, if you want to do the research, if you want to go find
these people, if you want to go hijack them and you know, blue or they're men. But hey,
it's another one of those parties. We got some sex. We got some coke. We'll talk some oil.
We'll give you some deals, some contracts. And then real men. I'm paying. I'm paying for the
production of that program. You better believe it. Okay. Well, is this going to be a long show
by the way? And this is another part of the problem. I'm having the track that I've gone down
and all the information that's coming out. It seems like it's expanding exponentially. And so
I couldn't even do less than an hour a day no matter what topic I just keep on talking.
And then I'm only a third of the way through today's list. And what are we at right now?
Let me just check. We're probably already 40 minutes. Aren't we? 36, 37. Yeah.
Bob Woodward. This is one of the journalists who uncovered the entire watergate scandal. He has
a new book out. And it's unfortunate because all this good stuff always comes out in books.
And that just doesn't matter to the American people because essentially the only people who
read are elitist. It's a very small percentage. I think of people who aren't reading tabloid
or watching TMZ videos or looking at Madison Avenue's representation of how women should really
look like. You're all sun goddesses. It's not about what make up you have or what bag.
If you're fat or you're thin or you're tall or you're short or you're skinny, you're all beautiful.
Bullshit. So Bob Woodward, who's kind of pretty himself, too? He has a new book out. And it's
quite astounding. And the main thing that I find so astounding is one part in the book.
And he was on fresh air, which is an MPR program, but Terry Gross, excellent show.
And I'm going to play this bit for you because I really want you to hear it coming out of
his mouth. Okay? Because we've talked about laser weapons, how tasers are just a precursor to
what's coming. So we can get used to it. I think they call them energy-directed weapons.
And it all sounds really futuristic and kind of wacky. But I want you to listen to what Bob Woodward
writes about in his book. Here he is a couple minutes, but well worth it. A couple of minutes
of him talking about it on fresh air with Terry Gross. Expectation, then all of this hyperbolic
rhetoric that we've heard for so many years. You're right that the surge is one of four things
that has contributed to the progress that's been made in Iraq. What are the other three?
First the Ambarawakenim where the Sunis came over, or this was before the surge, it started.
I'm sorry about the quality. I'm not quite, I transferred this, I don't know why it sucks
something went wrong there. But it's listenable. So he's going to explain these four things.
Really important you listen to the fourth. We're disgusted with Elkida in the extreme efforts by
Elkida to impose very strict law in Elkida made a strategic mistake. And so the Sunis said,
this is too extreme. We're going to sign up with the U.S. and this really sucks ass.
Why does it sound so shitty? Damn. Well, let me fast-forward to the fourth bit thing,
because I can you can't listen to this whole thing. A series of operations that have been developed
that allowed the U.S. forces to locate target and kill extremists, Elkida members and members
of the insurgency. On Friday, the White House, in responding to the book for the first time,
publicly confirmed that there were, quote, newly developed techniques and operations which helped
the situation stabilise and rock. If the request of the military and the White House,
you're not revealing any of the details you found out about what these top secret operations
are, what can you tell us? Okay. So in case it's hard for you to hear, he's saying at the U.S.
the White House saying they have all these secret operations and weapons that makes them invincible
super weapons. So we can track anyone, anyone, and kill them. That it's like any war. There is always
something. There's a game changer, a new development and you know, early early 20th century. It was
the tank of the airplane World War II, Manhattan Project and the development of the atomic bomb.
These operations and techniques are not something where you're going to see an explosion like
an atomic bomb, but they're incredibly effective. There's something that is present. Bush said to
people that are quote in the book, we are killing them all. We are killing all of the people who
were the leaders. Now it's not literally all that they are killing hundreds and hundreds of key
people on the other side in this conflict. So there you have it. We are killing them all,
says my president, if you can believe it, I'm so ashamed. And we're killing them with secret weapons
as big as the Manhattan Project, it's something totally new. I think it's pretty well documented that
there are microwave type weapons. I think about it. You have an energy weapon in your home.
It's called a microwave. You know, it's just a box that emits radiation. Radio signals, in fact,
a form of radio signals. And it can fry shit. And so imagine if they can pinpoint a beam of
microwave energy, they can fry anybody. And I've seen these pictures. They're around there. Go
Google it. Look for energy directed weapon and look for pictures. Do it in image search.
Make sure your safe search is off. Because that stuff will certainly get filtered out.
Yeah, they, it's almost like taking a hot dog. Put a hot dog in the microwave for for
50 to 30 minutes. It'll shrink down to the size of like a, a little breakfast sausagey thingy.
That's what happens to humans when they're fried with the microwave. That's what we got.
And we got a lot more. I'm sure of it a lot more that's not being talked about.
It's fucking crazy, man.
Hi, Adam. It's Matt from Games. We're on this week's show. We have a look at
Monster madness on the PlayStation 3. Facebook on the Xbox 360. You can also
in copies of Final Fantasy 4 for the Nintendo DS. And we've got some very exciting news on
February 9. That's all against Weasel.com.
Thanks for reminding you that GoDaddy has the best deals anywhere for domain names.
You can get one for $6.95 for an entire year by using one of my code. I actually want to use
DSC 3 for that. And I want you to be listening to all kinds of shows out there in the UK.
As we're now kicking off with the.co.uk domains cheaper than any other place to get a.co.uk
domain. And I mean by substantial amounts. This is, I've seen this. Well, I actually haven't seen
the video. I've heard the audio. I've heard extrapolations of Matt Damon, who was condemning
Republican vice presidential candidate Sarah Palin. And I figured we just watched, well, I'm
going to watch the video. You're going to listen to their audio. We just go through it together.
Because I'm not quite sure where my mind is at with Matt Damon. I'm, you know, when I hear
all this talk about experience and all this, you know, like any American, any American could
should be able to, and should be privileged. You shouldn't have to go to school to college
to university to be president of the United States. I'm just going to defend a little bit here.
And I'm really not liking this. You know, the same for Obama. I don't give a shit. If he's too
young or is only, you know, anyone can run the United States. It's more about your cabinet,
what you put around you, but it only really works if you have a healthy system. And that, of course,
we don't have. It's, uh, it's all been taken over by money. The corporations have bought and bought
every single piece of relevance and importance. Look at that. Look at the minimal management, uh,
service. That's how they get bought and paid for. Coke, sex, and nice work if you can get it on,
I'm not saying that ain't interesting. Here's Matt Damon. I think there's a really good chance
that Sarah Palin can be president. Um, and I think that's a really scary thing. Um, because I don't
know anything about her. You know, that's, so, uh, and I like Matt Damon. He's a great actor. I love
his movies, but, uh, what's got that, that's bullshit. I don't know anything about her. Well,
then you need to do your research. You know, don't rely on the news media to do the research for you.
That's the big mistake here. I don't think in eight weeks. I'm going to know anything about her.
Um, I know that she was a mayor of a really, really small town. Yeah. Yeah. And I just got to interject
there, too. Again, I'm, I'm against both parties. I'm not rooting or voting for anybody. If anything,
I'm going to take Dr. Ron Paul's direction and I'm going to, uh, go for a third, third party,
independent libertarian. Anything, uh, Dr. Ron Paul endorses on behind. Done. And we'll be
listening to Dr. Ron Paul in a little bit, too. Um, and she's a governor of Alaska for, for less than
two years. I just don't understand. Uh, I think the pick was made for political purposes, but in terms
of governance, it's a disaster. God, you know, this is what happens because I know Matt Damon
really means well. I really do. I think he does. But, you know, this is, this is not helping
the process. You know, and I think he was probably set up. This, of course, he only hears answers.
You don't hear the question. And it's probably about, you know, do you think that Sarah
Paine of the, she was vetted properly? Who cares? You do the actuary tables. You know, there's
a one out of three chance. If not more, that McCain doesn't survive his first term. And it will
be president, Paine. And this, and I think this is, uh, I actually this board is on sexist.
Because the way he's coming across when I'm watching this video is like, oh, you know, he's
following the talking points. You just, the heart beat away from being the president. We'd have,
we'll, we'd have a woman. Really, you know, we was talking about it earlier. It's, it's like a
really bad Disney movie. You know, the hockey mom, you know, I'm just a hockey mom from Alaska.
And she's the president. And it's like she's facing what, uh, what qualifications do we have to
have for the president? You know, that's, he's missing the point. He's saying exactly why
it's a genius choice. Because that's all, that's the way our system works now, which, of course,
I condemn is we only need actors. She's a perfect actor. So, Damon, Matt Damon, a couple
levels deeper, my friend. That's why she's a perfect candidate because she won't actually be
running anything. All she has to do is stand there, read the prompter of the prompter blinks off.
She has to be able to add live a little bit. That's what really, that's what the position is about.
Remember Ronald Reagan guy was actually an actor.
Down, Vladimir Putin. And, you know, using the, you know, the, the folksy stuff she learned at
the hockey, you know, rank, you know, it's absurd. It's totally absurd. And I don't understand why
more people aren't talking about how absurd it is. I, I, I, it's, it's a, it's a really terrifying
possibility. The fact that we've gotten this far and, and we're that close to this being a reality
is crazy. Crazy sheet. I mean, does she really, I need to know if she really thinks dinosaurs were
here 4,000 years ago. That's an important. I want to know that. I really do because she's going to
have the nuclear codes. You know, I want to know if she's thinking, uh, so I guess that's somehow
that's an attack on her creationist view over the world. I think that's, yeah, I think he's
gotten a little confused there. I don't know if she ever said anything about the dinosaurs,
not existing. The dinosaurs were here 4,000 years ago, or if she banned books, or tried to
banned books. I mean, that's, you know, we can't, we can't have that. You know, I, I bet that
the true owners of the earth really love people like Matt Damon talking like that. And the guy's
not doing it because he's evil or he's being paid to, to talk that way, but this is the general
perception. The general perception is that the people in the White House actually control stuff
actually are smart, actually make things work. No, they don't. All they do is just have to sit there,
read the teleprompter, look good. And that's also important, by the way. It's not to be underestimated.
How important it is, you know, to be a good performer when you're in that role and to carry the message.
These people don't write their speeches. You know, they really don't. But I think very few
speeches are ever written by the people who give them the speech writers. And that comes from
think tanks and from all kinds of lobbyists and money influencing what people are supposed to do.
But I think that, you know, I really hope Matt goes a couple of level levels deeper.
Because right now, he's, he's pretty much sounding like, you know, an ages sexist Democrat.
That's just my take on it. Okay. And let me see, you know what, it's Friday,
which means it's time once again for the handy work of young people.
Hey, Adam, how are you doing?
It's just hit us number 138. All right. And this is intro number one.
Oh, I think I'm going to like this week. I would say that's trapped by Colonel Abrams.
Another 80s show. Yannes that we're up to.
Number two.
Clarence Plyman.
Oh, man. Is it Clarence?
No, Clarence, Clarence Plyman's, you're a friend of mine, with a duet with someone.
And this is number three, Ice House, something with girl in it.
Oh crap. I think I get four out of six. I can't quite complete all three answers.
And it's time for the answers.
All right. And this is answer number one.
Now let's just go to Abrams and track.
I'm sick of you.
Colonel Abrams is answering number one.
And this is answer number two.
Clarence Plyman. And Jackson Brown, you're a friend of mine.
I need you.
Now, let's track it out.
Welcome back again.
And you can't call on me.
Oh, but you're the same.
You're the one who gives me so many more.
All right. I need to get the Jackson Brown part.
I'm an accountant, anyway. I'll say four. Four points.
Look, I'm Clarence Plyman. Clarence Plyman is in Jackson Brown.
You're a friend of mine, answer number two.
And this is answer number three. Crazy.
This is Ice House. Crazy.
Yes. I just remembered.
Crazy baby.
Ice House has answered number three.
And that concludes it. Number one, third, eight.
Go. So, Adam, how did you do this week?
I think because I came in under the wire before you give me the title.
I think I got six out of six. I'm feeling good on the football Friday.
Alrighty, hit this. Let me feel that calm is the place to find the answers to each and every hitest.
And also the links to iTunes, you can buy the tracks featured on the hitest online.
Thank you for playing, Adam.
And for now, special listening. Next week, I'll help you be back for another hitest.
So until then, have fun, take care and try to remember.
Think with your hearts. Bye bye.
And some of the things that happen here, tell you a little bit about what's going on.
Tell you what to do or not to do.
Things to avoid and things to enjoy.
Every couple of weeks or so, I focus on something.
It quintessentially London.
Quite often, I'll be taking my nose into place.
His where tourists went normally go to.
Trying to get under the skin of what's going on here and helping people understand.
Where we London as are coming from and why we live in this magnificent city.
You can find the show at www this week in London.co.uk.
Come by. Have a listen.
Tell me what you think. Bye bye.
It's my city as well. Now, of course, now that we're living in good old blighty.
And I want to talk a little bit about what's going on over here in the UK
because we talked enough about America for the time being.
Something that I noticed quite interesting when I was doing the Dutch radio show.
The government started talking about vaccinations and
notculation for 12 year old girls against cervical cancer.
And I had quite a discussion about this on the radio because I said,
you know, first of all, I don't like the idea of the government injecting anything into my child
period, particularly if I don't know exactly what's in it.
And the amount of people or girls that die from cervical cancer or women,
I should say, young women, is reasonably low on the scale of deadly diseases.
But it's also something that is passed on by sexual contact.
And, you know, so we had a pretty big debate about this and just, you know, I don't want to
get cancer. I don't know anything about cancer doesn't seem like anyone actually knows anything about
cancer, what causes or how you can stop it or how you treat it. My mom passed away from cancer.
But still, I am really against the government sticking needles in us, okay?
And so I saw this commercial last night on television here in the UK.
And it was like, it was like, hey, I got up, I had a really, you know, it's a teenage girl in
our bedroom. Like, I'm checking my my space and looking at my Facebook, I'm going to school,
I get a little jab, I'm really cool. It's called the Arm against cervical cancer.
And it's showing school girls who are really happy and they're smiling in there.
And they've got little tattoos that say Arm against cervical cancer.
And the vaccination program is coming to England in autumn of 2008. They're going to start
jabbing needles into our young girls over here. And I'm very, very, very afraid of it.
And you know that it's, it's, it's either the, uh, pharmaceutical countries because it's not
by coincidence that this is being brought up in the Netherlands and in the UK. And I'll bet
friends in Europe, chuckle heads out there in Germany, France, Switzerland.
Some of the Scandinavian regions, everybody. Tell me, is this happening in your country as well?
So a, it could be part of a pharmaceutical plot to make money on something which I believe is
probably unnecessary.
Um, or it's, uh, it's a way to shoot bad ass shit at our monomass scale into our children.
Or a combination of both, which is probably the most likely. And it's just highly suspicious to me.
I don't know anything about this new HPV vaccine. Well, hey, let me click on it.
Here it is, about the HPV vaccine. All you need to know about the new HPV vaccine that helps protect
against the main cause of cervical cancer. This vaccine protects against the two strains of HPV
16 and 18 that cause cervical cancer and over 70% of women does not protect, protect against any
other sexually transmitted infections or against pregnancy. Because the HPV vaccine does not protect
against all cervical cancers, it's really important for all girls to have cervical screening
later in life. Well, how about just doing that?
cervical screening, by the way, is offered in England from age 25. So you can't, you can, they're
going to force you to take a shot when you're 12, but you can't actually get cervical screening
until you're 25. How messed up is that? That's all they say about it. Uh, and let me see,
well, the surgery would be now we stop, which vaccine and how effective, how long is it last, doesn't
say what's in it? Nothing. Please download leaflets, posters, CR campaign materials.
Just shudder when I think of all this stuff. Okay, but that wasn't the really big news this past week.
The big news this past week in the United Kingdom was the trial of, well, they tried to convict
seven of these so-called al-Qaeda or operatives with links to al-Qaeda. We're going to
blow up aircraft on their way to the United States over the ocean. And they could only convict
three of them, the ringleader, the main guy, they, they, they, they'd let him go entirely.
And there's, uh, there's a lot of news articles about this and actually a pretty good aggregation,
um, let me see, this is on a site called on, on anger fan, I guess, WNGIRFAN.
But it has links to all these mainstream news articles. So of course you'll find this link in the
show notes a daily source code.com. And what I like about it is they have the actual,
here we go.
Uh, so there's a lot of, so in this, a lot of links about how it wouldn't have worked in the first place
is not actually, you know, uh, really feasible to take on the right liquids and mix them up in the
plane to create a bomb. Um, here we go.
I'm looking for the names here. Well, Muhammad goals are, uh, exonerate of all charges. The jury
failed to reach any verdict verdict on the four remaining defendants. Uh, Erifat was Wahid Khan,
Abraham Savand Savand, Wahid Savand and Umar Islam. Abdullah Ahmed Ali, Assad,
so Sarwar and Tanvir Hussein claimed, and they were convicted, claimed they were merely planning
a non-lethal explosion in London as a publicity stunt to draw attention to a supposed document
tree they are preparing on the plate of Muslims in Afghanistan in Iraq.
Pretty stupid idea if you ask me, want you higher a PR agent, but the jury and here it comes,
the jury could not, could not find these three of the eight, I guess it is, guilty of trying to blow
of aircraft. They actually didn't have a bomb, they didn't have tickets, many of them didn't have
passports. And what this, uh, what this aggregation of content suggests is, uh, that it was, uh,
the CIA's idea, um, to create more fear and anguish by saying, oh, they were going to blow
up planes with liquids. And so it turns out it's just not true and thank goodness, uh, Virgin Atlantic,
my favorite airline is awake. And they said, hey, you know what, uh, if, uh, if these guys didn't
actually do it, if they weren't really trying to blow up planes with liquids, if it turns out
there's pretty much impossible to do, could we please get rid of the stupid ass security idiocy?
And I want you all to think about this because a lot of people are already, and myself included
to some degree, you automatically think to yourself, you know what, we should lift that restriction,
let's get rid of it. But somewhere in the back of the mind, you're mind you're going,
but you know what, I feel really safe because I now know no, no one can actually pull that off, you
know, it's bullshit. It's bullshit. Okay. It's not going to happen. And let me keep my shoes on at
the same time while we're at it. Will you please? Just let me get on the flying bus already.
And, and give the crew some weapons. So guys with box cutters, a little peony knives don't
hijack us and fly us into buildings. There's your Disneyland movie, Matt Damon. That's the real
Disney movie. So now, of course, the you, and this is amazing to me. I don't know how this works.
I'm not familiar with with UK law, but I don't, I do know that we discussed the elimination
in the European Union of double jeopardy, meaning if you're convicted of a crime, you can never
be tried or if you're let off. You can never be tried for that crime again. And here it is
the BBC prosecutors are seeking a retrial of the seven British men who were accused of a plot
to blow up planes flying from the UK to North America with liquid bombs. Three men were found
guilty of the conspiracy to murder, but the jury was unable to decide whether they and four other
men had planned to target planes. So they don't like the outcome. Take them back to court.
Is that legal? Is that how it works? Let's see who's talking here.
Director of Public Prosecution Sir Ken McDonald said this will include a count
that each defendant conspired to detonate improvised explosive devices on transatlantic
passenger aircraft. They're going to vote. They didn't like the outcome. There's your
justice system in the United Kingdom. So we're just going to go back and I'm sure they're going to
rig it now. He added he had reached the decision after careful consideration with heads of counter-terrorism
divisions and counsel. Yeah, no shit. You guys look stupid. So the three of those guys,
they are being convicted. I mean, let's be honest. It's not okay to put together videos that say
we're going to blow the shit up and then go buy fertilizer and other ingredients. But the rest,
it seems was just made up and I don't want you to forget this. It was made up
and we're suffering because of it. It's crazy. All right, more UK news and I got to tell you.
I have actually gotten into into a place where I went shopping with the lady Patricia over the
weekend and said, I'm going to come with you because we're going to go get a lot of stuff. She said,
why is it? Well, you know, I don't know, man, a lot of people talking about a possible food crisis
you know, it could just imagine like if we didn't have any milk or bread. I mean, that it's
not the end of the world, but you'd be pretty upset. They could be messed up and by the way,
the wheat harvest in the United Kingdom has been destroyed by the weather. Literally destroyed
what was harvested is now going to cost three times as much as normal and they're going to have
to import wheat from, well, actually Germany had a banner year. They did better than ever. But,
that's going to make your bread really expensive and wheat goes into a lot of other things.
And now Britain, according to the express, is quite simply running out of power. This is the
stark warning from the head of an energy think tank, so that makes it suspicious, but still who believes
when I should finish the story about the wheat. So I bought a whole bunch of flour and dehydrated
milk and canned goods and dehydrated, freeze dried coffee. I just want to have some food.
If shit starts flying off the shelves and the cupboards are bare, I want our pantry to be stocked
at least for a couple of weeks. And the reason I get to this next story, because I'm also thinking,
I should probably buy a generator, a diesel generator, which by the way, I've done the research
very hard to get these days. It's much easier to get a gasoline power generator, but a diesel generator,
which you can easily run on any type of bio diesel, or a, you know, seeds, or hemp oil. I mean,
you can come up with a bad situation. You come up with a lot of things you can use in a diesel engine.
Because of this story, so this is the stark warning from the head of the energy think tank,
of these power cuts could be serious enough to spark civil disorder. Okay, this is mainstream news.
Campbell Dunford of the respected renewable energy foundation said,
it's almost too late to do anything about it. Nothing will stop us having to pay very high prices
for power in the future already taking place. British gas and energy just raised their prices by
an a published average of 30% as sure it's going to be much higher. Here comes a great English quote,
if we pull our finger out now, we can limit blackouts, but it's going to be pretty grim whatever happens.
To their expecting, I guess, a form of rolling blackouts.
Only last Thursday, the National Great Issue to an urgent call for power after a series of
power station breakdowns. Who was this released? September 7th. I didn't even know about this.
Suppliers were asked to bring all of their available generating capacity online, including
the costly oil fired stations in May. And I do remember this hundreds of thousands of people in
Cleveland, Cheshire, Lincolnshire, and London suffered blackouts when seven power stations were
closed. By the way, no, follow up on that story. You think the news media is going to go and
ask more questions. No, no, no, the way too busy with the, what was it? The National Movie Awards.
All important stuff. Gary Glitter. Yeah, we got to go do an in-depth. Let's go to Thailand and do
in-depth the in Vietnam in that investigation. I'm Gary Glitter, but don't actually go and find out
what these cock suckers are doing. Spit on my microphone, sorry. So one more here. This is not
specifically about the UK, but is about the European Union. And this really sums up a whole bunch of
articles about ID cards being ushered in. You could really, you could just go read 1984 by George
Orwell. And you'll, that's the news. That's the news over here. I'm trying to load this page from
the telegraph over here in the UK, mainstream media news reporting. You're going to love this.
60 page report published yesterday, the seventh anniversary of September 11th said that the
European Union now sees data privacy and judicial scrutiny of police surveillance tactics as just
obstacles to efficient law enforcement cooperation, rather than rights to be safeguarded.
The report, which is the shape of things to come, is described as a EU future group,
preparing a five-year security strategy that is being in the works right now. They're calling this
very, very shadowy. State Watch report quotes EU councils of ministers, council of ministers,
document on justice and security, which declared every object, the individual uses, every transaction
they make, and almost every there, everywhere they will go will create a detailed digital record.
This will generate a wealth of information for public security organizations and create huge
opportunities for more effective and productive public security efforts.
They're even offering kids. You don't need all these. The EU is fucked, man. This Lisbon Treaty
which will take place. They are going to ram it down our throats. Ireland stands strong.
We're all behind you. No means no, Ireland. They're still going to try and ram it down our throats.
And that'll be it. We've been sold. We've been sold off. All these global European laws
coming into effect share all of our data for security reasons.
Remember, though, the freedom exists between your ears. That's where my freedom is right now.
And nothing really, nothing really political, but there was a big fire in the channel tunnel
which was like he was really here about on the news. They don't have any video, of course,
which means it only gets 20 seconds of attention. But there were explosions and truck gas tanks going
off and people had to escape through escape tunnels. And this fire burned for quite a while.
And the the channel has been shut down. They say it might open today. But that's pretty serious.
And what's interesting is that not a single person is saying, couldn't that been of terrorist attack?
I haven't heard that at all. There's no video, of course, which doesn't make it
interesting enough for them to even get that far in their thinking. But what was it? Will we ever
knew? Will we ever know? Will they ever report on it? Probably not. But that's what our independent
media is for. Has this ever happened to you?
Welcome to the rock and roll diner. What will it be? Hey, they're gorgeous. What's the special?
Nickelback with a side order of follow-up boy in 6am. Same old stuff. Sounds like the same
special from yesterday. Oh, it's some new. Got anything I haven't tried yet?
Well, have you tried the love and the club with a side of some shot to get loose?
Yeah, give me gas. Have you got any independent dishes? No. Yeah, us and the tavern on the green.
You know, we've just got the same old same old. No, what'll it be?
Are you looking for something new and fresh? Are you constantly bombarded with the beat?
They love to repeat? Well, now there's a choice. Indy Radio Chat Nuke. We've taken over the
FM airwaves and internet radio every Saturday night at 10 p.m. We feature interviews, news,
and of course the best independent music we can get. So hop on over to Indy Radio Chat Nuke.com
for details and don't forget to subscribe. This is the daily source code.
You've got to emerge into a society of this thing that's called the state. What is the state?
The state is important as you are to see. It is the whole needs department.
It is the argument of the negative. It represents the system of the courts and what have you.
This is the state that is a impressive organization. But the state.
I thought my talk I care about the pre-thinking. You know how we think. Organize the hood.
On the ice shing battles. Red black and green. Instead of gang bad dancers.
FBI's final in the school. The radio and channels in the head and cameras in the street.
Like watch your society. We know it's back for the people's right. The privacy.
I take a slug for the cause. Like who you peed.
Or all you fake niggas try to copy master tea. I want to be free to live.
Ain't what I have. What I need to live. Bring the power back to the street.
Where the people live. He's taking words with crumbs and filling up the prisons.
Don't know what money and rely on. We live for help. We do the stuff like ants in a colony.
Organize the world for your socialist economy. Or where a life based off the comedy.
And on my comrades is ready. He just threatened to see.
I have a black man. There was a third of his life in the jail.
Because the world is the control of our white man.
And the people don't know what he just did.
And the women don't know what he just did.
And the problems don't know what he's called.
And the jobs don't know what he's called.
So the red always be late.
And you're late.
And there's no more bondage. No more political monsters.
There's no more secrets, face launches.
Government departments started it in the projects.
Materials, you objects, thousands up in the closet.
Could have been invested in the future for my comrades.
Battle contacts, primitive weapons out in combat.
Many never come back. Pretty niggas be running with gas.
Ravi gets shot and they back and fight you back.
Retired of that. Corporations high and black.
The nine effect is floating us all over the map.
I fly right to shit. I ride in my raft.
It's documented I'm in it.
Every day in the week I live in it, breathe in it.
It's morning to fucking believe in it.
I'm holding them ones rolling up my sleeves and shit.
It's the low who pushed up now.
Many had it but one concludes it.
Lick is ain't ready for rebel.
I have a black man.
Never third of his life in the jail.
Then I've got a world that's controlled by a white man.
And if people don't never get justice.
And the women don't know you just back there.
And the problems don't never get solved.
And the jobs don't never pay enough.
For the rent always be late.
Can you relate?
They've been in a holy state.
Yeah, dead president was a police state.
It's still pretty much hip hop and metal.
This really passing a message along.
It's not what's going on in coming.
Where are the days when our superstars were, I guess I can't happen anymore, huh?
When the big label artists that just can't put this stuff out anymore, the labels are
fused to release the politically tinted stuff, their true messages.
And they can't even put it out independently because then they'll still get in trouble with
their labels.
I think the last one and boy, he was ridiculed for, remember George Michael and he came out
with the song, I can't remember the song now.
I don't think it was a huge success.
He might have gone top 10 or top 5 after all.
It was a video with it and Blair was a Tony Blair, was like a little lap dog for George
Bush and people ridiculed him, totally ridiculed him.
And he was right, of course.
And they were laughing at him, too.
They were just laughing, I mean, what are you doing?
You crazy get.
And of course they got him, right?
They embarrassed him.
Okay, I promise you some Ron Paul.
And this is from C-Span, I really like this because it's about Georgia and about the billion
dollars in aid that has been pledged to Georgia.
Now, of course, you have to understand that this billion dollars doesn't actually go into
the pockets of the Georgians, it's a credit.
So the big companies, Boeing, Lockheed, Rand Corporation, they'll take that money and they're going
to build infrastructure in Georgia.
I'm going to get into that a little bit until you why they want infrastructure in Georgia.
You might want, if you're not in the car, if you're at the office, or if you're at home,
just go ahead and fire up Google Earth or even Google Maps and go find the region.
Okay, go look for Georgia.
You'll probably get a couple of results, it's not the one in the United States, obviously.
But go look at Georgia, look at the companies that neighbor it, look at its relationship to
Russia and primarily Iran.
While we listen to a little bit of Dr. Ron Paul asking the tough questions.
Has expired the gentleman from Texas, and this is actually the U.S. Russia relations.
That's what the C-Span2 has as the lower third the title,
their after conflict with Georgia.
All is recognized.
Thank you Mr. Chairman.
I understand we're sending aid to Georgia right now humanitarian aid in a military vessel, military ship.
If we're not the provocateurs, why would we use a military ship instead of a non-military
ship? What's the purpose of that if it isn't to provoke?
We've used military ships to provide assistance after the tsunami in Asia.
We've used...
This is Daniel Fried. He's the Assistant Secretary of State for European and Eurasian Affairs.
You got to see this video, links in the show notes, of course, dailysourcecode.com.
You'll look at this guy. If you actually believe in the whole reptilian story about the
leaders being reptiles and shape-shifters, you'll love this guy. He does look like some kind of evil
reptile. Listen to the lies that come out of his mouth. Listen, I'm going to just back this up just a
little bit here. Listen to the lies. Remember, it's documented and reported in mainstream media,
although not the headlines every single day, that Georgia attacked South Assetia first.
Before Russia came to South Assetia's aid, most of those people being Russians hold us a Russian
passport. Listen to the lies. Listen to the words. The code that he uses to skirt around
the truth. The tsunami in Asia, we've used military planes to provide humanitarian assistance.
So it's actually fairly standard procedure, not any kind of provocative act at all.
And we didn't regard it as a provocation. Certainly, it is perfectly normal to have relations with
Georgia to deliver humanitarian assistance in a standard way. It is after all the Russians who have
crossed an international border to attack Georgia the other way around. Let me have you pause for
a minute because obviously there's a disagreement on that. Certainly in world press, there's a
lot of disagreement on who did the invading first, but we'll not settle that here. But I think we should
all... I just love Dr. Ron Paul. I love you, man. Absolutely. World press has reported on it
and Dr. Ron's even smoking. Unfortunately, I'd like to know where do we actually have that
conversation? Can we have that conversation about who made the first strike? Is there a committee
for that? Breathe that when you give humanitarian aid, it's essentially military aid because all
funds are fungible and it just happens that the Georgians in their budget last year spend 70
percent of their money on the military and they got a lot of assistance from us. So this idea that's
humanitarian aid and not military aid, I think, distracts from what's really going on there.
But I was just wondering whether every bothers you or concerns you are the question,
every cross is your mind about, say, humanitarian aid to a country like this. What about,
what about the people in this country? We have a lot of poor people, not getting medical care,
not getting food and a billion dollars. What the heck? What's that of another billion?
Does it ever cross your mind that maybe that should be helping our people here and this,
this is getting us in the trouble? This isn't helping. This is making us less safe.
This is part of this empire. You might refer to it as our sphere of influence, but
everybody knows it's our empire, but does it ever cross your mind that everything that we do over there
and every nickel you take, you're taking it away from some poor people in this country that could have
been helped? I love the way he's putting that because in order to get through to people who are
brainwashed and mind control, which is 99% of the population, present company excluded, of course.
You got to throw it if that's so unfortunate, because really what he wants to say is,
dude, you're actually when I'm buying, we're giving money, we're selling, we're going to be
selling weapons to Georgia. And the reason why is because we want to, or we, the Bush,
Cheney and the evil owners of the planet, want to set up a front, a long rush, so they've
gotten your Cheney was in in Georgia. He was also in Azerbaijan, in the Ukraine, and they're building
up the plan. I'm pretty sure it was to build up a base in Georgia. And that's where the jets and
everything else could fly out and go bum around. And why else do you think that we're now moving
all of our troops out of Iraq enough, Afghanistan? Go, look at the map, go, look at the map.
I got some other interesting info about that in the minute, but let's just hear a little bit more from
Dr. Ron and this reptilian. I don't think of it that way, no sir.
Secondly, as a matter of fact, Georgia did not attack Russia. There's no question about that.
Russia attacked Georgia. Georgia sent in its forces into a part of Georgia, the breakaway province of
South of Session. Those are the basic facts. I don't know about Georgia spending 70% of
how do you like that? You just sat there and he lied and you hear Ron Paul laughing. This guy just
looking at Ron Paul and I got to roll that back. It looks like he has an actual smirk on his space
this guy. No, no, no, no, no. Georgia didn't attack Russia. It's fucking lying. It's proof. We know
it. It's been reported on. How can this guy just sit there and get away with these lies?
Or did it not attack Russia? There is no question about that. Russia attacked Georgia.
Georgia sent in its forces into a part of Georgia, the breakaway province of South of Session.
Those are the basic facts. I don't know about Georgia spending 70% of its budget on the military.
That doesn't sound quite right to me. And with respect to assistance priorities at home and abroad,
Sir, the same could be said for any form of foreign assistance anywhere. The question is,
is it in the American interest to support a small country, a struggling democracy that wants
to be a friend that has helped us out in Iraq? You're hearing the lies right here?
It has been attacked by a much larger country. The strategic stakes here are fairly high.
The administration believes it is in our interest to support Georgia, to help it get on its feet,
to prevent Russia from drawing a new line in Europe, and claiming it's here of influence.
And in the long run, we want to consider our relations with Russia.
Nothing to those words, sphere of influence, new line in Europe. It's all about
oil.
Under any harsh or in each earthquake, that carefully, if I'm sorry, but I only have a minute.
And I understand your point, but let me tell you, there are a lot of people in America
do not see this in our interest. They see it in the interest of some very powerful, special interest
groups that have an oil pipeline going through there. There's a lot of fact, most Americans
couldn't even find Georgia on a map.
Yeah, that's not the chuckleheads because they're the looking right now, Dr. Ron.
To convince them that this is crucial to spend all this money,
provoking the Russians, leading us into another conflict that we're not even capable of handling
militarily. Now unless we use some very big bombs. But we are true.
I don't even need to use big bombs because we've got the new secret weapons.
Secret weapons. Wasn't it Hitler near the end of his demise?
When he started talking about having super weapons and you can't get us,
you can't get me. I've got the super gun super weapons. Secret weapons
is history repeating itself, is that what President Bush is now doing?
Just spread around the world. And this has been exactly the plan of some of our enemies to do
exactly this and bring us to our knees. And all we do is proceed to continue to spend and
spread our troops around, diminishing our ability to take care of our people here at home.
And I yield back the balance of my time. Yeah, right on, Dr. Ron.
Right on. Okay, Russia today, of course, highly skewed.
But it's a very interesting report this came out today.
A title, of course, I catching U.S. to invade Iran any day now.
Well, here's the deal. It's going to scroll down here and find this. Okay, so the reporter
is talking about a friend who had been in Kandahar in Afghanistan.
And it would seem American battle tanks being unloaded from a Ukrainian registered onton off.
Onton off is the biggest plane in the world. And it can carry tanks with a lot of them. Remember
Ukraine, that's where Cheney just was. So all these tanks are being offloaded from an onton off,
which was registered to the Ukraine. Okay, you with me. So you've got tanks coming into Afghanistan.
Now, please go look at your Google Earth and, you know, Google for Afghanistan.
And actually, you know, how you can tilt Google Earth. Well, this is fun. You can do this.
Tilt Google Earth. And you'll see that it's mountains. It is terrain that is completely unsuitable for tanks.
So as this article continues, this friend asked if I had any idea what tanks would be
good for. And Afghanistan, I said, I didn't. It's an established fact that the Soviet,
from the Soviet war in Afghanistan, tanks are no good for most of the country's mountainous territory.
The good for flatlands. Now, back to the Earth. What do you see as a flat region right across
the border with Afghanistan? It's Iran. So we've got ships rolling into the Black Sea. We've got
tanks rolling out in Afghanistan. This is war. And obviously, Georgia was a perfect,
perfect place for an airfield. You can see this. You have to be see international airport,
which I think is a George W. Bush highway, no kidding, which which runs off into the airport.
And if you use Google Earth, you can see about maybe it's 20, 30 miles away. There's an airport.
There's two more airports. Perfect spot to put your fighters. And I think that what happened is
Kashvili, he got a little overzealous. And I don't know what went on there. But he's looking at
the way he's eaten up his ties. He definitely screwed something up. So keep your eye on it because
it makes sense now. When you hear about all this, oh, we're losing out against the Taliban,
we're losing out against the Taliban. We got to move all our troops in Afghanistan. It's not true.
They're getting ready to attack Iran. We've got the ships in the Black Sea. We've got the tanks
and Afghanistan, which means they ride right across the border into the flatlands of Iran.
And we are keeping our eyes on it because even between our ears, my fellow chuckleheads, that's
where we are still truly free. Hi, I am Dina, 25 years old. I am looking for man for long-term
relations. I am from Russia. I live in St. Petersburg, Dina. It's Hypernonsense.
It's very agile, man. I think. It's kind of funny. But it's so kind of long-term relations.
I like that.
Long-term relations over say, long-term relations ship. Yeah, but long-term relations.
Chris invited the fly back and forth to St. Petersburg. They'd be a long-term relations, just try to get there.
That's great. Hypernonsense.com.
It's so cold. I don't go. I don't go.
I don't go in. You have to speak the truth. You have to speak your mind.
Every time I speak my mind, I'm literally critical. The pinnacle of being revolutionarily pivotal
beyond anything ever-study that's metaphysical. Man, fuck am I nervous? I'm not politically
minimal, but obviously terminology that is statistical. A manufactured to be unequivocally subliminal.
Transmitted by monopolized media visuals. So I'll riddle hypercritically pitiful criminals.
Habitually utilizing typical rituals with false pretence in attempts to be spiritual,
to individuals who believe in biblical miracles instead of themselves. Because they're not thinking original
and the color of their skin makes them feel invisible. Like microscopic miscarriages lynched with the
umbilical only a fucking ambasile would think they're uncharacterable. Because you're susceptible to
becoming more than a spectacle. Remember that your flesh and blood and your body's dissectable.
I'll beat you until you're reversible and wake up in a hospital covered in poisonous chemicals
and a fetal position with your face only at testicles. Thinking that you were kidnapped by
extraterrestrial. You got heart on the blood that pumps in your ventricles. Technique. I'm like
your soul nigger indispensable with no respect for those who cover at the hour of revolution.
Because the government owes my people restitution instead of sedatives like cocaine and prostitution.
Conclusion is that you'll have to violently silence me because I raid the airwaves and
control piracy. In school my teachers blinded me. But now I can see. Now I mentally and revolution
never leave free, broadening horizons about what my people could be. If we wasn't set up to get
shot locked to OD, you see families bleed because of corporate greed and monopolizing weed is virtually
impossible. So it won't be legalized and that's another obstacle. But I'm still rolling up pocket
full of tropical. The government's involved directly. So it's unstoppable like a nuclear rocket full
of biochemical toxins that invade the ecological improbable. That the average intellect could
understand. So I encrypted this into hip hop that's in high demand and spread it through the
ghetto of every city like contraband. Storm for men of any complexion with a devilish nature.
Because I'm trying to save the earth but you're just getting in line to rape.
I gotta tell you. That is pretty much the final thought of the week. I couldn't have said it any
better. And by the way, it's not just our black and our brown brothers and sisters who are feeding
this. It's everybody. Everybody on the planet is enslaved and under control of thugs.
Absolute money, grubbing, horing, thieving, coke snorting, population controlling thugs.
And it starts at the top with the true owners of the earth and they're in trouble. Now
I'm talking about Rockefeller. I'm talking about Rothschild. I'm talking about Warburg. I'm
talking about the next level down. You've got the Lehman. You've got Merrill.
You've got to watch the mutual. You've got Fannie Mae, Freddie Mac. You look at what's happening.
Don't forget what's happening with the mineral management system. Taking drugs and sex and
booze and parties and trips for money and exchange for favorable contracts for oil. It's oil,
drugs and gold in that order with drugs moving up quickly to number one because
the oil is just getting harder to manage. That's what the true war on drugs is all about.
It's to keep other players out of the game. But anyway, my fellow chuckleheads as we get ready
for the weekend and we feel a little bit full-barred and really my intent is not to bring you
down. My intent is to expose and show you what's happening so that you can talk about this with
friends. Let them know when we're all awake, no one can control us. We'll just be too big and too
powerful with many, many, many citizens who are awake. World citizens and we all are children
of the sun and the stars. Speaking of which, this October 14th, where
extraterrestrials have been reported to surface a huge ship in the reports all vary between 20
two days and three days. I'm getting that from a lot of pretty good channels that people really
think that this is for real. I hate these type of predictions because if it doesn't
happen, then it's, if it happens, okay, great. It's still going to be a huge fight to actually
prove that what we're seeing is what was predicted and believe me, it will be counteracted by
mainstream media. It really will be. And, you know, tinfoil hatwares will be laughed at and it'll
be able to have all kinds of specialist and scientists coming out and telling us exactly what it is
and what it isn't. But if it doesn't happen, then it's like 10 steps back, you know, then you
then it's much harder. It just gets harder and harder. And I'm still very, very confused about all
this attention that Larry King is spending on UFOs and the disclosure project and all these
Air Force military personnel coming out and saying that they've seen him, that they've touched the
space craft. They've some of flown in them and they have video and radar and it's all true.
And I'm just so suspicious of why that's on Larry King. I may be, you know, maybe Larry King
truly isn't a pen that I don't know. But I do have high hopes and I, you know, look, there's nothing
to be lost by having a little bit of hope for that. It's a shortcut. It really is. It's a shortcut
to where we want to go. But we still have to go through all the pain, the financial markets are
going to collapse. And the sooner we can wake up as many people as possible, the quicker we're going
to be able to control what the reboot processes, what menu option we're going to choose, how do we
want our world to look? Now, everything's coming crashing down. We have a very unique opportunity
once in a more than a lifetime. And maybe 10 lifetime opportunity to actually change the way
everything works. And that's going to be up to us. And that's not me. It's not you. It's all of us put
together. So while it lives between your ears and you can clear your envisioned, please enjoy
your freedom, my friends, and whatever you do this weekend, live your life with passion.
Another fine, medial presentation. Stick it in your ear.