This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
About $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm trying to reach this journey.
Podgestic is a battle curry.
And now it's time to question is it a lie?
Who is it at a Montaukshu with the Daily Source code?
725.
I'm going to win the win.
I'm going to try to follow you back home.
I'm going to scream like you're there.
I'm going to wipe and break down and open up.
It's time to let me learn to live again.
It's time to let me give and give again.
It's time like this.
You learn to go again.
Time to help you.
You gotta find out better,
Never leave me forever.
They won't afraid that they're brought loose, yeah
Now and again, when I see your face
You need to be waiting for me
That you won't waste any of my steps
You don't know, I've brought me pain
You're never ready
There's time like leaves
Learn to live again
There's time like this
You can't live again
There's time like leaves
Learn to live again
Time like it
You won't waste any of my steps
You can't live again
There's time like this
I'm a little too tired
Do stay alive
Leave it all alive
I'm a little too tired
There's time like these you learn
To live again
There's time like these
Giving them give again
Yeah, that's the way to arrive in San Francisco
There's a lot of guns and roses and food fighters
Synchronize, match them up
Sweet times of mine
Hey, hey everybody
How you doing?
It's daily source code episode number 725 coming to you from the curry condo
I've spent let me see about 10 hours getting here
Played around on the plane with the setup
With some degree of success actually
I've completely reconfigured everything
And I've even made it so that now I can
Apparently actually take phone calls through the talk shoe system that I have set up
And everything should kind of work I guess
So of course everything could just blow up at any minute as well
So we'll just have to take it as it is
So the rules will be pretty simple
If you got something to say
What I'd like you to do is in the in the talk shoe chat room
Just just you know like basically raise your hand virtually speaking
Tell me what you want to talk about
Hopefully it's about a topic that is
It is current as if this show
And I'll see if I can get on
Also got some phone calls of course
Hey
I've never since you started using a Ableton live
When the volumes kind of
Every time the volumes go up a little bit
If you're in music when you get a little excited
You speak up
There's a crackling on top of it
When it's quiet don't hear it
But every time the volume goes up
There's just sounds like static and it's only the high volume
So you're going to let you know
Yep
You could also just say it sounds like shit
Yeah, I think I fixed that problem
And I'm not going to get into it today
Because there's just so much in my brain hurts
And oh man I spent an hour and a half of customs
I don't even know if I want to talk about it today
Actually when we get some more people on
People who can actually
Talk
I see looking at the room right now
It seems like we've got
I don't know like 20 people in there
Lots of them on computers
But only one of them actually
Set up to talk
So wait till a few more people come in
You know Adam
Just calling because they that
I agree with the one guy from a few weeks ago
Or when you last trip to San Francisco
Your son did so like crap when you
You first got out there
My question is if you're traveling so much
How come you don't believe a permit set up out there
Mike Professor why do you have to chair it all with you
I mean I can understand the
Wanting to be minimalistic when you travel
But if you've got a place to leave it why not
You know
I got to tell you
And I was wondering this myself as I'm on the plane
I'm thinking myself why why do I put myself through all this
I mean I can
Purchase a beautiful mobile equipment
I can get full broadcast gear
But it's been this quest of mine
For for
Oh man better part of four almost going on five years
I really just want everything to be self-contained
I want to set up a certain way
And I'm getting so damn close
I can't even tell you
So yeah, of course I could have a duplicate set up here
But then you know what I'm in New York when I'm on the road somewhere
I don't want to lug around a lot of stuff
That's also a big reason man
Just lugging around the suitcase with mixers
And the mixers aren't even in the the heaviest bit it's the
It's all of the power adapters you got to slap along
So it's a quest
I have no idea why I put myself through this hell
So it's getting better
But it's still not as good as it used to be
I think that anyway when you make an empty three out of it
It's still not quite as good as it used to be
So keep that's a good work
And
Love you mean it right here
Hope you win all that stuff
Oh, yo, I'm losing light here
White
Oh
Three kids
No time
Yo
Yo, and I know what that feels like for sure
Oh boy
Yep, just gonna mess around a little bit more and actually what I'm hearing
In my headphones right now
Sounds probably more shit than you're ever going to hear this episode
At least I hope so this is what my test have concluded up until now
But we'll have to find out
So we'll be taking some phone calls in a second
But first this this this is something that came in from the Netherlands and I'm really jealous of this man
Here I am podcasting for going on yeah four years
I've never gotten anyone to do this with me
You found that mark bar show
Oh, yeah
Hey Adam just letting you know how much fun I'm having with the broadcasting and stuff
Uh, lately I've been interviewing people and listen what happened this weekend
What happened this weekend
It's pink yeah
And it is
It doesn't smell
You don't have orgasms very often
No, we're not very easily
Now that's well been and while we had trouble finding her g-spots
So in the podcast we went to go look for it
You think you found it
I think so
Oh, that sounds like it's working
Now, maybe it can help other people who have trouble finding that g-spot
So we have trouble finding that g-spot
To listen to this show because there's clear instructions of our scientific research
Afternoon we did
Thanks for the plug
www.markbars.com is the website
And the show is a pot show too by the way
I love you great hair
No homo
And I'm a male totally chef from Tilburg the Netherlands
Effort's weight
I don't know what else you want to know
I find that
That's good man, appreciate it
He's lucky bastard
He's when the jersey Todd turned me on to
Hehe
We bring a noise
Come on
To sing
Bring the noise
Come on
We bring the noise
To hear
I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it, I
Loves me cream and noise cream and noise cream and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream, and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream, and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream, and noise cream, and noise cream and noise cream, and noise cream...
Break is on a little bit more, we feel your scream underneath, we know your I got sound, we know wheps sticks out, we like to change it of switch it up, and, yeah.
I really should look it up. Actually, I probably could, I guess, let me see. I think they're like 10 years old or something.
Man, let me look it up.
Seven, five, seven. Brook and Tyler, many each other through the audition and selection process of radio Disney's pop group, RD7.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's cute.
From the pot-save music network, seven, five, seven. We bring the noise on daily source code episode number,
120, five is worth testing out. The live set up Jay is in Pennsylvania, Jay.
Yeah.
Are you doing, man?
Not bad. Thanks.
Philadelphia, represented.
Y'all, holy.
Philly.
Philly in the house.
Most excellent, dude.
So there's like, there's like 20 people now. Maybe even 25 on now.
But you're one of the few.
Are you on a computer? Are you calling in?
Come again?
Of course.
Why would it work?
Crap.
There you go. Was that someone else?
Sound like somebody else was trying to get in.
Yeah. I'm not going to unmute anyone yet.
I'm just going to leave it all open.
See what happens.
You just flew in yourself from somewhere.
Jay?
Actually, then we got the Twitter text on my phone.
I was like, oh, let me check that out. Actually, I was in St. Louis today.
And I was listening to your weekend episode of the test show.
And I hadn't tried anything with Twitter before.
So I logged in and created a Twitter account today and looked into it a little bit.
And they're going to let me at least follow Adam and see if I can catch one of his live shows again.
And sure enough.
And I didn't go.
Yeah, worked out.
Yeah, I just flew in the afternoon.
And I went through the whole frickin' rigmarole again at customs.
Except this time, the guy didn't know me.
So I had to go through basically the whole process.
You know, I got the little and first the guy.
It was a little different this time.
The guy in the glass cubicle.
He had that same puzzled look as always.
And you know, like tapping away on the keyboard.
And then he made a phone call, which was new.
And he called some other guy.
I looked at it and they tapped on the keyboard.
And he said, nah, you know, having to have him do a baggage check.
And he wrote a baggage like BG on my, on my customs form.
Then he crossed it out.
And then he put that M on it again.
And it's definitely an M, not a W.
Yeah, you know, I was just two days ago.
I was in Canada.
And I was thinking about you because I filled out the agenda.
And as I came through customs, I watched what they did.
And I was thinking, let me take an extra one and see what happens.
Just in case.
But they stamped it.
And I'm thinking, Pan, how's that?
You can't falsify with the stamp.
Why did you call it a gender?
Are you a pilot?
Yeah.
What do you fly?
I fly an embryo regional jet.
Oh, shit.
Real hardware.
What's that?
Yeah, man.
So you fly a king here.
Let me, let me just finish this story before.
Okay.
So, you know, so I get my suitcase.
It's it's first off the, off the belt as usual.
You know, so I hold on my passport and my, my customs form with the end.
I say, well, so I'll just walk straight over to those guys.
And he's like, and if they were really helpful for some reason.
This guy even said, hey, man, that's really weird.
Is this happened a lot?
And I said, yeah, he says, maybe your passport numbers similar to someone else.
He's like, okay.
And so then I went up to.
His name was an officer, Ocada.
And, you know, so he went through the whole thing about asking for business cards and other forms of ID.
And I, you know, gave my pilot's license.
I was like a fuck with him and given it, you know, if you think I'm a terrorist here,
check out my pilot's license.
Right.
And, you know, and so then, you know, he went to the, the TL, which is the team leader.
And, you know, they looked at the computer and the guy said, well, you know, there's a lot of things in here.
But he asked me a couple of interesting new questions.
And the first one was, have you ever lived in Nebraska?
I'm like, wow.
No, he says, do you know, oh, what's her name?
Oh, I wrote it down.
Do you know Laura Rand?
I'm like, Laura Rand?
Yeah, she owns her own aircraft.
And this is getting weird, right?
I'm like, well, maybe.
I mean, it doesn't ring a bell, but, you know, I own my own aircraft.
So, you know, maybe it's someone I've flown with or I've known, which is almost like kind of stupid.
You know, why am I going to, I should just say no to everything.
And, but this was interesting information.
So, you know, I got to put a whole Google search in emotion to figure out who Laura Rand is.
And what she has to do with airplanes in Nebraska.
But anyway, you know, so I said, I said to the guy, finally, and after, you know, going through tons of tons of ideas, stuff, and paper works, shuffling around.
I, you know, I said, could you please tell me just what's going on?
He said, well, the way our system works is first it does look up by last name.
Then it does first name.
Then it does date of birth.
He said, on each of those three parameters, you get a hit.
So, there is someone whose last name is Curry.
First name is Adam.
And birth date is either exactly the same or close enough to mine, that they are, what they're really trying to do is,
ID me as, you know, not the evil Adam Curry.
So, so I finally have some information about this.
So, you know, they let me go, obviously.
But it was, it was, it was twisted.
So we got, we got to find out who this, this Laura person is,
and what she's doing in Nebraska.
And what she's doing here is remember,
a couple, I don't know, maybe it was a couple months ago.
A caller called in and benched something about a guy in a truck that said,
pod father was that guy from Nebraska.
And there's another Adam Curry.
Something in my birth date.
I remember that episode.
No.
I was recently catching up.
I'm some past episodes.
How long ago?
How old was that episode?
That's a good question.
I don't remember it.
I was catching up some episodes from the summer.
So it might have been back in September or late August.
Some, I remember you getting a call or somebody called in,
saying something about a pickup truck in some Midwestern state that said,
pod father on the back license plate.
And you had to, you know, catch a picture of it next time.
That's ringing a very faint bell.
It must have been like a hundred episodes ago at least.
It probably wouldn't doubt it.
But anyway.
So you're on track to figure in this thing out.
I hope so.
They can't take anything out though.
They still can't help.
There's nothing they can do.
They can't, they can't remove my name from the database.
You said, you know, when you come in, just tell them that,
you're in the system.
That's when I say every single time, dude.
All right.
Doesn't help.
So where'd you fly in from again today?
Today there's insane lows.
I came in from St. Louis.
I was this a regular commercial flight or a private commercial flight.
Good to you.
Scheduled carrier.
Scheduled operation.
Yeah.
Side around there all day.
I got in real late last night and just had a schedule to sit there today.
And last leg.
I finished up four day trip.
Yeah.
One day parry.
So I'm off for three days.
And then I do a three day trip.
And then I'm off the remainder of the month.
Nice work.
If you can get it, my friend.
Yeah.
You know, it's okay.
The pills.
But the Italian man, the TSA.
It's a pain.
But I hate it.
No shit.
Yeah.
It's the biggest downside to this job.
And you know, we have to go through it.
And I'm sitting there thinking, you know, these passengers every time I come through
security, these passengers look at us like we're crazy like why are you guys going through
security?
Yeah.
One, two, one, two, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one
one, two, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one,
Day to the city, give up now, let me suck your pity
Don't you want to see the ship go down with me
Down to the rest of the night...
Time to rest spend the night...
So I've been around...
Come of the low feet for dreams
Oh, come on, let's say be chai-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Rah-hram-rah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-
This is really weird.
It's, in fact, I've been kind of nervous about doing
the show this way, as I was setting everything up
on the plane, I'm like, this is going to be so weird.
I got to set some parameters and figure out
how this is going to work, because it's not quite the same
as, even though having the ability to take phone calls,
is of course very much the same as the radio work I used to do.
It's different.
I think in the future what I'll do
is, I'll post a couple links on curry.com.
Before I start recording, so that, you can take a look
at some of the stories I want to talk about,
and you can, maybe, form it opinion.
Actually, I want to go back to homeless second.
I'm going to go back to J for a second.
J, you still there, man?
Yeah, God.
I just got, I just got the final A, what is it?
A, A, I, B, report on British Airways,
the one that landed short.
Okay, yeah.
And here's the conclusion.
So, you know, it's a very detailed report.
You can, it's online, there's two things.
Yeah, so, so this is the interesting,
a continuing investigation.
Investigations are now underway in attempt
to replicate the damage seen to the engine high
pressure fuel pumps and to match this to the data recorded
on the accident flight.
So, they did find some anomaly, apparently,
with the high pressure fuel pumps,
and they can't figure out what it is.
And then there's also, there's also a safety recommendation,
because there was something else with the,
well, when they, they found out that the fuel control
was still on after they, after they had evacuated,
which doesn't sound right to me.
Essentially, the safety recommendation
is Boeing should notify all Boeing 777 operators
of the necessity to operate the fuel controls,
switch to cut off prior to operation of the fire handle
for both the fire drill and the evacuation drill.
That's weird.
You'd expect them, you know,
that's isn't it standard on every single aircraft,
it's like, you know, when you're about to crash,
don't you suggest to switch the fuel off,
or at least certainly before you leave the aircraft?
Well, when they pull the fire handle,
the fuel valves should shut off automatically,
at that point as well.
Yeah, it doesn't.
But it cuts the fuel off to the engines,
and down line as well, and I don't know about Boeing,
I don't fly Boeing product,
but I would think that a safety precaution,
you know, as the plane I fly, you know,
the valves are the lines will be closed
when the fire handle is approved or pulled.
So that, you know, it doesn't any kind of fire
or a potential of fire would travel down
through the lines to the tanks.
Well, the investigation continues.
We'll find out, but definitely a malfunction.
So a bit that gonna be all over that,
otherwise I can have to ground these triple 7s.
Yeah, it's kind of scary thought.
From what I heard, the last I heard was
that the aircraft engines were producing power,
but not the light.
Not enough was the light.
The light on the thrust levers.
In fact, it says in the report that, you know,
the last time they checked when they saw that the engines
failed to power up was they had an air speed of 107 knots.
I'd say that's not enough.
I think it's flying like a brick at that point.
Yeah, pretty much, you're coming down fast.
Yeah.
Got another, another call here.
Hey, Adam, this is Riched in Clagate.
I don't know.
I, with this morning about the launch
of a new online service for unsigned new artists,
launched by Paul Young, remember him from the 80s.
Wherever I may have, lay my hat and all that sort of thing.
Um, he told his servant,
what he told him, music as ETO, PIA, music.com.
We just meant to be a website where unsigned artists
can let a few tracks, so that normal punters can download
and they can get discovered by the music industry.
So their top ten artists are such unsigned,
unheard of people as simply red.
Bjork, Elvis Presley, Red Anderson,
I'm in Van Buren, Block Party, Tokyo Police
Love, Make Bear to Cossack and Fat Boy Slim.
Never heard of that, not.
Their top ten albums, Paul Weller, Elbow,
Lustrol, Cock 2 Twins, Stereophonics, Mercury, Rev,
Dave Matthews Band.
Well, I don't get it.
Is, is all of this available for free?
Or is this, I've got to check this side out.
No, this isn't pretty big names.
If that's a place where we can,
can upload and download courtesy of Paul Young, no less.
And the world Bob Marley and the wolf mother.
But now Young people all,
shall I bring them a bit to get sign up?
I'm sure.
And now they're charging our assists.
I have their tracks online for one to three tracks,
four pants for 50 a year.
Oh, I'm not just suppose.
But when are you getting in to having quite a few tracks
more than 30?
That's four to no pants for 50 a year.
And punters have to pay up a seat to download them,
but they're unrestricted.
Tracks is no copper protection or that sort of thing.
DRM free.
So I guess that's good.
But I thought that might interest you
if they're not how the pot-save music network.
Yeah, that's all from me.
So I can't say I love you on a middle-class English man.
So I'll just say I hold with high regard.
Best of luck with any hair competitions.
I'm 43.
In fact, nine days younger than you.
Married three children working in the media industry.
That's it from me.
Bye for now.
All right, man.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
So I didn't prepare too much.
First of all, I'm really tired.
What time is it?
It's 10 30 here, so I'm going to go to bed pretty soon.
Let's see.
We got bird from Belgium on the line.
Bird?
Yes.
How you doing, man?
Good morning.
So what time is it there?
730 the morning?
Yes, that's it.
That's right.
OK, you have nothing better to do, Bird than hang out.
Well, actually, I'm preparing a proposal.
I just want to present that a customer at like 11.
So I'm sitting in my nose in the kitchen and preparing.
And I should be working with, I thought, well, I saw that the thing coming into
that's it.
Well, I'm going to go to the main child.
Oh, man.
Are you on a phone, are you?
Are you just on your computer?
On Skype?
Yeah, it sounds kind of shitty.
Just tell me what's the presentation
I'm going to make.
It's a, it's a, I can't say who actually, but it's a, it's a, it's a huge gas station
chain and everything for a company to help them with the marketing, their stuff to
in the internet.
And we're going to do a technical thing on how to integrate all the websites.
And we also have to, you know, invent a nice story about how we're going to mobilize people
and get some conversation and then they're brand and then, and then we're going to do
your sales result.
I am actually, what strategic fields are either something like that.
All right, man.
Unfortunately, your Skype is just too shitty to, to continue.
That's okay.
That's too bad.
But I appreciate you.
I appreciate you.
Okay, Bert, thanks.
TJ, steam or stain.
What is it, actually?
Hello.
Hey, man.
Hey, you hear me?
Yeah, of course.
Oh, cool.
I can't even say, it's kind of weird.
Um, yeah, is it DJ stain or DJ stain?
DJ stain, it's a Dutch name.
Ah, we have the, uh, the Europeans are awake today.
That's nice.
Yeah, well, I'm going to Australia, but, um, my dad's Dutch sir.
Holy crap.
So, it's, what is it in Australia Thursday?
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, that's about it.
It's one of the two days in the week.
All right, man.
What time did it just tell me what time is there?
Is it like 12 or 14 hour time difference between here and San Francisco?
Uh, yes, yes.
The moment, yes, the morning hours.
Okay.
All right, dude.
Well, enjoy.
I appreciate you.
You might have mentioned something about, uh, major bandwidth, um, here in Australia.
Um, we, I think we pay, uh, about $90 a month for, um, 25 gigs.
And, uh, we kind of just make it within that and then forget over.
It's, um, slow down to dial up speeds.
So I hate it when they do that.
I hate it when they, when they start messing with your connection.
And then you get really, really slow speed.
Yeah, um, and so what I have to do, like, sorry.
Drop, uh, uh, listen to, like, all the podcasts I want to.
Because I listen, like, keep breathing, anything big video podcast.
I'll have to download them, like, in the last few hours of the billing cycle.
So that we don't get so down during the months.
And so that I can listen to watch on my stuff.
Oh, that sucks.
So what, can you buy extra bandwidth or do you have to pay overage when you go over your 25 gigs?
Well, on the, on the plan well, you don't have to pay overage, but most plan to do.
With most companies.
I think the highest plan you can go on is broadband is like 60 gigabytes or something.
Which, yeah.
I tell you, man, I'm amazed that you guys have any kind of broadband down there.
I was in Australia.
I did a documentary in 1991, I think, um, and, you know, no one had heard of the internet.
And I looked at the country.
And I, you know, I went to Kubor PD and a couple other places I stayed in the out back.
And just in general, I was like, how are they ever going to wire this place?
So the fact that if any kind of connectivity at all, you know, Australia, I'd say you're a lucky.
Yeah.
That's true.
All right.
So it seems like we got to, it's probably a little bit too late for most people or, you know,
a good time for you guys and them in, uh, was it, uh, was it, uh, was it afternoon where you are?
And morning in Europe.
Call it on Europe.
Yeah.
But, uh, all right.
So maybe we'll have more callers tomorrow.
Let me, uh, see if I can fire some over here.
Hey, bird.
Thanks, man.
I'm sorry.
DJ Steen and Bird and Jay.
Thank you guys very much for calling in.
Can I have me to come?
All right.
Good dog.
Take it easy, guys.
I appreciate it.
Yeah.
All done.
One sec.
I'll be right back with you.
And I'll pay you too much.
And I'll be so weird that I cannot seem to pray for you.
I'm running the mail store.
I'm driving me where I can help myself.
I'm trying to speed up my phone.
So yeah.
Try to keep my distance.
I'm your coach.
You're taking this way.
I've never heard of you.
Makes me weak in the needs.
Makes me so, I can't breathe.
Once my dream is when I see.
I'm coming so with dignity that I cannot seem to pray for you.
I'm running the mail store.
I'm running me where I can't help myself.
I'm trying to speed up my phone.
So yeah.
Try to keep my distance.
I'm your coach.
You're taking this way.
So good old.
Simple smile.
Feels like I want to be lost in love.
I'm not in love.
Cause I've never heard of you.
And I can't seem to fail.
So good old.
It's now and you know when I can't help myself
I'm not a sweet bird, I'm from a soul yet
Try to keep my distance on now
Because you'll be the same
I'm not in the midst of the pain
It's Kirsten Gray, blood from a stone
From the pot-save music network of course
Links to everything that I've played in today's show
In the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
My email address at them at botcho.com
And just looking at the talk shoe interface here
Lots of people with lots of comments
But you guys should be calling in
You know, don't just listen in, call in
Next time, tomorrow
Alright, that's it for episode 7-25
With a daily source code
I'll be here all week everybody
I'll just talk in the background there to Jay
And you said, how long are you going to be in San Francisco?
I don't know
A week, 10 days, something like that
I have to be home by the end of the month
I don't know for sure
Anyway, for those of you who called in
Thank you very much
And we'll try it again tomorrow
And I'll try and post a link with some stories
To look at earlier on in the day
And so we can have some rants and raves
Looking forward to it
Until then
Live your life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear