What better way to start your day than with a hot cup of coffee, the financial times,
a little DSC-810.
Well, you might want to go to the bathroom first.
Here's Adam Curry, and the Daily Swordsman.
I was $16 million worth of airplane straps by yesterday, and the next generation
radio content in my ears.
We don't need a speed increase in-
I like to think I'm trying to teach the intro-
I'm just taking this feeling curry.
So far, now I don't love when it's time to explain, but it seems like things are just
kind of insane because the world is crying, and nobody's listening so please leave
a message on my cell phone.
Let's see, while it's been there, the baby going well, and the guy on TV, it's like a
phone, and so why you wear it tonight, it's a never-definery surprise, but I'm taking you all
right now, she's so stupid, I don't know much, I don't know too much, but I know it, she
is what I love, it's what I love, it's what I love, it's what I love, it's what I love, I'm telling you,
what I love, it's what I love, it's what I love, it's heart is so bad
I love, it's just bugging like I love every parent,
I love, it's what I love, it's what I love, nothing got below media, but saving the day,
Let me be new, still the bullshit views
I think we're losing this fight
Sponsored to fight, blood, light
Now we're walking the gas ball
Taking the black, jeans out of the bottle
And we can't put it back
I'm in love with someone
Well in my brain, can't see the storm coming
It's coming, it's way too much
I don't know too much
But I know this, she is what's on
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Come hiї
I love you
I don't listen to you
She is walking
I love the guy
I want you to be
But I know, Still theuntime
You gotta be
Just one bass
I think she's sexy after Fiji and this I've been my right politics, you for my everywhere
at the Fii, I don't care!
I don't care!
I love it.
That's a success is messed up.
Take these stars, Cody, eight Zero Nine.
Tell the shehred Charlie on every where hey, everybody, how you doing.
One show, Charlie this week, oh my goodness, not a very good record.
But all for a good cause first of all, welcome to the show, David Source Coda, as I said,
episode 809, we're getting up there on the numbers these days.
Beautiful day in the affluent suburb of Suri known as Gilbert in the, in the curry
Remember, I see blue skies, couple clouds, nice and cold, the perfect flying weather.
Of course, I'm going absolutely nowhere.
Lady Patricia is on her way to the Netherlands for her two live shows this weekend.
Next weekend, she'll have off and then the weekend after that is the finale.
The grand finale, I'm actually going to fly over Comheller Highwater, hopefully with the
Delta Sierra, if not with the Juliet echo, with the echo Juliet.
Actually it's echo Zulu as their code, which is easy jet.
My favorite airline when I fly.
Well, what's been going on is, it's just been crazy busy.
Of course, the move is starting to spin up, we got the keys to the new Casa, which I think
indeed is going to be named the Curry Terrace, it just has nice ring to it.
No illiteration, unfortunately, I'll just have to live with it.
I got a great office, I cannot wait, so this is, of course, as a terrace house in London.
Very typical, and so you have a, you walk up a short flight of steps to walk into the
house and then that's where you have the living room and we've got an overhang and
conservatory at the back, and it's really fantastic, you can also walk down the steps
from the front or internally, of course.
And on the, I guess that would be the Sutara, is at the back is a huge kitchen with another
aga, which I'm very happy about, because we've gotten quite used to the aga cooking.
If you've never seen this, look it up, A.G.A. of Gulf of Alph, the aga oven, often discussed
on Noah Genda with my friend, John C. to Warach.
Of course, we've got the teenager apartment out back, which is right outside of the kitchen,
so, you know, she can come in and get her midnight snacks, and we have the whole house
to ourselves.
Now, on the front of that is where I get my new office, it's probably in size, it is probably
somewhat smaller than the attic here, because this is kind of a rectangular shape, but
it has very high ceilings, which I desperately need, because I've been doing, finally,
I'm getting into video production.
It has taken me several years of focusing a lot of attention on the management sales,
etc.
So, we're at a place now, we got our new CEO Jeff Carpin, I really got to get him on the
show, we've just, you know, we've been all over the map, getting stuff done.
So finally, I can get into some production, you've probably seen at mevio.com every
single day.
There's a new little, at these days, it's like three minutes, three, four minutes,
highlighting stuff that's new on across our four networks for that day, so that's men, women,
music, and tech, you can play those channels, they roll out one after another, it's literally
in one of our channel systems, so one show, one episode plays after another, I'm very happy
with it, advertisers are happy with it, and it's looking cool.
So now I want to get into video production, and it's been, at least, what has it been,
five, almost six years since I blast work with the final cod pro, probably version 2.3,
or something like that.
Well, they're up to version 6, and I will reiterate what I said many years ago, the
guys over at Apple who work on Final Cut Pro, or really Final Cut Studio, I should say,
because that includes live type, motion, color, you know, you have your cinemas tools,
which I don't use obviously, but as soundtrack, pro, how it all works together, these guys,
they are smoking good dope, and they should be sharing it, because whenever I'm thinking,
if only I could do this, it pops up as a possibility.
The thing that has really been just so incredibly daunting is understanding the formats,
the sizes, the compression, the compressors, to use, and I have to say, good old Dexter,
Christina's boyfriend has really been helpful, and he's, he's helped me, he's set up some
lights here, which, I got the new lights in now, I was basically using the equivalent
of desk lamps, I still don't have an official, green screen, I've been using this
blue window shade that I found at home base, which is kind of, you know,
as a home home improvement store, and I hung it up right behind me, right behind the desk,
and so I've got that actually, it's still Dexter's camera, I've got one of our HD cameras
coming in. This is just regular DV, big red hat light, and it's been a lot of fun
figuring out how to do this, and it's just given me so many ideas of things I want to do,
I'm thinking of two shows that I want to put together, one is tentatively titled,
my gear, because I've got so much gear, and people are always talking about it. Why don't
just do a show where I show you my gear and show you how I use it, how I have it set up.
So, not like a feature review show of all, here's what the new Nokia can do,
now, but show you how I use the system, how I use my phone, how I use my
certain types of software on my computer, but it can also range from my airplane.
We can do an episode about that, it can be anything. So, my gear, I think, is a one show I
want to put together, the other one, which kind of came to me last night, since a lot of people
have been asking me to do a politically oriented video show, particularly at HQ, they've been asking
about this, because they listen to the DSC, it's going to say DHL, they listen to the DSC,
and they say, I can't you do like some kind of video thing, and I'm thinking, yes, and it hit me.
They work for us, that's the tentative title of the show, and it's going to be perfect, because
there's so much video, official news video, which I can use under the auspices of fair use for
news, and they work for us, will be a news oriented show with commentary.
And I'll show all the, every episode, I'll show one crazy video where you can see what
government is really doing, particularly what they're saying. The stuff that we talk about all the
time, the stuff that is on C-SPAN, but that never airs on the news. There's a lot of that over here
in Europe too, a lot of stuff being recorded in the European Parliament that never makes it on
a mainstream television. So it's that kind of stuff that I'm working on. So that shouldn't have,
you know, so yes, it's been hours every single day, and I, you know, I got all set up, I got a huge
terabyte drives, I've got my USB hub, I'm really getting my shit together, got the wireless mouse
out of, and using the trackpad on the, on the laptop, I've got a, you know, huge mega honker,
quad processor, G5, whatever, coming with dual screens. I won't use that until we're in the new
place, but I've had set up there. Nice cup of tea. I even got my old, uh, Maharashi mouse pad out.
I got to take a picture of that. That'll be a part of my gear. I'll show you that, my Maharagi
mouse pad. It's more than just a mouse pad. It's a, it's a lifestyle experience.
So none of that should have really slowed down at least one show earlier this week. We're
at not for my dear friend, Michelle Harper, uh, outstanding citizen in Gilford, uh, who was
run a business here for 17 years known as, currently known as Harper's, but he has several, he has
an entertainment complex, right in the middle of the, um, of the industrial part of town,
or the, I should say, the, um, we're the offices are. So, you know, in a, in a good location,
fantastic parking. Now he has Harper's, which is a nightclub. He's got barmombo. He's got, uh,
the lines, then, which is the lap dancing club, which, if you have not heard that edition of
Noah Genda last, uh, yeah, last Saturday, John C. Dubork, and I talked about a Noah Genda that
mevido, mevio.com, uh, very different from other lap dancing clubs I've been into. And I,
you know, and myself and the lady Patricia, we're, uh, we're a big, big fans of this. It's, uh,
it's stress relief. It's, uh, we believe it's good for guys, and, and it is completely a, um,
a feminine power trip. If you, if you ask me, that's my personal, uh, experiences that, uh,
when, when, when that's, when there's lap dance time, uh, the women performing the lap dance is
in total control, which is kind of, I think, what guys like about it. It's probably a lot
less sexual than it is just about control. And sex may be all about control, I guess. Anyway,
you probably know through listening to this show over the past four, five years that, you know,
I've, I've learned a lot about, uh, certainly in the United Kingdom about the councils,
and the councils have a tremendous amount of power in this country. They can order telephone,
taps, email, taps, uh, route through your postal mail. They can do all kinds of nasty things.
Plenty of news articles about that on the source code drop, uh, which, uh, please take a look at it.
If you're new to this, drop.io slash daily source code. Man, we're doing seven pages a day of
information, and it's all good. There's no way I could, I could go through the 20, 20 to 25 pages
from the past week, which I, you know, it's just, you can't catch up. There's, there's, there's no way
to do it unless I was doing this show daily, which, uh, it could ever be this long. That's for sure.
Anyway, so he was, um, called to the Gilford Hall, which, um, is right in the middle of the
high street for a hearing regarding, um, his license. Um, they want to review of his license.
So it was licensed to operate as a, as an entertainment center to serve alcohol, etc, etc.
And it's not, it was not a, and this is why I was so fascinated and I went to the proceedings.
It is a, a hearing by the leaders of the council. So it's not a judge, not a jury, but yet,
they are going to determine whether there should be a review of his license. So they have legal
powers, of course. Um, and this was brought on by the Surrey police. If you can believe that,
the Surrey police say that there is so much violence and uncooperative behavior from his door
staff, that, uh, they believe that what's going on inside must be 10 times worse than what they're
seeing outside. And therefore his license should be under review. Again, Mr. Harper's been here for
17 years. And, and, and, and, and, big disclaimer, I love this guy. He crashed like Christmas
party about a year ago. He's introduced to me by another friend of mine, the Super Agent Keith
they ship. And, uh, lovely guy. And we stated his house in France, uh, we've met his mom, you know,
we're almost boyfriend and boyfriend. But he's, uh, he, he's a good guy. He's an entrepreneur and a
very free thinking spirit. And, uh, if you live anywhere in Surrey, you've probably seen him in the
Surrey advertiser regularly. Because he fights it. He fights them all the time. All the time. And,
and that's probably what, you know, what clicked about us both the most. He's a real doer man.
He says screw it. He'll go out and he'll, and he'll fight. So, um, now they've, uh, they took
them to the Guild Hall, which is where they used to hang people in the high street right outside, uh,
from, uh, there's a balcony there. We were actually in that balcony room, which I'm sure was the room where
they sent people to the gallows. And, um, and, you know, it wasn't a legal proceeding yet, you know,
they acted like one. But the thing that really freaked me out as I was sitting there is right at the
beginning. They started with all the CCTV. They had a presentation. They had a whole screen set up.
They had multiple shots, 10 different movies, slow, slow mo versions, and let me tell you.
This shit is like television. We're talking full 24, 25 frames a second, panning, zooming the whole
deal. However, no audio. And, um, and of course, only one perspective that not switching back and forth
between shots. But, but what blew me away is how the, uh, the, the lawyer for the police,
how he set up each video. He would tell you what happened inside the club based upon accounts
from the people who were ejected from the club. Who, of course, were drunk in 99.9 of the
cases and gave drunk testimony and exaggerated. He didn't mention any, any, um, counter, um, or cross-examination
information from the, the staff. And I know all the staff. I've met them all, you know, they're
good guys. And you know what? They kick, drunks out. It's like that. And if they assault them, they'll
assault back. I mean, it's nightclub business. It's, I've been around this all my life. This is the way
it goes. In fact, two officers testified on the spot, um, in this hearing, which was not a court
proceeding and said, uh, yeah, no, it's the same everywhere. It's not like, uh, like, as any different,
which is kind of funny. I think they, they didn't get the memo as to what they were supposed to
maybe they're afraid because these are the guys on the street. So then the, uh, so this, uh,
this lawyer, he would set it all up and get you in a frame of mind and then roll the video and then
give play by play. There's no sound. He's providing the voice over. It was exactly the way
reality television is made and it was certainly not honest. And how can it be factual at all?
You're just seeing shit. You know, there's, uh, one scene, which is where dormant, you know,
so it's like this dormant grabbed her cell phone camera because this girl was, uh, video taping
him, uh, being abusive. And he took the camera and smashed it on the ground. And then you see the
video, you couldn't tell from the perspective, but I could see basically just from experience looking
at it. She had it maybe four inches away from his face. I mean, that's intrusive and it's
and then after like a minute, he grabs it and smashes it on the ground. Look, I'm not defending
one way or the other. What blew me away is the use of CCTV footage in basically railroading this guy.
Now, there are two things that play. The reason why the police are doing this and specifically
against his bouncer's his door staff is because all of Gilford, uh, and perhaps all of
sorry for all I know, uses bouncer's and security staff from one firm, from one security firm.
Mr. Harper does not because he wants to have his own people and they all, they all are under,
you know, whatever guidance of the security industry administration or whatever they have to be licensed,
et cetera, et cetera. But of course, you would expect that this one company that provides all the
bouncing staff is filled with X-Cops and it's the cops who are bringing this against him. So
we know what that's about. He basically get rid of all your bouncer's bringing the guys that we
pre-approved, a disgusting display, literally disgusting, but what made it even crazier is this
insatiable, um, quest by the, and all women I might add, all women, and women you wouldn't touch
with a ten-foot dick that belonged to a guy on the other side of the earth. Just, uh, and you just
want to, you know what I mean? It's, hey, I, I just, I'm not, I mean, look at them.
Whew, which is tough for me because I can always find something beautiful in all women, but
I, I found them to be incredibly evil. And they want, I'm to make a long story short. They were
saying, look, you, cctv, because, you know, they say, one of the complaints was, well, the cameras you
have in the club, you know, they're not sufficient. There's no obligation, by the way, under the 2003
licensing act, to have cameras inside the club. Michelle Harper has about 40 of them, mainly at
cast registers, coat checks, you know, really for his customers, security that people aren't
ripping them off, and a couple of the door. But this was really all about these women who lead
the council and can phone tap you, do whatever you want, they want the cameras inside the
lap dancing club. That's what they want, and it really came down to that, we want cameras inside
the lap dancing club, because, and this came out today, and then it also, and that all, it all
clicked together for me. I, well, actually, I guess it happened yesterday. In the, um, what does it
the Queens? I don't know what the hell it's called. They had something in Parliament, and they're
talking about what, you know, what laws are coming and what they're going to do, they want a crack
down on lap dancing clubs as an article in the show notes. It's actually an old article from
2008, but this was, I just read it in the times yesterday. Um, you know, councils are powerless to
stop the spread of lap dancing clubs and licensing laws need to be tightened up. They want to, um,
they want anyone who has a lap dancing club to be licensed under a sexual encounter club,
i.e. a brothel, and, you know, the things are saying, lap dancing clubs are in contradiction
to efforts to promote gender equality. You know what, there has to be an end somewhere to the stupidity
of this. It is, it is an emotional stress relief. And by the way, I think women would enjoy the
same benefits of lap dancing, but there's not enough of them that actually, you know, do it,
go to lap dancing clubs, you know, or there's not enough clubs, obviously at Chip and Dales, but
and by the way, in all honesty, the penis is not a very attractive thing to look at.
So, I think women, most women think that as well. But, um, it really gave me an insight into
what is going on in the United Kingdom and, and where it's going, you know, this along with, uh,
with now arresting people who frequent, uh, or make use of sex workers, um, if they are
under slave trade. Of course, that's horrible, but please go after the slave traders and
not the Johns who are just out there for more stress relief. And obviously, I'm not saying that all
prostitution is is good times, but the extent that this is, this can only lead to one thing
to domestic violence, increase domestic violence, rape, just just Sodom and Gamora and violence
in general amongst the civil public. And I've lived in countries where prostitution is legal,
and of course, lap dancing is no issue at all, such as the Netherlands, very, very low, domestic
violence, rape, very low in teenage pregnancies, very low in rape. Meanwhile, it's the same
story police who killed a guy in Guilford, killed him, an unarmed man, oh, it looked like he had a
gun right outside the Guilford, because the usual guy was very confused, he was depressed according
to his family, and they, you know, we that choppers chasing him for an hour, and then when they
finally caught up with him, put a cap in his ass, killed him, killed him, a man without a weapon,
killed him. So they work for us, I guess, is, uh, oh, man, oh, man, oh, man, oh, my batteries
are hold out for the entire show, it's going to be a long one, my friends, like very long one,
dear Mr. Corridor, yes, I have listened to several episodes of your podcast, no agenda, yes, I must
commend the war act on his excellent work, from what I've heard thus far, I must say that you often
come across as an egocentric asshole, you seem to think you are American, Dutch, and British, yes,
I understand you have lived in each of those countries, yes, however, you will not British in
the slightest sense, oh, and it's insulting that you would ever try to insinuate that you are,
okay, just listen to yourself, yes, and that's so called English that spews from your mouth,
you talk us a rubbish, you are an idiot, yes, you are disgusting, yes, I hope one day you can see
how much of a scumbag you really are, you know what, you really tell you really made my day, thank you so much,
Gives me some, with my car, hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show, I'll
review left for dead on the Xbox 360, take a look at Guitar Hero World Tour on the PlayStation 3,
you can win copies of Prince of Persia for the 360, and I'll look at the best casual party games
for Christmas Day to play on your PlayStation 3, that's all a Gamesweasel.com.
There's no main priest's voice, just he's a legend, it's no instead, there ain't no plan to walk,
so we'll just shoot you in the end.
Yeah, that's what they want you to think, man, that's what they want you to think, man.
They're pirates, I, oh, the dog is unhappy downstairs. Well, you're in for a long sit, because I got
a long way to go. A couple more things about the UK, and I talked about this on Saturday with
John, as well as you haven't heard about it, it's really important to look into what is happening
here where an opposition minister of parliament was arrested. His home search by the terrorist
anti-terrorist brigade, because, well, essentially, because he's leaking out the shit that the current
incumbent government is doing, all the mistakes, and Jackie Smith, the home office, what is
her name? Home office secretary or whatever? Like homeland defense. She's in charge of the police,
essentially. She's denying everything, oh, I didn't know about it, if I didn't know about it,
you know, it's important. This is what, this is the stuff that happened before the second
world war, my friends. And it's happening here in the United Kingdom. I know the good article,
which I won't, I won't read, but I do want you to take a look at link in the show notes at
dailysourcecode.com, also across post that are curried.com, from the Daily Mail, which is, there's a
lot of good stuff in the Daily Mail, or the mail online, but it's from the Daily Mail, Richard
Little John, title of this. If I'm not here on Friday, you'll know I've been nicked,
which is basically saying exactly what I just said. Hey, you know, if you go against the government,
you'll get arrested. And this is what they're doing. It's actually taking place. And a YouTube
video as well, which you must have a look at, it is fantastic. And she could actually be right
on the gilford council. You'll take a look at her, you'll take a look at her, and you'll say,
oh my god, he's so right. He did when the dog does, you know, the house is empty.
Maybe it's the window washer possible. Well, he gets all up. He's too old to get that upset. I
wish you wouldn't do that. Also, according to the Daily Mail, just to show you how the
crunch is progressing here in the United Kingdom. Thousands of homes worth 250,000 a year in the United
Kingdom now up for sale for under 100,000 pounds, unbelievable what is happening with the prices
of housing, unbelievable. And this is, uh, uh, there's something wrong with my, uh, my wireless mouse here.
I'm going to have to stop this recording, go downstairs, and talk to the dog in a minute, because
it's really putting me off. Thousands of internet users have been told they'll be taken to court
unless they pay hundreds of pounds. That's, uh, these days only $147 for illegally downloading and
sharing hardcore porn movies. Yeah, just when you thought Hollywood was after your bucks. Oh, no,
German company called Digi Protect claims. The users are breaking copyright law of course they are
and they're demanding out of, out of court settlements, 500 pounds and we won't take you to court.
It's just like the RIA. You know what, peeps? This is crazy. You know, we can just go make our own porn.
We don't need these guys. It's not going to need German porn. I'm not, you know, fan of porn over here.
Not a big fan of German porn. It's, it's, it's usually German porn. I find to be
Bushy Harry and
Tom Bushy and Harry.
Something like that. Oops, sorry about that. This is what I wanted. Hey, Adam is ship long time.
Caller, um, adder to the drop by O site and all kinds of things like that. I hope you're doing well, my friend.
Doing good. Um, kind of interesting thing going on right now is a matter of fact. I'm in a little town called
Clinton South Carolina, you know, hotel room here. And I was an interesting conversation I had with some of the people here.
They're having Congress come in to town on a sportsman's retreat.
And from what I've had it's being sponsored by three big oil companies. No kidding.
And so I decided I would go up to the old computer in my room and
try to research what that might be. And you know, I've looked everywhere. I possibly can
and can't find any information on it. No, it's course not. So I thought that was kind of
interesting don't you think? And it's optimal that. It surprises you. Bye. Doesn't surprise me.
I were the disperseist. We climb in what was this. We come in pieces. I said to bigger and so we come to work.
The landing coming into my white scrams. Well, it's just the five days. We will like all.
So we move here. Come on. Fresh way home. The signal for the day.
We took this time. No man has any right to buy. I'm so near the private guy. My fifth and
bow down. That took the land. Now everywhere the world's spring up a day. Come on.
Dying like the loose inside us. Well, the pudgy does last. We never know. Like time
into hell. We will not work in the nicer. We've got a green of these. The rich while
poor men stall. We will be together. We need no soaps. We will not bow to the masters
up. I went to the lords. We are three men. Now we are poor. Take us all stand up for glory.
We stand up now.
From the men of property, the orders kind. They send the hard men and
they begin to push to wipe out. The diggers climb, tear down their cottages. Destroy their
corn. They will disperse but still the vision lingers on. You poor tycariate. You rich
tycariate. He says, was my little comment, treasure it, for every one to share. All things
seem common. All people one, we come in. They steal the order sky to cut them down.
Yeah, it's a little bit of a history lesson there on the Chuck for you 809 on a
Fubar Friday afternoon. The world isn't neat upside down even more when you hear
That the French are now
And was funny because we were just talking about this
Johnson de Borgreck was telling me about the truffles he had eaten
I don't know if you have ever had a truffle, but
the French are now essentially planning to clone
truffles and create them synthetically of course why not the world is indeed upside down
I can I can hear the window washer
He'll probably stick his head up right in front of my window in a second until it should be kind of weird
A couple more good data points for you from the drop drop.io slash daily source code
the whole Mumbai
slash
Bombay killings are
Are baffling to me baffling and there's you know there's information coming out sporadically
I could probably do a whole show just about that in general
Don't tell me my mic is running low is it now okay?
Could do a whole show about all the disinformation or the weird things stuff that just makes no sense
But I will point out as this article from the times does
that the top anti-terrorism officer in Bombay was
a specialist in so-called encounter killings which is exactly what this was and he was killed
during this horrible ordeal and I just want to point out that
If if you know this really gave me a little interesting perspective on the on the terrorism debate
So this is being called in the you know India's 911. It's terrorist terrorism
If there really were terrorists in the United States as an example with all those guns all those hundreds of millions of guns
Wouldn't this have happened the long time ago? No because terrorists don't usually want to go out and kill people
governments go out and kill people
Yes, there are some terrorists of course
Of course, but if they really wanted to do it it would have done it
Seriously this was this was not hard to do unless you lock down the entire city of Bombay
Which of course is coming next that's what it's all about every single country in increased homeland security
Increased border protection controls increased airport security makes me want a puke
If you would like to see
Lindsey Williams if you don't know who he is he's the guy who was accurately almost perfectly predicted the price of oil and how the true owners of the earth the energy a
Leat are controlling us and
Controlling the price of oil and are now out to bankrupt the Middle East. There's a great new Google video
Where he predicts the next 12 months. It's a multi-part Google video
There's a lot of background in it that if you've
Never heard of him before you don't have to go hunching around for other stuff because he actually gives you his background
Which is very important and key to his story
landmark case in the European court of human rights
That and this has been all over the news that if the
If your DNA is taken this was a British case which was taken to the European human rights court
In fact, this happened with
Two gentlemen from Yorkshire I believe
Their DNA was taken upon arrest. They were then exonerated
Not charged with anything and they took they took this the court is at hey
You know our DNA should be erased from the database if we didn't do anything wrong
And luckily the human rights
Um
The European court of human rights said you're right indeed
But the thing of course that is nuts is that it shouldn't be taken in the first place
Yes, if well
It'll never get off. It'll never get out of the database or it'll get left on some train or some car seat and
It's all a part of the big plan the part of the plan that is to get all of our information control us give us ID cards
Keep us as hat little fucking slaves keep working keep paying your taxes and
Present electobama is just as bad when it comes to that
Good article in the show notes about how obama vows US military rule over the planet
Because we're gonna have one million soldiers
Working to secure the homeland
One million soldiers and
Already they have five battalions just in case there's any unrest during the credit crisis
Which of course is no it's it's beyond a crisis. We are going down the tubes no stopping it the
The bailout now in the United States 8.5 trillion dollars. I'll talk a little bit later on how
There's even discussions that the United Kingdom is going to convert to the euro
It's going to happen and all they're doing now is keeping the shit afloat until obama is
President the minute he's president and he knows it's coming he's part of the plan
That's when it ruled that's when the wheels come off this thing. I'm talking global meltdown the minute maybe a minute
Maybe two minutes after he's president you know Joe Biden this said it
Someone is scyping me and it's very irritating so between the dog and the Skype it's a complete football
Hey, Kerry you're watching this I haven't heard from you in a while bus
We're moved to the
Cree terrorists is going well
That my loves a lady p
So I was just gonna to the BBC hopefully
You caught this one there talking about a
Transition team for Barack Obama and I think it's talking to one of the
Coffee representatives for
People behind the change dot
Website yeah, yeah, yeah, I've you know that this is all coming out of course as a lot of stuff is happening the the bomb bay bombings
The financial crisis and boom boom boom boom all these announcements are being made
A lot of people are still staying in the same spots such as our Secretary defense Robert Gates the same guy was been operating under bush
Taking over from Donald Rumsfeld the evil position
True Uber warlords there. He'll stay on yeah, and Hillary Clinton a Secretary of State sure
He's got a nice body count attached to her name. They're talking about a
The Barack wanting to improve
You know government transparency
Yeah, and they said something very interesting and might be a topic worth looking into about how
You know the text messaging the emails that we sent in real time or by passing the
Filter or quote during the campaign
Yeah, yeah, this is uh, this is a very interesting topic you're bringing up here Russ
I am by the way still receiving email from Barack Obama and
Very plough he's the campaign manager. They're both listed on the emails and they're doing parties and get together and
Hold on here it comes
I thought I had the sneeze, but it went away crap. I hate that
Yeah, there's still emailing the propaganda is still flowing
This is the direct this is what changed. Gov is also about is about getting the word out directly going around the news filters
Yes, indeed
I wanted to use this in the white house and
And this interesting that you know initially I thought it was
Good have the news being that filter and so you know on the one hand
I say well obviously the news I think by and large has failed in that regardless or leave it not being it
Poeton is it can be or should be and
You know so I said on the one hand, you know, I like that there's more direct interplay
That's the same time. I said don't I have to question you know
That just seems like right for a prospect again without some type of analysis
Now when it then you can probably get a whole of this in terror to party you know
It sounds like but you'll act directly in our action
And I don't know what do you think Kerry you think this is something that will help with transparency
You think it's just they
Employee to get kind of into people directly without the
The interference wasn't so well figure to be a topic to discuss in the DSC so
Great air hope you win love you. I mean it and
They'll work for us one way or the other peace
I'm at Russ. Thank you so much. Yes, very good point
I think there are this has already been implemented. I think it's genius strategy
Of course they're not gonna go around there
They're butt buddies from the mass media because that's that's how we elect presidents and that's how we control the pop the populist
But instead of releasing talking points
They're just gonna put it all out in the open like change.gov
You know everything is out there. You know about all this increased security. We're gonna get about the
The soldiers protecting the homeland hint a lot
So there's no culpability, you know, it's like hey, man. We're just gonna put it all out there and then
Because you know the American public
Well the world in general doesn't read. Yeah, we'll read the paper and we read about you know the gossip the gossip section
That's all we care about. We read headlines
So they can now spin their own story and
Kind of hand. It's it's basically it's giving the press
Even less work to do
So they'll write their own headlines. They put it out big on change.gov. They send it through email and every single new story will be
You know Barack Obama communicated to the American public into the world today that bloody bloody bloody blah instead of people going out doing
Investigative work and finding out what they're really up to but in fact, it'll actually be there in the documents
It's already unchanged.gov. What is coming? You can see it happening. You can read all about it extra x to read all about it
I should look that up from Tommy the musical
No, no, no, this is a brilliant strategy has nothing to do with transparency. It's kind of like that internet thing though
Oh, you should be transparent and be able to triangulate and you know if the lies are gonna be there
Doesn't it doesn't have to be a lie
We're so stupid. We just let it all happen
Great article that was left on the drop
It was funny the American people demand to know who sent you
Obama has lived for 48 years without leaving any foot prints none
There is no Obama documentation no records no paper trail none. This is no accident
It's being done on purpose with media help but to serve home and why
I'm just pretending I'm not hearing the dog barking in the in the background, okay?
And they go on to say
missing or hidden documents on Barack Hussein Obama an original vault copy of certificate of live birth in the USA
has not been released
Certificate of live birth released proved to be counterfeit. That's the one from Hawaii
not released Obama done a marriage license not released
Soutoro done a marriage license. That's
his mother
Adoption records not released
That's so as I guess his mother's adoption records
school
application has been released
Puna who school records not release that's in Hawaii selective service registration
Released proven counterfeit
Occidental college records not released passport Pakistani passport not released
Columbia college records not released Columbia thesis not released Harvard college records not released
Harvard law review articles none
Baptism certificate none medical records not released Illinois state Senate records none locked up
to prohibit public view
Illinois state Senate schedule are they lost all other Illinois uh they lost
His state Senate schedule all other Illinois state senators records are intact law practice client list not released
University of Chicago scholarly articles none
Very interesting and so of course the
The crux of this article is
You know this guy is the mentoring candidate by the way
Was not for John McCain and Sarah Palin either
App to I'm anyone who's gonna
In the United States who's going to stand by the Constitution gets my vote it's that simple
That's what was set up that's how the country was set up and when we go and we'll actually I'm gonna
Read you another piece once again from at the end of the show
If you deviate from it then you're going against the laws of the land why do you think this thing was set up this way
Democracy republic set up by the French
initially
Who say they need the biggest condoms
I love this
Hold on pop up you're really that
I'm sure this was some kind of report some kind of survey the friends say they need the largest condoms in
Europe while the Greeks get by on smaller ones you know according to a
Europe-wide study by a German consultancy that provides advice on condoms i.e. the condom industry
The snappily named singing based institute of condom consultancy
Asked ten and a half thousand men and twenty five countries to measure their penis and enter that number into a database
Oh my god if if if the DNA wasn't enough now we've got them put in our penis size in databases
You need an oracle for mine
From those undoubtedly accurate and entirely true responses they found Frenchman on average claim to need
15.48 centimeter long condoms six point oh nine inches
About three centimeters longer than the Greeks whose condoms size requirement was the most modest
Amazing
The French have big dicks
Okay, let's hear from your frogs out there we want to know if this is true so you we can put it in our own
DSC database the DSC PDD the daily source code penis database got to love it
Hey Adam out from out wrong.com here in Texas
Hey man
Come to weigh in on the true currencies of yours
Oh yeah, yeah, this is a GOD gold oil and drugs three true currencies of the universe
Which of course is an acronym for God I agree with the GOD but I also have to say
Food
Food is definitely a currency. I'm reminded of the scene of Black Hawk down when
He local warlords are killing people when the
Eight food arrives oh you're so absolutely true
Or right on that it is the truth and there's counterfeit
Currency when it comes to food when talk about that in the second counterfeit basically genetically engineered counterfeit
Currency if you consider food to be a currency. I think you're right though it will become a currency
We know that predictions for next Christmas the best gift you'll be able to give anyone will be food because we're going to get pretty hungry
And that's logical
It's logical it's all part of the currency system coming buckling coming to its knees farmers cannot get
Credit or loans for fertilizer
Okay, you know what that means we're gonna lose out on the crops. We're gonna lose out on real food and
So obviously food is definitely
Currency in that situation been secondly weapons. I think weapons. I can't say I agree with weapons. I'll tell you why in a second
Next one example of a currency specifically like
You know nuclear weapons high technology weapons, but even just you know small arms
Definitely to be used as a currency and then finally you know what I disagree because the United States government uses drugs to buy weapons
They this is what's happening. They get the the poppies
You know, they protect the poppy fields and I've got a star and that's what our troops are doing there most of the time
Productions up 125% since the Taliban wiped it all out our troops came in. Well, that's up back again
They transport the coke in the heroin back to the United States that gets sold the money goes right into Wall Street companies
because they're the only companies that are allowed to take money from
From abroad without
It going through all kinds of complicated systems or scrutiny and
Then the basically by a weapons with that and send it back to cause mayhem and other parts of the world
So I would have to say that weapons not a currency drugs
Trump's that one in this case
They are radical feminist catalyst the first thing became to mind when this conversation came up was sex
And sex is a
Is of one of the ways that women have been able to use or even maintain any power at all in the current
And wow, that's a that's a big one man. Oh, boy. I
Don't think I disagree with you. It's not a currency
sex is
An necessity of life like oxygen and
Like oxygen in the near future or today already and like water it can be purchased
With GOD gold oil or drugs. So I I you know
You I think you're taking it to a very difficult level. I'm too much of a feminist to agree with you on
You know what if he if we were both on the same
You know on the same side on everything the show would be boring. We've got to have and that's the whole point
It's not like crossfire, but you know and I kind of enjoyed slowly reeling him in and just the other day
I came up with a theory and John said shit you could be right about that so no, no
It's challenge and I like it that way and it's not abuse and and I love him
He's the only guy that will listen to my to my ranting consistently without condemning me
Or our friendship I should say and also this global warming skepticism that you have is a
Relient retaining and it's good to hear somebody else out there who doesn't buy
That it is absolutely certain that the anthropogenic
CO2 production is
conclusively causally related to global warming. So great here
Yep, thank you best sharing show business
Okay back to the to the food. This is a Yahoo article which you probably want to
probably want to read about
Just about what this is here's what I like about this article is called food crunch opens doors to bioengineered crops
What I like about it's a very factual article about bioengineered cramps being grown in China
Surgeon cost population growth and draw it and other setbacks linked to global climate change and links to all kaita
I'll just throw that in myself our pressuring world food supplies while soaring prices on the street of triggered riots and raised the number of people going hungry
To more than 923 million according to UN estimates almost a
A billion people hungry in the world
The fuck are you complaining about sitting there listening about some bullshit about your job or whatever
You're not hungry yet a billion people going hungry and that's according to the UN
Can't even trust their numbers
With food demand forecast to increase by
Half by 2030 the incentive to use genetic engineering to boost harvest and protect precious crops from insects and other damage has never been greater
But of course we don't actually know what this does to your body
You know the variety of
Vegetables and fruits
That you can eat is diminishing
You know how many different tomatoes tomatoes
Can you buy in your supermarket go count them if it's more than four a BMAs but of course there's a hundred different varieties
And it same goes for carrots and for potatoes and you name it
No, no, it all has to be brought back. It's all bioengineered and we don't know what this is doing to us
I do know one thing we're not looking much healthier as a populist now. Are we?
Thank God for Prince Charles who's coming out against this stuff
He may be the shill after all
For the first time the food and drug administration has issued a warning that the mercury contained in silver dental fillings
May pose neurological risks to children and pregnant women this the first time that they're actually
Advidding admitting it. It's a neural toxic effect
And I'd like to point out that in many of these vaccinations that the government is trying to force on you
Certainly on your children they also use mercury
Mercury is contained in these vaccinations
And it is extremely toxic and it is killing our children go ahead. Do your own research
You'll find out that mercury is very a little tiny trace amounts not a lot needed
But it's being used in vaccination. So let's help them trip over their own stupidity of
Even admitting to this
Mercury is a well-known neurotoxin that can cause cognitive and developmental problems
Especially in fetuses and children can also cause brain and kidney damage in adults
Crap I have gold. I don't have silver no silver in my mouth
Okay, let's take a little break you see what else is going on in the rest of the world of podcasting
Just clips and what you would have heard if you're releasing the podcast you know member
Before the world wide we have seen some nipple was enchanting
Will our first hand that you better not take that fine little nipple for crayons
Man
Yeah
Yeah, that's the story.
Did you think you're gonna throw the such a junkie in the room?
And yes, the satellite repair minute.
So, it'll be WFETN and the second board.
Hope you like those things.
And please, check out the party cast.
It's roughly 30 minutes of mostly rock and roll,
although as you can tell, we do play.
Quite a bit of other music.
Thank you very much.
I'm proud of you casting with Adam Curry.
This is the hit test.
It hit test number 150.
No, goalless!
Hey Adam, how are you doing?
I'm good man.
I feel like shit and I sound cool.
Sound shit, unfortunately.
It's alright man.
But this is the...
And the first three episode of the hit test, it's number 150,
and it's somewhat special.
So, okay.
We're in trouble.
Number one.
Yeah.
Not too hard for a Dutch guy.
Gold nearing radar love.
Hey man.
Almost three years of this hit test.
Damn, that's a lot.
Number two.
Down, down, down, down, down.
From a health fiction.
That would be...
This is where this Dutch episode,
George Baker's selection and a little green bag.
Oh, I know these are easy.
And the final one is number three.
Yes.
Seven, nine, nine, nine, nine.
Number one.
Venus, shocking blue.
Marisa ferris, unfortunately passed away.
Another Dutch man.
All Dutch.
It's time for the answers.
And this week they're all from Dutch bands with international hits.
Of course.
One hundred fifty.
And this is answered number one.
Two stars.
title at BANN.
radar love the golden earring
heaven driving on our hands wet on the wheel
and let's have basketball now shifting gears
we got the name of the call
radar love
we got the name of the year
oh radar love
answer number one the golden earring
radar love
answer
hello Adam
this is George Baker
this is his last number
hundred fifty
five through number two
is my hit from 1969
little green
back
that's cool man
behind
just a kind of
little time
man
what
it's
bad
Your answer number two
a
This is better than I could see her playing.
This is a lot of beauty and love.
All of her name, maybe.
She's got it.
Yeah, baby, she's got it.
Well, I'm your Venus.
I'm your mind.
You're so desire.
Ancestry number three, shocking blue and Venus.
And that concludes hit this number 150.
Excellent.
So Adam, yeah, how does she do this week?
Well, I mean, obviously, you're not going to need these right.
I wouldn't really been a disgrace to the country of the Netherlands.
Yeah, six out of six.
Got all the titles in the band's right on episode 150.
Yeah, Ancestry Edition, any other hit list.
And also the iTunes link so you can buy the tricks.
Featured on the hit list online.
Or to be found at hittest.mifio.com.
For the 150th time, thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you, young.
Everyone else, thanks for listening.
Next week I'll be back for another hit list.
And I'll be feeling better as well.
We hope so as well.
So until then, have fun, take care.
And remember to try to think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
Well, he did a show.
Congratulations, young.
Fantastic.
Once a week, 150 episodes.
Hittest.mifio.com.
You got iTunes links.
You can go purchase the songs.
It's a good deal.
Or, of course, you would go to emusic.com.
Slash DSC.
And you can get 35 songs for free.
By the way, there's a whole bunch.
And you guys are using it.
BrooksDon.com.
We've got eHarmony.
Where you.
Um, I like this.
This is very successful for us.
eHarmony.com.
And you can go to dailysourcecode.com or create.com.
It's crossposted there in the show.
No, as you can find all my codes and direct links to getting these great discounts.
So BrooksDon, of course, is kind of like the sharper image for outdoorsy stuff selling
a shitload of stuff there.
And, of course, it's normal because we're all looking for a good deal these days with,
you know, we're watching what we're spending.
So, you know, it's not like we're not buying at all, but we're doing it to
actually the go daddy domain names.
Of course, dirt cheap can get it cheaper.
All these deals.
Budget rent to car.
But eHarmony is three months free.
And that's a really good deal.
And we're signing up people left and right.
A lot of lonely people out there.
And if you used my, my code for eHarmony.
And you found a mate.
Or if you found no success.
I'd love to hear from you.
In fact, on anything you purchase through the DSC codes,
let me know how went for you.
Dog is still barking.
Fuckers 15 years old.
You're going to bark yourself to death.
And it's just because of the window washer.
I guess didn't pop up on the third floor, which is too bad because that means he
also doesn't get his check.
From salon.com.
Interesting little thing, a little history lesson on the history of,
actually it's called a brief history of the criminalization of cannabis.
I'm sure you've heard of the movie.
Refer Madness, which gives you some of this history.
But this goes back to 7,000 BC.
And takes you through the 1700s, the 1800s.
A lot revolving around cannabis and hemp in the 1900s.
The Mexican connection.
Jazz, alcohol prohibition.
Journalism, newspapers.
And of course, all the way to that was even a marijuana tax in 1937 that was proposed.
It's a great, great page to have a look at.
And you should ask yourself.
You should ask yourself.
Why is it illegal?
Some that I'm surely going to use on under my gear show.
When it comes out, it's not until mid 2009.
Have you seen the Nokia N97?
Hello, boner time.
I mean, I love the E71 that I've been using.
I mean, I really love it to death.
You know what?
I get a hand people this phone.
I gave it to AL.
He's our, our CTO.
I handed it to him the other day.
So I wanted to show him something.
And he had it in his hand.
And he said, crap.
What kind of phone is this?
Because when you hold this thing,
the works are the same thing.
It just feels good.
You know, and that's, that's the one thing.
The Apple iPhone never felt good.
It felt like you got to hold it a certain way.
Because otherwise you'll touch the screen.
Just didn't feel ever really feel perfect.
But the E71 is outstanding in the hand.
If it's well in my hand.
But this E, this N76 essentially is kind of a hybrid.
It's like the E71 had sex with the N810 and came up with a
Symbian based keyboard slide out pop-up screen computer on the go.
With a phone built into it.
Very excited about that.
And I am definitely going to beg the candy man to get me an Evel device.
I'll send it back.
I'll buy my own.
I just want to be the first one of my block to have one.
This seems like it is the perfect device for me.
Even though I'm so happy with the E71 so far.
And of course, Nokia knows their phone shit.
So you know that all the other stuff is going to work.
Now let's see how they do on the multimedia computing.
It'll do flash, by the way, as well.
The specs are just amazing.
All right.
So let's talk about money for a couple of minutes here.
As we round out the show.
Like it or not, right CNN.
There's only one way we're going to be able to pay for our
ballooning deficit.
Now $8.5 trillion added to that.
Thanks to the bailout.
It's a value added tax.
This is in place in many countries around the world.
It's in place in the United Kingdom in most of Europe.
Essentially, it's a sales tax on top of everything.
And by the way, prostitutes will have to charge it as well.
Which is fine by me.
Because if it's a business expense, you can deduct the VAT.
I'll make it a business expense.
I need to de-stress before the show.
A lady Patricia approved, obviously.
Otherwise nothing will happen.
Highly possible, if not inevitable,
that Americans will soon live under a radically different tax system.
One that the pundits and politicians aren't talking about.
It's called the value added tax or VAT.
I'm pretending not to hear the dog.
A very good point.
Boy, you know that thing is like 17%
19% in the Netherlands.
21% value added tax in Belgium.
Yeah.
We're going to pay for it.
That money has to be paid for.
It's going to be us.
We're going down the tubes while it takes place.
Interestingly enough, this is not happening.
These bailouts or not happening in the same fashion in Italy.
Checking in from the hills of Florence is my sister Willow with a little bit on Italian bailouts.
The lack thereof on the banks or perhaps a lot of them when it comes to airline industries.
Willow, come on in.
How are you doing?
Hello, it's your sister checking in.
May I say, by the way, Willow, you're disgraced to the family.
Listen to this audio quality.
This sucks.
You're going to have a lot of complaints, Italy.
And I'm checking in with regards to the bailouts.
Because I thought it was interesting to point out that in Italy, not one single bank has been bailed out.
Or actually has had the need to be bailed out as far as I know.
And there was something going on with it when it created so.
But as far as I know, no banks have been bailed out.
And I have my own theory of why there is no need.
Definitely the Italian government is all linked to bailouts.
Just think of Italian.
Yeah.
They bail out industry all the time.
Even carbon companies.
And they bail out fiat I think or alpha or whatever.
Most disastrous bailout.
Anyway, my own theory is that it has never been easy in Italy to get a mortgage.
And they never got into the mortgage hype.
Up until five years ago, it was almost impossible to get 100% value mortgage.
Which by the way, is a huge mistake.
A hundred percent of mortgage.
I'm a total believer in down payments.
It should never be a hundred percent.
You need that wiggle room for precisely what just happened,
minimum ten percent.
Some countries.
Some banks require minimum of twenty percent down payment.
So I think that's probably a very good thing that that didn't happen.
Three years ago, I couldn't get a three year mortgage.
Everything was twenty or fifteen years.
So they never got into the mortgage hype.
Not into renegotiating mortgages as I know out of experience.
Yeah.
I gave you some advice on this.
But the banks no longer can actually negotiate your mortgage.
I mean, used to be, you get your mortgage from your local bank.
You run into, you lose your job, you run into some other problems.
You go to the bank managers.
I did.
I gave my situation.
Here's what I can do.
You know, here's, you can talk to my boss.
You know, where am I going?
New job.
You can, you can book banks.
They want to work with you.
But what happened is they took these mortgages, chopped them up into millions of pieces
and sold them off as assets.
And we're added to balance sheets worldwide.
This is, you know what?
I'm going to turn the noise gate on.
Then I just won't hear him anymore.
That's going to help.
Now, I don't hear him anymore.
So, you know, so there's no one to go talk to because your mortgage was split up into thousands
of little pieces.
That's why there was no one to go to.
No one to talk to when you want to renegotiate your mortgage.
A big part of the whole problem.
Not our mistake, of course.
Not easy to get done here.
So that just means that the, and I know that I was parents and actually
turns out that the most solid bank in Italy is my very own bank.
The claim to go pretty real, who denied my renegotiation.
So anyway, I just thought that was interesting.
And another thing is that Berlusconi, with all his faults,
that he has, I thought was interesting that he,
doesn't, isn't bailing out banks or the CEOs or whatever,
but he's bailing out the little people, which.
Okay.
Oh boy, okay, sis.
I'm ready for it.
He's bailing out it.
So you're going to tell me that Sylvia Berlusconi,
who owns all the media and is the El Presidente,
that he is a good guy.
And he's thinking about the little people.
Look, I know, no matter what.
Sorry.
I said, look there.
I hate doing that.
Please.
He does not love you.
Let's hear.
Let's hear what this savior is doing for Italy.
I even be a good idea either, but I definitely, you know,
using his bailouts.
And one was already six or seven months ago.
He passed the degree, ministerial degree,
where banks were obliged to sort of
renegotiations spreadsheet scheme.
I'll call it.
The user words were the spreadsheet,
where you pay less.
You go back to the interest rate.
They had in 2006.
And then the monthly payments are at that.
The interest rate for until the mortgage is ended.
And then at the end of the mortgage,
they see what you actually had to pay in or in.
Yeah, that's called a balloon payment.
Okay.
This is happening, Europe.
Why?
This is not just a good old Sylvia there.
Gordon Brown announced this just yesterday.
One billion pound bailout package for the little people.
For the wee people.
As our mom would say,
it's bullshit.
Yeah.
So what they're doing is they're going to.
So everyone got popped through these adjustable rate mortgages,
which, of course, tripled your mortgage payment almost overnight.
And, you know, it was like a three year or five year arm.
Adjustable rate mortgages would arm stands for.
But what they're doing is just delaying the inevitable.
So at the end of your term, which will be in two years from now,
then you get sucked.
When you absolutely can't use it.
When you're completely ready to sell your soul,
that's when they're going to come in and throw you out on the street.
I think the economy's getting better in two years time.
You're wrong.
It's going to, with the way that they're interfering,
it's going to take 10 years.
We'll have a 10 year downturn.
It's going to be horrific.
So all they're doing, again, is just keeping all the shit afloat,
get Moroccan and Barack is going to be the one to communicate directly to you
through change.gov.
How you're all getting fucked.
More than, you know,
when you pay the new,
you'll keep on paying.
And if it's worth me,
actually your mortgage finance is earlier.
It's a whole complicated scheme.
But it's not complicated.
They're just deferring it.
And they make it look complicated.
So you don't understand it,
but all you know is you don't have to pay,
you can start paying less than they want from you.
For now,
but they're going to hit you at the end,
and it will come as a crushing blow,
because there's no way anyone can make up for it in 24 months
time.
There's just no way.
It's going to be a huge balloon payment.
And that, that,
my fellow chuckleheads is when you really get shocked.
We did apply for that,
which will bring our mortgage payments,
you know,
we'll reduce them by 300 euros a month,
which I think is a lot of money.
So that's a scheme that he passed.
All right,
let me just bring up the calculator here.
Okay,
so we're talking 300 times 24
is 30,000.
Wait, and that,
and do that right.
300.
I did it wrong.
I was 24.
7200.
So in two years time,
Ed minimum,
but they're going to charge you interest on top of that.
You'll probably look at a 10,000 euro nut.
You're going to have to satisfy
or they'll kick you out of your house.
I don't want to sound like a downer here,
but this is just delaying the inevitable.
It's a temporary bailout.
It's like giving you a credit card for your house.
Because there's any way you can pay more,
do it.
That's my recommendation.
Or pay nothing,
which is what a lot of people are going to wind up doing.
Pay nothing,
and just let the bank fail.
And then you'll probably have a couple of years
until they're already changing all these laws.
Now,
if you're a six months behind on your,
on your payments,
they won't kick you out.
They want to move that.
It's all coming in two years.
You guys want us going to happen.
2011.
Ooh, gee.
Conveniently moving in in 2012,
that's when everyone's going to get hit.
So, yeah, short term.
It sounds good.
It sounds like silly,
oh, your buddy,
but he's not.
He does not love you.
And although interesting,
I'm not only 30,
I read today in the newspaper.
Only 30,000 families have used this,
this spreadsheet scheme for a good negotiation.
But what they said today,
because they,
I don't know if it's already past
or whatever,
but they're having the crisis package,
the package deal.
Yeah, crisis package.
This is the stimulus package.
I haven't even heard this comment from Willa yet,
but I'm going to guess it has to do with spending money
for you to spend somewhere.
So, we can continue to keep lending going
and continue to have the system working
where we enslave to the energy elite with debt.
And in the crisis package,
which I thought was very funny,
among other things like,
they have the social cards for people
with a certain income.
Yep, social cards,
which means you're registered in the database.
They know who you are.
They know where you are.
They've got your biometric data.
Of course, a national ID database.
That's a great way to get people to sign up.
They'll be the first to be put in the camps.
The wee people.
And also that for the year 2009,
anybody with a mortgage,
with an adjustable rate,
will not have to pay more than 4% interest.
That's without the spread.
I mean, for it is just a pure interest,
not with the spread point to whatever in it.
And anything that is above the 4%
the Italian government will pay.
And let me just think,
who is the Italian government?
It's,
where do they get their money from?
Oh yeah!
They get it from you,
willow.
So they're going to have to pay for that.
The only way to do that is through taxation.
And if they don't do it through taxation,
they'll print the money,
which means you get inflation,
which means prices go up,
which is a hidden tax,
which means you're paying for it anyway.
It's a trick.
It's a shell game.
It's just moving money from one place to the other,
but it's your money.
You are now paying for the people who can't pay for their mortgages.
People who are paying for their mortgages,
now will be paying for people who can't pay for their mortgages.
That's what it is.
It's called socialism,
throwing a little bit of fascism.
That goes very well with Sylvia.
So say that right now,
I'm paying 6%
and but the actual interest rate
was probably at 5% you have a 1% spread.
Then the 1% that I don't pay,
the time government will pay.
You will pay for it.
Not the government.
The government is not a company that has,
it's you are the government.
You're paying for it.
You don't think that it,
because it's not coming directly out of your pocket.
You're not sending it directly to the bank.
It will come out of your pocket
through taxes.
They're going to have to pay.
This is what America doesn't understand.
Fucking boneheads.
Eight and a half trillion dollars.
Someone has to pay for this.
That's why it's going to probably be a value out of tax
and a whole new funding system.
For this whole year of 2009.
So I thought that was a very interesting bailout.
But what you like even more
is who is paying for this.
Actually, you're a dishonor radio
right before coming home.
So I haven't verified it.
I haven't Google it yet.
But what they said on the radio and the news
was that there will be the porn industry
who will be paying for this.
Okay, wait a minute.
No, we were now interested.
The porn industry.
Okay.
Let me hear how the porn industry
is going to pay for your mortgage.
Because the raising,
I'm not sure what tax by 25%
on the porn industry.
There you go.
I risked my case.
That's like taxing beer 25%.
The porn industry is not humongous for no reason.
Hey.
Tell me how a sondo doesn't have an account somewhere
on some porn site.
Tell me he doesn't.
He's going to be paying for it
through his porn consumption.
Well, I don't know.
You might even have a porn.
I got a couple porn accounts.
I'm not ashamed to say it.
There you go.
Now it's finally out.
The porn industry.
You know what?
Porn is going to save us.
In fact, this is a very good idea.
I think the porn industry should stand up and say,
yes, we'll be happy to bill you out.
Because you know why?
Get rid of all the stupid restrictions.
Stop the idiotic filtering.
Let the people have their porn.
I'm happy to pay 25% extra.
If that'll keep you at housed.
Absolutely.
Porn is like oxygen.
Sex is like water.
It's necessary.
Give the people their porn.
Tax them to high hell.
That's fine.
But just remember, at the end of the day,
it's the people paying for it.
Not the government.
So anyway,
that was just my update from the bailouts in Italy.
And then that's it.
Yeah.
Nice day.
Alright, Willa.
Thank you very much.
Love you.
See you down, my friends.
Thank God the porn industry is there
to stop us from the free fall.
She's a good girl.
Love's in my heart.
Love's Jesus.
In America too.
She's a good girl.
It's crazy about elves.
Love's for us.
In her boyfriend too.
It's a long day.
Give the people your seat on.
There's a free way.
Run through the arm.
And I'm a bad boy.
So don't you miss him.
I'm a bad boy.
To break in her heart.
I'm free.
Free for this.
Free.
All of them are walking through the valley
Move west down, venture over the wall
All of them are standing in the shadow
In the good girl, they're home and broken the halls
Are free!
Revoluvel!
You're free!
For free, all in power, free, all in power
Free, all in power, free, all in power
I wanna glad to have you, all in power
All in power, all in power
I'm even scared, gotta free, all in power
How is nothing gonna leave this world
Now I'm free, all in power, free, all in power
All in power, all in power, free, all in power
We're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling
We're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling
complicated. So you could do that for me, but I highly appreciate it. I want to
half end of the show. And nearing the end, but I just really want to get this
whole financial crisis straight in your head. So you know that, you know, you've been
bombarded with this on a daily basis. Oh, hold on a second. What's this text
message from my lovely wife? What does she say? Okay. Someone wants to talk to me. I
don't care. Now, right now, I'm talking to the chuckleheads. Peter Schiff, who has
been on CNBC, he's been laughed out in the past, but he is called everything pretty
much that's taking place on the money. It's the same things we're saying here,
same thing I've been talking about for the past year. But very interestingly, when he was
on CNN during this interview, he really laid into what's the name Becky, I think.
Well, one man he's been keeping a close line of the government. Sorry. And he gets
cut off at the end. They literally pull the plug on the sidelight and old Fox news
trick. Listen to what he has to say, though. And this is on an update on the Dow.
Let me see what's it up load at the 24th of November or the Dow is up. I can see on
screen, 335 points. Listen to him break it down very simply. Listen to Becky
try to interrupt. You're really frustrated. He keeps going. And then they just
disconnect him. They pull the frickin' plug. Now, to plans, all of them, they
is a piece of chef, he's the president of Europe, Pacific, capitalists, a global
investment strategy company and the author of the little book of bull moves in bear markets
or to be a good reathie. So, if you want to be now, like, let's talk about city group
given that we've just been hearing from Alan on that. You know, they make the decision
about the bailing city group out. They say it's to important to fail. They don't say
that about laymen. They're considering what they're doing with the auto companies that
the moment they haven't made a decision about that. We think of these decisions at this
point. Well, the only good decision they made was letting Lehman Brothers fail. And somehow
they think, that's the source of our problems. What about all the companies that they did
bail out? You know, we're in this mess for a reason. It's because of government spending
because too much debt. And these bailouts simply, you know, we're accumulating more debt.
And the government is broke. You got a Brock now talking about $700 billion a stimulus plan.
Maybe a trillion dollars. We don't have any money. You know, we need the world to lend
us this money. We need the Chinese. We need the Japanese to lend us money that we can't pay
back because no, we're going to do with the money. We're going to spend it. And then what
is gone, we're going to be begging for more.
Yeah. Let's talk about this stimulus package because this big and it's getting bigger by
the day. And Brock Obama's put this group of, it called an e-grip together as it were.
We're beginning to learn the names of those. Are they the right men and women to the job
at this point? Look, if they think the economy is more stimulus, they don't, they shouldn't
be in these jobs. You know, we should, we don't even need any economic advisors. We should
abolish them all. I mean, look at this mess. We're in the, they're giving bad advice. We don't
know, this is so true. This is exactly what it's all about. You have to let the shit go.
The system has to come apart. What, what is happening now with all this money being printed
up? Which we can't borrow because the Chinese are going to borrow. They're going to lend
us shit anymore. You kidding me? They've already had to write off billions and billions.
No way. I'm nuts. They're not going to throw their good money after bad. The dollar is going
to come crashing down. It's being held afloat. This is all to get ready for President Obama
because he's going to be the Messiah, the Savior. He's going to make us feel good. But we're
getting raped. And the fucking has all, I'm sorry to put it that way. It's already started.
These stimulus. We don't need American spending more money. That's how we got into this mess.
We borrow money and we spend it. Now we can't pay it back. Americans need to make things.
Then you do go to work and then just save their money. We can't try to stimulate the economy
through more spending. And we can't do anything.
You're using the economy by more spending overnight effectively because you don't make anything
anymore. That's the problem. That can't change. Can it? Yeah, yeah. A lot of countries don't make
stuff anymore. That is indeed a huge problem. Oh, Lordy, Lordy, how I yearn for alternative
energy that really works and is propagated. Something you can just rub your hands together
and make something, make some spark or fire. Is it the ore going around us? It's something
is there. We're going to find it. We got to continue. Continue finding alternative energy beyond
wind and solar. Can change. That's a long term plan. Yes, but it has to change. And the government
has to let it change. The government has to get out of the way and let our phony economy collapse.
I know it's going to be painful. But it's necessary. We can't keep pretending. We have a
viable economy and expecting to rest the world to finance it. You know, we have to actually
make things. We need a real industrial revolution in this country. We don't need more economic
stimulus. That's more of the problem. And we can't keep rewarding people. Look at the city
core bank bailout. I mean, look how much money these executives at these companies make.
How can we let these guys pay themselves millions of dollars when the companies are broke?
I'm not going to make any money over there for years. So the government's going to keep giving
them more and more money so they can lavish it out on the executives. And now we're probably
going to have to bail out general motors because we bailed out city. You know, general motors
needs to fail. But now we've got to support the overpaid union workers. I ended right because
we're over with the support. He's trying to interrupt. She's like, she's because, you know,
she's got an IFB, right? They're telling her, tell them to shut up, get them off the air already.
Because this is on the day that Obama called for an ambitious stimulus plan. See an end being the
Obama station of the nation. They're trying to stop him. Like, she's trying to interrupt him.
We got to get this guy. Stop, stop, stop. He's making Obama. Our man. Look bad.
See you later. You let city bank fail with you today. Of course. I don't let AIG fail.
I don't let bear. There'd be a lot of firms that would be failing if the government had stepped
out of the way. But capitalism isn't about cropping up failed companies. We need to let them fail.
There's reason that these companies are going broke. We don't want to prop them up. Now, of course,
behind it all is the Federal Reserve. If the Federal Reserve had never intervened in the market
back in 2001 and 2002, had they not poured all this out? Note those dates 2001, 2002,
no George Bush came to power in 2000, 911 2001. Does it sound like a plan was being executed here?
I'm really starting to believe it. I'm starting to really think that conspiracy is for real.
And he's getting out. He said it all up. He's teed it up and Obama's going to make us feel good.
Well, he get the flaming hot poker up the rectum.
Fall and Wall Street wouldn't have gotten drunk. But they did. They made a lot of bad decisions.
Which is, by the way, just so you just to set it straight, just exactly why Sarah Pailman was on the
Republican ticket. Because she would have met, they thought, it's a hedge, right? You know,
she could have made America feel good. I think a lot of people believe in her.
And would buy her. She's great actress. Obama's a fantastic actor, you know, but she is just a great great great
actress and mill fee. And now we've got to suffer the consequences. But it's not fair to try to say that the whole
country that everybody around the world who's holding US dollars has to pay because of the bad
best made on Wall Street. Here it comes. All right. So given what you're saying, you say,
government get out of the way, uh, the invisible hand of the free markets work this time,
you be staring down the barrel of awfully difficult times for a very long time for many,
many Americans at this point. So you know, yeah, she's getting fed that you can see that this
information is coming into her ear. And she's basically saying, you schmuck, you shit,
are you nuts? You want to kill people? And he's about to say, oh, man, if we let it go,
this way, the government's going to kill many more. No, no question about that. But it's, it's
false to assume that the government can do anything about that. I am convinced that every thing
the government is doing to fight this off is going to make, uh, gone, bars. And I'm afraid we've lost,
uh, I'll guess that I'm sorry about that technical problems. But, uh, we heard, um,
his thoughts, uh, interesting ones, Peter Schiff, they're the president of Europe, Pacific,
capital, these things happen right. Well, news of, oh, man, 10 Downing Street, the British
equivalent of the White House denies a shift in Europe policy. The government is denied a shift in
policy on the euro after the European Commission's president said the UK was, quote,
closer than ever before. It's a joining. Right. It may not be the euro, but we're definitely going
to move to some other monetary unit. It has to. That's what they want. That's what this one
world government is about. That's what the, the new world order is about, uh, just a note of reference,
from money market monitor, all these links in the show notes, a daily source, uh, drop.au,
slash daily source code. Many Americans are pleased to see the federal deposit insurance corporation
to FDIC raise the insurance amount of bank accounts from $250,000 to $250,000 from $100,000.
This is, and I, and I, I'm just raising this because it's temporary. And you need to know that it
expires on December 31st, 2009. Again, I'm starting to see a plan form here. I've really, really
your government doesn't love you, but your bank certainly doesn't love you. Certainly not.
Yeah, Adam, it's Matt from davidmatcho.com. I was listening to your DSCS and when we was talking
about how the banks continue to find ways to take money from you, your money from you,
of many years back, I'd started a college fund for my children at Morgan Stanley. And, uh,
I'd let it go for many years and, uh, didn't notice that one of Morgan Stanley, of course,
the leaders of the reptile nation. That's where all these guys come from, including Obama's
fantastic economic team. This is home base, man. Morgan Stanley, uh, statements that came along
said that they're going to be charging a, uh, quarterly fee to go along with it. Now, I didn't pay
attention to those monthly statements. So, you know, error on me, but I was told by them,
well, there's no need to pay attention to this. This is a long-term investment. So, I had gone
about a year without noticing that they were taking out quarterly fees out of that until after that
year, I had seen that I was down about $120 that I was never going to see again. So, I called them
up, ripped them a new one, told them to send me a check for whatever the fund was worth and was
completely taken over by the banks. So, be sure to pay attention what you're doing when you deal
with banks. They're not always on your side. No kidding, Matt. Thanks for checking in, man. Good to hear
from you. Hey, you know, you could always leave a message either an MP3 that you upload to the
drop or there's a right on that page, a drop.au slash to the source code. There's a phone number
and pin code. You use that and then you can leave a voicemail message. Um, New York Times has an
interesting, uh, blog post titled The Worst is yet to come, almost like, you know, during Tom
Petty, I ran downstairs and I shut the dog up. So, I can turn off the annoying noise gate. There we go.
The Worst is yet to come, anonymous banker weighs in on the coming credit card debacle,
which is a good read. I'm not going to go through it now, but you should take a look at that. It's
in the show notes. Uh, and those are found, of course, at dailysourcecode.com and crossposted
at curie.com. Just when you thought that we needed, you know, a little break in the action, a little,
a little something from the European Union, perhaps, from maybe an expert.
Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip. Comic strip.
You just be a company, my friend. Hello, Adam. Hello, the fat carry. Use your eucrospotted tb. So,
today we'll have to tell you a story about Jean Monne, a French, who is considered to be one of
the funding fathers of E.O. Imagine, Monne bought a house in France from a Swedish politician.
The price was negotiated in the US dollars, but when the sale was taking place, he insisted on buying
it in French francs. And next day, after the sale, the franc was devalued many, many times,
and surprise, surprise, Monne was a member of the committee that oversaw the devaluation.
There are other words, funding fathers of E.O. Jean Monne was a congruent, a congruent, Adam.
But Adam, I have to tell you personally, I prefer a little bit of trickery,
conmanship than was, with killing of millions of people just because they are Jewish or Slavic.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, I don't think the evil uberlords and shadow puppet masters or the
energy elite, as I like to call them. I don't think they, I don't think they really care what religion,
background, creed, color ratio are. As long as you have money, they want to take it from you.
And that's, you know, devaluing a currency significantly. That's killing people. People can't
pay to heat their homes. People can't, you can't afford to eat right. No, no, it's, it's just as bad.
It really is. And I just want to remind everybody that there is a little booklet you can get at any
library, any public library in the United States. It's called the Constitution. It's what the
country was founded on, built upon. And it would be a great thing for all countries in the world to
have a look at it. It has been completely forgotten in particular, in particular article eight.
And I just want to, from time to time, remind you on what it actually says.
The important bits, I don't even know where to start. It talks about what Congress is allowed to do
and specifically what the states are and are not allowed to do. So let me just do a quick little
browser search there. The states, okay, here we go.
I'm not messed it up. Hold on. It's coin is what I'm looking for.
No state shall enter into a treaty alliance or confederation, grant letters of Mark and
reprisal, coin money, emit bills of credit or make anything but gold and silver coin a tender
in a payment of debts. And may not pass a bill of any attainer, expost facto law or any law
impairing the obligation of contracts or grant any title of nobility. But it says it right
there in the Constitution. You can only use gold and silver coin to tender in the payment of debts,
not paper, not fiat currencies, only gold and silver. Why is this overlooked? Why is this not discussed?
It is something that it's right there. It is the founding law of the United States.
And of course the Federal Reserve has hijacked our our system in America
and have created this paper currency. It is not backed or based upon gold. And what can happen
is exactly what happens to all central banks. That is what the Federal Reserve is. It was not
a part of the government. They have a contract with the government to lend the government money
and charge of interest. That's how we what we pay for with our taxes. And they have the printing
press and hands. This is exactly what happened in Iceland. And now in right cubic, as you know,
the country has broke thousands of Icelanders. There's only 300,000 of them. Mark the 90th
anniversary of their nation sovereignty with angry protests on Monday. Several hundred stormed
the central bank to demand the ouster of bankers. They blame for the country's spectacular
economic meltdown. That is what's that's what's coming. It's the way to do it and it's what's coming
if you're in the banking business. Get ready because we're coming for you with pitchforks.
And someone left this on the drop. I love it. Yank the bank. That's what it's all about.
Get rid of the central banks. Yank the bank. This is where we have to spread far and wide. Yank
the bank. The Federal Reserve and the Fed. Yank the bank. And the Fed. Yank the bank.
I love it. And there's one other thing you can do. If another were in Yank the bank mode,
anyway, an article from Newsweek. People nationwide may start hoarding their cash as
recession, recession fears grow. But in river west, which is in Milwaukee, residents have another
answer to their money trouble. They're printing their own. Check this out. That's legal, by the way,
because it's not coin. And it doesn't look like a US tender. It's the river currency. It's going to
be used like cash at local businesses. What they do is essentially it's giving you a 10% discount
or maybe 20%. So you go into any local store that's participating. Or in a bank, I'm sure it
would participate in this. You give a hundred bucks. They'll give you 120 bucks in your local
your local currency of your community, which now you can use as legal tender for goods and services.
I like this idea. I really, really do as long as no one's printing up tons of it. And it's
regulated somehow. Very interesting. Good article to read there. It's Newsweek.com.
Links in the show notes at dailysourceco.com and crossposts at curie.com. All right. One more song
as we get out of here. Remember, bear in mind, we need to end the Fed Yank the bank. And of course,
we need a little bit of holiday spirit. So no one better to bring that to you than the hives and
Cindy Lauper. I've bought no gift this year and I slept with your sister.
I know I should have thought twice before I kissed her. But with the year we had less and the dress that she
wore. I just went along for the ride and I came back for more. And I'm sorry baby.
I got a better, better, better. And I know you can use it now. So I know you can use it now.
And I know you can use it now. And I know you can use it now. And I know you can use it now.
We should always be late. We should always be late. We should always be late.
And maybe you left here that you thought was so cool. Right. But I was strong as I was strong yet.
I made a mistake and I risked all that fail.
I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake.
And I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and
I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I
I made a mistake and I made mistakes and I made a mistake and I made aragament and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and it, I made a mistake and I made a mistake which, the mistake and it, was like a mistake. The mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake and I made a mistake. and I made a mistake and I made a mistake.
It's me, it's me, it's me, it's me
It's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me
Stingelopper in the Heights
Christmas duel, did she actually sing I went down in your mother?
I love it
And wrapped up pickle of eggs, your own partner
They make a source code
And of course tomorrow I'll be back with you with the Noah Jenna
Cutten that with John C. Devorek looking forward to that one
reminder, if you're doing some Christmas shopping
Christmas shopping and you're looking for the frugal way out. We've got great gifts, great stuff that
you can buy. Go to the show notes at the bottom. You'll see all these links for GoDaddy, Brooks
Stone, E Harmony, E Music, Crap, Rovio, love that thing, by the way, that little robotic webcam.
It's all there and you can get great discounts that are greater than anywhere in the
brick and mortar in the brick and mortar world and online as well. You could find that at
dailysourceco.com and of course, crossposts at curie.com. So that's it. I'm heading into the weekend.
I still got lots of stuff to do even though what is it now? 340. Wow, we've been really
working it today, haven't we? So keep checking out mevio.com for the new shows, my gear, and they
work for us. And if you have any suggestions, just throw it up on the drop that's where I check in.
Many times a day, because it's an awesome place for the Charcoal Head community to convene and keep
each other informed and pass that out to other people. We'll let people know that we're really
collecting all the interesting stuff that's coming out that never makes the headlines on the six
clock news. And you've got freedom. You really do. You still have it. You still got some left.
You need to protect it. Fight for it. Enjoy it and live your life with passion. Another fine
video presentation. Stick it in your ear.