This is the real Tuesday world.
Welcome to the daily source code.
Can you dig it?
Here we show host Adam Curry.
Delta Sierra Charlie 738.
16 million dollars worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to wake up flying to the future.
The podcasting is a matter of curry.
That's the answer.
It's nothing needed.
It's real cold feeling when I'm making one thing.
It really needs you, really needs you.
Take yourself and feel it now.
When it looks good, what do you mean?
A real, really good one.
While I love you so much,
I feel it now,
Feel it now,
I feel the inside of myulated self love.
I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I
I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna get in view See how, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna
I'm too full, I let up cheese for
I had a moment fixed, don't mama, don't wanna get fired up in the hole
I like most, you're not, I love to chew some kind of bottle, but I ain't use the deal
You would say.. I'm kinda tripping the bottle, but there's things in the net
It won't be free for them, but I won't be ch
Because I wanna say, we're a whole street, I wanna work One straight from the oven that's all we got
I'll see you in the next video.
David Jo, Christine Malone,
expertly matched up by FWG,
along with Jimmy Hendrix,
Angel,
and Perfect Melancholy Melotune for a Tuesday.
Welcome to the daily source code episode number 738
from the first time,
Simon,
Simon Casting, I guess,
in a reasonable quality through live 365.
And that's, of course,
that set up as the reason there was no show yesterday.
I was totally fell into the trap yesterday.
I'm like, okay, I've got, I'm going to try something new.
I'm going to try streaming live in,
because that's the thing that really bothered me about talk show.
We had these interesting tests where you could call in
to the talk show number.
You would hear basically really crappy audio coming through,
kind of like a phone line connection,
even though it was through Skype,
it was still a dial in essentially.
And it just didn't sound right,
and I said, I'll get, let me fix that part first.
So, I've got,
I'm streaming now until live 365.
You can find my station.
It's Adam C. 1999.
Oh, shoot home on a second.
I just noticed I didn't plug my cut my,
the power cord in.
Oh no.
I didn't plug the,
everything's messed up.
I forgot to plug in the power to my MacBook,
but I still got an hour and 14 minutes to see.
We can keep the show rolling this way.
Yeah, so I had to get nice cast in order to use that.
And nice cast, and I should have known better.
Then I should have known better.
Name that song, young poet.
I should have known better that when it said,
hey, it looks like you have a new,
there's a new version of sound flower.
Now those of you who've been experimenting with
the virtual devices on the Mac,
you'll probably know what this is.
And I'm like, of course I want to know.
Oh, yeah, sure, I'll install that.
Why shouldn't I have a new version of something?
Dumb, because that, of course,
immediately messed everything up.
The entire setup I had going,
wouldn't work anymore.
And the reason why for some reason this new sound flower,
just it's a geeky thing.
This new sound flower doesn't,
I don't know.
It looks like a bug, actually.
Frequency sample rates being like round numbers,
like 4100 or 4800 or 9060 or 9060.
Instead of that,
there's a two at the end.
And the Apple Core audio does not like combining devices
that I've different sampling rates.
So, it took me a while to figure that one out.
And then, of course, I had to roll back
and, I messed everything up.
It took me a long, long time.
I wound up learning a lot of things about Ableton Live, actually,
as I was playing live music yesterday.
But it was cool because I could set mixes up
in the future before they actually played.
As the program was playing out,
stuff, so I did learn some things there.
But essentially, it took away,
it took away from our time together.
And I'm in a kind of a weird mood today,
because there's so many weird things going on
in the world.
There's just so many real major topics of conversation.
And people are sending me all this stuff.
Remember, you were the guys that really put the show together.
So, I want to make sure that I represent
all that you were thinking, including, of course,
some sexy shit from Cat and Chris.
And why not?
Adam's Captain Chris is a playman as podcast,
but hey, man, I wanted to bring her attention to a redhead,
flight attendant at Delta Airlines,
who is doing a new end flight safety video over there.
And I think once you see her,
you'll see what I'm talking about.
And it's the awesome to get her on the daily source code.
So I'll try to get some more information.
I sent you a link to the video,
so you can check her out.
And that's it.
And I hope all's good.
And see you at flight safety.
Yeah, thanks, man.
I looked at that video.
You can find it over to PlainMadness.com.
That's Captain Chris's podcast.
PLA-N-E.
PlainMadness.com.
I hear you.
How come I never have those flight attendants on my flight?
Oh my goodness.
I would sit in coach if she was giving the demonstration.
I would sacrifice all of that.
Lots of you responding to the conversation topics
from the past week or two.
Here's an email from Gordon Walton,
who said me this link,
which I knew nothing about.
Apparently,
in every single state in the United States,
newborn babies,
are tested for genetics.
You believe this?
And I was looking at this webpage.
I'm like, this can't be true,
but it's actually the National newborn screening
and genetics resource center.
And I'll put a link to this in the show notes, of course.
And I guess the main thing here.
Here we go.
Parent and family resources.
And they have PDFs available,
so you can see what tests are done
on a new Whoa.
Oh, oh.
Oh, don't do that to me.
She's breaking up Jim.
Alright.
Wait a minute.
Oh man.
Let me try this for a second.
Check it too.
Oh man.
Oh, I'm running.
I don't know what to do.
It's all necessary.
Well, I'd have to say,
that was pretty interesting.
Oh man.
You know what?
When something ain't broke,
Adam just don't go trying to freaking fix it.
Will ya?
I'm such an idiot.
Meanwhile,
people were Skyping and let me see if,
oh,
baby,
I can't take that file from you right now.
I can't take any files.
Anyway,
uh,
back to this genetic screening thing.
Hold on.
So here under the FAQs,
why does my baby need newborn screening tests?
Well,
answer most babies are healthy when they're born.
We test all babies because a few babies look healthy,
but have a rare health problem.
If we find problems early,
we can help prevent serious problems like mental
retardation or death,
or criminal activity,
perhaps.
Interesting.
Keep our eyes on that.
Uh,
doesn't look like the exact same thing we were talking about
over here in the UK,
that Scott will yard announcing,
hey,
we should have a debate about
screening kids five years of an older.
You know,
this is half thing again.
I don't know if I'm going to make it through this show,
where this crap going on.
Okay.
Um,
yeah,
we'll give it another shot.
There we go.
I'm just messing with the settings.
Now,
just trying to get it said,
so that everything works and doesn't fall apart on me.
It sounds,
it's something with the,
uh,
with the sound device that's messy.
You know what?
It's just messed up.
I'm sorry.
What can I tell you?
Um,
okay.
Let me see what other stuff do we have.
More email that came in.
Hey, Adam,
listen to the football Friday show at the beginning.
There was a mashup with Queens.
Another one bites the dust,
where they were playing it backwards.
I remembered in the old times,
used to play another hit test like game called
the back track podcast.
If I'm not mistaken,
whatever happened to that.
Says Antonio Solgado.
I don't know,
man.
I like doing it a lot,
but it just kind of disappeared.
You know?
People send stuff in and then they stop sending stuff in.
I pay young people to do the hit test
so that I know it's there.
Every single week.
I really appreciate the work that he puts into it.
Uh,
Let me see.
Oh, you know,
I did spend some time yesterday since I kind of blew the whole,
uh,
the whole opportunity to do a show.
And, uh,
and you know,
with all that live testing stuff.
Um,
I took another look at the Google,
the eye Google homepage.
If you look at this thing in a while,
they've gotten pretty sophisticated
with all the widgets that you can install on there.
And, uh,
in fact,
you can display like a Twitter module.
And, uh,
a Google reader module.
And, of course,
a Gmail module.
It really,
I have to tell you.
I was quite impressed.
I, um,
I set up my,
my Mac dashboard widgets.
I do use a number of those quite frequently,
actually,
just because one swipe to the upper left hand corner
of the screen with the mouse and it appears, right?
But having,
um,
a web browser page open with all that information.
That, uh,
that I'm, uh,
that I'm interested in,
just sitting right there and refreshing dynamically.
I'm,
yeah,
I got to tell you.
It's, uh,
pretty appreciative of it.
Jam on his,
uh,
oh,
by the way,
I'm, I'm looking at Twitter throughout this experiment with,
um,
Simon Casting on live 365.
Jam on says,
loving the live show experience even when it breaks.
That's probably the best part when it breaks, right?
Dave Johnson,
you are suffering from too much technology syndrome.
I'm hanging in there live, though.
Okay.
And, uh,
Marcel,
Delta's red head is indeed inspiring.
Yes.
That's cool.
You guys are out there surfing at the same time.
I'm giving you the details.
I love it, my friends.
One night only,
this Saturday at the Royal Albert Hall,
the All-Star benefit concert day eight has their meals.
That's right.
The former Mrs. Paul McCartney only received 50 million pounds in her divorce,
and needs your help today.
Schedule to appear.
Queen,
Robby William,
singing crazy little thing called love,
and fat bottom girls.
The reunited spice girls,
performing one of me,
John Melanchap,
singing,
kettle leg up,
Bjorn from Abba,
singing money money money money.
Elton John,
performing don't go break in my heart,
and special guests,
the radio city musical rockets,
and of course,
super tramp,
and featuring a special appearance by Sir Paul himself,
singing,
I'm blood to acoustic versions of,
something in the way
he moves her crap out of my house,
and I want to hold your leg.
Standing room only tickets
available now through ticket master,
and at all,
I have locations worldwide,
help Heather Mills avoid having to fly coach,
cook her own meals,
or drive her own car.
With a poultry settlement,
like 50 million pounds,
what is a woman to do?
To donate online,
go to www.conser-to-benefit.
That horrible one,
like at true.com,
or call 1-800-Lake-God.
Operators are standing by.
Markill's mother name call,
for someone who's almost
coming in his fall,
Heather Mills,
starring in Pretty Woman 2,
really,
I'm not a prostitute.
You know,
pretty twisted, my friend.
Now,
this request came through
Twitter last night,
I forget who asked it,
of course it has to go.
Back into my Twitter history,
and find out.
Of course,
she was female.
Requested the shillas with faithful.
I gotta tell you,
I have,
and of course,
it's spot save.
You know,
I have,
One, wouldn't me If I could dare to hate you
Oh, to me Won't let someone hate you
You don't need to call me, see me, I'll know where you are
If you don't do the face now, I know see me all
Oh, to me Won't let someone hate you
Just take it home, bringing you to me
What it takes to keep you faithful, faithful, faithful
Say it baby
Spice special Twitter request
However, actually I think we're singing the songs
She tweets me just now
Oh, man, I love that a lot
Actually, those of you listening in on the live stream now heard one of my secrets to success
You heard me pick up a broken link because the minute I cracked the mic at the end of that song
It went all ballistic on me again
I clearly have not yet figured out what the exact configuration was
Because it was working so fine before until I had to go and mess it all up
Andrew coffee sent me a tweet as well
He said apple rumors today on 3G apples up the shorts are not working
That's interesting
So we got some hot financial stock tips for you
Well, we're at it
You heard the intro today two today show
Which was a nice Michael Jackson slash thriller type intro
This is because Joseph Vela
Was hired by Sony BMG to create the thriller cast
Which is a series of podcasts individual episodes
With someone who has either worked with or been a part of the phenomenon known as Michael Jackson
And
Mainly as it pertains to the thriller album
Which was released what 25 years ago to date and my episode which I did a couple weeks ago in San Francisco drops today
In fact, I've got a little piece of it that I can play for just to give you an idea
And there's a lot of very interesting people who are doing these episodes
So you can find that at michaeljaxon.com slash podcast here.
This legacy recordings podcast is brought to you by icon collectibles
The Sony BMG
Sponsor of its biggest artists go to icon-collectables.com
Hi, this is Adam Curry of the Daily Source Code
And of course the former MTV guy
Welcome to my thriller cast
I'll play a first bit for you just to get a little taste of it
The first time I heard through actually I think I was in college
I went to college for about three months which is a very successful educational career
I was in West Virginia
But I remember very well when thriller came out
And it wasn't so much even Michael Jackson honestly that just blew me away
It was the production of this record
Alright for the rest of it you'll have to go to michaeljaxon.com slash podcast
Oh man there's also a delay now in my voice
So when I'm talking I hear it like half a second later
You don't want to know about all my problems I do you
Here's a cool piece of voicemail feedback
Actually I think it's this isn't even a voicemail
This is a full on full blown recording
Because my friends from Jamaica are tuned in
Mr. Curry
This is Dijamekan in New York
Lo me to introduce myself
Well, I'm a loyal listener of the DSC
And you know I've been listening for a couple years now
Yes, yes, it is true
You do have Jamaican listeners
Well at least one
That makes you cool. Cooler than you thought you were actually
Cooler than here
The here makes you
No, I was listening to DSC
And I was thinking myself
This is what I heard
Take a listen
I think I do our thing
What do you do every night
And if I'm battery if I'm not seen someone else
Really
This is very interesting on him
I was thinking to myself you know there are quite a few things that I am an expert in
Some some which I'll reveal to you later
But no, no this
This is definitely a part of my expertise
I'm thinking you know
I'm in New York I live in Brooklyn
Brooklyn
And she lives in Brooklyn
There's just no reason
This sort of thing to be occurring
I agree man
Okay
Yeah
She
She could use some help
And I
I'm volunteering to be assistant
To this this thing that is going on
That's right
I feel like there's a space for me
In this
One problem though Adam
Yeah, what's that man
I don't know her
And you are my gateway my friend
So Adam, hook it up
Hook it up
Adam, hook it up
I need your help
I'm in this senior brother
Let's get this thing on the road
Jimmy can in New York Adam
There's four
Folder, not a scruncher
Big hero who'll be in the upper blind
I'm only going to do this one time
Love you know
All right
Cool
Thanks for listening to today's podcast
That's the Jamaican in New York
I knew Savannah on the Charlie
I'm pretty sure I could help you
I do, it shouldn't be too much of a problem
I do have some Skype databases if you're interested
Somehow because we're doing a live today
I feel like it should be played more amusing
Is Dolce Vita right?
We are walking like in the Dolce Vita
This time we've got it right
We're living like in the Dolce Vita
I'm gonna dream tonight
We're dancing like in the Dolce Vita
We're like some music home
I love this made in the Dolce Vita
Nobody else than you
It's all it's night
Together with our love again
Another light
Before we're trying to say
You never live enough
Say you're gonna love enough
We made it down the Dolce Vita
We're living like in the Dolce Vita
I'm so alone in the Dolce Vita
Oh baby, tell the phone
There's magic going in the Dolce Vita
Nobody else than you
It's all it's night
Together with our love again
Another light before we're trying to say
You never live enough
Say you're gonna love enough
It's all it's night
Together with our love again
Another light before we're trying to say
You never live enough
Say you're gonna love enough
I'm at the first of natural
I was supposed to spend 36
I can show myself a spin the right field crowd
Thanks to you
There's been a few things I've been up this agreed with you in the past
For number one being the moon conspiracy thing
That was maybe last year or year before
I agree everything with what you were saying about the DNA
With the exception of the global warming thing
I don't think it's probably a good idea to be lumping that into everything
Because I'm sure there are going to be people who are going to try and scan you
And all that would be screen credits and all that's fake everything
But I, I honestly believe that global warming is true
And I'm sure you know there are tons of people who agree with me
But yeah, otherwise keep up everything from what you're doing on this whole DNA thing
That's disturbing
I, and I love you
And I hug you in right here and all that stuff
It's a music home
I love it's feelings that don't you've been done
Nobody else than you
It's all it's not to get along again
I'm not alive
In what we're trying to say
You never really know
Say you've got a girl now
We're living like a needle to die
I'm not a dream tonight
We're dancing like in a wheelchair
Nobody else than you
It's all it's not to get along again
I'm not alive
Before we're trying to say you never really know
Oh say you've got a girl now
It's all it's not to get along again
I'm not alive
It doesn't get much more 80s than that now, doesn't it?
It doesn't get much more 80s than that now, does it?
On your daily source code for today episode number 738
So I finally got everything kind of working and looking for some feedback on Twitter
And then what is Twitter if I show me?
Twitter error
Twitter return a bad request error
This happens when you exceed 70 requests per hour
Avoid running other Twitter applications or refreshing too frequently
Nice
So now I can't get any feedback either
That's what this show is all about
Experimentation
In the technical sense as well as in the
Well civil sense
The psychological sense
The advertising sense
Ooh, I should probably do an advertisement, that's a good one
Dude, have you seen the price on the Nokia and 810
How incredibly cheap that's become?
Especially with pod shows, exclusive 15% offer
If you want one of these internet tablets and by the way
I think they don't they also have
There was some tie in there with the e-music
Candyman sent me a note about that
Of course I promptly forgot let me just take a look and see
E-music
Luke, this is always a good way to do it
Here we go
Yeah, they work together
Let's put it that way
I'm not going to tell you about the e-music promotion
Just at this moment I want to do that on Fridays
Keep that kind of exclusive to Friday and the soundtrack of our lives
Oh wait a minute, Twitter
Rekindled all of a sudden, there we go
Brittany Mason on, good to see everyone in the house
Okay, there's something I want to play for you that
Without a doubt, we'll be deemed very controversial by many
But I really feel like I have to play this because this is a fellow countryman
In this case, a Brit, his name is Pat Kondel
And I stumbled upon this guy through a number of different avenues
You know the story about this Dutch politician, his name is Heardveilders
And although I don't think his party has any seats in the government
Well, I'm not even sure about that
He's in the government clearly because he speaks in the Parliament
So he has been promising someone say threatening
But he's been promising to release a 15-minute film called Fittna
Fittna of the movie
And this is supposed to be, well, some call it
Racist film, although no one has seen it as far as I know
His whole platform in the Netherlands is look
There's a million immigrants who have come into the country
And they are living by Islam rule, strict Islam rule, not all of them
Of course, but these are his numbers, not mine
And he's saying that a number of things, although I haven't heard him say everything
First hand, a lot of this is reporting, that's just out there
And that's, you know how that works, right?
I mean, I saw this happen with Pimfortan
There was assassinated one week before the general election
And this was in 2000, I believe
And he was so on track to win, in fact he won posthumously
So it was assassinated and his party won the next week
Anyway, won the elections
And he was basically running on a very similar platform
He was saying, look, you know, if people who are strict Islam
I want to live in the Netherlands, that's fine
But you have to live by our civil rules and actual laws
And he called, where do you call Islam?
He called it backwards, he said it's a backwards religion
And of course, in the strictest sense of the word, you'd have to agree
When it comes to general mutilation
You know, the women's rights
Honor killings, a whole bunch of stuff that goes on
Now, I have no idea what the real scale is of people who are
Fundamentalist, Islamist, or
Extreme Islamists, it's certainly not all Muslims
And it's not all Islamists, but anyway,
I guess what's happening is there's a conversation that is not taking place in Europe
And the conversation is what takes place behind closed doors
Where lots of people agree on what they're saying
But they never go out and say that in public
Can I get a break here, people?
No one will go out and say these things publicly
Because it's not deemed politically correct
But I do want to play this a piece of audio for you
Now it's rather long, it's about six or seven minutes
It's from a YouTube video, this guy has a channel
And he is speaking the way I've heard many many
Brits speak in the past couple years that we've been here
So I think it's worth it to have a listen
I don't agree with everything he says
Which I know sounds like a cop out, but it's not
Maybe I agree with what he says, maybe I don't necessarily agree with the way he says it
Or sometimes it just cuts the corners a little bit too short for me
But man, I've heard this conversation everywhere
First time I've actually seen a proper Englishman stand up and say the following
According to a recent opinion poll, many Muslims say that the way for the West
To have better relations with Islam is to show it more respect
And who said Muslims don't have a sense of humour
Given that Islam is officially above criticism in the West
It's hard to imagine how we could give it any more respect
Short of closing down all the pubs, growing bids and beating up women
Who don't want to dress like nuns?
Ah yes, of course, silly me
I think many people in the West are now realising that Islam has already been given far to much respect
Especially here in Europe, we're according to another poll
People now see it as a threat to their culture
The carry on accommodating it's every demand of course
But this is not because Islam is welcome in Europe, far from it
It's because people have been conditioned by the lie of multiculturalism
To believe that what they should think is more important than what they do think
Although people will criticise Islam in private
They know that to do so publicly, in other words, to be honest about their feelings
Would instantly make them racist and Islamophobes and Nazis and disgusting imperialist
Ethnocentric fascist bastards grinding their jackboots into the faces of the innocent and the weak
So best not make a fuss, you want to beat your wife and mutilate your daughter, be our guest
We'll even subsidise it because we want to be your friend
What's that? You want to destroy our corrupt society?
Well, that's our fault, not yours
Here, have some more money
This film that's coming out in Holland shortly, which has got the whole country in a state of heightened terrorist alert
Is yet more proof that everything in Europe now needs to be measured against the possibility of Muslim violence
Every play, every film, every art exhibition, every magazine article
In fact, our whole culture is now subject to Muslim approval
I just want to stop this guy there for a second
Boy, is he right there, huh?
Is he right there?
It's absolutely true that there's this meme out there, this vibe, it's like whatever you do
Don't say anything against Islam because it'll start all kinds of shit
Interesting though, huh?
Interesting
Because yeah, look, I even take God's name in vain on this program many, many times
Although people don't like it and they get angry with me about it
That's about the extent of it
But then this is Europe and we have a history of appeasement and caving into threats
Radical Islam knows this and is playing us like a violin
They know that Islam will never get blamed for anything in Europe
No matter what happens
So that for example when the Danish press reprinted the cartoons recently
Which was followed by a week of rioting by a Muslim youth
Copenhagen's chief of police refused to admit that it had anything to do with the cartoons
He said it was because they were born
Yes, that's right
They all rushed out and set fire to the city every night for a week for something to do
If only they'd had a table tennis club
The whole thing happened because three Islamic fanatics were caught planning to murder the cartoonist
Imagine how bored they must have been
Oh yes, also a newsflash for European journalists
An anti-Semitic attack by Muslims on Jews is not a conflict between communities
In case you hadn't noticed Islam hates Jews
Even if Israel didn't exist, Islam would still hate Jews
Their holy book tells Muslims that they should hate Jews
So I think you'll find what's happening is not a conflict between communities at all
But a violent unprovoked racist attack by Muslims on Jews because they're Jews
Just thought I'd clear that one up for you so that you can report it accurately next time
If you bother to report it at all
If we were serious about respecting Islam, we would give it an honest reality check
Islam needs to adapt to Europe, not the other way around
Now I know a lot of Muslims actually agree with this and they make an effort to adapt and to rub along with everybody else
Which is great, and it's very welcome
But we all know that a lot of others don't, which is why many European cities
Have large Muslim ghettos controlled by religious bigots
Where indigenous laws and values are increasingly unwell come
Places full of people who have no intention of integrating
And who want nothing less than the end of our civilization
While we pander and defer to them thanks to a biased press and complacent judiciary
And the kind of politicians you wouldn't wish on your worst enemy
Actually you probably would
And this situation is as much as threat to the freedom of ordinary Muslims as it is to everybody else
And it's a clear indication of what we need in Europe now is not more respect for Islam
It's less respect for Islam and more respect for ourselves
We need to stop pretending because that's what we're doing
Pretending that all cultures are equal
Where we can clearly see that they're not
Islamic culture is not equal to Western culture
It encourages violence against women against Jews and homosexuals
Its sanctions polygamy and marrying old men to young children in a disgusting
Travesty of human relations
Anyone in the West advocating these kinds of values would very quickly find themselves in jail
It's not equal, it's inferior
And given radical Islam's openness about it's totalitarian agenda
This is not something that should be encouraged in any way
It should be discouraged by firm legislation and by rigorous enforcement of the law
Remember the law?
Now I know that I'm going to be accused of racism and Islamophobia by the usual self-righteous pinheads
But I don't mind because those words have no value in this context
One has been neutralised by repeated dishonest misuse
And the other is just a bare face lie
Concorted by the political left in tandem with the religious right in a marriage of convenience
Which is well quite simply beneath content
A phobia is an irrational fear
Resisting Islam is not irrational
Pandering to it is irrational
Indulging the lie that Islamic culture is somehow equal to Western culture
While ignoring the victims of that culture is more than irrational
It's downright criminal
And if you really want to talk about racism
Then look no further than the poisonous fiction of multiculturalism
A divisive and patronizing racist ideology
And the governments of Europe who promote it are racist governments
The civil servants who pander to it are racist
The university lecturers who encourage it are racist
The journalists who lie about it are racist
And the ordinary people who say one thing in private
And another in public are cowardly racist hypocrites
If we can't bring ourselves to say what's in our hearts when it truly matters
Then we've already given up our freedom and with it the freedom of future generations
Which is something that we've got no right to do
We didn't earn this freedom
It was handed to us on a plate by people who did earn it with their lights
We don't own it, we're custodians of it
It's not ours to give away
So it's time to speak up Europe
It's time to stop whining and belly aching about the Americans for five minutes
And show a little backbone for once
Just once
Or do we want to spend the rest of our lives cowering like frightened mice
From a handful of violent bigots who think they have a right to poke a finger into our chest
And tell us how we're allowed to live
What we can and can't do say and think
Well, I don't know about you
But anyone who asks me that question is going to get a very short answer
And I'll give you a clue it won't contain the words Allah or Akbar
Peace
Wouldn't that be nice
Alright, so
How loaded is that guy?
I mean loaded with ammo
I wish I was that eloquent
Because in the context of what he was saying, boy, it made a lot of sense
And I think there's a lot of things we can discuss about this
In particular, that this conversation is taking place
I have seen this, I've witnessed this happening with my own two eyes
In the Netherlands
I hear it here in the UK and people aren't speaking out
I'm not saying it's right or wrong
But that they're not talking about it in public
They're keeping that behind closed doors
That is a fact
See on Twitter people are interested in
And whining out more about this guy
His name is Pat Kondel
You can find him at patkondel.net
P-A-T-C-O-N-D-E-L-L.net
Of course, I'll put a link to that in the show notes
Have you stuffed though?
You know?
And the thing that really hit home with me is this whole idea of the multi-cultural society
And I have to agree, I think that is full of shit
Alright, we play one more time
And then get out of your hair
But that's homework clearly for the rest of the week
What do you think about this guy Pat that Kondel is saying?
It's funny how the smile in your eyes
I slowly fade in with last days and July
The year is drowning like the calendar rose thin
And set away again
You're back against the wind
Don't know how cold will blow your ball
And I will hold my head again
But you can't run from our juice
Oh, the light in red
Don't say it loud, you'll be no less than what's on your face
I swear I'm falling for that song that you will stick
I can't shoot, I'll leave it, I'll take it anywhere you
Don't say it anywhere, you'll be no less than what's on your mind
You'll be no less than what's on your face
We're the living, London Rain from the Podsafe Music Network
Very appropriate, I think for this part of the show
Lots of Twitter's coming in
Christian says, Adam, most of those things could also be said about Christianity
I'm not a big fan of organized religion in general, honestly
Gun for hire, is that the BNPs, that's the British National Party's Nick Griffin speaking
No, not at all
I don't think this guy is politically motivated, I think he's just a Brit who has something to say
That's what I kind of liked about him
He looks like a TV producer, I know actually
He's like a really regular guy, he doesn't look very radical, he doesn't look very hateful
But I think he's just speaking his mind, and it's very refreshing to hear that
At least that little bit
Okay, so that's homework everybody, we'll talk about that tomorrow
On the rest of the week, I'll be around most of it Thursday amount
I think I got some meetings in London to take care of
There's a couple of phone numbers at dailysourcecode.com
You can call and leave a voicemail message up to three minutes y'all
So I'd love to hear from you
Don't we speak tomorrow?
Hey, make sure you live your life with passion
And while it lasts my friends, enjoy your freedom
Another hot show podcast, stick it in your ear