Yeah-
You Walter Sierra Charlie 72 4
He loves you
It's $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
Here's the guy that's getting used to the rubbery loaf, and I'm curry on the Charlie.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, all true, I refuse you, promise me, I love you, I love you's, I love that, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love love love love, I love you, I love love love love, I love love love love love love, I love love love love愛 love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love Love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love
It's up in the back of me, I don't want to let it go, no, no, no
I think that's the time, let's have my daily breaks down one
Just want to make you feel me never, I'm old and so old
When I call you make you feel me never, I'm old and so old
I think that's the time, let's have my daily break down one
Just want to make you feel me never, I'm old and so old
I think that's the time, let's have my daily breaks down one
Auntie und I'm the time.
That's a potty big someone.
Just want to make me go, go, be mine,
oh oh, yeah, oh, baby.
Help myself.
oh oh oh oh oh, oh oh, baby.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Man, there's nothing like a party band track to kick off the weekend is there and of course
Here on the Charlie we consider Fridays to be a part of the official weekend
We have can't help myself the remix Amy Winehouse of course with the four tops kicking off today's episode number
724 the daily source code coming to you from the curry manner. We're up in the attic in the affluent subwoofer
Suri known as Guilford
I love this track man. That's awesome. Hey, this is the official load latency
No stuttering edition of the show. I've actually
You know, I actually already kind of did the show for like 60% of it and said, you know what?
The sound was so messed up screw it. I'm gonna take this one over take it back and do it all over again
He doesn't mean a show ain't full bar just my setup got it all fixed up now though
We can figure it out some more stuff with Ableton Live not gonna bore you with that today
Because we got to keep the music flown. We got to keep the angry brids coming in because I got a couple as promised yesterday
All of that and more on today's food bar Friday edition of the daily source code episode numbers of the 724 his Rex Clamp
Jim beam in the morning Jack Daniel's a night sometimes need a little vodka
I'm making a feel on right lately. I've been drinking all the captains here at my room
But I just called my deal. I said man. You got to give me some cause the weed is my need
The weed is what I mean
All this liquor is gonna kill my cause the weed is what I need
First time that I tried it
There's a much younger man
And now I want to do it and it's time that I can't
Some folks think it's bad
Well, I'll think that they're wrong
Hey, I like it so much
I just have to write the song
It holds the weed in what I mean
The weed in what I mean
All this liquor is gonna kill my cause the weed is what I mean
All give it to my man
What if we're feeling bad?
I just listen to me
I've got the answer for your relief
Don't drown in that whiskey
Don't swim in that wrong
But just roll a fat ass
Move it to its guy
And it holds the weed in what I mean
The weed in what I mean
All this liquor is gonna kill my cause the weed is what I mean
Call the end
I've never heard of all this liquor
You're gonna kill my cause the weed is what I mean
Rex, he claimed the weed is what I need from the pod save music network
Excellent
Links to that song and everything else played on today's show at datingsourcecode.com
Delicate balancing act today, my friends
It's what time is it now?
It's 3.39
I actually already did about 60% of the show and kind of modeled through it
It was extremely distracted by the setup crunching and skipping
So I know that I'm on the cutting edge of technology here
Because I'm literally working with audio devices, MIDI devices, processing, chains
Doing everything to keep the processor level of this MacBook Pro
Which is running everything now
It's all completely internalized except for the microphone going in
The external Fader Fox MIDI controller which is just the hottest thing I've had
And here is I love it
So I have to keep this latency otherwise latency kicks in on the program
And then it starts to crackle all that shit you heard yesterday and earlier in the week
So I think I finally found the perfect balance I'm very excited about it
So we'll see how it all goes today on this show
Which is of course the football variety of the daily source code
I promised you yesterday was it yesterday or the day before
No, yesterday was Valentine's Day
What am I talking about?
I got to tell you that Patricia and I went out for a Valentine's Day
It was awesome we went to see strictly come dancing at the O2 Arena
Which was great
You know we're big fans
This is strictly come dancing of course is the original format of what you in the states
Or another country's on the world would know as dancing with the stars
And Patricia of course participated in the Christmas special in the Netherlands
And we've been big fans of the show here
And I've watched it pretty much religiously
So they have the tour version which is essentially it's the television format on stage
It's crazy
They don't have Brucey who is you know the major host they have the co-host as the show
A couple of the stars the one the only two people I was really interested in watching
Matt and Flavia Matt plays or played I guess character on East Enders
And Flavia who already had a you know she's a world-class dancer
She's I think she's a world champion and maybe Latin or something like that
She and her partner but actually she and Matt hooked up during the you know because it's really intense stuff during the series
And they're just cute the great to look at when they dance
Anyway, so we had a great time and today of course is Friday
And I was referring back to the comments that I promised you I would play some of these angry brick comments
Now one person who called in when I started talking about the Snoop Dogg nation the surveillance state of the United Kingdom
One guy who called in
Let's do a little bit more reverb here hold on one two two two
There we go that's better. I can now control all of that manually. I love it
Maybe that's a little much. There we go
One guy got called in was his name is Bob and Bob said a couple of things that I I didn't necessarily agree with what he was saying
But I've heard them said many times before here in the UK and in the US and other countries around the world
And I kind of let it go in the hope that someone would pick up on it and and someone would say something
And thank goodness there is a comment
Adam Jason from San Diego
I'm calling about Bob
I found his last couple of statements in your agreements with his statements a little just
Disconcerning
Bob's last statements about the country where there's Polish coming in
Moving in
Working on the cheap jobs
Send in all their money back outside of Poland
And they're filling up the hospitals
Having date
Now the hospitals are probably already full
I don't think the polls are having that much more
But sure there might be more coming in
Lower income folks to tend to have more children
You know the only form of entertainment
But
The overall argument that they come in
Send them money out
This always been one that's pissed me
The fuck off
All right, so before you continue with all that
Let me just tell you that I'm happy you picked up on this because
I've heard that said a lot too and I happen to disagree with it
I don't think there's any chance that foreign workers are really taking away all these jobs
Taking away jobs mind you
I think that they're doing jobs a lot of
The native citizens just don't want to do
And then as always the you know they use up all of our services
Well clearly if they're in here and they're in here legally
Which as far as I know
Most of the polls would be
And by the way they're allowed to move around Europe
And work in different member states which is why you sign up to the European Union
That's a part of the deal
Okay
So I'm sure that they're paying taxes which cover their
You know their usage of services such as healthcare
But you're right man, it's something that you hear over and over and over again
Except you never really hear the set on television or in the mainstream media
Because this is what everyone says on the street
But once they're offered the opportunity to say it in public
You know in like a big mass audience public
No one really comes out and just says it
Just says what they feel whether it's right or wrong
Whether it's true or false you never ever hear that
So I'm so happy that Bob said it
And I'm so happy that you're picking up on it
And let's hear how pissed off you are about it
Because they say the same thing here in the United States about Mexican
And I just I don't buy the idea that the folks who come in
Do the labor have money paid go to state taxes
Local taxes
Municipal taxes
Of course the hands federal taxes
They get to spend they never get to take any benefit from it
They never get to vote on how it's spent
They don't even see any
Or they don't have any desire to influence how it's spent
Because they understand that there is not their country
They're just here doing a job
But they get no respect
They work hard
If they if the jobs weren't there they wouldn't come
They would stay if they could afford it
But they would stay if they were welcomed
But they're not and they can't afford it
So you know what you're going to do
Send them any back home where it goes for miles and miles
Live like a king
Work hard in another state or another country
And you
Jason San Diego
Later
Jason, thanks man
Where were you calling from your helicopter?
Sounded like it
Yep, I agree
And this is of course extremely dangerous
I think it's in a way it's called
It's called nationalism
I think it's dangerous when people start to talk that way
And this is from very intelligent people is just they're hurting
People are hurting and you know it's easy to turn around and point a finger at somebody
And that has happened in the past and it wasn't really good
Was it now?
So
Speaking of pointing the finger James
Frequent caller of the show
Took some offense to my finger pointing
Adam's James
But a demand for lessons to them that it's not really how it is going around a fucking tool
I'm not going to a problem
I just like know exactly how it is of a fucking tool
Because to say somebody's a fucking tool
Very easy
Adam Curry is a fucking tool
James is a fucking tool
How is he a fucking tool?
Jim that's fighting
If you're being used as a tool then you're a tool
I just added the fucking part in for color and flavor
And of course he's a tool
He's a tool of the whoever the hell runs the world
The new world order he's a part of it
I'm convinced of that
Look at what he's done with Northern Rock
And by the way the latest reports there is that
There's still a good chance the bank will be nationalized
Instead of rescued by
Let's see the only bitter left on the outside is virgin money
And the reason is because virgin wants to
Bring in like something over a billion pounds
Which will dilute all of the shareholders which will mean
They'll have less share of the bank instead of an alternative plan
So again doing it all for the shareholders
And not for the people whose money it actually is
And yes some of that is mine
I pay taxes here
Oh man
It's messed up
I'm not even going to get into that non-domiciled thing today
I'll do that on Monday
Because there's a whole row going on about that too
But yeah
And by the way look at what Gordon Brown is doing to help out
You know the surveillance society
The Snoop Dogg nation
Set up by new labor Tony Blair
You know all this you can't protest within a half a mile of
Parliament and now Gordon Brown saying hey well you know
Some of this intercept
Should be admissible in court
Oh man come on James
He's a fucking tool and you know it too
You really is
You know you said you don't know you
We will blah blah blah blah
And then spend the night in all of them
Do you honestly seriously think that you don't know
Do you honestly seriously think that things don't
Being booked in the states and in France and Germany
No James one second of course I do
Of course I do
That's the reason why I'm trying to wake everybody up here
You guys got to get with it
This has to stop this lunacy
And in the states you know
We're once again up against this horrific bill
That is now passed the Senate and Congress has to stop this
Which would give immunity
To all the telecommunications companies who illegally wire
Tap to American citizens to help the government without any appropriate warrants
I mean that shit has to be stopped dead in his tracks
Oh no James this is exactly why I'm talking about this here in the UK
But there is one big difference here everyone's just letting
Letting themselves be steam rolled
It's like where is the outrage about 800 different organizations
Or yeah organizations in the UK that can actually request an intercept
IE a wire tap or an Eschalon
Trying to get picked up by the filters Eschalon type filter
That'll read your email and see what websites you're surfing
So of course it's happening worldwide
I'd like to wake up the Brits because I happen to live here James
And I'd like it. I like it here. I want it to be better
I mean you're the pivier of the red pill for folks sick
We go out and this is going on worldwide
Just have a chance to wake up
We as a global community are being watched by the few all the time
And you can think that's conspiracy theories
You can think of a little fucked up in the head
But take a little bit more of a take a few more red pills
Because this is going on everywhere
You're being watched all the time
Adam Curry is being watched as he goes through the airport
He's been watched on the internet
He's got these mobile phone calls and it happens to everybody
And it happens everywhere throughout the world
Doesn't matter where you live
Sorry mate but that's the way it is
That's okay James
But that doesn't make it right or doesn't make it something that we should
Allow to continue to happen
It has to stop
And you know now that I'm learning that you can't even protest here
Or not with any reasonable ease
You know we've got to wake up from this apathy
Alan the Britain Basel sent in an email about a show coming on this Sunday evening on the BBC
BBC one called the last enemy
Typical theme that of being constantly under surveillance
The BBC's last enemy website states that in this show
Britain has been transformed into a security state after a major terrorist attack
ID cards are strictly enforced in citizens every movement is watched
So the government can catch the terrorists before they strike again
A situation of course at many genuinely fear and in some instances
Even hope for will become a reality
I got to check that out for sure
I'm not leaving for San Francisco until Monday
It's president's day on Monday
So I might as well just travel on a day when no one's working anyway
And parky sent some awesome stuff in
He says that he picked up confessions of an economic hitman after I pitched it here on the show
He says since then my red pill side has gone wild
I'd already got stuck into the book of taking liberties by Chris Atkins before you mentioned it
Of course that you can see that series
I still have a link on it's actually embedded at curry dot com taking liberties
You've got to see this
And he has some quotes here
He says or well here's or well
I think these are all or well quotes
Go read this go read or read
1984 you won't be disappointed I'm telling you
Here's a couple quotes
In the time of universal deceit
Telling the truth will be a revolutionary act
A family with the wrong members in control that perhaps as near as you
One can come to describing England in a single phrase
Oh man
Early in life I'd notice that no event is ever correctly reported in a newspaper
If you want a vision of the future imagine a boot stamping on a human face forever
Man
And then finally
He who controls the past controls the future
Who controls the present
Controls the past
Yeah or well a genius indeed
Hey Adam it's Jamie Gummy
You're calling up your call for three people to come up to the plate
Yeah
Well I've got a poll just so that's all about the call quality
It does probably quite shortly
I couldn't agree more
Basically after listening
Yeah you know I thought really quite a shame
You know we should be causing more of a fuss
We should have a bit more firing on there
We should be just saying hey we're not going to take the sort of thing
Right on
Crime example
The data that went missing
All that child agency data that went missing
There was a big colabaloo for a couple of days
And then what I don't understand is why no one has a certain sort of class action
So sure we can see you know
I'm showing people can see the government
They saw a thing and just they look
Oh yeah I mean
Surely you can but you got to actually do it
We need that kind of fire man
The stuff that I'm hearing from you
We got to step up and do something
That's why I'm really big on this flash mob stuff
I really hope we can get that started
It would be a lot of fun too
We're not going to take this
This is just not acceptable
And today I even saw that they're now trying to push through a pipe
Like a three stripes and you're out
For now my respect
Respected legal material
Copyright infringement
Yeah I talked about that early in the week
Indeed
And this is a proposed bill
It's a green paper
So it's a way it's a way off from actually being effectuated
But just the fact that people are thinking this way in parliament is nuts
So you're going to listen to you're going to intercept all of my internet traffic
And probably slow it down in the process
And the only reason you're doing that is to find out if I've downloaded something illegally
You know so where's that database reside
Where you can find out every single piece of content
And maybe I have some content that's being downloaded illegally
Can I make use of this as well?
Ah fuck I didn't give a shit about that
Stop snooping on me
Don't snoop
Dog
Nation
If you're called three times you're off the internet for good
Adam, I couldn't agree more
We're just totally out of self-gootweaver
And I'm totally up to doing the flash mob and standing up
I'm just kicking out
I am 28 years old living in Birmingham
I'm a programmer
And I know it's been a while but you've got all the news sign off
Great head
Love you
No, I'm on take care
I'll speak to you later
Hi man, thank you
We need more people like you
And I've purposely not started winding up the flash mob
Where you know the idea is everyone wears t-shirts that say
You work for us and we just created a couple of these flash mobs really quick
Of course completely within the half mile perimeter of Parliament
Because it's not actually a demonstration
We're just kind of all flashing mobbing flash mobbing together
So that's a big difference, isn't there?
By the way, Birmingham, I heard yesterday
You know you'd be 40
They're from Birmingham and I heard that like 20 years ago
Maybe even longer than 20 years ago
When those guys first got started they purchased
You know the building
That they were I guess working in or living in in the middle of Birmingham
And bought a couple of buildings around it
Which is now pretty much the center of Birmingham
And these guys own it
They're like set for life and then some
Which is really cool when you just see those guys stoned it out on stage
Hey, there's a new episode of Dr. Cockney
If you haven't seen them international sex therapist
Let's try that again
International sex that's
Fuck me
What are you saying?
I love it
I know
You know what I know sex is a tool?
Yeah
Do you think women are really bothered about the size of your male men but
Yes, she's a lot in your house
You're sexy man
Yeah
That's right
I just go to podshow.com and search for
Dr. Cockney
International sex therapist.bt podshow.com
There I got it out
I got it out
I had them
You ready to be stunk
Tell me how does he use the
Fantastic
With young format
Bring it on
Hey Adam this is hit us number 109
And this one's kind of special
Why is why?
You're assistant
You know how the three songs I've selected for this week's
That's funny
And this is the first intro
Alright
Oh yes
I know
Carry are these your favorites?
That's kind of cool
That's a
Terence Trendarby dance little sister
From 1986
Number two
Oh
I've even practiced this one
On the guitar myself
I've got my first real sixth string
Some are 69
Brian Adams
And number three
Oh
I just want to
Need a hell was that
Oh
I didn't want to get close
And time's up and these are the answers
Two
Down
Answer number one
From 1987
This is Terence Trendarby
Dance little sister
Hey
Give up the goff that's onto you now
Yeah
You're so true
Dance little sister
I don't give up
Hey
I don't do tomorrow
I don't want to hear it
I think
Dance little sister
I don't give up
Hey
I don't do tomorrow
Terence Trendarby is answer number one
And this is answer number two
I come a first real sixth string
Was a summer of 169
Let's get it out of your mother's voice
You told me that it lasts forever
And for the best things of my life
Oh yeah
From 1990
Brian Adams answered number two
The summer of 69
Now what was this?
And this is answer number three
Also from 1990
This is Maxi Poosh
Shit of course
I got the title right
Girl you'd be my jeans come to you
You make my jeans come to you
I just want to be close to you
Not tell you
You are the things you do want me to
And answer number three
Maxi Priest and close to you
And that's it for a hit test number one
Oh nine
How did you do?
I don't
I got two and a half out of three
Carries
As always the answer for this hit test
And also the links to the iTunes
You can buy these tracks
Online are to be found at hittest.botjo.com
Thanks for playing Adam
Thanks Gary
Next week I'll be back for a hit test number 110
So uh
Until then
Take care
And bye bye
Bye bye
Bye
Can't test that she mail.com
In Pooh
Young Pooh.com
And P.O.L.C.T.
Just go
Ah I was very cute
Thanks Gary
And uh and John of course
One oh nine already man
Can you believe that shit
And I was listening to the Brian Adams track
And I was thinking of myself
For years
I thought the first lyric to that was
Had my first real sex dream
But of course it was sixth dream
And I was thinking you know
I think we did this a couple of years ago
When I was at the cottage
If you have any messed up sound
A mess up song lyric that you want to share with us
Something that you completely
Were mistaken on and sang for years
Probably much to your embarrassment
When you found out
Uh
If it voted in
And uh we can probably do something
With the organization to the preservation
For the soundtrack of our lives
And uh and play some of the
Of the original tracks along with it
Uh it would be a hood
It's the football Friday
It is the day the source code
It's episode 724
We've got a review of Burnout Paradise on the Xbox 360 in PlayStation 3
We put our thinking caps on with Zach and Wicky on the way
We also get a little look at the story
All humans on the way as well
And you can win one of five copies of a real tournament
Three on the PlayStation 3
That's all at gamesweasel.btpodshow.com
Your honor
I'd like to make a motion
To rock this mother out
Your honor
Please don't bang that gavel
You can try this cowbell out
Let's all give a night
To the hardest work
And law here
It's jersey time
Yeah
Oh yeah
Your honor
What do you say
There you go
How's it going Adam
It's jersey time
The official musicologist of the Chacha
And while I say that I'm your musicologist
After hearing your comments earlier in the week about Sherry Miller
I think what you're really really looking for
Is a pimple
It's actually right
Because I think what you really are looking for me to do
Is go out on the positive music network
And find you some bass
Yeah
I've done it again for you
In fact, you've had her in the past
Why don't you have her again
Name is Alice from the Alice project
She's got a lot of great tracks up on the PMN
In fact, she's one of my all-time favorite female artists
She's got just a great new track up on the PMN
Which is perfect for a football Friday
It's I'm having a great day
On the Daily Source Coach
Check it out
I'll talk to you next week buddy
All right, but thank you very much
Bring it on
I'm gonna go look into the page on the PMN
Okay, you guys listen to this song
I'll be right back
Because I'm having a great
Having a great
Having a great day
I'm walking on water
Because I'm feeling better
And no one don't have no way
Because I think I'm having a great day
So much love to share
I feel less so high about you
I think I have some sun to share
Keeping down to you with
Some kind of island being my head
No one can take this
Feeling away
And I'm feeling okay
Because I'm having a great
Having a great
Having a great day
And I'm walking on water
Because I'm feeling better
And no one don't have no way
Because I think I'm having a great day
So much love to share
Having a great day
And no one don't have no way
Because I'm feeling okay
Because I'm having a great
Having a great day
Feeling away
Because I'm feeling okay
Because I'm having a great
Having a great
Having a great day
And no one don't have no way
Because I think I'm having a great day
The Alice Projects
Yes, Sir Jersey Todd, you're right
Alice from the Alice Project
Qualifies
Having a great day
You'll find it on the pod save music
Network
You can go to podshow.com slash music
Or to the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
And right there you'll see a link
To every song played on today's show
Now there's something that we kind of started
Was it many, many moons ago
Called the organization for the preservation
For the soundtrack of our lives
Upsole
And in fact there was a soundtrack of our live show
Upsole.podshow.com
OPSOL
Wait, let me do this
Oscar Papa Sierra Oscar Lima
Got to stay in practice for flying
Even though I'm not
And so people have been sending in their stories
And their songs
And some of them fit really well
Some of them not so well
And what I don't need is people calling in
With their own stories
She's right at it
Because I want to read it
You've got to all set up and templatize
It should be able to crank out a couple
In fact I did a few
Was it last Friday
I had to do a whole bunch of productions
So I'm trying to get one week out at least
But these are kind of every green
Because as you kind of stay at stick around there
And even though this entry
Was not exactly what I asked for
I just figured I'd play it for you today
On the football Friday
Because everyone seems to enjoy it when we just kick out the jams
Adam, Prof Ross here
Redondo Beach California
Called Austin
Hey, interesting on 709
I'm a little behind you
We're talking about picturing the record labels
You know as they spun on the 45's vinyl
And just that phrase
Took me back
Talking about
You know soundtrack of our live
Preservation
Took me back to
Concept Blanca records
It's at outkiss
Donna summer all
Stuff and I can totally picture
Like
The brand new vinyl
Pulling it out
The smell of it
Kind of shrink raft
That tour
And then you're broken it open
Just
Sometimes a little phrase
A little music
Soundcrack of our life
Me and the way
They're down by the school
Not on our farm
Tonight
I want to give it up to you
In the dark night
It's so much I want to do
And tonight
I want to let it go to be
Because girl I was made for you
And girl you would make for me
I was made for loving you
And you were made for loving me
And I can't get it over
You made it again
You can't get it over me
Tonight
I want to see it go right
Feel the magic
There's something that I can find
And tonight
We're going to make it all come true
Because girl you would make for me
And girl I was made for you
I was made for loving you
And you were made for loving me
And I can't get it over
You made it again
You can't get it over me
I was made for loving you
And I can't get it over me
And you can't get it over me
Oh yeah, man
Remember where you were?
And that song came out
And I must have been 15, 16
I must have been 15, 16
Going to dances and barns
You know, getting my first experience of the opposite sex
And you dance your brains out to this track
And then all you do is you just hope for a really really slow song
To come on next so you could get a nice, close and personal
With the girl that you found for the evening
Oh yeah, man
That's a soundtrack to my life
And with me now
43 year old old bastard
Here's the first track
I wish I was cool
I used to be a key
Every day of the week
And something stupid came out
Every time I speak
Every Saturday night
I've known the media if plans
I didn't live on the dead
Played for games again
I was bored like a fool
I wish I was cool
Why was useless in class
So I tried out for sports
Where the chalk's got a kick got a kick
And I can't get my shorts
Still in my town
When my shower was gone
I walked through the window
I couldn't find one
I had a street to school
I wish I was cool
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Cool
Mama, dear Mama, thank my shorts
I'll come in down
I held my tight to my books
Got my mouth shut in class
And my hammy down closed
Even the teachers would laugh
I prayed to the clock
And I'd eat lunch alone
We haven't even gotten to the box
Right home, no teachers knows
I wish I was cool
Hey
You see, we live in a house
With too many kids
And too many beds
And I'm much fooling the fridge
And the kids on the box
Call it the house
So they hear excuses
Too many cars on the lawn
Been fixed by my dad lost the truth
I wish I was cool
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Mama, dear Mama, your broken boy is coming along
So right, it's the moral of the story
You say the king and the jacks
Turned out to be gay
And all the little cool kids
They didn't have a small town
Where some used to be nerd
Kibos them around
It's our turn to be cruel
Oh, yeah
Say it all with me now
I wish I was cool
I love it
Jersey Todd, thank you man
Great suggestion, Chris, trapper of the push stars
Which I was cool on this football Friday edition of the Daily Source Code
Hey, where's Roger Smalls
Roger
It's been a while, buddy
Love to hear from you, really wood
I got one more track lined up for you
Another one from the soundtrack of our lives
But first, and I told you, you know, now that of course the coverage
The, certainly the mainstream media coverage of the primaries
In the United States has, you know, more or less dropped off the crevice
Dropped into the crevice, I should say
Because, of course, it's all over now
Or it's not
You know, we still don't know who's going to be in the Democratic side
Maybe, yeah, it could be John McCain on the Republican side
But, Huckabee is still in the race
As is Ron Paul
And Ron Paul has a strategy
And you know, I support him
So I want you to hear it too
Hey Adam, this is Terry from Seattle
Hey
Yeah, I heard you on Wednesday the 719
Yes, the, you were talking about Ron Paul
And now he was losing
Oh, let's not get our dober down
He isn't out of this thing yet
There's a lot of delegates that are committed
There's a lot of stealth delegates
This, this caucus we had in Washington State on Saturday
The party is engineered in McCain
A victory, that's an air quotes
Because you didn't really win
There wasn't really much to win
Nothing's been won yet
That's my point exactly
You know, how they say it in over till the fat lady sings
Well, it ain't over
And not until the convention
When the actual nominee is presented
Anything could happen
You know, I mean, it's a horrible thought
But what if McCain
Could it be president for some reason
Health reasons or anything like that
It's a long time until
Well, in general, it's a long time until November
When we have the general election
But we're still away from from the Republican and the Democratic
Conventions
So give it a little time, you know, it's
It's a media has made this into such a frenzy
And everyone thinks they know who won
But they don't really, and I'll tell you, I see people over here
They're confused, they don't get it at all
Because of course, the people who are actually reporting this don't even get it
They just want something cool
Oh, there's a race, let's report on it no matter what it is
Doesn't get decided until
A, the primary, which decides
51% of the delegate
And B, the state convention, which yesterday's caucus
Was just the beginning of that
And so we'll be going to convention
First we go to the county convention
Where we pick our state delegates
And then we go to the state convention
Where we pick our national delegates
The other 49% for the Republicans
And also, if we have a broken convention
All bets are off then
Because people that may be committed to McCain
On the, if he doesn't win on the first ballot
On the second ballot, they can vote for whoever they are
So I know there's a lot of wrong policy supporters
That are elected as, we're going to try to get elected as
McCain delegates and then hoping for a second ballot
So they can vote for Paul
So let's keep up the positive thinking and prayer for wrong policies
Because he's not out of the yet
So please keep pushing
We're going on to, we're going on to the convention
All right, I'm 48
I've been listening since February of 2005
And no homo
That's not good
All right, thank you
I also posted a video from Dr. Ron Paul
On at curry.com
I should probably, I tried doing that in the show notes
Pod Show, but it doesn't work for some reason
Maybe the embed code is host or something
But he basically is called for a march on Washington
He says, you know, this is really risky
But we've done risky things before
Like, you know, putting the money counter
Right there on the homepage
And of course, all of the money bombs have been significantly successful
So the risk here, of course, is that you call for a march on Washington
And no one comes
However, if a lot of people come, it could really say something
And that too could change the course of who is, who becomes the Republican candidate for the general election
So
I'm keeping my eyes on it doing what I can
And clearly other people are as well
All right
Rollin' out one more from the op-sold libraries
For some reason, I was thinking about these guys in this song
Almost all week and for just now
I kind of humming it back and forth
Talk, talk
It's my life on the football Friday for the Chuck Charlie
But it never bothers me
No, I want you
What day?
It never could bother me
I'm there still no way
On the very front door
All you've asked was so
How much do I do?
Can we ask just a
It's my life
Don't give more time, it's the life, it's the love of you
If I were sometimes played apart, I'd raise to love
I tell myself, what can we do now?
Children's myself, it's the life, don't give more time, it's the life, it's the love of you
Don't give more time, it's the life, it's the love of you
Oh, that's myself, how was the year?
Can we choose him? It's the love, don't give more time, it's the life, it's the life
Don't give more time, it's my life, it's my life, it's my life, it's the soundtrack to my life
and all that goodness, sorry for the extraneous audio that's crept in there
and now I've got the Vorac technique to send me text messages saying
Hey dude, let's do the show because you can be packing over the weekend
since you're flying out Monday.
So maybe I will, you'll have a lot of stuff to listen to today and tomorrow
and of course if you're living down under in Australia, or if you're New Zealand, it'll be about Wednesday
by the time you get all of this.
What's the idea today?
There it is.
It's Friday, Monday Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Thursday, Friday
and a spinal fund for the week.
Yeah, well, I guess the only final thought I can have is wake up people, wake up
We've got to do something.
And you know what, just by realizing what is going on and then you really should do something
you're already awakening.
That means the red pill is taking hold and that's a very good thing.
So, mull it over this weekend, then I'll be back next week from San Francisco
coming to you from the curry condo, of course, and we'll talk about some civil disobedience
shall we?
We'll be really fine.
Oh, man.
Yeah, that's really the only thought I have.
It's just running through my brain continuously.
I can't help myself.
But meanwhile, don't forget to stop sniffing all the flowers once in a while.
If you're in the UK, we've got like what looks like an early spring.
So, plenty of flowers to be sniffed and birds to be heard singing.
So make sure you do that as well.
Yeah, that's good enough for a final thought of the week.
So, it's adamantpodshow.com, dailysourceco.com, for all the show notes, live your life with passion
and while at last, enjoy your freedom.
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear.