We're 60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass, done the next generation
of radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying to the future.
I'm casting this fellow curry.
Hey brother, welcome to Cell7Tain.
All the eight years old.
I was having a plane at the pub.
They got me from being a baker and an alcoholic.
How about you?
I had a cold.
Took more than the recommended dose of the medicine.
So they got me for being a drug addict and spreading the virus.
A good thing you didn't run, it'd be good.
What about the guy sleeping in the corner for the toll blonde one?
Oh, that's Adam.
They got him for producing the DSC 765.
Talking about liberty, freedom, and all the things they despise.
Good morning, Pinging up.
It's seeming many can't.
We come in numbers and I'm all wrong.
We didn't come to dance.
We came to make it known.
We're like the motherfucking covers on a naked go.
Don't want to break in us.
And that's the bottom line.
Take it by the everything to take.
We're in these fun and time.
It's time to throw the shoulders.
It's time to go to work.
Getting tangled in the muscles for another more.
I can't look at your mane.
I guess I've had it good.
I guess that I think he won't act in like his Hollywood.
But what about the people?
Don't want to see you.
There's the end of the people dying and they think it's evil.
This ain't a fairytale.
This ain't a common book.
This is baby skiing.
It make a wilder mama look.
It's the philosophy.
Based on hypocrisy.
The province and province.
If you're in the economy.
So where's the honesty?
Beneath the blanket statements.
The government's creating nature.
Make you think there's seven nations.
We're here to hold your head.
In this broken land.
We brought a list of everything that just took off the hand.
We throw it in anger.
It's safe.
Exactly.
I just throw that.
But everybody should be happy when they hold the flag.
You let away the pride.
You better say it loud.
It's time for you to play.
Delete and so we'll take you out.
We're going to kick it up.
It's easy.
We ran again.
We're coming numbers.
And I'm almost having jettison.
We didn't come to death.
We came to make you known.
We're like the months.
When covers on, I make you come home.
So we'll do things enough.
And that's the bottom line.
They can buy it.
That we can take with it.
It needs more to time.
If I'm sure the show was just trying to go to war.
Getting taken.
They look what's just for another four.
I guess I should be thankful.
I guess I really am.
I guess that I should stay.
I'm proud to be American.
But what about the one that's crowded on the other end?
Well, hope is getting crunched under the power of the upper hand.
This thing to revolution.
This thing to remedy.
If it's a show that you can control it.
What's the enemy?
It's the reality.
Based on the priorities.
Started with the steps.
And it driven by your salary.
I wonder how you eat.
We brought the distance.
Just taking population.
Think it's rolling.
I'm like living pump.
Speak a little.
You think it's a bit up.
If you want to say a lot.
It's a problem to the sunset.
Don't you believe in God.
You can't believe in me.
Don't you know that we will rest until we see you free.
It's time to celebrate.
We found a better way.
You better love it.
Or you won't get in the heavens game.
You won't get in the heavens game.
We come in numbers.
And I'm almost happy to understand.
We come in numbers and I'm almost happy to understand.
Finally I'm on the source called Drop somewhere,
I examined my little lot outline.
Ready to play for you and with that intro from Petey Love.
How could I resist?
Coming to you from the west side of GTown hay here in gil.
For to get a little different set up,
oh, by the way, that of course is the affluent
suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford.
I've changed the position of my mic.
I've been doing so much work behind the microphone
for the best, oh, what is it?
I've passed a couple of weeks, really,
because I've been doing this Dutch thing in the morning
for Arrow Classic Rock, which is so perfect
to have me in the morning.
And, you know, so my ass hurts, my back is starting to,
what I really need is I need the big ass,
you know, the podcast console that my father
and I built for me, which was too big to even get into the house,
or even to get out of the old house,
since he actually built it in the studio over there.
That's what I need, man.
I need to be able to stand up
when I have to look into one of those tables
that you can change the hide automatically.
So now the microphone is, instead of off to the left,
it's right in front of me,
we'll see if it makes any difference.
But I gotta tell you,
I've really been doing something kind of on the slide,
which I, you know, I didn't want to really talk too much
about it until I started
succeeding.
And that really happened over the past two days.
See, the main reason I was interested in participating
in, you know, looking at transferring
some of what I've learned on the daily source code
onto live radio in such a very small market as, as Holland.
Is, I want, I'm really trying to infiltrate.
Now, what do I mean by that?
You know, I sit here, day in, day out.
Sometimes actually record it and we share it together.
But I basically all day long, I'm thinking about
what the hell is going on in the world?
And how can I affect it?
How can I affect things?
How can I make things change?
How can I figure out how things are really working?
And of course, you know, together,
we've already figured out quite a lot of stuff
with just the chuckleheads in general.
And of course, this advanced checking in.
But I need to infiltrate into the political circuit.
Not being in the United States, I say,
that's pretty much hopeless.
I've been trying with Dr. Ron Paul
and, you know, to some degree,
I've learned, well, certainly learned a lot.
Really haven't, you know, we haven't gotten quite
where we need to be.
It's also very, very complicated, you know,
being over here most of the time,
or even half of the time, as it sometimes turns out, it's tough.
Don't know, shit all about the United Kingdom.
You know, only only know some of the cultural things
I've picked up since we've been living here.
The Netherlands, though, I do know a little bit more
about, and most of the politicians there
are, believe it or not, they're pretty much my age now.
There's a whole, you know, new generation
of young politicians.
And many of them quite a bit younger.
And boy, do they love media?
They don't understand, you know, independent media,
podcasting, anything like that.
They really, they really don't.
And quite honestly, I understand, because a lot of their
conversation is played through the news media, or the live
media, and radio being a perfect example of that.
So really, you know, I've been out on a quest
I've been trying to figure out, how can I learn something?
How can I get further towards this new European Parliament?
You know, I understand what's going on here.
I mean, this is going to be the United States of Europe,
whether they say it is a risen.
And there's all kinds of, man, this is just so much stuff going on.
And, you know, if you look online and look at any of the,
and by the way, the DailySource Code drop drop.io slash
DailySource Code is a great resource for all kinds of conspiracy
theory stuff.
But when you look at it, and you know, on at face value,
how the Rockefeller's initially invested in the United
Nations, or gifted the money to the United Nations,
which in a way down the line has become a lot of the vision of
what the European Union is, and how all of these 27 states
are coming to it.
Look, they call them states.
I mean, Christ, did not make sense.
Did the United States of Europe isn't pretty obvious what's going on?
And it's going to be a huge, a huge superpower already.
The euro is outrageously powerful, certainly compared to other currencies.
And this is going to be a four, 500 million people all on all told.
And, you know, we're seeing a democracy, a, maybe even a Republican
away, but certainly a union forming that is just, you know,
it's a once in a lifetime opportunity.
And it's going to be a force to be reckoned with already.
Even today, it touches the US in many different ways.
It affects our lives, even how companies like Microsoft behave is
now dictated by the European Union.
So when it came down to this constitution, which I talked about in the previous episode,
the one where only Ireland can apparently save Europe from going into devastation.
I've had the opportunity over the past two days to talk to ministers or parliament.
Actually, one of the ministers who is in the, what is it?
The minister, the council of ministers, I think, in the, in Brussels.
And I'm going to share some of that with you,
because I learned some things.
I asked, and see, unfortunately, here's the whole bummer to this thing.
All of that shit is done in Dutch.
There is a podcast version, which the guys at the station do by agreement with great
diligence.
They cut out all the music, of course, because a lot of license, most of the music
that's played is licensed.
And it's still a good, you know, 60% of the show, 70% maybe, even is music.
And all the other, you know, the interviews are in Dutch, which, of course,
is what makes sense is why these guys even come on the show to speak in the,
in the mother tongue of the land.
So I kind of bites that I can't really share the actual audio with you.
But as I get to know them, and I'm now on first name basis, because that's the first
thing I do, they say, look, you know, can we just, you know,
on a first name basis here for a second?
Because you know, the, in Dutch is a very formal way of addressing someone, like,
unlike French, we have two would be the informal way, and vo would be the very formal
way.
So we have that in Dutch as well, but it's tough because here I am translating questions
I have in English into Dutch.
And then I have to, you know, also be correct and address them in the formal way,
you know, or her, you know, so the first thing I say is, you know, hey,
can we just address each other like friends?
There's a word for it called two, two a year, which is, of course, a French word.
So can we use the, the two, the informal version of each other?
And they all, you know, and they all say yes, which really really changes the whole
conversation.
So I want to talk a bit about that today.
And of course, there's lots of stuff you guys have been sending in.
Let me just make sure I've got everything set here and got to set that one.
Okay, ready for blast off.
Here we go.
Curry, personal awesome thing.
Quick effect, God boss, life, liberty, and of course happiness, one of the most famous
phrases of United States, that worries of independence.
Yeah, you know, when I said it yesterday, I realized I messed it up.
Go ahead.
It has absolutely no legal grounds for the constitution of America, is simply telling
the British at the time to piss off.
Now certainly, the pursuit of happiness has appears in the 1960s, so it's your main court
case, loving versus Virginia.
But technically speaking, a lot of people misquote that and say it has nothing to do with
our constitution or our laws.
And while certainly the constitution is based on my idea, that it's not in the constitution
or rather in the integration of independence, but, again, has no legal binding within the
U.S.
I'm glad to make sure you've gotten to that straight boss.
Great here.
Hope you'll win.
That's it.
Folder.
Oh, that's good.
Two times this week, and to all of the bastards there in Washington, D.C., you work
for me.
Peace.
Right on, man.
Absolutely.
Another thing I've been telling these politicians, I'll start it off, I'll butter
him up, I say, hey, man, thank you very much for coming on the show, and thank you
for your many years of service to us.
They all go like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, finally props, but you know, in the same
time, I'm saying, thanks for your service to us, which is my little private joke, oh, I wish
you guys could be in on this.
Anyway, so as I get to know these guys, of course, they're all completely well versed
in English, and I'll be able to set up interviews, particularly the guys who are in
the European Parliament, but they got friends too, you know, they all visited each other
right now.
One of these guys is meeting with Bush today, in fact, the prime minister of the Netherlands
is meeting with Bush as well as the minister of Foreign Affairs, I believe.
So I've just taken an interest to this, and he's got the European Union, they're so stupid.
They put everything they do on the internet, everything, and it's unedited, complete,
raw form, which, of course, is horrible for communicating stuff, because you just can't
understand what the hell it's about, it's like this whole constitution and the, the
trade, the Lisbon Treaty, you know, it's, it's legal speak, which I talked to these guys,
this fucking law, and only a lawyer can understand this, and maybe he won't even know exactly
what it means.
Yes, you're right, you know, we need to simplify, yeah, so the lot of talking around
simplification, which they're not doing, which, of course, makes everyone, including
the highly suspicious.
Anyway, I do want to clarify some things about the constitution.
Here's what I've learned.
So I confronted a couple of these members of Parliament here, or not here in the Netherlands.
I said, you know, according to the bylaws and the protocols, which, you know, you
have to refer to from the Lisbon Treaty, this is so crazy how these guys have it set up.
It says, you know, for instance, you have a right to freedom, unless you are spreading contagious
diseases, or unless you are a vagrant, or unless you're a drug addict, or an alcoholic,
or of unsound mind.
Like, dude, that can't be in the constitution in a country where I live, because I'm,
I'm, you know, I'm out on three counts.
Well, no, Mr. Curry, let, actually, they said, Adam, let me just restate how it works.
That is a global, go, go, guideline, but each country individually can supersede on a national
level.
So that was interesting to me.
It says two things.
One, at least one or two of these 27 countries that make up the member states, it got
some pretty messed up human rights issues, and I want to avoid it.
So I'd like to have a laminated card, please.
The television, which one will arrest me if I'm a vagrant, or an alcoholic, or a drug
user, or if I can spread contagious diseases?
So that's one.
So when I say, what's the benefit?
So by the way, I think, you know, that's a, that's pretty important because that was
really what my whole rant was about on Tuesday.
By the way, when questioned, no one could actually point in the treaty, though Lisbon
treaty, or the original constitution document to where it actually says that, apparently
it spread out over several different pieces of language.
So I'm still highly suspicious.
There are some interesting things, though, on an EU level, on a European level, there
will be policy for immigration as an example.
Now they haven't said it yet, but at least they've got some kind of legal guidelines.
And I guess that's kind of good, because at the end of the day, you've got to have a lot
of lawyers talking to each other.
But what bums me out is that no matter what country you're in, if I contest the law in the
United Kingdom, I have to go to Brussels, you know, I could, I could actually have to go
to Brussels for other reasons.
They could call me there immediately.
So you won't really be, you know, it's kind of like the states, I guess.
I think it really is turning out to be a lot like the United States of Europe because
you've got your state laws, they've got your federal laws.
But they're starting out with a bloated government, you know, we built one over over a couple
hundred years.
They've got it all set up, man.
And they've got this all bloated.
They can't even be in one town.
They've got to be in two towns.
They've got to be in Brussels.
And as an incredibly, as an incredibly said Luxembourg on a previous show, I meant
Strasbourg, they're in two towns.
And I totally believe that they, what's going on in Central Europe in Brussels is definitely
some kind of political elite who want to control the world, or at least a little piece
of it.
No doubt about it.
And it's proof of that all over the place, like our good buddy, fellow chucklehead from
the Netherlands, the limonada man, or the limonada man, known as the lemonade.
I was thinking, last 23rd of May, the Dutch minister of youth was seriously proposing
a law that would forbid teachers to be in the street after 9 or 10 p.m., as known as
a curfew.
Without parental guiding, I can't imagine how bloody the streets will be on a Saturday
or Saturday morning, if this legal killing at for example, is just a surface, would
become any in effect.
Yeah, you know, so that's what there you go.
It's confusion.
Here's a citizen saying, like, well, first of all, how can they make a law that
keep that a curfew?
I guess you can do it locally, but then what if you break that, they could kill your
kids?
Actually, I think that was part of the other piece of the freedom doctrine there, was that
they could arrest your kids if they need to be educated properly.
So yeah, I think we need to figure out what the local laws are in each individual country,
but some of them have gotta be messed up, just read the documents.
Anyway, you might like to talk to Richard Feldhaus, all the largest commercial radio station
in the Netherlands.
He spent many times to discuss the proposed constitution of the EU.
Yeah, just a reminder, you know, the Netherlands voted no as, as did France, France.
And I'm convinced now that no one actually voted because they read the document and said,
hey, this constitution sucks.
They voted no because they said, you guys are being sneaky.
Screw you.
We're not going to let you have anything.
He barely could get any yes, Father.
In my own inner circle, I couldn't find any either.
Now check this out.
10 foil hats on, everybody, you're going to need it for this.
The end result of the referendum was 49, yes, against 51, no, to me.
That was the indication, the voting machines were having malicious firmware.
I love that.
Wait a minute, let me adjust the tin foil hat, or what is it, what's it known as?
The aluminum foil deflector beanie, that's what it is.
Aluminum foil deflector beanie, hold on a second.
Yes, the voting machines are rigged, I hear you.
By the way, the same Dutch voting machines that were used in this referendum were also
tested by the Irish national lab.
Were they used in Florida by any chance?
A lab just like Sania in the US is halfway, those tests, the Dutch voting machines were ignored
because they were too ridiculous to spend any attention to anymore.
You might like to refer to Wifterhaus Tempcomputer's.nl.
I got to write that one down, which is also available in English.
This organization finally was able to make the government discontinuing the use of those
machines.
There are danger for the democracy.
The manufacturers were trying to drop those machines in New York after the Dutch government
discontinued the use.
Wait a minute, the Dutch government discontinued the continued use of the voting machines
because they were rigged basically and then they tried to drop them in New York.
It looked like the first of their prevented that New York would start to use them.
That's outrageous, man.
Give me the URL.
Let me mention the URL again, but to prevent perfect programmer like URLs, I made that
mentioned URL, tiny URL and that's tiny URL.com slash and now it'll spell Yankee, Echo, Delta,
Delta, 5-2.
You might like to put it in the show notes.
Dude, dude, dude, I will thank you so much.
Excellent intel there, lemonade man.
See, we're expanding our horizons, my friends, so a country that's never really been
into podcasting because they love their stupid radio, which, and believe me, it's pretty
stupid over there.
Let me see, I got all kinds of new clear stuff I want to talk about.
Actually, let's, I think I've finished up that topic for now, right?
So I'm keeping, there's another thing I'm tracking right now, you're going to love this.
It's been around for a while, but it only kind of doubled up to the top of someone sent
me a note about it, about the use of RFID chips in the euro.
There's also a rumor now that it's in the new U.S. $20 bills, I think.
You know what an RFID chip is?
It's a minuscule chip that can transmit a very short range radio frequencies, and it basically
is just identity itself, it's sending out an ID number.
Our pets actually have it.
The dog and the two cats, you know, when they enter into the country, then they have to
have all kinds of paperwork, and then they have an identification, and the vet has a little
syringe, and just shoots a chip in there, and he has a little sensor holds it over the
pets head, and blip, there's his number, so completely trackable.
These things are used in industrial purposes to track, basically you can insert it in
anything and contract parts or items, and of course, you could leave it in the close as
there was people by them and walk out of the shop, I would call that a security risk right
now, because of course, you can connect that particular garment to a credit card, therefore
an address and identity, but the rumor is now going around that they're actually embedded
into the money over here, not in the UK, but into the euro, in the five, the ten, and
the twenty euro bill, and you can test this, and this is the thing that gets me, and
by the way, I think you can also test this with the new US $20 bill, you put it in the
microwave for a couple of seconds, and literally within a second, you'll hear a pop, like
a little mini explosion, and you'll see a hole, and it might even start to burn a little
bit, it might start to flame, your results may vary due to your microwave's condition,
and it will be an exactly the same spot on all of the bills, which of course leads
the conspiracy theorists to believe, and I'm wearing the hat, my friends, I'm wearing
the beanie, that there's an RFID chip embedded into these bills, and of course there's
a lot of implications there, I mean, just imagine walking in somewhere and someone being
able to see how much cash you got on you, I mean, that's pretty scary, oh, he's got
four fibers, he's got a couple of 20s, he's got three tens, but you know, it makes
it trackable, and so that's when I'm on a quest now, I have calls into the Minister
of Finance, into the Minister of Economic Affairs, and I will take this all the way to the
European High Court to get an answer for someone to say yes or no, I'm also calling
to the guys who print the euro, so stay tuned for that.
Hello, Adam, it's Grey Lemme, I've put it down on that spot, this isn't a DSC 753,
it's bloody high prices, a diesel, but down here, I was playing, I just filled up this car,
and it was a £1.29, a liter of a diesel, who's that person saying, no use, you put diesel
it in a airplane, a diesel power airplane, since when does that, I thought the EF will
airplanes would need a petrol, out of gas, or jet, jet engines, so they wouldn't even be
possible.
Just a power to wait.
Oh, let me stop you there.
Dude, this is the big thing, particularly the diamond, I think, is there a Mitsubishi,
the diamond aircraft?
No, it's just diamond.
They've got 20sols, oh, it's really big, by the way, diesel is very close to jet
fuel fuel.
I have actually witnessed when training with what I think is not such a great training
for them, actually, because I was on a training flight, and we actually started to run
on a gas and had to find a place, an alternative to an airport to refuel in a fucking
Robinson 44.
We put it right down near gas station, and got, I don't know, I've got about 20 liters,
or 25 liters of diesel, and put that right in.
And it worked, it fired up, jet fired up, no problem, turbans spin, spun up, and we flew
off, and, you know, topped it up with jet fuel, then worked perfectly.
No, diesel's great, and there are engines that are specifically built to run on diesel
fuel.
Of course, they were kind of designed when diesel was a hell of a lot cheaper, and now it's
actually more, well, it's not as expensive as Avgas, which, of course, is 100 or above
stocktain, which I'm now paying two and a half euros per liter for, if you can believe
it is.
Thank you.
You know, and you'd be much heavier, because of the unit, but there are not about aviation
airplanes, the aviation engines, and they have a quatter, they have a quatter, they have
a quatter, they have a quatter, they have a quatter, they have a quatter, they have
to be lightweight, a diesel, and you would be pretty heavy, that's what it's full, that's what
it's got, but self-sufficient, they'll need to know.
Anyway, they went for us.
Bye.
Hell yeah, they do.
A lot of people called in about this, man, a lot of people interested in the price
of diesel and how it works, all kinds of different opinions, and, of course, I've also
mentioned that, you know, if it's taxation, then it's not entirely fair for these prices,
because not everyone uses diesel to travel with.
Adam, zero here in North Carolina, you were just talking about not all people using diesel
or generating the wear and tear that tax pays for an economic phenomenon called in.
You referred to airplanes, you referred to other things.
There is a foreign diesel that you can get, it's not taxed the same, it's illegal to put
it in, a car that's driving on a road, it's meant for trackers and form equipment.
Yeah, they call that red diesel over here in Europe, yeah, I'm aware of it, and it's red,
because it's actually the color red, which is the quickest way for the authorities, the man,
to check and see what kind of diesel you're driving on.
And I have seen cars pulled over and checked for that, and I've seen people get busted for it,
but yeah, it's a hell of a lot cheaper, at least it was.
Not quite sure what the percentages these days, but yeah, I'm aware of that.
It's not putting wear and tear on the road.
There is a form diesel, like that, where you buy it, you're not putting it in your car,
you're not putting wear and tear on the road, and because of that, it's not taxed the same.
So if you knew that, I'd be live out in the stick.
And that was, I could see that a bit, all right.
All right, man, thank you.
They work for us.
Hell, yes, they, you know it, let's see.
Uh, Daniel Kleinberger, Adam, don't know if this is a fact, but an interesting note,
my grandpa is a guy nut, I'm not quite sure what you mean by that.
He's been, he's been one his whole life, and knows as far as I can tell everything about the vehicle.
Maybe even a car nut, diesel prices have risen because of a government conspiracy, kind of.
I just wanted to say that, but this is the reason he says why, okay, this is grandpa talking.
Global warming kind of, here's how he broke it down, they used to be cheap, very cheap.
This is because of all the great black smoke, you remember, seeing his kids behind the school bus.
Yeah, I remember that.
Well, the global warming conspiracy, charge more to people, as I call it, he says, wants
to make money.
Well, if we reduce how dirty diesel is, takes more money to refine it.
So the end result of diesel costing more, in our wisdom, well, we say we're destroying
the planet, we need to fix it and to make diesel cleaner, we need to pay more to refine it,
and now diesel costs more to make the gas, we're in the past that dirty diesel used to
be cheaper than the new and improved clean diesel.
That's what I've been hearing consistently, let's listen to a couple more voice comments.
Here we go.
Hey, I'm Jason from London, just calling to tell you why diesel's gotten so expensive.
Mostly, it's because of three factors.
First, diesel's in high demand worldwide, second because refining diesel is very close to
heating oil, with recent cold winters that demand for heating oil is up, which dries up
the price both heating oil and diesel, and last but not least, the US government regulations
are demanding lower sulfur content driving up the cost of refining.
Well, that's all some questions you've had of you.
No, I'll talk to you later.
And they work for us one more.
And I told him from that way, I've got a question.
That's Tom from Melbourne, he's weighed down under, so it's actually a weekend where he is.
I have about the oil prices, and I thought that the price of oil is shut up recently
is because we've hit the top of peak oil, and since 2005, there hasn't been any more production
than that, because we have a lot of big demand.
Same supply, it sort of means that prices go up.
The Dango curve of this natural distribution is obviously like quicker than the
outgoing curve, because the whole infrastructure to use the oil is already there.
So basically, it's just that the matter of supply and demand, I think people are getting
confused about that, isn't that the reason? It's running out, it's a natural resource, it's running
out petrol prices will not come down until a scalable alternative is found.
And I'm sorry, folks. I'm going to live a bit. All right, I wish I could say that work for us,
but I think they work for themselves.
Now, you got to be optimistic, my friend. They work for us.
I think you're all right, basically, it's a number of factors. It's a perfect storm.
The peak oil, of course, I've seen the documentaries online that has something to do with it,
no doubt about it. Although, if we truly hit the peak, then the price will just keep going
up, and it is fluctuating. It's going up and down. So, yeah, supply and demand definitely,
and that is how the price of oil has been determined historically by
the organizations, the organization countries like OPEC saying, look, we're turning it down or
not, you're turning it up and not, you're more supply, less supply, totally just by, you know,
nudging it could change the price. It's traders. It's big institutions like insurance companies
who are buying up oil and rolling it over month to month and have oil literally sitting around
in tankers and circling the globe. Something else I read. Someone dropped something on the
source code drop drop.io slash data source code. It was something called splash and dash
where the tanker will get cheap oil in South America. I think that's what it was. Then
Bob on by, you know, stop, maybe it wasn't South America. Somehow, I should look at it again.
But somehow it was like, you know, drop it in a dash of a US oil on top of it to get like a dollar
tax credit and then floating it over to Europe. It was some scam that I got to look into. I'm sure
someone whoever dropped it in their sending a voicemail comment or calling the voicemail lines,
if you don't mind. So anyway, so it's big institutions. They're definitely part of this. It's
greed, no kidding. The credit crunch, you know, it's just a perfect, perfect storm at all fits
together. And there are some people getting really, really rich off of this. And it's not just
necessarily the oil companies because they do have to, you know, if they want to grow, they're
not stupid. They know that they, you know, they're not sitting around and saying, look, well,
I'll be dead in 30 years anyway. So let's just live it up. You know, these are big corporations.
They got to figure something out. I personally have really starting to lean towards a nuclear energy.
Oh, speaking of nuclear energy. I got to, let me just read this email from briefly,
from D.D. And she says, she's from Ontario, Canada. And she said, you were talking about
nuclear and I had this feeling I'd heard about it somewhere before. And indeed, it was an
ad that was running Ontario, Canada rebranding nuclear to nuclear. And so she sent it over to
we check this out. It's perfect. It's exactly what I want. This is how nuclear energy should be
marketed at all times in the future. This year, Ontario will decide on its future energy mix.
So just insert your country's name here. The reality is, the equivalent of 80% of our current
power capacity will soon need replacing conservation renewables and hydro can help. But nuclear
will continue to play a leading role. Nuclear is clean and reliable. It's been with us over 40 years.
Already supplies 51% of our electricity and must gear up now to help power the years ahead.
A message from the Canadian Nuclear Association more power to you. It's fresh. More power to you,
exactly. I love it. That's a nice happy kind of messaging we need. You think it sounds scary,
but I'm telling you, there's really something to this. I think that a lot of money is being spent
on keeps steering us away from nuclear energy and keeping us focused on windmills and shit.
That is just not quite there yet. This technology has been around a long time. It's really been
improved quite a lot and already, as you can hear right there, connect, connect nuclear.
Right there in Ontario, 50% generated by nuclear energy. It's still hard to say, even though
I rebranded it. Let me see, what should we do? Should we play one more song?
Actually, there is maybe one thing I just want to read and then I'll play a song for you. This was
email titled, The Drunken Londoner is he mad. I wish this was audio. It would be so much better.
Adam, I have to agree with you with the state of public transport. Now, this is regarding the new law
in the United Kingdom where drinking of alcoholic beverages or carrying an open container of alcohol
is no longer allowed as of June 1, 2008. Drinking and drunks on the last trainer bus makes it very
intimidating and I'm a big bloke. Also, fucking twots playing music on phone speakers. It's
bad enough one person, but sometimes you can have four or five of them all. Most of the time,
some other tuneless gangster rap and if you ask them to, maybe they use headphones,
you get abuse. It's at this time that I use my powers given to me by the queen to ask them to leave
the bus. If not, I use force to do so. Usually, to a round of applause. The Drunken
Londoner, that of course is our very own chuckle head. Sorry, pal. Why do you need to drink on the
tube? Don't you get 24 hours drinking in pubs and clubs? Make get over it. There's some more serious
attacks on our liberty. Oh, Adam, on CCTV, I use that in my work. I disagree strongly with that
senior officer. CCTV is a valuable tool if used correctly, but what concerns me is the number of
large shopping centers that stick up CCTVs sometimes a long way from their own property. Why?
In large cities, there can be hundreds of different CCTV schemes, most of them overlapping,
to want to come see, discuss it. I'm willing to arrange a visit so you can see for yourself. Yes,
I work for you. Work long hours, long shift hours. And I'll just say this is from
Mueller. He signs off. And actually does provide some details, but he's a cop. So maybe
I'll go have a look and see how that's working. I'm open, you know. I'm the first guy that put the
tin foil hat on or the aluminum foil deflector beanie. But I'm very open. I'd love to see how it works.
And I'd love to have a look behind big brothers, you know, set up. I'm saying sound seeing tour with
the hidden camera, my friends. What do you think? All right. Let me, uh, let me play a song here.
Wait, hold on. Do want to play that one. That one will play tomorrow. Oh, there we go.
Tomorrow will be food bar Friday and I'm totally expecting to throw out a massive jam. So get
to your suggestions in, drop some songs on the drop. Drop.io slash Danny source code.
Reverse in the rules today. The mashup comes last on 765.
I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. Keep me in this
pain until you run that mouth. Didn't know I'd have to play and break the fuck out. And
it will see you slap. I'm the one right with it. And what about bringing that? Just know it's
red and that. So what about you? Well, I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded.
I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded.
I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded.
I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded.
I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all
incorporate. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded. I'm fucked up all-branded.
No, we stay anymore.
You're not a movement, I'm a movement
He is a man, he is a man
God, but I can't help you, I'm a joke, I'm a joke man
He is a man, I'm a reader
God, but I can't help you, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke
I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I'm a joke, I
expertly mashed up by DJ Dropbase again,
Limbiscan and Black Sabbath.
Yeah, kind of angry sound that I'm looking for at the end of the show.
Cannot wait until tomorrow.
I hope you all participate drop.io slash daily source code.
Of course, this show you can be found at daily source code.com.
Other important homework for the Chocoheds at curie.com.
Of course, an atom at mevio.com is the current email address.
And you know, I'm one more thing.
I'm looking for, I'd like to make some merchandise for the show.
And what I'd like to make is kind of like, well, be cool to have aluminum foil,
deflector beanies, but kind of like made of wool or maybe some kind of aluminum foil
strands.
It has to be certified.
It has to actually work.
But I'd like to be a garment that we could have like a DSC logo on the front,
maybe they work for us on the back or do not enter or something like that.
Just something we can all wear more when we're listening to the show.
I'll wear it when I'm making it if you guys promised to wear it while you're listening
to it.
And I'll definitely talk to you tomorrow right here on the DSC for the Fubar Friday.
Until then, enjoy your freedom and live with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Stick it in your ear.