You were listening to the last DSC, you heard Adam talk about the iPhone SDK.
And I got to tell you, it almost makes you want to quit your job and just develop apps for the iPhone.
It's like, I know I could do it.
I know I could be really good at programming this stuff.
I know all kinds of cool widgets I'd want to make.
It'll be interesting to see how that plays out.
We'll have no fear because if you're hearing this, then Adam is back.
He's not abandon us and he's bringing us the DSC 733.
Perhaps one of his widget he builds will be making his iPhone a submarine when
he drops it in the floor.
The 60 million dollars worth of airplane straps by us.
To the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I've guessed it, it's Adam Curry.
God, I believe it's above and more dead.
I went out for a ride and I never went back.
Like a river that falls over its floor.
I don't know what to look at, but just keep going.
Everybody's got our own brief heart.
I love everybody who needs more days to rest
I never know about all the hell
I've always loved you and I've always loved the one you said
I've loved you and I've always loved the one you said
Everybody's got a free time
Oh man, I got to tell you
Nothing like a bit of the boss to kick off a footballer Friday
How you doing everybody?
It is episode number 733 of the Daily Stores Code
Thank you to the organization, the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
We're a bit of a spring-steen there under educational auspices of course
Hey, I'm back
You know what?
One episode this week, it might as well be the football Friday episode
Correct man
I got so much to tell you guys, a lot has happened
And why don't we do it while chillin' out together
I'm here, I've got the Al Jazeera Bathrobe on
It's Friday, just a bit past 12 in the afternoon
I needed a bit of sleep, so I'm rested
I'm really bringing you your football Friday
Only two big topics today, so make sure you stay tuned to it
Without the entire episode
And of course, kick ass tunes
To wrap up your week and get you ready for the weekend
From the affluent suburb of Surrey
It's the west side of Gitan and Gild for upstairs in the attic
It is the Daily Source Code, the football Friday edition of 733
Let's bring it on y'all
We're gonna go, cause I have a way
Come with tonight
We'll start with going to us
Crossing your pruning
From the head and the distance
So wish you moving
I'm really on my side of the town
And just a bit of night
And this is gonna go
From the mission room
I was talking too much
I was just gonna be having all this good evening
And chillin' out together
And show me the way
We're gonna go, cause I have a way
Let's do it all, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let
go, let's go, let's go, from here, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, they're literally
It's a bit intense, kind of takes away the original vibe of the song, and grow one, the Eagles
Hotel California versus Hustle Athletics San Francisco. Just to keep the football
train running, you can't check in any time you want. You can never leave.
Holy moly. All right, everybody. How you doing? Oh, man. It's good to be back home,
been on the road for, for most of the week was home yesterday, but, um, oh, man, it's been so
incredibly busy. Yeah, I got another high frequency pitch tone coming from somewhere. We'll
just leave that for what it is for today. All right, everybody. Well, um, gee, I almost don't know where to
start. Um, I was on the road part of it in support of my, uh, my lovely wife, the lady Patricia,
who, um, has been selected. Actually she's been asked to make selections. Uh, I don't know. I'm sure
if you live, well, probably it's probably in about 60 countries now. So if you live, um, almost any
way you've probably seen a version of America's Got Talent, or perhaps Britain's Got Talent,
which actually, um, produced an amazing opera singer in the UK. So now there's the Holland's Got Talent
version of the show. And now you know, the, of course, the lady Patricia after, uh, walking around
with, uh, an effective effect that appendix for over a year. She's back. She's back on the sheen,
she's ready to rock and roll. And, uh, this offer came along. She's like, oh, wow, I can be a judge on
Holland's Got Talent. She said, I don't think they got any talents. So that, that should be a pretty
fun show. And of course it turns out that, uh, there is some talent hidden in those lowlands.
So anyway, um, that was a, I think a three day, uh, three day project for her and she's going back
at the end of the month. I won't be able to join her for that. I was able to take care of a couple
other things that I want to talk about. And of course, while on the road, a lot of things were
happening, uh, uh, back at HQ and San Francisco as well as in London, uh, you probably noticed podshow.com
and BT podshow. Our com have changed brand new, uh, looking field. This is not the coveted version
three V3s we call it. This is more like, uh, V2.5. And, uh, the reasons behind it, I will talk
about later on today because I think it's pretty exciting what's going on. Uh, yes, they, uh, spent a
lot of time on the phone, talking to a lot of people who work with us, um, talking about the transition
that we're making, uh, some of the changes, uh, it affects everybody across the board. But we're really
focused and I'm, I'm extremely happy, uh, at the place that we're in right now because, uh,
man, I think we're, uh, I think the rocket ship is, uh, is lit and we have some lift off.
But boy, interesting working out the payload. Okay, let's see. I got some songs lined up. I
do want to talk about, uh, that ends, and in something else, I've been getting some amazing offers
myself that I just want to share with you because they're so funny. And, uh, one or two, I might
actually, uh, I might actually consider. So I'd love to hear some feedback from you guys.
One of the thing before I forget, of course, that was an agro one mashup that I played for you.
Uh, you know, I spent some time yesterday, Patricia's working on another project.
And, um, she wants to do a version of Martha Reeves and the Van Delas doing heat wave.
And she was playing this, um, you know, the original track for me and she was, uh, saying, okay,
no, I want to do it differently. I want to, uh, I want to, uh, I want to basically shorten this
bit here, uh, move this right after the, uh, to right after the intro. And as she's playing it,
I'm listening to the song and I'm going to jade a bug, uh, jade a bug. And she's like,
wow, you're right. You could do a perfect mashup of Martha Reeves and the Van Delas,
and uh, wham's waking me up before you go go. And like, you know, I'm sure someone has done
that one already. It makes so much sense. I mean, everything about that song is just like
wake me up before you go go. And I did some Google searches. I went to mashuptown.com,
which, of course, is the official supplier of mashups. Um, I did some searches on SeekPod,
absolutely no luck, no joy whatsoever. And I'm amazed. So this weekend, actually, um, my plan is
on Sunday. I'm going to see if I can do my own mashup because I think it'll be a perfect combination.
Of course, if anyone has a mashup, please let me know before Sunday, fire me off an email or
something like that. Let me know because, uh, I'm sure that whoever has done something,
it's going to be better than what I come up with on one of my first mashup tries. So please
do let me know if you have something out there. Or if you think you can do it because I'd love
to have a version. I'm Sean. I'm Joseph. And we're the ad bastards. The movies convince you
that advertising was the greatest job owner. Well, welcome to your wakeup call podcasting for
the studio and DFW. We've got insights into what's really going on in advertising. So check us out
on iTunes or adbusters.com because, you know, the movies were just a lie.
All right. Yes, I'm sure they are. Adbusters. Uh, ad bastards. You got to listen to that show.
Yeah, I'm a big fan of marketing shows. CC Chapman does one. Uh, Joseph Jaffee, of course,
has across the sound. He celebrated over 100 episodes recently. I believe in these guys
when I want this scene. That's good stuff, man. If you really want to know what's going on with
mainstream and what's happening with advertising, that's the place to listen to them. Okay. So
I'll be talking about some of that myself later on, at least the mainstream portion of it, uh, and
how it's, uh, how it's been, uh, touching my life. So we'll get into that a bit of, of course, it's a
food bar Friday. That means we have to have some surges. He thought he'll be coming up just a little bit.
And we're already up to episode number 113 of Yon Paul. Let's hit test. Yon, bring it in.
Good to use the test with Yon Paul.
Hi, Yon. Hey, Adam. Hi, doing. Um, I'm doing is hit this number 113. And we're going to start
right away with intro number one. Okay. Oh, dude. Come on, man. I'm a child of the 80s and 90s.
I would recognize Angel of Harlem by you two in the middle of the night. Number two.
Whoa.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh. Okay, that I would not recognize the middle of the night.
And this is intro number three. Oh, Joseph is on a vacation for, um, um, um, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
I think the titles, Josie, uh, I don't know. And these are the answers. Okay, bring it on. There you go.
This is from 1980, it's an answer number one. Hell yeah.
Thank you, YouTube.
Excellent day.
YouTube Angel of Harlem is answer number one.
What was that?
This is answer number two.
From 87 to Gino Vanelli.
Oh man.
What a choice young wildborses man.
I would never have gotten out.
Gino Vanelli and wildborses is answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
This one I know for sure.
Congratulations.
I don't want to lose your love tonight.
It's the outfield for sure.
From 1986 outfield for your love.
All right.
Again give me that.
It's number 113.
Yeah.
So Adam, how did you do?
I think I got like one and a half or close to two right.
And not bad.
You're not bad.
All right.
The answers to this hit test.
And also the links to iTunes so that you can buy these tricks online.
And to be found at hittest.potshow.com.
Again, thank you for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I'll be back for number 114 to until then.
Have a very nice week and take care.
Bye bye.
Be back to test at gmail.com.
info.
Young bullet.com.
JNPOLVT.com.
Oh man.
If you thought my singing on the hit test was bad.
Please look at the American out.
Can I say the obvious before we start,
which is I think you're over 20 years.
All right.
Tell me why you hit that.
If you've ever seen a film for the Wedding singer,
it was a guy who performs a wedding.
That's what he looked like.
What are you going to sing today to prove that you are the next American artist?
Snatch from pushing the musical.
There's a part of me that's been killed.
When I'm weird, I'm always out drinking.
There's something special about you, girl.
If I'm not thinking, I'm all out.
I'm sure you think of it.
I've heard some weird auditions in my life,
but I've got to tell you that it's possibly the weirdest I've ever heard in my life.
I mean, it was like a one year old singing song.
You don't really cut out to be a singer.
I don't think.
I'm a singer of K.
I'm a singer.
You don't.
Okay.
Zero for effort.
Zero for style.
Zero for stock quality.
And you know what?
I think you just killed my favorite song a little time.
So you think you can sing any better?
Prove it.
Head over the music.potsho.com
and pick out your favorite pot-sake track.
Then go over to thepot5.com for all the details.
We'll be competing against some of the best
and some of the worst singers on the internet.
And who knows?
You may become the next pot-five aisle.
Okay.
There you go.
It could happen.
All right.
The first stop on the football trains coming up after a song
from the pot-sake music network.
Got a couple of those lined up for it.
Because, man, there's some good stuff coming up.
I'll talk to you on the side of a Sarah Vaughan
to hard as I got sunshine.
Living in a dangerous court.
And it's so hard to find a time
to really open and need my plea.
Keep my soul in drink the wine.
So much more for me to be.
I'll be on what I can see.
I choose to let the sunshine make what.
And this is how my day can end.
Don't lie to me.
He said, I mean, email a while ago, he says, you know, we've got this show and I think
it's perfect for you.
I'd really like you to take a look at the treatment and see if you're interested in doing
the pilot for us.
The first thing I said, of course, is dude, I'm not interested in a mainstream television
career.
I'm not interested in, you know, I don't have no intention of a career in making television
pilots unless they're for pod show and we're making them for online.
That I'm interested in what kind of show is it?
It's a game show.
I'm like, wow, I've always wondered what it would be like to do a game show.
And they've come up with a very interesting, very simple program.
And so they sent me the treatment, read through it, and so I did hook up with them.
And we went through kind of like a version of the game and I got to tell you, I had a lot
of fun.
Really enjoyed, you know, basically being a game show host, it was great because it had
nothing to do with me, nothing to do with, well, actually, the way this thing is set
up, there's a lot of freedom for the host or the presenter to bring a lot of his own
personality and really a lot of freedom of movement, which to me is quite the opposite
of the restrictive environment of television.
You know, I'm a much more an audio guy or a radio guy because I basically control
everything from beginning to end.
And I don't know, you know, if we can strike the right deal, I said, look, I'm not interested
in making a pilot.
If you'll give me a piece of the action, well, yeah, then we can talk.
So I think, I think we got something, we're pulling something together there.
And of course, this is the perfect, you know, almost all game shows you can make derivatives
of the work perfectly online, you know, not a 22 minute or 30 minutes with commercial
version, but I'm pretty sure there's something we could do in a, you know, one to three
minute version.
So I'll keep you up to speed on that.
It was just really interesting to get in touch again with some mainstream media folks
and they're still to say nothing has changed.
And they're all in awe of what we're doing, I might add.
They're all extremely envious of how quickly we can, you know, we as independent producers
can crank out new ideas, test them out, you know, we don't have a pilot season.
We can, I look, as far as I'm considered, or as far as the show is considered, this
is still in pilot phase episode 733 of the pilot.
I am the pilot of the airwaves, 16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
What can I say?
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Your honor, please don't think that, Gavl, you can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give a nod.
To the hardest work in law here, it's Jersey time, yeah, yeah, it's Jersey time, oh yeah.
You're out there, what do you say?
You might even come to the end.
Yo, yo, yo.
Yo, how's it going Adam, it's Jersey time, the official musicologist of the Cha Cha.
Dude, I'm a little sad, don't know.
I've got to tell you it's been a rough week with no DSCs.
I don't know how people are getting through, I mean, the economy's going to shit.
The world's just changing.
It's just sad, man.
I need something to cheer me up.
I don't know what I need.
I need the temple of soul.
Check these guys out.
They're out of flooring and man.
If they don't make it happy, nothing will.
Cause they got sunshine in your smile.
They're just...
You know, in this life, there are circumstances that happen beyond our control.
And you can say it.
But no, I love you.
Do you know how it's touching?
We have it.
You know how it's touching?
It was so good that I actually noticed that I had it scheduled I put this song in again for this daily source
Got to find another song in the show with fantastic temple of soul sunshine in your smile
Selected by the official musicologist of the cha cha sir jersey Todd links to the songs of course in the show notes a daily source code
Doctor metal has this is then in order in the shadow side. Bye. This is just a different way to listen
Hi, this is Tommy's dog
Hey, this is Diana. Hey, this is for a good eye. This is staff at Davis from I O I his job for TV team
And you're listening to and you're listening to
That's in the radio chat a new bed
W w w w dot in the radio chat a new good dot com
Try to g coming up back to this next track another one from the pod save music network
We've found out in a little bit if we've got to do this in my pocket
We've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little
bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit of people who are further than that if we never found out in a little bit if we've found out in an any little bit if we never found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we've thought in a little bit if we've found out in a little bit if we
Get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get down, get
13, jungle juice.
From the pod say music now, work at music dot podshow dot com and, of course you can find
a player at Podshow dot com slash music.
Uh, look for crow.
Crazy and uh, I'll put a link in the show notes and you can find it easily.
alright, so uh, we released v2.5 yesterday.
Um, pretty big deal for us.
Um, kind of, yeah.
I mean, uh, we're still a relatively young company, even though man, we've been doing
this for three years now since 2005, we started the company,
the company.
But we're still agile enough to make some fast moves when we really need to make them.
And let me tell you a little bit about what's going on.
If you look at the new site, so this is really a, I even posted it on curry.com.
This is not a face lift, really.
It's more like a Botox injection, if you will.
As we continue our way towards V3, which you'll have more technological improvements.
This really changes the home pages for Potcha.com and VT Potcha.com shows a little bit of
a direction where we want to go with how we're displaying media.
Most of the underlying things are still the same, there's some design changes.
And of course, there's lots of bugs and it should be worked out as you can always expect.
But it has sparked a very good conversation because I believe that people are seeing
that we're now finalizing our strategy and I want to drill down on this today.
So you can think about it over the weekend.
Obviously, I didn't have, I really didn't have the energy, honestly, to go through
voicemail feedback for today's show.
So I'm sure we'll have plenty of it to talk about next week.
And darn, if I don't want to do a five show week next week, man, I really need it.
This was no good.
Again, apologies.
It's just the way it worked out.
Tough.
That's it.
What?
Who needs sleep?
Oh, by the way, I forgot to tell you that I've also been asked to participate in a morning
radio program on a regular basis.
That's the thing I have to say that interests me the most because I've been experimenting
a bit with live shows.
Haven't done one on the Charlie in a while.
But I think I have an idea of how we're going to do it next week.
Because that is another part of what I love doing, man.
I love talking to people live and chatting around.
Anyway, if you look at Pachot.com, if you haven't, maybe if you're not in the car or
if you're not on the road, you could take a look at it now if you haven't seen it.
You'll see here that we're really playing into our strategy.
Let me tell you what that is.
So first of all, about two months ago, maybe three months ago, we really discovered
that we have two lines of business that are absolutely kicking ass and really, really working.
One of them is already making really decent money.
The other one is just about to hit.
So I'll start with that one.
That is online video.
When I say online video, I'm not talking about necessarily YouTube, like user-generated
clips because the real business turns out is independently produced, semi-professionally
produced or even professionally produced because it does work for sites like Hulu.
Short form, I must say, episodic content.
So of course, we have several hundred video programs now on our network that are short
form, that are very targeted and that are formats that are absolutely created for the
online audience and they're working.
What we figured out is how to market those programs and I know I've talked about this
a lot.
You know, it's, yes, there are some advantages that mainstream has because they have
a channel.
There's only so many channels on your television.
It is an ever-expanding universe, I might point out.
So that advantage is slipping away quite rapidly.
But essentially, in the mainstream entertainment business, whether it's music, whether it's
television, whether it's film, it's all about marketing.
If you make a $100 million film and you have a $20 million star in that, the first thing
that's done is that $20 million is considered a marketing cost.
Tom Cruise is an OK actor, but he's not all that great.
Is he really worth $20 million?
Yeah, well, at one point he was because he was a big name draw.
His name will put butts and seats and theaters.
We'll get people buying DVDs.
So that's basically part of marketing.
You make a $100 million movie.
You could easily spend $125 million on marketing the movie all the way throughout its lifespan
from film onto DVD.
Same goes for television.
In fact, when you have a number one hit show, dancing with the stars, it's not like,
oh, we're number one and we just kick back and relax and the audience just keeps coming
back.
Exactly the opposite.
The marketing money is turned up even further because you're going to sell more advertising
at higher prices.
You need to keep those numbers there.
So you start marketing it and there's, oh, man, they spent so much money on it.
Let's just take that show as an example.
Outside of advertisements, promos, you run a promo in your own television network.
I think that's what is dancing with the stars, Fox.
That's not free.
That's, you're using up that airtime instead of a commercial.
So that's a cost.
There's billboards.
There's advertisements and magazines.
There's PR firms that are taking the stars all around to all the different shows, talk
shows, to be talking about their experience.
There's a huge PR machine that's working for the program and it costs a lot of money.
The more successful it is, the more marketing that has to be done to maintain that.
So what sites like YouTube and AOL and now there's really the user generated sites while
extremely entertaining and while there's tons of good stuff and of course a lot of that
good stuff is stolen content.
That's not like you still can't find the daily show on YouTube or the documentary that
aired yesterday that you missed on television.
You can still find that all over YouTube.
In general, brand advertisers, the big boys, the Coca-Cola, the Proctor and Gamble, the
next 10 billion dollars of advertising that's going to come online, has not really come
online yet because they are afraid to advertise in a non-brand safe environment.
What do I mean?
My non-brand safe?
Well, to look at YouTube, they don't want the risk of all of a sudden having their advertising
sitting next to on top of or being pre-rolled in front of someone shooting a firecracker
out of his ass.
It's just not what brands are into.
So of course YouTube did build up a huge audience of eyeballs, but it's unmonitizable.
In fact, I know for a fact that last year, Pod Show made more money on advertising sales
than YouTube.
I think they just got it like an $8 million Microsoft Xbox 360 campaign.
That's obviously a really good deal.
Clearly, that's a brand advertiser who does take the risk and they'll live with it because
it's a gaming industry.
There's a lot of risk already involved in the content that are contained in the games.
And I think they're right.
I think that is appropriate for that type of advertiser.
You're not going to see cover girl.
You're not going to see Coca-Cola necessarily rolling out brand advertising in a broad way
on user-generated video or on social media sites.
In fact, Google guaranteed a rather large amount of advertising for my space, they can't
fulfill the order.
You know, the traffic is just not valuable enough and it turns out that on these social
media, social sites, social networking sites.
People are getting pretty good at avoiding the ads.
Go figure.
That's because they're ads.
They're not integrated within the content and they're just, they'll still not relevant.
Okay.
So meanwhile, you've got brand advertisers desperate to advertise on video online.
So they wind up eventually going to people who have brand-save video.
So an example is Hulu.
An example, I think juice dual put them in that category even though they don't see
anything to be, you know, quite as on fire as they were and I believe that's because you
have to download a separate application, but that's just me.
But also, I haven't really seen great content from them yet, but you know, they're definitely
in the game.
AOL Yahoo, you know, they do have some independently produced, semi-professionally produced,
or even professionally produced content.
Of course, the independently produced stuff is what interests me the most personally,
because I think it's the most creative and hits the audience right between the eyes.
So with the amount of content we have, with a number of episodic shows and our knowledge
of how to market those shows online, which we've gotten really good at.
Make no mistake and mistake.
We spend real money using other types of networks.
We use Google AdWords.
We use all kinds of different ways to introduce relevant audience to the programming we have.
And if you don't market, yeah, you have organic growth of every single show.
You know, the numbers drop down.
You turn the marketing up, the numbers go up again.
This is just the way media works.
We, you know, people kind of forgot that with these viral videos.
You know, there's no way to advertise on a viral video.
You know, if something all of a sudden goes viral, and let's say it is even brand, brand
safe, you still have to get the rights to sell advertising on it.
And by that time, you know, millions of people have seen it, you know, how can I go to an advertiser
who's trying to plan their advertising campaign and get them to advertise on it?
It's too late, the moment's over.
So it's not a stable, sustainable, or predictable business model with any type of visibility.
So we have one.
And it's gotten so interesting now that there's hundreds of millions of dollars out there
for online video, episodic, brand safe, independently produced.
And these big guys can't fulfill the order.
They just, they just don't have the inventory or they don't have the rights or they
can't promise brand safeness.
Okay, that's what we're coming in.
Come in.
Some of this opportunity is now starting to spill over and start to start to drip into
our lap.
And, you know, it may not take much.
We could be close to a tipping point where a lot could just come streaming in.
Again, we have the ability to fulfill these orders because we know how to market to our
audiences.
We know how to get, you know, a hundred or a hundred and fifty million views in a month.
And we have the knowledge of how to do it and it's working and it's paying off.
And people like the content, co-figure advertisers love the fact that their messages
are relevant, that the audience that we're bringing in to these programs are relevant
and the paying for it.
So that's obviously awesome.
And that's something that we've been focused on for a while and it's a real line of
business for us and we're concentrating a majority of our efforts on that.
Now we have the other side and on the other side would be this side of the house.
Let's just call it podcasts, but it's really mainly audio long-form programming that
is not necessarily brand safe.
I would not call this show brand safe at all.
In fact, you don't hear many advertisers on this program do you?
You've got some bold ones like Nokia who of course allow me to sell the Nokia N810 at
a 15% discount.
We've got a new price by the way, go to podshowoffers.com.
The price has been reduced.
Use my checkout code daily source code to get your 15%.
You can't get this thing cheaper anywhere and there's been quite a price war and all kinds
of confusion going on, but podshowoffers.com still has the cheapest price.
If you use my code daily source code, then of course there's also go daddy where you can
use my checkout code DSC3.
Now on all of these and you've heard me do these before, these are, we just call these
our campaigns and we have a large group of producer, producers who make, well, I've got
to call them, you just differentiate their podcasts, you know, I really think the audio
part is, even though there's all kinds of confusion in the marketplace about what
a podcast is, let's just say this is audio only just for the purposes of this discussion.
Now in audio shows and you know, that's, that is the genesis of our company.
A lot of the shows don't have huge audiences, there's not many, in fact, there's only
probably two handfuls of shows that can do over a million listens a month.
And some of the, you know, of course there's always some stuff that there's always some
exception to the rule, but in general, most of the shows, if you were to look at an advertising
ratio where ads are spots are sold at a cost per thousand.
So for video, I think it's between $25 and $35 per thousand.
So if you have 1,000 people listening to the show, we could essentially sell one commercial
and that would get you 25 to 35 bucks.
Okay.
So you can see where that's not going to be a lot of money for most of these producers, however,
the audiences that these shows have, including you chuckle heads out there, are an extremely
loyal.
They listen to the entire program, they catch up, they're involved or as the advertising
business likes to say, they're extremely engaged.
And they're convertible into customers, purchasers of product, either endorsed by the host,
or discussed in the program.
Sometimes even, only Ancillary mentioned the program, but further promoted on the show
side or on a weblogg.
So, and this is what we discovered with music, of course, you know, the Potsay music network
is built on this principle of loyal audiences who will listen to what, you know, their
buddies saying on the show will give something to try, they're willing to try it out,
and they'll provide feedback if they think it sucks.
So I believe in the past trailing 12 months, we sent out over $1.4 million in checks
to this pool of producers who are on these campaigns like GoDaddy, like Nokia, because
over every GoDaddy account they sell, every listener they bring in and convert to becoming
a customer.
Obviously, the host gets a piece of that, gets a piece of the action, and this is really
working.
We've got people with only a couple CPMs, if you will, who are making over $100,000
here.
So, if they're making money, we're making money and I'm extremely excited about how successful
this has become.
Almost, I have to say it's kind of exclusive to what Potsho is doing because it is a lot
like an affiliate sales network, only it includes a programming, which makes so much sense.
It's almost like podcast advertising, you know, it was meant to be this form of hybrid,
and it's really working because you don't have to worry about really what you're doing
on your show or the content of your show and the companies that are driving these campaigns
they're only interested in sales.
They just want to make money.
They really don't care that much how you do it as long as the money keeps rolling in.
And isn't that kind of a beautiful situation?
So, we've got those two lines of business, and they're making money for us and the things
we do with them are profitable.
So, you're going to see Potsho.com focus on those two main features.
And we're making those into many networks.
We're making them into channels where we're going to open up our producer pool.
Much, we're going to open up much wider.
We're going to come up with a whole new set of contracts that makes it much easier for
people to come in, you know, get on our programs, see if they like what we're doing.
Check out some of the deals that they can participate in and make money with.
We provide you with training, with tools, with all kinds of support outside of the architecture
of course that you just need to get your show up and running and statistics, et cetera.
And of course, there's the business back and the real infrastructure that was necessary
to do this.
And I'm, although I love doing video, I got to tell you, I'm extremely excited about
this.
And so, you can look forward to a number of campaigns.
Those of you who are already already in the Potsho producer group, we've got a couple
of new campaigns on the way, which are going to blow your socks off directly related
to your audiences, where you're actually in a way, we'll be selling yourself.
Not in the horrors kind of way, but you'll find out that's coming soon.
As I said, we're going to open it up much wider so that, you know, with less restrictions
and I think we'll probably be able to convert most of our existing producers into this
new contract, new agreement, which contains most of what people have been asking for.
You know, easy way in, easy way out.
We've already been really cool about, you know, we don't want to own your shit.
It's your shit to do with what you want.
Here's how you can work with us, here's how you can make money and hear the, and here
are the examples of the quite a large group of people who are actually doing it.
So that affects us in a big way.
So this past week, we've been, yeah, we've really been restructuring, reorganizing, re-shuffling.
We continue to, excuse me, blow full steam ahead to get the, to get V3 out.
I think probably around the 21st, yes, that should be another week or so.
You're going to see stuff coming online continuously.
And of course, stuff will break and there'll be some good stuff and some bad stuff.
And we'll just do what we can, right?
And I look, oh, listen those birds outside.
Oh, man, spring is almost here, except it's really wet, really cold.
It's a UK spring.
What happened to global warming, man?
I thought I was going to have exclusive beachfront access here in the UK.
I, I, I, all right, I want you to think about that over the weekend that if you have any
ideas, or thoughts or feedback, just call it into the voicemail lines, I'm still looking
for a new voicemail jingle, by the way.
The numbers are listed in the show, no, it's a daily source code.com.
Hello, Adam, let's listen to the chart chart.
This is Robert Gold and Toronto, host of the business cast at businesscast on podshow.com.
We just got the anti unjust Smith jingles.
Wait a year, here is latest for the business cast that's business cast by podshow.com, swing
Jeff Swing from a local bagel shop somewhere, it's the business cast.
Grab a hot press, bagel and a cup of Joe, a set you step down, and here we go.
It's on top of the trend, and gets them advice with new perspective.
Yeah, that's nice.
Buildness, business, digital entrepreneur, for those to make the best of their business.
It's your business, take it to the next level, make it that out of the mess, make it
the next level, make it that out of the list.
Nice.
All right, to wrap up today's Charlie, and then the footballer Friday, this is a track that
was sent to me, or actually brought to my attention by Matthew Eble, of course, good friend
of the Charlie.
This is a couple of his buddies from Nashville that just joined the pod, safe music revolution,
he wants me to share him with you, and I, hey, kick this, fans called the Lila
Y, got a front man with a ten-toned voice, no fool on baby.
Here's walk on by on the footballer Friday.
I remember only breathing alone, when I bet that I'm side of pride, I know my will
is by the sea, I wonder how it cuts over here's the lead, only watching life bring a
change in time, oh, what these lives have got to be, so the keys that I've ever made,
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no or just an access, excuse, I'll make a sign.
But with her eyes on her past,
Yes, and this body,
I can't believe there's something so beautiful,
Believe I feel it's so handy,
And these lines on a face,
And the way when I'm a lighter,
This one gives in heels and heels,
Oh, she said no, don't you wake up in your head.
Nope, no, no, that doesn't matter
Oh no, don't betray me
Oh, no, don't betray me
This is a moment, I just wanted
Where Lord, walk online
The world allows that I can tell you