We don't need lost digging trees in
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk
I guess this is a great
Game is the right
The man of my brain
The one who did not belong
The only thing we lost is a real man
And the one who did not belong
All you make and hide it's no matter what you get past it'll be right now
Feel many times, you need to be the one
But all you ever want was the past little girl
But now that I'm not in love with you
It's not how that's me, feel like I'm in love with you
I'm not like I'm in love with you
You've got a lot of my way of being a body
It's getting red, yeah
If you're having a good look, don't you feel like I'm in love with you
And I'm in love with you
What's no matter what you get past it'll be right now
All you make and hide it's no matter what you get past it'll be right now
Oh man, and that's what I call a mashup
Go home production's coming out of mashup retirement source by Dr. Art for mashuptown.com
C.C.Penistan and the Sex Pestacles
Yes, now that is the way a mashup should fit together finally. Did you know wrong daily source code episode number 754. Hey everybody. How you doing?
I just want to talk to you. I'm much I know that new website of yours
That maybe a web-shodditch Mr. Snowberry
You got a nice yellow lips to their boy
I'm glad you love it everybody. How are you coming to you from an absolutely astoundingly beautiful
Beautiful United Kingdom of course we're in the affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford here in the curry manner
I've got all the all the windows wide open here up in the attic
You can even hear the birds tweeting around a little bit and I apologize for yesterday
A lot of things went really really wrong technically
You know, I've you know we're exporting some of the daily source quick source code format to terrestrial radio in the Netherlands
And so the way that's being done is through a digital connection with their studio in the hay from the from the manner and
Conversely from the condo when appropriate when I'm there of course
Please calculate your local times on where necessary and I've never really worked with one of these things before
And this is a tried and true, you know, it's been tried and tested and it's worked in the field over and over again
I just never really had the opportunity to work with what is known as the co-deck connections of course
We know codex from
From the video and audio world empty three of course
Is a compression technology you need a co-deck a coder and a decoder
But for some reason in broadcasting they call a co-deck just this big box that hooks up to an ISDN line
It I gotta tell you it is absolutely phenomenal like I called
The
Jonsi de Borac before he left for Korea and I said dude you've got to get one of these
I know you have an ISDN line which he has somewhere probably has to reactivate it
But wow you can you it's like sitting next to each other
And there's almost no delay it's like you know just it's probably less the delay than talking over a cell phone
Which of course is also a digital connection
I'm just blown away by it however
As I said about putting all of this together
I know what am I hearing here
Oh I'm hearing lawnmowers and shit outside
A couple things that I learned something and I discovered something I just say
The first one is for some reason whenever I connect my
My monitor my have an apple cinema display
It completely
Introduced some kind of ground loop into my in fact
You know how you have on the on the cinema display you have
USUSB ports on the back so you basically you plug in
One USB cable which goes into the monitor along with the DCI connector
Whatever that monitor connector is called
Just listen what happens when I went and the monitor is not connected
The monitor is off it is plugged into the mains unit
But listen what happens when all I'm going to do is I'm just going to plug in the USB into the Mac
That I'm using to record hold on
Wait a minute I got to unplug something here and let me try this
Check this out it'll freak you out ready
Where is it which slot there we go?
Is this the right one?
I can't even get it in
I can't get it in honey give me a break
Wait maybe the other way around
Listen to that
That's just out shit
I just spilled my tea
My Louis Catordesk is completely ruined once again
That's not good
Wasn't a big bunch but
So you know I love working with two monitors and my whole setup
If you see the picture that I posted over on flicker
I think was it last week or the week before
You'll see that I've set up for two monitors is perfect
But I can't use them and I have no idea why this is happening
I've tried you know I spent the whole literally five or six hours
Most of yesterday's working day before San Francisco kicked in around 4 o'clock
Trying to debug this and I could not find it
First you know it's just unplugging everything and then who would think
Who would think that the monitor would cross such a such a bunch of crap
So I'm back to using the laptop screen which is kind of a bummer
But if anyone has any ideas and this ground loop shit is really really tricky
I know it is but I certainly appreciate any help
And then the second thing so I was testing with these guys
In the studio and you know the way I have my setup
And I'm so happy I got this before I created the long promise screen cast
Of what my setup looks like
So the guys were listening they said you've got a noise gate on it
Which you know right whenever you
Whenever I stop talking then all of a sudden it goes really really quiet
Because I don't want all this extraneous noise coming in
It says you know that's kind of a loser way to do it
And I was like oh really
He says yeah what you want to do is you want to
Take your microphone you want to put it into a compressor
And you want to lower it down a little bit
And then you want to put an exciter right after the compressor
And it almost works like a noise gate
Which is happening right now so for instance if I'm quiet
You'll hear a little bit of things in the background
But it's not like bringing up that big noise and then cutting it off
And so it's yeah it's actually
Much nicer way of doing things I think
So learn something new there I never heard of
I've setting up a compressor and an exciter or an expander
I think they might call it sometimes never heard of setting up as an noise gate
But there you go learn something new every day
And still to come still to come I promise you
Full blown screen cast of all of the bits and pieces that are the the curry setup
I got a fantastic link from someone
I want you and I will remember to put this in the show notes
It's called life goes on in Tehran
It's life goes on in Tehran.com
And Tehran by the way if you don't know the way
I think this is the official English spelling is T-E-H
Or actually tango echo hotel Romeo alpha november
Tehran
It's basically every single I think it's every day
But at least once a month
It's pictures from Tehran pictures of ordinary life pictures of Tehran itself
Pictures of the city of Tehran which I have to say right off the bat
Looks pretty damned depressing
But pictures of people
You really get an incredible feel
What Iranian or Tehran life is like
And of course parts of Iranian life
It's a pretty big country I'm sure it's not all like the city of Tehran
But I want you to take a look at that
Next time someone is doing some saber rattling
About bombing Iran
Take a look and see what will be bombing
Take a look at this beautiful country
And tell me that you agree with that
You know this is a saber rattling
I love that we talked about that in no agenda
And something that I hadn't actually brought up
This is kind of funny
There's something going on and I'm not quite understanding what's happening
They call it a Thoritarian behavior
There's a huge movement amongst Chinese youth
And there's a lot of them
What is a country hold?
One point three billion people
There's a huge movement who are saying
Hey you guys got the wrong idea
You're giving us a bum wrap
Where a China's great
And I think the I forget the name of it
But the translation of this movement
This group of kids is called Angry Chinese kids
I saw it in financial times
I'll have to look up the article
to see exactly what the description was
Like Angry Chinese kids
Is kind of what this descriptive name
And so we've been talking here on the daily source code
About perhaps not buying products from China
But in the meantime
Since the Olympic torch was accosted
Well I guess France had the biggest kind of to do
They tried to douse it in London
In France I think they were actually successful
They got a hold of it
And it was just more of a kerfuffle and skirmish
I love those words
Then in any other country
And so the Chinese are now
Lashing out at the French gross
I think it's gross re-retailer
Cocklefour
Which is kind of like a French Walmart
I'll just leave it at that
It's not exactly that
It's like a big box store
And so they're analyzing the stores
And they're doing exactly what we've been discussing
Here about doing to them
They're doing to the western to the western people
Not to the US but they're doing it to the French
Are we nuts?
And should we just write that off and say
Oh well you know they're probably pre-programmed
Or this concept of being a authoritarian
I think that's what it is
There's a whole PDF on the daily source code
Drop about this
Some PhD wrote like a 237 page book
Which you released a free
And I think I've gotten to page 18
But the whole idea that people will follow leaders stupidly
Which of course we're pretty good at
And I'm thinking is there really that much difference
Between us and our Chinese brothers and sisters
It just you know
Maybe they've been indoctrinated with all kinds of
Media messages for the past 50 years as well
I think that's pretty possible
And I don't know
I gotta get my ass over to China
I really really have to go
All right
A couple of things that hit a nerve
With with you chuckle heads
Which means that I got a lot of responses
The first one was my idea of rebranding nuclear energy
In general
Actually when I was prepping the show
I was thinking you know
I was particularly after speaking to
Our energies have on rod atoms
Atomic rod
Now I'm relatively convinced that
The nuclear waste issue is not quite as bad as it sounds
And it's you know nuclear waste is not a barrel of oozing goo
It's basically a block
Which can be easily restored
I'm not quite sure about radiation
I mean there's a lot of things I don't know
But I do know that there's been a very systematic campaign
Against nuclear energy for the past 20 or 30 years
And that technology doesn't prove
And I'm very interested in learning more about it
And then I saw Boston legal last night
And it was about this very issue
About a nuclear power plant coming to someone's town
On the town didn't want to have it there
And it was about radiation
So I'm more confused than I was
But one thing for sure
If we do want to go down this route
We have to remove the word nuclear
Or atomic
Because that has all these connotations
Of an oligay and mushroom clouds and bad stuff
So I thought maybe we could rename it
Well technically it's called fission
If a fuck-straught India CRSCR or India Oscar November
And I was thinking yeah that's not quite a sexy name
Can we call it fusion? Well I got a lot of comments about that okay?
Hey Adam
I just wanted to let you know that rebranding nuclear energy is fusion
Might be a little difficult
Fission and fusion are definitely not the same thing
Fission is breaking out of the part
And fusion is putting them together more or less
Both of them can be sources of energy
But at the moment, fission that is nuclear power
Is much, much easier to perform practically
And fusion is still quite a ways off
It seems as far as being a viable way to obtain energy
So rebranding fission is fusion would be
Very misleading and very confusing
And probably not the best idea
But I'm sure we can find some sort of cool name for it
That will turn nuclear energy into something that might be a little more acceptable
To have around our homes and businesses
So see you later Adam
Alright so of course solar and wind is known as green
Well it could be, it could easily fit under green
I mean I think the waste is green isn't it?
We'll start to glow green if it goes wrong
I can hear atomic rod just getting ready to record some feedback as we speak
The other thing I asked you I think last week is
Why no one has purchased any of the insurance from acuco.com
Which has been sponsoring the show for about a month and a half
The sponsorship is actually over
And I just want to continue because I want to understand it
And I got some fantastic feedback from you guys
Two pieces that I want to play for you
Well worth it because I've learned something about you chuckle heads
And you might even learn something as well
Oops sorry about that
Here we go
I understand from Boston
I'm driving along
Interstate 95 towards New Hampshire
I'm a way to graduate school
Completely secure in the knowledge that if I do something stupid while I'm talking on the phone
Hey hey, where'd that guy come from?
Oh sorry, I'm just kidding
If anything stupid happens to me and I die my wife is going to get my insurance policy
That I have through the United States Army
The servicemen's group life insurance
We call it signaling because everything's an acronym in the Army
So I already have my insurance buddy
Thanks for offering
I'll be show by that
Yeah man, thank you
And please be careful
We don't want anyone to have to get in on that
Yeah, I of course I don't know what the payout is of that type of insurance
But I had forgotten about that
A lot of people who are in the demographic of the daily source code have served
Hey by the way, if you've been to Iraq or if you've been to Afghanistan
I'm trying to get my English accent going here
Afghanistan
If you've been to Iraq or Afghanistan
Give me a call man
I'd love to talk to you
I'll just call on the voicemail and just tell me what's going on
Or if does anyone over there listen to it?
Do you guys have access to it?
Is there someone who can actually get the show?
Boy
I would be really nice
Alright, here's another one
This is actually a little more explanation
Why this charcoal head didn't go for the ACU code offer?
Check it out
Hey Adam, this is Sean J.
It'll restrict the cast and Hamilton
I got a comment about the ACU code thing
I actually did go to the ACU code site
And I used Jersey Todd code because I didn't have money more than you did
Yeah, thanks
And I don't know if I was just not paying attention
Or I was kind of surprised that it was a
A comparison site that compared other companies
I was assuming it was its own company
Like I don't know if some of those other ones
They're insurance and stuff like that
Yeah, that is a good point
And I kind of went through the same process
When I was looking for car insurance over here
And I went to compare.com
And I also thought that that was an assurer
who would give me a quote
And that was also the name says it
A comparison site
They are hugely successful though
I mean they're advertising on television
And something is working really, really well
So
Interesting to find out what kind of person
uses a site like that
Clearly not this chocolate
And so I think it's the nature of that company
Because I did look at the prices
And I did look at different companies offering the prices
But then I went to my insurance company
That I have for other stuff
For my auto and things like that
And it's a more comparing
So to get me to go back to that site
Was going to have to be
You know yet another trip to the computer
And that's okay
So you're insurer wasn't one of the ones being compared
That doesn't sound right
Let me know what you're insurer is
Let's see why it wasn't on theacucot.com site
Or why you felt it wasn't represented
And that's interesting
So I kind of feel what's happening now
There's too many steps from the actual product
I think
I don't know if that's true for everybody
But that's kind of the experience that I had
Because I did want to support you guys
But it seems to me like a
Reference role of a refer
Of a company if that makes sense
So it's a little bit removed
I'm certainly not a reason why I didn't buy through them
You know I didn't consciously say oh there's just three first
I'm not going to purchase through them
But it was an extra step removed
From the process of purchasing
To me
And I think that's why I didn't go back
Now I still have yet to purchase
But I think that that may be part of the deal
That I initially thought it was a company that was selling the life insurance
As opposed to a referral company
That could gauge discounts from various
Insurance companies like a
You know a travel office or
With the other one
Kind of website
Anyway
It's great here
Hope you in
Love you
Don't care if you're home
And I'll talk to you later
Keep up the great work
All right man, thank you
What I don't know is if you got any insurance
I don't know
I just wanted to congratulate you on a no agenda
Number 20 I think it was
I couldn't find the number for calling in
So I just called into the daily source code
It was highly entertaining, highly topical
Really funny, in fact I laughed my ass off
For any DSC listeners who are not getting no agenda
Get it
I never thought it would be so entertaining to listen to two guys
Just two in the fight
But it's fucking awesome
And you guys are real
Right here in the home
Three times a week
Look at some improvement
Looking for improvement
Let me see the prostate cancer prevention
Quotient here in the curry manner
stands at one for this week
So I am also a little bit behind
If you are wondering what this is all about
Well, then you should be listening to this show more often
Daily scores go to episode number 754
We missed the Friday
You know what that means
Time for y'all pull that shit test
Hey Adam, it's time for hit test again
And we're gonna start right away with intro number one
Oh
Works to be in
Oh, yes, y'all that would be genophonelli
Number two
Oh, y'all these are great
Janet Jackson's control
In her old incarnation and number three y'all hit me and the final one is number three
Oh, gee
Let me think couldn't be arrows mid to run the MC walk this way
Did I get three this time three stars out of three
And times up and all of these weeks answers are from
I mean
Test
And so number one genophonelli
And
Oh
That's number one in this week
It has the genophonelli and it hurts to be in love
And this is answer number two
Janet Jackson
We're not certain
I think people
Don't be
Oh
I don't
Never go
It's the
I don't
I want to go
Janet Jackson
Go
As answer number two
And this is answer number three
Arrows mid and run the MC
Walk this way
No
Don't do it
It's way
Walk this way
Don't do it
One DMC, there's Nathan walked this way and danced with number three and that concludes
hit us number 120.
So, Adam, how did you do this week?
Well, Ian, I am so happy you took the song for 96 or 87.
I got three out of three, I love it!
Thank you.
Review the answers to this hit us or in the older hit us or if you want to buy the tracks,
just feature it on the hit us online through iTunes.
You can go to hittest.mifio.com and there you'll find everything you need.
Adam, thanks for playing.
No, thank you, Ian.
Thank you for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for the next hit us.
So, until then, have a very nice week, take care and remember, try to think with your
hearts.
Bye-bye.
Hi, Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show.
We've got a review of UEFA Euro 2008 on the PlayStation 3.
We look at the new Call of Duty variety map hack for the 360 and you can win copies
of Warriors and Watchy for the PC.
That's all it gamesweasel.com.
Yeah, I'm a match, I'm a fighter with the wall against my back.
You better get a big hook on them, not dead yet, I'm ever seen your hand, your tight
jack level deck.
That's what I'm made from, you play a warhead, it's from a jet-white with no parachute.
Shop by fire, fire, squad of rake, fire, business, do it.
If we don't let my one leg live, I can still crawl and I'm not dead yet, not dead yet,
not dead yet, I'm a match, I'm got it with the wall against my back.
You better get a big hook on them, not dead yet.
You better get a big hook on them, not dead yet, I'm got it with the wall against my back.
You better get a big hook on them, not dead yet, I'm a match, I'm got it with the wall against my back.
You better get a big hook on them, not dead yet.
You better get a big hook on them, not dead yet, I'm got it with the wall against my back.
Nothing, yeah, I don't want my heart waitin' in the middle of the day
You better get up, make it go for nothing, yeah
Nothing, yeah, nothing, yeah
What's not, yeah, nothing, yeah nothing, yeah nothing
Nothing, yeah nothing, yeah nothing, yeah nothing, yeah nothing
That example, not dead yet
I'm not quite sure if that's pod save for none
It was a drop down the daily source code drop
What you can find in the show notes drop.io slash daily source code
Now I want to talk to you about something else that relates to that very, very cool
The billboard article finally came out
Let me just see if I can bring up a copy because I only have a PDF
I've also put this PDF into the drop by the way
At drop.io slash daily source code
This is the article that was written by Evie Nagy
I think it's Nagy, Nagy, Nagy and November alpha golf Yankee
It's a full page article, it's all about the pod save music revolution
Features quotes from myself
It's a monk, it really kicks off with monk's success story
It brings in mainstream, here, this is the, I love this
I really love this, check it out
We view it as an artist development tool
Jason Spiewock, president of rock ridge marketing
Which uses the pod save music network to promote tracks from acts
Including collective soul and buck cherry
Quote, it's directed file sharing, love that by the way
Directed file sharing, great, great concept
It's a calculated risk, research is proven
The giving away music doesn't not inhibit sales
If anything, it's the opposite
Wow
And you know, this is really, the title is kind of funny though
The title of the article, which of course I'm sure Evie didn't come up with
It's called potting along
Subtitle, podcast growth, creating viable marketing route for artists
Nah, that's cool
And of course, an incredibly glamor shot of myself inserted there
But what's important about this article
And again, you can look at the PDF
Drop.au slash daily source code, link in the show
No, it's a daily source code.com
What's great about it is this billboard is still an industry magazine
I've already received about 10 emails from people who haven't heard from
40 years
Including from the independent promotion business
From promotional departments and record companies
Just people saying, wow, you know, this is fantastic
It's finally happening in congratulations
And I'm like, yes, yes, yes, yes
I'm loving it
I think Evie did a really really good job
I tried to scammer into letting me see it before I went to print
Which he refused to do
And when she was actually pretty funny about it
She said, well, just like you wouldn't release revenue
And earnings numbers for at the time pod show
Now, mevia, which she also got right in the article
By the way, she said, we have a policy
I'm not showing it
Not showing the article before it's published
But factually, I think it's
I think even the numbers are seen very factually correct
So I'm just proud of this man, this is great
You know, you get to do a lot of interviews
And a lot of it is online these days, of course, websites, etc
But to have something show up in billboard magazine full page
I don't know if it's the left hand or the right hand page
But I'm sure it's going to wake some people up
And my feeling is that
My feeling is that it's going to lead to something
So I would say, watch this space
Particularly because there's a drunken Londoner walk
And throw it
Hello
Adam, hi, it's Charles John Londoner
It's London WMI, I'm in Warren Street
Basically, he's London Central London
So if it's program, what a great message that was
He had me in pictures
Oh, God, this money stuff, the Gordon Brown thing
Oh my God, it's not going to be so angry
It's making me so angry
I don't comment on it, I don't think about it
Because I feel so fucking powerless
But when it was the monetary scientist
Dude, phone deal was
I mean, at the billgate sounding guy
That whole section, just finished listening to it on the tube
Oh God, it just makes, I want a scream, I want a yell
What do we do? What do we do Adam?
Guide me, help me, what are we fucking do?
How can I change it?
How can I get the message to these guns?
So they can't just go stealing our fucking money
I'm getting, I've got a gun down man
I listen, uh, Charles about to check drunken
From now, Western way, W1
I'm 33, uh, I'm a folder, I'm a dyslexic
I'm sure you've got good head today
You're already won as far as I'm concerned
And I hope you continue to
Because I enjoy what you're doing
And, uh, please stop being up for us
Please don't get that man in, give me words
To be a lot worse
Uh, vote for Ken, if you have to
Go green, because uh, she's a hot man
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Clearly, uh, Charles, phone this in
Before the results of the London mayoral elections
Uh, which, of course, was W1, was W1 by uh
BJ, Boris Johnson
Sure, there's a joke in there somewhere
Yeah, so Charles getting pretty worked up about that
And, of course, he's referring to
Uh, the way the UK government is taking
Tax money and bailing out banks and
Proping up the global financial system
Uh, he's angry
And this is uh, fits right into this email
I got from John Christenbury, he says
Adam something I've noticed that I'm sure someone
As mentioned before is the absurdity
In the fact that when a sports team wins or loses
America, people storm the streets
Turn over cars, light shit on fire
They take to the streets
However, when petrol, gasoline
Is $4 a gallon
And the government is screwing us
Taking all our money, giving it away
We all sit back and watch
What the fuck is up with that?
Thank you
I'm very good going
What the fuck is up with that?
What does it take to get people to get
On to the streets?
Apparently, uh, a friendly sports match
By the way, I've also started to think a little bit about
This $4 a gallon gasoline
You know, in reality
Um, I think it could probably double
Double to about a seven or eight dollars
Before any actual protest will take place
And I based it on the fact that pretty much
Everywhere else in the world
Unless it's a place that really is producing a lot of oil
But certainly
Certainly here in Europe, continental Europe, Western Europe
You know, we're paying seven to eight bucks a gallon for gasoline
And it's expensive, but we're getting by
So, can America take a doubling?
Will it take that long before people get pissed off
And take to the streets or do we have to have your favorite team
Win or lose in the Super Bowl?
Maybe it's something we can do with the children
Hey Adam, Jason from San Diego
So I'm just going to throw in my two cents about this
People taking action or not taking action and things
Getting the government they deserve
I agree with you
I think it's a lot of apathy
But I also think that
Maybe United States is not breeding leaders
Like they used to
They're not influence and their children to be leaders
They're influence and them to be individuals
To be standalone and stand out
From the crowd
And the best person you can be
And you know, make it to the top alone
And you know, do what you can to survive
But it's not about, you know, greater good
You know, become a, you know, the mayor
Become a school board, become a president
Nobody's growing up anymore saying
I want to be the president
So that's what I think the problem is
Not breeding leaders breeding
Emphasitic, not empathetic
Appasitic, a little branch
Late
Hi, now some good points there
This is one of the reasons I enjoy this
So whole process of Holland's Got Talent
Which Patricia is a judge on, of course, the lady P
It's the Dutch version of
Britain's Got Talent or America's Got Talent
I love watching the kids that participate
And I like it for a number of reasons
One is, you know, it's like
And this is here's to be an incredible amount of people
Who still have past times such as
Baton twirling, acrobatics, magic, clowns
And, you know, although I'm not a big fan of all those genres
I really do like the fact that our kids are doing that
You know, they're not all just playing grand theft auto
Which by the way, I so have to get my hands on that
I got to get a, what is it on a playstation or whatever
I got to get a console, I have to play this
This looks really good
So that really makes me feel really happy on one hand
But on the other hand, you know, you can see that they're
Really competing because they want to be famous
And they want to have what they think is a fantastic career
And of course, if you were really to look at the amount of people
That are featured in celebrity ragmags
The numbers of those who are actually making lots of money
It's quite small, it's probably 1%
So that's a, it's a far so by itself
But, you know, that being aspirational is pretty sad
You're right, I mean, where are the kids?
If you have a kid at home
If you have a kid who is said, I want to grow up to be president
I want to talk to him or her
You know, in fact, that's another good question
If you have a daughter, she does she look up to Hillary Clinton
Like, wow, maybe one day I could be in the front runner for president
My daughter has not said one word about it
I don't think she cares
And we talk about this stuff all the time at home
But, man, it's hard to break through that wall of iPods and Facebook
And hangin' out and part of that is just being a teenager of course
But, where's the conversation they're having about the world?
I know they're conversing with the rest of the world
I know that she talks to people on the internet
Or converses with people on the internet all over the globe
But, where's the conversation about what's happening?
Where's the conversation that goes further than Bush's a dick
Or this guy's a crap when this guy's a Clinton, whatever
Does it really take place?
Is there a place I can find this on the internet
When teenagers are talking about this stuff
I know I certainly was thinking and talking that way
When I was her age
Let me see how we do it on time here today
What do we got?
Just about 40 minutes
Let me see
All right, two more questions I got
Let me do this promo first
Then two more phone calls and I'll play another song for you
Okay, hold on, don't go away
Holy cow, it's a promo
That'll be the next 30 seconds
Also, you watch this cover and all the new podcast
Roughly cripple your listening pleasure
The name of the mod
Sadler and all this investigation
What is this nonsense?
I'm random, British is touting
I so called human, you're down
Well good evening, cynical fans
Actually, it's a really look at the weeks events
It's the first sketches
Sounds awesome
Well, perhaps this montage of hilarious movies for the show
We'll persuade you
Oh, you realize you've already got it to 20 of your 30 seconds
What?
Ah, then the listeners will just understand
They don't work for it
The Sadler and all the investigations
Is downright here there
So just pretend you've had some rips floating clips
Whoa, that's right
And that was all gasmig
Where'd I get my hits?
Much better
Stop by Sadler and Thomas investigations
Stop wordpress.com
That's S-A-T-L-E-R
And T-H-O-M-A-S
Investigations of all one word
Flyby
Stop wordpress.com
Without flying in the middle
Or just search for a spy day
But Polkels that we all know
And tell all your friends about the Polkels
Because it lives a metric house
So it'll finally directly into your ears
Hello, my name is Darren
And I have a podcast on the
Partial systems
I've just got to help
If you have the big app system
Which you're all excited about
A one point and we are
I believe they had a couple of competitions
You were randomly put
Additional material into certain downloads
And I know that you're using this
What I think you're using this system
For putting the commercials
Onto the beginning and end of some podcasts
But just wonder whether
We like to see any of the patients
They're already stuck there
They're already using this system
All right, I hate when they're going on cellphones
Yeah, that's a good point
We haven't used that
I mean, we are indeed using it
You're referring to the golden tickets
Which we did a couple of years ago
And I think it's a great idea
I'd like to read and state that
Give me a week or two to set it up
The idea is or the execution of the idea
Because it does work
Is I can predetermine
Any number of shows that are downloaded
So for instance, this is number 754
I could say I want 10
10 of these downloads to include an extra piece of audio
Which would indeed be what we call a golden ticket
Which would make you a winner
We used it very successfully
I think we gave way in iPod
Did a couple other
I think there were some other shows
That used it
The problem is it's all still manual configuration
And it really needs to have some kind of interface
The most beautiful thing would be
If we could actually set it up
So that you could
Insert a golden ticket yourself
Determine how many etc
There's some scaling issues there
That we would have to look at first
But even people who tried to gain the system
We're unable to
It's a good call man
I'll look into that
See if we can do some fun with golden tickets again
Hey Adam
It's Tim from Boucher
Tim Able from Boucher
Just listening to your latest shows
And you mentioned that you think you're having your perfect site
And you go really fast download
And then it drops right off
Now I've noticed
At the heavier that I think
You can blame the browser for
If you start
If you click on a download link
For a big file
And then you spend a while passing around
Just finding way to save it
And that kind of thing
When it finally pops up
The downloading dialogue
I think it calculates the speed wrong
I think it
Those the data that it sounds like fall
When it's already started downloading the background
But the time from when you finished passing around
So you get this ridiculously false download speed
And then it means closer to the real download speed
Yeah, okay, good point
But that's actually I was looking at my traffic
Within with a packet monitor
So I'm not looking at the
You can't trust that little meter on your browser
Now I'll give you all kinds of wacky results
No, I actually see the throughput
Through the internet
Through the the Nick card
As I know the network interface card
And I can see it happening
I particularly in the condo
Where I'm on
Comcast
You'll see stuff come in
Like 10 megabits per second
And then all sort of
Oh, it slows down to like
You know one or whatever
And uploads the same thing
You know I can see it do a
Megabit per second up
And then all of a sudden it starts slow down
It hangs around
4 to 500
Kill a bit upload
And I'm not quite sure
I don't know if that's the way
That's the behavior of
Interface cards
Or it just feels to me like something is being shaped
I'd love to have us of on checking on that
Let me know what the score is
Des Bartlett said to Adam
I heard what your shows you said you wanted to hear some protest on
Well, I found one from the pod save music network
He says it's called snapback to reality
Done by the undercover hippie perfect
For this source code
7-5-4
Don't know what it's coming to
But I see the world through different
I just lit it
So he's like we're coming through
So many of us who are visual
It's going crazy
People amazed me
Act so hasty
Rest a minute
Then they call you lazy
Whilst the game
We've gone insane
We're chasing money
Till it brings us pain
And it's so plain to see
That we need to
Snap back to reality
On it's so plain to see
That we need to
Snap back, snap back
To reality
Snap back in my living room
Looking at the TV
Telling me I want to wear around
Dreaming up another day
When I get away from the walls
That keep me there
Why do I care about
So wonder where I'm
The reasons that I sit and stare
To the scene that I'm just green
I long to live inside the TV
Dreaming
It's so plain to see
That we need to
Snap back to reality
On it's so plain to see
That we need to
Snap back, snap back
To reality
Don't see who represents me
Not the TV, not my MP
Not the MC, not the MTV
Talk to me, not the MC
Well it's talkin' about cash
Ego plenty
Ego's in trick and then Ego's in trick
Make me feel sick but come for them
From my dancing mind
Dreaming up another day
When I get away from the walls
That keep me there
Leave it to reality
Don't leave it to not free
Don't be the coach
Nobody got a cold
Wake it up
Just keep on planting my seed
Positive and see
Because I believe that
I'm taking it free and I'm taking it my mind
Making it see and I'm taking it this world
Making us feel as if the reality back till is real
I'm taking it my life
Making it free and I'm taking it my mind
Making it see and I'm taking it this world
Making us feel as if the reality back till is real
Back till is real, back till is real
The superficiality back till is real
Don't know what's coming to
But I think I might know what was coming from
You'll know what we're gonna do
And I think I might know what we're gonna go
And around crafting
You'll know what is coming to
But I think I might know where was coming from
Don't know what we're gonna do
But I think I might know where we're going around
for the podcast music network probably featured in the Billboard magazine as
the way to get your music out to the masses check it out on new stands everywhere
at the undercover hippie snap back to reality that wraps up daily source code episode
number seven hundred fifty four check out the show notes at daily source code.com
of course you can also find that curry dot com where I gladly cross post
and uh... for uh... email
it's adam and me vio dot com mike echo victor india osker and uh... if you just want
to drop some shit off hit my drop drop dot a.o slash slash daily source code
so with the date i'd like today i can only say i'm gonna live with a lot of passion
i'm gonna soak up some of those raise i hope you're in a position to do that as well
and please enjoy your freedom another find vio presentation stick it in your
year