Delta Sheriff Charley, 7-81
What's 6-year-living dollars worth of airborne, flies throbting my ass.
the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I just did this very early.
The fight and sick girl, the status quo.
The real eyes we must make it go.
I have come here to tell you.
It's time to stand up and watch the corporate's fall.
At one time they're converting us.
Now they're converting us.
I'm thinking everything I'm gonna take.
Now it's time for us to break away today.
Don't ever let them take you away.
The same I never did today.
The cast held the truth cause it's classified.
The TV set keeps us classified.
So now we're trapped in the lion's den.
Will it travel us over and over again?
Don't ever let them take you away.
The same I never did today.
You're only going to give up yourself.
Don't ever let them take you away.
The same I never did today.
Hey, whoa, don't ever ever give a shot, you're only going to be so...
Oh yeah, you like it heavy huh?
It's the free fall of fact right here on the Dating Source Code episode number 781 Chuck Hitz,
how you doing the Source Code is on.
Coming to you as always from the affluent suburb of Serino as Gilford.
We're here in the manner on the outskirts there of G-Town,
and boy it's good to talk to you guys.
I'm back once again.
It's good everything all squared away here.
It's so weird when you go away for a week and you take half the studio with you
and then you have to kind of rebuild and away that if I turn this down.
There you go.
That's better.
I thought I heard it.
Yeah, that's exactly what I heard.
Some feedback.
I've got to rebuild everything.
It seems like it's more or less together now.
So it is Tuesday today is the 19th of August 2008.
Time really moving on.
We've got just horrible weather here for the past.
What is it?
Well, even since I got back, it's just been nasty weather.
In fact, it's been that way for a couple weeks, not just here, but globally weather is a little bit screwed up.
Call a global warming climate change if you will.
I think they just turned on the harp system up there in Alaska.
Let's see, we've got natural dam walls breaking in Colorado, the Grand Canyon.
We've got just unbelievably horrible weather high winds, thunderstorms, rain, vertical rain almost in parts of Europe.
And the Antarctic penguins are actually freezing to death from cold Arctic rain.
I mean, come on.
What's happening?
Do you want to know what that reference was to harp?
Just look up, H-A-A-R-P, Hotel Alpha, Alpha Romeo, Papa.
The CT's out there.
That'll send you down a rabbit hole.
A lot of stuff to go through with you today, because obviously I haven't done well.
I did a no agenda over the weekend with John, but that doesn't take much preparation as much as you know.
Just looking at the drop drop.io slash daily source code.
Thank you very much.
You put together a great show for me.
Top of the news without a doubt is of course still the conflict in Georgia.
And it's been interesting to, you know, and this is really what I love so much about where we're at with mainstream news and with the internet basically.
And I think I've tried, I finally figured out, we actually do need to work together.
But we don't have to do anything together because it's already happening automatically just organically almost.
Because the real information, the true news that is going on out there in the world is actually being reported.
There are really good journalists in all walks of life, all types of publications.
The truth doesn't get through as an example.
And this is the thing that has just been fantastic to watch unfold before our very eyes.
You know, with the knowledge which has been widely reported, but it's not the headline.
It's not the top of the news.
What the agenda, it's not the talking point, is that Georgia attacked the peacekeeping troops and the civilians of South of Syria.
This is an unknown fact.
No one's disputing it.
But of course, the whole headline and what the news is about is, oh, Russian bad USA good.
Well, kick their ass, put missiles in Poland, put missiles in Cuba.
You know, it's like, you can call it Saber Radling, you can call it just thugs, bumping chests, essentially.
And it's not like we matter, no one gives a shit about us or the civilians, thousands of civilians that were killed during this recent conflict.
But the news is actually being reported.
And I think what is what we're seeing happen now is that you have aggregation sites.
And of course, these are, you know, people who want to prove a point or have an agenda, which is fine.
And you can now collect mainstream articles, which by definition, the reports, many of them do have credibility, many of these reporters are credible.
But it's really the editors and the DNA of these companies who decide what is going to be the topic of the day.
And that is just done through simple mind control we call media and advertising.
I mean, it's nothing new there.
You know, it's easy to make a, a number one hit record just give me enough budget.
You know, and give me access.
Let me pay off the radio stations.
It still happens to this very day limit anything else and get through the, that can get through the funnel.
That's how hit records are made.
You know, it's not like there aren't any other good records out there, good music being made that couldn't be as popular as anything else.
It's number one.
Now it's just the way it's the way this system works.
It's restrictive.
It's not inclusive of everybody.
So that's why the agenda, the real top of the news, you know, like important stuff in the world, like the Olympics.
That's going to get front page coverage.
You know, we've got a guy who's got eight gold medals.
That's front page coverage.
Not about the true agenda of the world's elite or as I call them the energy elite.
So when you think about the new world order.
And you know, I know a lot of people are going to ask you had a new world order.
Here we go again.
It's kind of interesting when you get to aggregate all this fantastic news.
And it's not just reporting.
It's also interviews.
And this, and of course, my aggregation site is created by the chuckleheads.
Listen to the daily source code.
It's drop.io slash daily source code.
And of course, they also pop stuff over to curry.com.
You're really helping understand what this means.
And listen to Georgian president, Mikhail Sakashvili.
And this is on the Glenn Beck show.
So check this out for a second.
And you'll hear him say new world order.
He's calling for it.
Okay, so hold on.
I'm playing this directly from YouTube of hijacked the audio from the browser.
And of Georgia Mikhail Sakashvili.
Mr. President, quickly if we can, you speak very frankly.
And say things, I was listening to you last few minutes.
You don't hear a politician speak the way you do in America.
That's funny, by the way.
Glenn Beck, know you don't hear him talk like politicians in America.
It's just a different accent.
The bullshit is still the same.
You just lay all your cards down on the table.
This is you a couple of days ago under flat jackets.
You're being targeted.
Now you're standing on an open roof.
You know, if you haven't seen that, look that up on YouTube.
Look up Sakashvili, look at him eating his tie.
There's a BBC documentary or documentary of peace and newspiece.
You see, he's so nervous this guy.
So wound up, he's sitting there while cameras are watching him.
He's eating his tie, which is just weird.
And then, like, he's outside and a plane flies over.
And he starts running, like, you know, just hysterically frightened.
So, you know, Glenn Beck is, you know, making a sound like a hero.
But if you look at the video, he's like, you know, pretty wussy.
I mean, I'm not saying that I would be any different in that situation.
But Glenn Beck made him sound a little bit too more, too heroish there.
Anyway, so listen to what this guy is all about.
Do you believe that, um, do you believe that this will, and Russia will end if you are dead?
Nice posture, Glenn.
Well, you know, it's not the fact that I was targeted.
My people has been targeted.
I couldn't care less whether I was targeted.
The worst thing was that I was standing there with my people.
They were bombed.
And I was just targeted like them.
And they selected president, official and charge of their protection.
I couldn't do anything about it.
But the one here is, it's not about me.
It's about the idea of freedom.
Freedom.
It's about the future of the whole region.
It's about the future of Europe and a new world order.
There you go.
It's about freedom, the future of Europe and a new world order.
I don't know.
I don't like that idea of a new world order.
This was a George H. Bush's idea.
He said it first, the first time in American president, as far as I can recall,
said it really publicly that way.
Like, it's a big idea.
It's the new world order.
And here he is.
Here's your guy.
Here's a George Jr. Bush's guy.
And Cheney's guy.
Talk about the new world order.
I don't want to have one set of rules and one government governing everything we do.
I don't want that.
I'd like the idea that countries are different.
It's kind of cool, you know.
It really is.
So another great thing about the medium that we have to work with,
my friends, is that we actually talked to people
in Georgia and in Russia, and they talk back.
Hello, Adam.
This is Dennis.
No, as Radio Greench.
By the way, you know, this is not about the people of any of these countries.
There's no way I hate an Iraqi or an Afghani, an Afghan.
That sounds like a dog.
Someone from Afghanistan.
I don't hate them.
I don't hate people from Iran.
It's beautiful.
People from Russia don't look as cute as the ones in Iran,
but they're just people.
It's these are thugs.
All of them.
All of the elite and their little puppet thugs who are the gangs.
And there's gangs everywhere in China in Russia.
In the United States in Europe.
There's lots of gangs in Europe.
And they're all muslim for power.
And, you know, we're just finally waking up to it.
We're seeing it.
The veil has been lifted.
And a lot of it is thanks to the Internet, which, of course, is next.
You know, that's what they're going to come after.
They've been trying for a while.
They're really going to go for it.
All right.
So our buddy from Russia here, the radio grid.
In Russian podcasting.
You're colleague, by the way.
Yes.
Anyway, I'm listening to your show.
I'm a little concerned for you because sometimes I know that people
want to grow old, they get into old.
Hey, hey, who are you calling old men?
Kind of conspiracy theories.
Oh, that's bullshit.
There's even that.
There's no proof of that.
That's just me.
I think you're still healthy.
I'm not a doctor, but anyway,
you're right.
And I would like to thank you for speaking on behalf of Russia in the
situation related to Georgia situation.
Let's start it on the first day of Olympics.
Western media sucks as bad as Russian media.
Exactly.
Oh, yeah.
In fact, media everywhere sucks because they're all in
Kahuts.
But, you know, a lot of the people, you know, like you and I,
are also reporters and they're making reports and they're trying to get
the word out and they get a page five below the fold, you know.
And it's still the truth.
And it's still getting out there.
It's just not.
It's not where we're so mind-controlled.
I remember when my parents used to say, don't watch television all day
long.
It'll write your brain.
And it has.
It's rotted our brains.
So yeah, Western media, Eastern media sucks equal.
I agree.
So you can't really trust them.
But anyway, thanks for speaking on behalf of Russians.
I'm not saying again that we are good in this situation.
But we're not definitely as we're portrayed in the Western media.
You're no worse than we are.
Or the way what our government has done, you know, Iraq, Afghanistan.
All kinds of nastiness.
Now, you know, I wonder what we're going to do next in Pakistan.
Now that Basharraf is a man, we're kind of dealing with he get, huh?
He, he, I think he really, this guy's going to wind up dead if they don't
get him to the states if they don't take care of their boys.
Because that's exactly, you know, Basharraf is total, total operative.
And he just didn't do a good job.
So I wonder if he, I wonder if he did this in in collaboration.
If he said, look, I got to get out of the situation.
Or if he was told to leave or it'll be interesting.
Let's see who jumps in that slot next.
That'll tell us a lot about the plans for Pakistan.
Okay. And you know that.
And you're right about that.
This whole thing is all about the oil.
You're right about that.
Yeah, and the pipeline, the gas.
Obviously Europe, you know, and Europe is in the hardest position right now.
Because they want and they need Russian gas.
And the US is poking them with a stick.
That's what's going on.
Oil and gas.
There's no doubt about it.
So anyway, Adam, I just wanted to thank you for your show.
And I would like to tell you, like, there's a situation that needs clarification from maybe someone from inside of Russia.
Don't hesitate to email me and ask your questions.
And if I have answers for those, I'll give you those.
If I don't, I'll find people who might have those.
All right, man, I appreciate it.
And of course, if you're in Georgia, I'm not familiar with any Georgian podcast,
but it's such a western, westernized country.
I would presume that you can give us some details on what's going on from your end.
I'd love to hear about it.
Email, voicemail.
And by the way, I'm going to start phasing out the regular voicemail phone lines.
And just trying to keep it all on the on the drop because it's just so much more convenient.
And a lot of people are starting to use it now.
It's a kind of a downer because you got to use a pain code once you call in.
And that if anything, I'd love to have the folks over drop.au,
make that a direct phone line.
I mean, I'm paying for it with J2.
Yeah, J2 facts or whatever.
I'd be happy to pay for it.
Just to have a direct line straight in.
Because you can kind of mean to what a great system that is.
You can categorize everything by media type or by a blog view.
I love it.
It's very, very cool.
Although I've been having some problem with the pictures.
Pictures that are uploaded.
If you click them, then you don't get the pop up screen.
Something's going on.
Now those, you know, they're in data, whatever.
So they're working on it.
And here's nobody who stopped by the drop and left this message.
Adam, what's up?
It's Kevin Reeves going in.
Kevin Reeves?
One time to talk, buddy.
Yeah, man.
First of all, let me just say congratulations on this great awakening.
The show has gone in a great direction.
I too have been on a interesting journey in the past four years as far as
way to do these kind of things.
With the help of my friend and colleague, Ian Beard, who is just provided me with a wealth of information,
which completely lines up and corroborates with what you say and with Alex Jones.
And it's just unbelievable how all the pieces just fit in the place.
You know, and this is funny because this is what I'm witnessing as well.
All the things, all the people that, you know, I was kind of taught and brought up to think,
you know, they're weird.
You know, not like hippy, weird, but just, you know, on the fringe off the edge.
You know, there's lots of troubled people in the world and that's one of them.
You know, so now obviously I recognize that I've turned into one of them.
But it's really because those people were awake and there've been people have been awake for a long, long time,
and have really seen what's, you know, you know, you know, like you've always got that grumpy uncle,
who's always sitting around reading the paper and going like,
God, damn these bastards, you know, how can they be, it's like kind of like the kid from Brooklyn,
right?
Who see through it, who can see with such clarity and see what's going on.
I've had many people in my life throughout the years, even in recent years,
who have been like this.
And you know, and I remember Ben Cohen, one of my, one of my big influences in life.
I remember when George Bush senior became president and then I can remember sitting in this living
going, hey, he seems like a pretty cool guy.
He'll be a big good dude for the American for the state and for the world.
And he looked at me and said, are you kidding me?
That guy is the biggest crook there is.
And I remember sitting there going, huh?
No, we're talking about man.
This guy's good.
Listen to him.
He means that he wants to hook up, hook us up with China and make good.
And I think a lot of this, of course, is once they cast George W. Bush and put him in the,
acting role of president.
You know, that was, I mean, they really chose the wrong actor at that point.
That was that guy's just he's the wrong guy.
And that's when the crack started to show.
And of course, you know, they couldn't do much, but leave him for all eight years.
Because it's all, it's all bought and paid for.
It's all set up.
It's all, it's all one big show.
It's a big show.
As I've always said, politics is show business for ugly people.
And we're, no offense.
But we're, we're, we're realizing that.
And now that that veil was starting to lift off, things just like a puzzle start to click into place.
So good on your body for this.
This is great.
The show is so much now more so than it ever was before about community.
And communicating something and trying to dialogue and open up a conversation.
So this is an awesome incredible.
About girls I have.
Now he launches in this whole long thing, which I'm not going to play for.
That was, we were talking about about women and how they have such a horrible self image of themselves.
Also thanks to the media, by the way.
That's, you know, that also is a form of mind control.
Whereas, you know, first of all, we're happy we get anything.
If we get attention, not even talking sex, just attention.
We love that.
And you know the game.
But anyways, Kevin launched into like a full another minute of that.
And I got so much I got to move on today.
Because this is, it's, I've really, I got to tell you, I'm feeling so incredibly positive about all of this new information,
opening up, all of us starting to, to see things, to start to put things into perspective.
And that's really, that's the most important part is just that we're realizing what's going on.
And talking about it because that does make change.
Look at the FBI.
They now have to come, you know, there's been so much questioning about this Bruce Ivan's,
so-called suicide of the anthrax terrorist that they now have to show their, you know, their full evidence.
And oh, gee, isn't that a shame.
They actually destroyed some of the evidence.
Yeah, well, we thought it wouldn't stand up in court anyway.
So we decided to destroy the evidence.
Oh, come on.
So, you know, when this gets talked about a certain point, so many people are talking about it,
then it becomes a slug on the news.
And then it becomes a little joke there.
And another little chunk, chunk in the arm, a little bit of piece to the arsenal of,
of the bullshit that we're being fed day in, day out.
Now, you have, of course, we didn't do a footballer Friday.
And I apologize to many of you.
Some of you called in and said, hey, man, I had an 11 hour trip back to school.
And I was really jones and for a footballer Friday and the no agenda.
Well, I got you halfway there.
And I've got part of the footballer Friday for you right now.
I'm proud of you casting with Adam Curry.
This is the head of the test.
Get it, test.
Don't pull that.
Hey, Adam.
He's got this number 134.
I'm going to start right away with intro number one.
Okay.
I don't know.
This is like, and I wanted those 90s hit tests, right?
No, absolutely nothing.
Okay.
I don't know this one.
That's for sure.
Number two.
That's, um, that is Jocelyn Brown.
Oh, it's like always, always be there.
Something Jocelyn Brown.
I'm pretty sure of that.
And this is number three.
Stereo MCs.
I don't know the title.
But I recognize this sound.
This is like 92 or something like that.
This is not my strongest years.
I was way too consumed with myself.
It's time for the answers.
And this week they're all from...
I didn't even know what.
That was a good hit test.
Hey!
And this is answer number one.
This is Johnny Gordon.
We know I'll be there this time.
I would not have known that.
I know I can't just be there.
We'll be there this time.
I'm going to get you baby.
Baby.
Great.
I'm just going to number one.
Lonnie Gordon and gonna get you.
And this is answer number two.
Incagnito featuring Jocelyn Brown.
Yo, this is always there.
There you go.
I'm just feeling...
I remember this from Ray Brady.
Yo, I want to be...
Yeah.
Always there.
To raise you all again.
With not me.
Always there.
So not you.
To keep all.
Always there.
Yeah.
Incagnito was answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
The lost in music.
Lost in music.
The stereo MCs.
You see.
Yeah.
This is lost in music.
There you go.
I got that one.
There's wrong one.
I got the new one.
My name goes wrong.
Yeah.
The blue box.
They look like ground.
You're lost in music.
Never too.
But.
Oh, those guys still.
I got it.
I lost in music.
This is a compression on that.
The stereo MCs and lost in music is answer number three.
And that's it.
That's it for hit test number 134.
So Adam, how did you do this week?
I did four stars out of possible six.
You're on XM surprise.
We're being a 90's hit test.
Thank you for the challenge.
I would say.
The usual place to find the answers to the hit test.
And also the links to iTunes.
You can buy this right.
Featured on the hit test.
Online is hit test of mepeo.com.
Thank you for playing.
Adam.
Thank you for listening.
Next week.
I'll be back for another hit test.
So until then.
Take care.
Have fun.
No prize or you remember,
think with your hearts.
Bye, bye.
Amen.
Challenging the brain.
It's hard, man.
Because I was doing I was not into the.
Brilliant to the music scene.
It was...
It was.
It's the American music scene in 91.
And I was at the time for very different from these songs.
I did do a show called Ray radio, a radio show.
And Ronald Molondike would always send me these mixes.
This is when I was beta testing pro tools at the time.
I was like one of the first radio uses of pro tools,
which is really intended for studio work.
And we're doing that with that tapes,
and oh man, remember those kids, that tapes?
So part of this whole media controlled mainstream media,
as of course, meant to dumb us down to narrow our focus, narrow our vision.
And the Americans, of course, are the best example.
And you see the test on all the time, go ask any average American.
So I'm seemingly very simple worldview question,
and they usually fail.
So at least it's fun to edit the failing ones into the piece.
And this showed up on the drop.
Drop.io slash daily source code.
Man, that's something wrong with the bandwidth here,
at the manner for some reason.
Something's really slowing things down.
Hold on, let me just see.
What's going on?
Let me just check.
Maybe if I just reload the page.
This is harsh in my mellow.
Okay, come on.
Here we go.
This is from the telegraph.
British anti-Americanism based on misconceptions.
Now, first of all, I live over here,
and I don't feel any anti-Americanism.
Maybe people who don't want to do business with us
or just don't order anything.
Maybe that's anti-Americanism, but I don't feel it.
In fact, as I say, we all, the people of the world
get along just fine.
However, British attitudes says this article towards the United States
are governed by ignorance of the facts on key issues such as crime,
healthcare, and foreign policy, according to a new survey.
So I thought it'd be kind of fun to read down some of the results
of this survey, a poll commissioned by America in the world
and independent pressure group that launches that, I guess,
launched on Monday, aims to improve understanding
and appreciation of the US and Britain and around the world.
We wanted to find out how British people understood
American found that there was an unbalanced view.
So you brits pay attention.
This'll be fun.
The survey showed a majority agreed with the false statement
that since the Second World War, the US has had more often
cited with non-Muslims when they had conflict with Muslims.
Wrong.
In fact, the 11 out of 12 major conflicts between Muslims
and non-Muslims and Muslims and secular forces
or Arabs and non-Arabes, the US has cited with the former group.
Is conflicts included Turkey, Greece, Bosnia, and Yugoslavia
and Kosovo and Yugoslavia.
As to if it was true that from 1973 to 1990,
the United States sold Saddam Hussein more than a quarter
of his weapons, 80% of British responded said,
yes, however, survey shows the US sold just 0.46%
of Saddam's arsenal to him compared to Russia's 57%.
Francis 13% and China's 12%.
That'll teach you.
I didn't know that.
I would have gotten that one wrong.
Uh, let's see.
Almost a third of Britain's believe that Americans who have not paid
their hospital fees or insurance premiums
are not entitled to emergency medical care
by loss, such treatment must be provided.
And more than half the respondents believe
that polygamy is legal in some US states,
while it is illegal in all US states.
And most Britons were unaware of positive aspects
of the US such as the robust environmental movement.
Huh?
Or the social justice work of evangelical churches.
Interesting.
Now, of course, Americans can't find Britain on the map.
And also, the reason why the Brits can actually
find the US on the map is because it's so damn big.
But we're kept dumb.
That's what it is.
I can see it.
I can see what these kids are being taught in school.
I can see with my own daughter.
And she hears stuff.
She hears Patricia and I talk about stuff.
She's always interested.
Like, wow, it's amazing.
I never heard about that.
I didn't know that.
And more increasingly, I might say,
I'm quite happy to report that often she says,
yeah, I read about that on the internet.
Thank you.
There you go.
Something for the Brits as well in about a week's time
we're kicking off a real special GoDaddy campaign.
We're going to have the best deal anywhere in the UK on dot code
that UK domain names.
And I'm very excited about it.
We're going to have a lot of shows working really hard
to bring this offer to you.
And we've worked with GoDaddy.
They have their own dedicated site.
It's all going to be in pounds.
And you'll see it's, of course, the major discounts
for dot com and dot net addresses as well.
It's at trend dot EU or dot TV or whatever we got.
But specifically dot code, I UK.
And you will not be able to be this price.
That's coming in about a week from now.
Let's see the BBC reports.
A US bank is bound to fail within months.
Yeah, I'd say so.
I'd probably say that would be Fannie Mae or Freddie Mac.
But it could even be one of the non-tax payer back banks.
I mean, it's just really hitting the fan.
It's almost like we're being distracted to go look at what's
happening in Russia and make sure that we pay attention
to the Olympics.
And anything, please don't look at what actually
is happening.
And as Lindsey Williams predicted, oil looks like it's
going to go down to $50 right now today.
It's at 1111.
So how does that happen?
And by the way, no one's talking about speculators now.
Are they?
Well, it can only be that this was either speculation
or pure manipulation of the price at the source,
which is what Lindsey Williams has always proclaimed.
So any else as a gold will be down.
Gold is now what, under $800.
And the intent is to bankrupt Saudi Arabia.
Well, that's going to work.
And of course, the dollar's going up a little bit,
but you may not have noticed that in all this confusion
and a lot's been going on since the seventh of August
and the invasion in Georgia, that an extra $50 billion
of currency was bought up by foreign investors,
foreign banks, you can just say it's the foreign central banks
and bought more US debt.
So there's a lot of stuff going on behind the scenes
that's propping up the dollar.
And whenever you hear financial programs,
like I love listening to the CNN like hourly update,
there's a podcast version of it.
You can find it on my channel'satom.mevio.com
on my on the go channel.
I forget which you can subscribe to by the way
with any way you want with an RSS feed or whatever.
Just go with the name of the CNN show.
It's like market headlines or something.
And whenever you hear a financial guy,
like clearly a guy from the pit or some trader,
and he said, well, yeah, this is the bottom.
This is totally the bottom.
This thing is going up from here.
The dollar is on, it's on the rise again.
You've got to go get yourself some dollars.
Whenever someone's saying that you know
that you've got to go the opposite direction,
you know that's a sales pitch.
So they're not stupid.
They know it's all about to come crumbling down.
There was another.
Where is that?
Well, Dr. Doom, I'll get to him later.
I just want to stay with Britain for a second.
This was great.
This is from the telegraph.
How big brother watches your every move?
You know, ever growing surveillance society,
the average Britain is being recorded 3,000 times a week.
3,000 times a week.
And that's telephone, emails, web surfing,
swiping of a card, click of a mouse, cameras everywhere.
And no one's up in arms about it.
Either they're putting something in the water here,
or you know, everyone's just hammered all day well.
I guess that's true.
People are pretty much hammered all day long.
Maybe, you know, maybe it's the, it's the chem trails.
I don't know what it is.
Maybe it's harpsing an ultra low frequencies.
But man, we aren't brain dead over here.
I can feel it too.
I can absolutely feel the low energy, low vibrations.
And I had been away for a while
and it was very different in San Francisco.
It really was.
It wasn't, it was a higher frequency level.
There was just more positivity,
something in the air.
And there's something, it, it almost feels like this,
you know, like someone switched on a transmitter almost.
And it's just bringing you down,
which is why I talk about harp.
Yeah, another one from over here.
This is from the business times.
Yeah, this is a part of the terror act,
which is, but now being used.
So you, and now constables or cops on the streets,
excuse me, I just need a sip of tea there.
Cops on the street.
They can invoke, what does it, like rural,
a section 44, I think it is of the, of the counterterrorism bill.
And they can actually prohibit you from filming anything
on the street at their discretion.
So there's an uproar, as this article says,
to plan to hold inquests in secret now,
and I'm not quite sure the procedure of an inquest,
but I think it's obviously questioning
and researching to someone who's suspected of crime.
And so here's the story in quest
that are deemed a risk, too,
of course, national security by the government
would be held in secret in future under proposed powers
to come before the House of Lords this autumn.
The provisions under a clause in the counterterrorism bill,
that's kind of our Patriot Act over here in the UK,
allow the home secretary to stop a jury being summoned,
replace a corner with a government appointee
and bar the public from inquest if it is deemed to be
in the public interest, which means, you know,
basically just as serving behind closed doors
and, you know, no checks and balances on it.
Whew, we're just brain dead.
We're just slowly ebbin away,
paying lots of attention to David Beckham.
That's what we're doing.
House Beckham doing over there in LA galaxy.
Watching the Olympics.
Nothing to see here.
Move right along, please.
Here's bad news.
If that wasn't bad, this is really bad news.
Um, this is from the inquire.
Now, looks certain that the RIA and its tame political puppets
will kill off web radio.
This comes through Pandora who under the new payment scheme,
which I believe is retroactive,
will have to pay 70% of his projected revenue of $25 million
to keep the RIA or in this case,
its government appointed monopoly in forces,
sound exchange, off its back.
Small webcasters claim that demand,
the demanded dosh, that's Britspeak from money,
would be 100 to 300% of annual revenue,
which sound exchange, of course, believes is fair.
So there you go, that's pretty much over.
And what's so nuts about it is so why you've got,
you know, and of course they're playing licensed music,
which is the whole problem.
And so, well, and, you know,
and they're just trying to put together cool playlists,
and they're, you know, and put rich full 24, 7 radio stations
on the air, which I think, you know,
it could be good, and no one's willing not to pay,
you know, it's like, you know,
the web radio streaming guys want to pay,
they just want to pay a fair amount,
because it's just what the business, you know,
the business just isn't delivering on the cash.
Which, of course, you know, the whole fact that the RIAs
doing this means that they've really researched it,
and they know that this business model
will not work anyways, not going to mean a lot of money.
Therefore, that they might as well kill it,
because they don't want their shit floating out there.
And, you know, if they, if they knew if it worked,
they'd already be doing it.
But what's crazy about it is if you got the Podsate Music Revolution,
and now we've got guys like George Clinton,
you, as surely you've heard of him,
who, you know, is totally gets it,
which is like, all right, you know,
I'm going to sign this license,
which I have the right to, because I owe my shit,
and I'm going to let anyone who wants to put this in their show,
and their podcast, no matter how it's distributed,
I'm going to let them use it,
just tell me that you played it,
and I'll figure out how to make some money from it,
and I'm good enough.
So, let's listen to that then.
The alternative way of doing it.
George Clinton ain't that particular.
I'm a killer, I mean of course.
I'm a killer, I need to do it.
I need to do it.
You do, you do, you do, too.
You do me raw, but I'm still crazy about ya.
Then wait too long and I can't do without ya.
Have no choke, you know.
He's hurt, makes my love stronger than any more
I know from the way, but how can love
No pain, pain, no pain
No pain, no joy
Can be, can be, can be
Can be, can be
But not so much to know, it's a baby that I know
The baby won't say, the baby won't do it right
But it's not a big lie
And the little boat came along me
Make all your recipe, true
To make love better, no
I do love, make love stronger than any more
I know, from the way, can be
Can be, can be, can be
Can be, can be
Can be, can be,
Can be, can be, can be
Can, can be, can be
Can be, can be
Can be, can be, can be
I know there's all the less to each
You know, it's because I didn't take my walk yet, that's why.
Yeah, you normally take that walk around the block and then, hey, just do some more there, will ya?
Excellent.
I'm going to take one right up for the show.
George Clinton named that peculiar featuring Sly Stone and Elba Orange.
Always one of those guys we're doing.
Here's your answer.
Nice.
Lay back and mellow.
I think I've mentioned this next story.
I just want to make sure it stays out there and I'm going to put a link.
In fact, I've been pretty good with a new production system because Drop.au makes it really simple for me for a number of reasons.
I've been pretty good with the links and the show notes.
I just want to make sure that I keep this book the way of the world in focus.
The book written by four of that Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist.
Ron Susskind.
I think it's Susskind.
And, you know, this basically is the proof that would allow the impeachment of a large, well, George Bush and Dick Cheney for sure.
But could put a lot of people in jail including those guys.
And it needs to stay out there and you've got to read this book and you've got to hear his interview.
There's an interview with him on Democracy Now.
If you don't know what I'm talking about, I'll just read the blurb here.
The way of the world, Ron Susskind, on how the Bush administration deliberately faked an Iraq al-Qaeda connection
and undermined diplomacy, democracy in Pakistan and Iran.
Does that say enough for you?
Do you think it's worth checking out?
I think so.
See, I was going to, I'll put this link in the show notes about Dr. Doom.
Even though I won't go into a two-death, but this is, if you want some really good analysis about what's happening with the monetary meltdown that we're witnessing before our very eyes.
Good piece in the New York Times about the Sky Nuryo Rubini and a economics professor at New York University.
And in 2006, he was predicting exactly what started to take place about a year ago and he's got plenty more predictions.
Now this guy is, you know, is speaking circuit. He's everywhere. He's the new Messiah.
And it's not that hard to see, you know, in the next, you wait, you'll start hearing about derivatives.
Okay.
I know a lot about derivatives. I help build a, actually, our think-new ideas.
Our company built a Java based back in the day when it was Java.
I was, I think it was Java on the client.
I don't remember any more, but it was a derivatives trading desk, which was web based and we built that for bankers trust, which was bought and doesn't exist anymore.
And those guys that had a huge problems with derivatives, huge exposure.
And I think that the global derivatives deals that are out there of which only 2% or some ridiculously low number is actually covered with any real asset.
And that's why it's called a derivative because it's a little piece of a chunk of it's, you know, all these deals are,
tidying a cash flows and once that starts to slow down a mess up the system, but the total value, I believe is around 400,000 billion.
All right. So a billion is a thousand million and that 400,000 times.
And when that shit comes unglued, then it's, you know, everyone head for the hills.
Don't head for the coastal waters. I heard John C. to War Act talking about this on tech five of all places about the so called dead zones. You've got to read this article.
Dead zones and coastal waters are regions of ocean floors so deprived of oxygen.
The most marine life cannot survive and they're spreading worldwide and the alarming pace scientists say.
Diving the trend or nitrogen and phosphorus and phosphorus from chemical agricultural fertilizers that reach coastal waters after flowing off of farm fields and into rivers and streams.
So this is these dead zones where it's just water, right, but it's just wet it's there's nothing growing nothing feeding nothing nothing nothing swimming except us idiots, of course.
A couple of these dead zones, biggest one measures about 30,000 square miles that's 80,000 square kilometers in the Baltic Sea, followed in size by one in the Gulf of Mexico starting at the mouth of the Mississippi River in the states.
And one of the mouth of China, China's young, say, River in the East China Sea.
Damn man. We're messing that up.
How are we doing on time? You know, these shows are long doing less of the shows, but I'm making them longer. I'm not hearing anybody complain, so I'm just going to presume that it's okay.
Yes, I know what it's time for. It's time for another episode of the soundtrack my life. Here's Ray on the Charlie.
Let's take a look at the landscape on a road trip through your life.
This episode of Anchorage, the soundtrack to my life brings us back to 2002.
And it was 38 years old, and after selling his business in the US, he moved with land to Trisha and his daughter Christina from the land he was born to a beautiful cottage in the Lake Foreshode, Belgium.
And he also owned a piateir on the ingracht in the center of Amsterdam using a helicopter transportation to St. Tarts with these two places.
At the right years of being over there, and started to host a radio show on Das National Radio for Friday, 90, and 50.
At the Friday night, Funkathon with Curry and Kid V and a welcome many artists in the studio to perform live on here.
He carried out several old installation assignments and his family briefly started in the reality soap and his family.
Well, there's a lot to say about this soap. It was fun to watch every week about half an hour. I really enjoyed it until the moment I was having a pizza.
You know, with a pizza box on my lap in front of the TV, that's my first bite of the pizza I've ordered.
And there he was, a big willy and full erected penis coming through a TV screen, my living room watching me and my pizza.
I'm sorry, that was not the apple I wanted to see. I mean, it's not like I was jealous of something.
Till these days, I truly believe you didn't delete this scene on purpose. So thank you, Adam, because every time when I'm just always trying to eat pizza,
I get a kind of weird feeling in my stomach.
Soundtrack to my liking, my liking.
So 2002 was a year in which Adam got followed by several cameras for two years.
Twenty-four hours a day. The Adam's family aired only in Holland in 2002 and 2003 with a leader June from 1967.
Howard Kale and his five friends from the Turtles.
This song, Happy Together, was released in the spring of 67.
The song, Not The Beatles, Penny Lane, out of the number one slot for three weeks on the Billboard Hot 100s,
is was the group's only chart offer.
Anchories, the soundtrack to my life, takes a trip down and relayed to 2002.
Imagine me new, I do, I think about you day and night.
It's only right to think about the girl you love and hold a tight, so happy together.
I should call you up, invest a dime, and you say you belong to me.
It's my mind, imagine how the world is.
So we're fine, so happy together.
I can't see you, I know I didn't lie to you, but I'm not alive.
When you love me, I can't see you, but I'm not alive.
You and me, no matter how they toss the dice, to be the only one for me.
And you and me, so happy together.
I can't see you, I know I didn't lie to you, but I'm alive.
When you love me, I can't see you, but I'm alive.
You and me, no matter how they toss the dice, to be the only one for me.
And you and me, so happy together.
And you and me, no matter how they toss the dice, to be the only one for me.
So happy together.
What do we do for you?
Going right from tonight.
Thank you.
All right.
Let me just add a little bit of explanation there.
a guy named Greg Johnston, who used to be an associate producer on the headbangers ball and
I was like this is so brilliant. And at the time, it was not as contrived as they became.
And I said, this is fantastic. You know, and we were very much in the public eye in the
Netherlands, having, you know, returned and been back for a couple of years. And we had this
great pad and we had all this cool toys. I'm like, why don't we put together a show? But do
it all on Final Cut Pro, Final Cut on, yeah, Final Cut Pro. And we'll do it with Firewire hard drives.
And we'll just have a really small crew. We'll have our friends and had two friends, one editor,
and one camera man. And I'll do secondary camera. And we'll just wireless mics. We'll see we can
make a show out of it. And I sold it for, you know, a good price to SBS broadcasting. And so we had to
make this show. And it was fantastic. And even, and it was very much the way, it was, it was done in
sequence. The production was kind of like the Davis source code in a way I would have to say.
You know, some, some things with a little extra production boost. So we real, real heavy on playing,
you know, putting hits in there and cool tunes that you remember. And indeed, the opening music
was the turtles happy together. Because, and that's just the song that Patricia and I both love.
It's one of those songs, you know. And, and I've got it on DVD. You know, Patricia keeps saying,
you know, you should release that. You should do something with this. And first of all,
you can't clear it. There's no way you can get a DVD release because it's filled with,
I don't know, a 70 or 80 tracks. You know, you have to get clearances from every single one of them.
That worked on television because it's different rules, different rules apply. And of course,
you know, the ASCAD BMI was paid through the station. But I don't think you can sell it on a DVD.
And, you know, it's kind of cool to have something, a document of a certain period of our life.
And it was also a technological test. And it was a lot of fun. Now, about that one particular scene.
Okay. So first of all, it wasn't fully erect. You know, I hate to hate to pop your bubble there,
my friend. Second of all, it was only a few frames. No one saw it. In fact, it wasn't until the
edit that caught your editors that, hey, you do. You got like the log poking out there.
And I showed it to Patricia with letting out the shot, obviously. And she said, you know,
you know, you know, it's so many shots where I'm staying there and my bare ass, or I got my boobs hanging out.
So, you know, you should leave that in, damn it. And I think that's kind of fair. I said,
you know, it was only a couple of frames. So I don't think anyone would see it. But then,
young builder, a guy on a late night talk show, he had seen it, or someone had pointed it out to him.
And then he put it up full screen, freeze frame, and then started, he went to work on it with a
telestrator. Which is one of those, you know, they use it for sports like for football games.
They can draw on the screen and show where the movement is. And then, of course, it kind of became
lower. You can probably still Google that and there's a freeze frame of it online. There's no video of it.
Because, you know, as I said, it's like three frames. So that's why we didn't edit it out, Ray.
And was it cool to be back on the radio? Yeah, I mean, communicating with the, with the community.
That's my hobby, man. I love doing it. And with the source code, I'm able to do that, you know,
as a part of my job, which is, are you kidding me? I, I love it. Doing it live on the radio is
different experience, but very important to me as well. Because, you know, it's my roots. I love,
I love the live vibe, the direct interaction, which is why from time to time, I'll, I should try that again.
I should crank up the live DSC. You know, even better, I need to get Patricia on the show.
There's been a lot of change in the Charlie. There's been change in me personally.
And we should confront her about it. But she knows. I'm sure she'll have something to say about it.
And it may not all be good. So why don't I get her on the show?
That's what I'll do for this week. Because she's home. I'm home. I'll be cool.
Another thing I've just started to look into, thanks to John C. Devorek, is Oregon,
which was, I think is Oregon, Oregon, Oregon, which is a, uh, yet another description for the
energy force around, uh, which surrounds everything in the world. And this, uh, invented or discovered,
or coined by this guy, Wilhelm Reich. And it's all part of the energy awakening that's taking place, um, as well.
And of course, we got, uh, some calls about that from some familiar voices. Adam,
Atomic Rod here, enjoying your awakening to the idea that the energy elites
have a desire to keep their elite status and to keep out the riff riff. I'm not a big fan of
zero point energy, but I've know a lot about almost zero point energy. Remember, I used to go around
the world and a submarine whose fuel volume was small with the fit underneath my office desk
it lasted for 15 years. Just imagine having fuel with that kind of density in an automobile,
why you might get about 700 million miles per gallon. Yeah, I'm down with that atomic Rod.
I know I've done the calculations. That's seven hundred million. I'm not some kind of guy who has
done this at a swap meets and, uh, behind the scenes. I've actually operated those nuclear
reactors with, hey man, what you got against swap meets tiny fuel sources. Just think about how
threatening they are to the energy elite. Yeah. Just imagine the profitability of the deception
campaigns that have been run to keep people afraid, fear uncertainty and out slows down the nuclear
competition and makes it more expensive. The energy elites work for themselves. Bye now.
Bye, Rod. Thank you. Patricia just snuck up behind me and came around from the right hand side
in which it means I didn't, you know, usually I'll see you're called the steps and, uh, nice little
snack here. Huh, what are these shrimp? Butterfly shrimp. Crisp, crispy, butterfly shrimp.
It doesn't get much better than that. Yeah, man. Of course, there's so many different
forms of energy that are so poorly researched. And, uh, and, you know, I'm awake, man. I'm awake
to the atomic energy. And I think there's more. I really do. There's more coming. There's more and
more happening. But, you know, maybe we have to see, and maybe it's all coming to a head all the
right moment. You know, maybe the meltdown will actually wipe out the energy elite for a while.
Then maybe we can, we have a shot. You know, when the lights go off, people are going to come out
of the woodwork with shit to make the lights go on. And that's what people are going to
gravitate towards. So we may have to get to that point. And we may be moving there pretty damn
quickly. One of the, the big government initiatives, and I'm sure some of it has must have to do
with power. I mean, they're using magnets and protons and neutrons and all kinds of stuff that
I really don't understand is this collider project in Geneva, the large headron collider. And I've
asked for, you know, if you chuckle heads to check in and try and explain it to me. And here's one.
The collider is the basic two of particle physics. It takes a stream of particles and accelerates them
to really high kinetic energy levels before slamming them into a target. Both experiments create
new particles predicted by theories or to examine their behavior. In order to research and discover
more of these particles, larger colliders are needed. The U-lars, headron collider is a 10 billion
dollar underground ring shaped tunnel. There's 27 kilometers and street conference with two
beam traveling and opposite directions. It seems particles with 7 trillion electron volts of energy,
probably at 99.9999% the speed of light. Now, this by the way is Russell,
Biden, Russell, I'm still not getting it. And held in place by powerful magnets. It is the
largest collider built to date, but a smaller compared to the discontinued superconducting
super collider, 87 kilometers in street conference, or the even larger proposed very large
headron collider at 105 to 650 kilometers in street conference. Considering that the universe already
does 10 trillion lifetime runs of the headron collider every second such its inception,
and our planet has yet to be destroyed. I doubt that anything that we humans do with our collider
will have any negligible negative effect on our planet. And if anything, we'll expand our knowledge
of the universe and how it was created. Alright, Russell. Okay, I'm down with that. I just find
it suspicious that there's not a single politician who clearly okay, the payment for this thing,
10 billion. We're going to actually explain what it's for. You know, we're looking for the
god molecule. We're looking to find alternative energy. I mean, what's the direct benefit going to be
if we actually find out that there was a big bang, and that's how the earth was created?
What's the direct benefit at this moment in time? How much is that change? The energy
elite are still going to run the show? Is that going to change anything there as far as I know?
Or is this their project? That's what I'd like to know. And this one, it's another one of those
new stories that actually, I almost, I almost considered not even giving it a second thought,
and then I thought, wait a minute, that's really stupid. I should talk about this, and this should
be on the show because I didn't hear about it anywhere from anyone. Adam here's the girl
in here. In the unreported news category, oh my god, until I seventh last month or a month ago now,
Obama's plane had to have a emergency landing. They were calling out crash and fire rescue to the
landing strip in St. Louis, and I didn't even know about this until today on emergency landing
ramp apparently deployed in the nose cone or the tail cone of the aircraft. Does this ever happen?
You're a pilot. Does this happen often? Do you call for crash and fire rescue if it's not serious?
Do you declare emergency landing if it's not very, very serious? Is this an attempt on a
bomb of life? Was this an assassination death that we missed? Was this an intimidation? Was this
pre-caximet? I don't know. But I ain't letting nothing come by me on dream land.
Yeah. Yeah, so I saw this. And I thought nothing of it initially. I was saying, oh, you know,
yeah, it didn't seem too serious. And then I started seeing news reports. Let's see, I think it was ABC News.
Yeah, ABC News, they actually broke this story. Let me see if I can bring this up for you.
Yeah, the bandwidth still sucks.
Right, here it is. The incident involving Senator Barack Obama's campaign plane last month
was much more serious than the airline or the federal aviation administration said, according to
FAA control tower tapes obtained by ABC News. At the time, the pilot did not declare an emergency
and the airline owner Midwest Airlines said safety was never an issue. And then they broadcast the
tapes. So, did you hear this? Yeah, it's see if I can fire this up from, of course, YouTube has it.
Let's see if you can hear this. It's pretty interesting.
It's ABC News, everybody. It's Charles Gibson.
In the mid-X-80-653 changes, that's the same. It looks the other mechanical problems.
And it's sending to one-one doubt. It's just to keep you advised. We have a control ability
if you would to the aircraft. We have limited-fetched authority at the flight levels. We're
just sending to see if we could re-keep it to authority. And we're going to have to stop
probably around 8 to 10 steps. If you can figure the aircraft to make sure that we have
to start. So, what I'm hearing here is they're at a flight level, probably like 35,000 feet.
And I think it's a 757. And so control pitch issues means they can't,
well, wait a minute. He says he can go down. So, I guess he would the only way to do that if he can't
control the upper-down pitch is by reducing power. That'll do it. That's a pretty scary position
to be in. If you can't push the nose forward and have it go down or pull the yolk back and
have the nose rise. So, it sounds like they were going to be trying different ways to move that
on their way down and they must have been reducing power to do it. That's what it sounds like to me.
Hello. Hello. That's the Clarenone Emergency. That is an emergency. And you're only declaring
that the guy wants to land. That's what he wants to do. That's why you declare an emergency.
It doesn't mean you're on fire, but it's like you need priority. But if it's emergency status,
that's the FAA didn't, it was not truthful. It's an emergency status. It doesn't mean necessarily
that there's something really, definitely wrong. It's like need to land, need priority. Now,
and that's how the controller will respond. I'll say that it's easy for a standing fire,
see you, let's medicate you 653. I will show that. And would you be able to put it on runways?
Would you like runway 3, or right or runway 3, or left? Well, which one is the longest?
I'll medicate you 653 runway 3, or left. Okay. Sorry. I'm eating one of those butterfly shrimp.
So there you go. Immediately comes back. Well, runway do you want? Which means, you know, he's
going in St. Louis and he asks for the crash and fire rescue, because he's thinking he can't control
the nose. He's going to have to do that with a combination of perhaps flaps if he can control those
and power. And that's why I said, give me the longest runway possible, although in any emergency
situation, you want the broadest, longest piece of landing strip available. That'll just make
you feel good. Okay. We'd like 3-0 left. It's just for informational purposes. We have Senator
Obama on board, the aircraft, the Biscuit F8. Medic 8663. Roger that. Medic 8663. And can you give
me the souls on board and the fuel that you have remaining in counts. 51 souls on board. You
want that out to what he wants out. Medic 8663. Roger that. And that's 51 and 2, including
all the pastures you include. That's affirmative. Medic 8663. In addition to confirm the problem
with your emergency is it's a equipment problem, an understanding that the ability to
control it. That was up on higher altitudes, so you're going to have that problem all the way down.
So we had a pitch authority problem. Now that we've come down to a lower altitudes, it's team
to rectify itself. We do have pitch control of the aircraft at this time. Medic 8663. So
do you need any special handling other than the CFR or Sting Blackboard? So, now for what I understand
they went down to like 8,000 feet. And that the problem was indeed like either an emergency
raft or emergency slide that deployed inside the tail cone. And that was, I think the equivalent
of what the story is is that was rubbing up against the wires because of all of this is control
controlled from the front, you know, the controls eventually come to the back. It is a high tail.
So the pitch will be controlled from that. So it's possible. And I'm just and I see I'm sure
we need to get like cat and Chris or someone else who who's flown these these aircraft and
can understand it. I mean, it sounds feasible that maybe that thing deployed. And of course the
tail cone, there's a lot of the function of the tail cone is for pressurization. So they got down
to 8,000 feet. They were able to depressurize and maybe that helped loosen up whatever was rubbing
against whatever control wires. But it doesn't sound like a really credible story quite honestly.
And if it wasn't a assassination attempt, then it was definitely CIA because that they loved
killing people on airplanes. That's what they loved doing. And then it wasn't the Clintons doing
anything because they'd just like to shoot people. And at least that's what I've been seeing
in all these documentaries. It's crazy. Absolutely nuts. And it's going to be interesting to see
what happens with the Democratic National Convention, where they're going to do a state-by-state
vote. And, you know, if I were a super delegate, I'd be thinking, hey man, that guy in Arkansas
got whacked. You know, I'm a, but maybe that was a message. I might want to be kind of careful.
Now we've got lady to Rothchild. There's a name for you. One of the true owners of the globe.
We're enslaved to them. Slowly breaking free mind you. She's in support of Hillary. And actually,
you know, if you go together for us.com, you'll see. She's what she's exactly what she wanted.
She got and we want a roll call vote. And we want the 18 million people who voted for Hillary to be
happy. And essentially get her in office. Would it be wacky if, if she won and then she turned around
and she said to Obama be my VP? Wouldn't that be crazy? Wouldn't that not work, but wouldn't it be nuts?
Ha. All right. I'm running out of steam. Let me play one more song which comes with
its own intro. Thank God. I got him. This was Justin. I just dropped a file and the drop I
owe called Peruvian cocaine. And unfortunately, I couldn't get it to take the metadata. This
is a mortal technique revolutionary volume to track called Peruvian cocaine. All right,
man. I've heard whispers about the financial support your government receives from a drug industry.
Well, the irony of this, of course, is that this money, which is in the billions,
is coming from your country. You see, you are the major purchaser of our national product,
which is, of course, cocaine. Okay. On one hand, you're saying the United States government is spending
millions of dollars to eliminate the flow of drugs onto our streets. At the same time,
we're doing business with a very same government that is flooding our streets with cocaine.
Let me show you a few of the other characters that are involved in this tragic comedy.
Like a slave, the poker fields have to be pretty, distributed. My people is starving,
broken and sweaty, dreaming about revolution, looking at my machete, but the work load is too heavy,
derisa been ons, and ever ran away. I know they probably murder my mom, so I pray that has
some good Easter when I go to the mission, process the cocaine paste and play my position.
This war is so hot. Feet your kids. I need these bricks. For the tons of total, let me test it.
Yeah, this is good. Pass me your tissue and don't worry about them. I paid off the affair.
Yo, it's all come as a challenge. I'm the son of some of the fellas, the legend by my people.
The only one in the family born in bread to console with beds. I laughed at fate and assassinate.
My predecessor had his place in a thorough world fashion state.
Locked a nation with 90% of the wealthy 10% of the population, essentially,
intelligent, agency takes away faithfully. The finest type for China, white and cocaine, you see.
Honey, I'm home. Never mind when you think it can't suddenly grown. It's funny with so under this debt for this money,
we owe a job. Whenever told you that I had to give a mental, but grown to keep us underholding a private school,
but to keep us home, he's swollen. Come on, I fucking home was built in a foundation of bloody roads.
The hungry stole the nothing so across this country's running cold. I took a stunning oath,
the hush, the ones who know that see I acreed up to the flow for this young hush,
you know,
And
He
he
This is my true promise, stop it and back in
Take your pictures and tap and phone
The bacon snitches and crack and cold
Fast the couple blast the phone
And he hush the stack and soul
Let's pull the crack up low
And my overtime is where your taxes go
A game you trust
Get you the hand way to us
Cause we paid up front on the lower cameras
Taping up, getting proper weight
The prison said this is doing
Make the collar that leaves with two keys
Out the evidence
We're wet my frame
Trunk both the plane and watch it
You're hungry, you got work
They're clapping too
We can throw black
They lack countries and own companies
We had nice cars and sneaker money
Now it's payin' us out here
Talk about they hold it
So busting it house
Like they down south
When those open, let the way long
Roll, you take shots and swoops
That's it be a billion mouth
Like fucks and swoops
So when you're the rush
The pressure, co-brands
When you're being in south with me
Like ch any low pass
And this cool, I was a bully
Now life is fully in joke
I keep a flow on the ball
For moving in cool
Plays do favors for governors
And tax makers
Fat quick and slow
Crack and sex act
What fat man is
So what's got edge
Big mouth's probably snow
Not prepared to do this
Like high-ve-are
The story just cold
It's an example
It's half the truck's tape
I narrated every neighborhood
And every state
And it's country
It's a lot deeper
Than it niggas on your blind
So when they point the finger
This is what you got to tell them
I'm not guilty
You're the one who's guilty
Low makers, the politicians
The Colombian drug lord
All you who lobby against making drugs legal
Just like you did with alcohol doing the prohibition
You're the one who's guilty
I mean, come on, let's kick the ballistic here
Ain't no dosies made in Harlem
Not one of us in here
All's a poppy feet
This thing is bigger than immortal technique
This is big business
This is the American way
There you go, immortal technique
All right, there it is
There's the word that's how it works
You know, you can go read legacy
The ashes and
Go all the way through a
Was it 700 page book and come to the same conclusion
Well, you're listening to a four and a half minute song
And I who you're going to believe
I'll believe these guys before I believe CNN
All right
Okay, so there you go
It's a big scam and
And all of us, all the people
We're just, you know, a part of their machinery
And we're starting to wake up to it
And there's people inside the machinery
Inside governments inside all kinds of institutions
Who are also wide awake
They're listening to the show right now
They're visiting websites, they're figuring it out
They, in fact, they know a head of a lot more
And we welcome our brothers and sisters on the inside
And we want to help
And if you are working there
And you feel that you truly
Should be working for us now is the time
You know, now is the time to do something
We can do it together, I'm sure of that
So my mission
To get the lady P on the show
We got a lot to talk about with her
And keep stuff coming into the drop
Drop.au slash daddy source code
If you can, please use the phone number for that
With the unhandy pain code
And check out the links at create.com
For some great offers
We got to offer us a budget rent a car
Those some got an offer on e-muse
Of course, the long lasting go daddy
Just use the codes
And I'll talk to you later this week
Until then, live your life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another fine, medium presentation
Stick it in your ear
If you like this video, don't forget to subscribe
And click on the bell
Click on the bell