Delta-Share Charly 728's The Wet Edition.
With $16 billion worth of airplane straps by us.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
On casting, it's Adam Curry.
I love me, I'm kind, I'm a baby.
I love me, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind.
I love me, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind
I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kinda, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I'm kind, I
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code, it's episode number 728
a special Saturday edition because I just didn't have the energy
to bring you on on Friday for a food bar,
but everything you'd expect in a food bar is included in this
edition and then some.
No live chat room, no live calls.
I've been sitting here inside the condo for the past 24 hours,
and it has been the most atrocious weather I've ever seen.
We've got 35 mile an hour winds gusting to 55.
Of course, you know, I'm up here on the 24th floor over looking
the bay and I'm literally seeing debris flying up
up to the height of the 24th floor, you know, like paper bags,
plastic bags, homeless people.
It's just, it's crazy.
And I'm here all alone and I'm feeling a little bit
melancholy and I thought to myself, why don't I share a couple of
songs in the soundtrack to my life that kind of fit in with the mood
that I'm thinking of right now because, you know, I'm about five,
six thousand miles from home, and they said it's not supposed to rain
in southern or northern California.
We've got on board a westbound seven, 47,
and they've been there for decided what to do,
all that total opportunity,
TV breaks and we'll be right home.
Sure and true.
Seems it never rains in southern California.
Seems I've all heard that kind of talk to both.
It never rains in California.
We've got to know that kind of talk to both.
Yeah, I think you've got to be at least 35 to appreciate most of the songs I've got lined up for the breakups in the game.
This is definitely one from the 70s, Albert Hammond, it never rains in Southern California or Northern California for that matter.
Especially sad because today is the Chinese New Year.
It's what Lisa's being celebrated here in San Francisco and Chinatown actually went out for a walk just before it started to pour down.
And they were setting up bleachers and all kinds of, all kinds of stuff on Kerney Street for the route and I feel bad, man.
Paper, dragons and fireworks just don't mix with this kind of weather. It's stormy outside.
I don't know why, there's no sun up in the sky.
It's told me whether, since my man and I, together, keeps raining all the time.
Like this day, you and this year everywhere, stormy weather.
Since my man and I, together, keep raining all the time.
Not that keeps raining all the time.
When he went away, the moon was given and met me.
He and these days away, old, ruggin' tears on my head.
All I do is create a lot of buzz.
Gonna let me walk in the sun once more.
And all I had a life is gone, stormy weather.
Since my man and I, together, keep raining all the time.
He's raining all the time.
And all I had a life is gone, stormy weather.
Since my man and I, together, keep raining all the time.
He's raining all the time.
The wonderful sound of Ella Fitzgerald, not King Cole.
Stormy weather on Danny Source Code, episode number 728, from a very, very wet San Francisco.
I've been getting a lot of comments about the new set up, particularly about being able to talk to people live on the show.
And of course, there's pros and cons to everything.
And it's really, for those of you who haven't been listening, I mean 728 episodes, it's impossible you heard everything.
And you may not have been listening from episode one or before we even started counting or before it was even called the Daily Source Code.
But it's an experimental show, you know, we try stuff out.
And obviously, I have the capability now to talk to people live.
That's very cool.
And now, of course, we've got to have something to actually say.
So there's pros and cons everyone's picked up on it, but some people love it.
Some people think it's, ah, some people don't love it so much.
One thing for sure, though, this business of naked pictures.
Yeah.
Oh, great.
You know, I get no naked pictures.
Just when I spend for them all the time, you sound like a desperate person.
That's why you don't fucking get in.
Don't go in with your money.
Thank you.
Hey, James.
Thank you very much.
One more like that.
Hey, Adam, let's David and Jackson go calling again.
They just wanted to give you a little insight.
And I know you're growing up.
I know you probably know this, but when a woman tells you that she's going to
work on getting some naked trees of it, that means you're getting exactly nothing.
Just a little helpful hand from a guy who has spent the better part of his life asking
you know, online chicks for naked pictures of himself.
It's a pretty fruitless effort.
So right here.
Love you.
Anyway.
Right, man.
Yeah, you're right.
I should stop doing that.
You know, my wife hates it when I do it.
Well, she doesn't hate it.
She thinks I sound like a, oh, kind of what to do.
Oh, kind of what James said, like an old perv.
So, of course, we missed the food bar Friday.
I really, I was just too tired.
I was, uh, knackered.
Shall we say.
But I did, uh, no agenda with the Johnson of Orac Friday evening.
About six, 15 is when we started to record that.
And it was a lot of fun.
You know, we actually ran long like an hour and 10, an hour and 15 minutes.
And I was just wiped out nothing left to say.
And I, I didn't have the energy to go and pull everything together.
And also this time zone.
It's a very, very difficult time zone to do.
To, uh, to taste people to do things.
Because, you know, what is what time is it now?
It's Saturday night five minutes past eight.
Look at me.
How sad is my life, huh?
What, what else could you be doing on a Saturday night at eight o'clock?
I just had my ravioli from Chef Boyardy sat down.
Pull out a whole bunch of tracks from the soundtrack to my life.
And of course, I scan the Gmail.
Because we cannot finish a week without young palettes hit test.
Oncoming casting with Adam Curry.
I Adam, who are you ready to be stunked out?
Because he is the new test.
Bring it on, baby.
It's young palettes.
Hey, Adam.
This is hit test number 110.
And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
Take it.
Oh, it's all young.
Oh, you read my mind, man.
Oh, that's one from my soundtrack, my life.
That, of course, is Rupert Holmes and him.
No doubt about it.
Number two.
Kind of sounds like like the SOS band or something.
No, I give up on that one.
And number three.
I know it's easy one.
That would be a bunch of people to keep the faith.
And I'd recognize that intro anywhere.
And times up.
And these are the answers.
Oh, yeah.
Answer number one is from 1980.
I got a signal.
The window.
There's a pack of cigarettes.
Him, him, him.
What's she gonna do about him?
She's gonna have to do without him.
It's me without me.
Me.
No.
That's the answer.
Answer number one, him from 1980 by Rupert Holmes.
What's this?
And this is answer number two.
Oh.
Who's human hunting?
86.
That's his host.
Zooming there.
I read that.
怎麼 him?
Oh.
Zooming.
Jordan Hammer.
Zooming who has answered number two are Rupert Franklin?
And this is answer number three.
Oh yeah, from 1992, this is Banjofi.
Uh-huh.
Hold on, hold on.
Let's go get your children.
That they're tied to your feet.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
Another great example for the wall of sounds.
Banjofi and keep the faith.
Let's answer number three.
We need this number 110.
Oh, so Adam, how did you do that?
Two out of three.
Yeah, I'm Mr. Rita.
Sorry.
The answer is to this hit test and also the iTunes links
so that you can buy these tracks online
or to be found at hittest.botsho.com.
Thank you for playing Adam.
Next week, I'll be back for hit test number 111.
So until then,
have a very nice week.
And take care.
Be back.
Hittest.botsho.com.
Impolent.com.
J-N-P-O-L-E-T-T-A-C-O-C-O.
And the cheese just keeps on coming.
Another perfect California song.
This is a wishful thinking.
Top-down, driving around music.
Sunshine, and I'm just imagine
in America's Ventura Freeway.
Where's it, highway?
You're gonna be so good.
Walking down the road.
There'll be no I long you're gonna stay here, don't.
It's on people's say.
This found a little good in the snow.
You don't care. I know.
You're gonna be a good one.
Mince your highway.
In the sunshine.
Where the days are longer.
The nights are stronger than moonshine.
You're gonna go.
I know.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Thanks lots and just the same
That you're highway in a sunshine
Where the days are longer than nights are stronger than sunshine
You're gonna go, I know, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Because of free wind, it's blowing through your hair
And the days surround your day life there
Season's crying, no despair
I'm a gamer in the air in the air
Now, of course, I must remind you that today's daily source code is brought to you under the educational auspices of the organization
For the preservation, the soundtrack of our lives, but I know it's up-sol
You can find out more about up-sol
Ask her papa's share of Oscar Lima.pacho.com
In other words, everything I'm playing is illegal
You can't tell anyone you ever heard the show or I'll just have to kill you
I'm sorry about it
Hey, this is Paul Smith
From Kingsville, Florida
Here's a little sound for the day's on a 500
I'm on the backstrapes
And as you can tell, the cars are going by
This is the 50th running of the Daytona 500 in Daytona, Florida
It's not you. Get a kick out of here in the cars go around
So again, this is Paul Smith
Check it in from Florida
41 Mary
Two kids
Love the show Adam, right here?
Love yet? No homo
How's the singer?
She stands up
When she plays
The piano
And I close
How's the singer?
She sings songs
For the lost in the lonely
Her job is entertaining folks
See your songs and town jokes in my club
Piles a singer
And they say that she wants
Was a winner
In a contest
How's the singer
And they say that she wants
Can't track her
They played her wings
On the local radio
They never made it
She wanted to be magic rainbow
But now she sits there at the famous date table
Dreaming of the things she never got to do
All those dreams that never came true
How's the singer?
She stands up
When she plays
The piano
And I close
How's the singer?
She sings songs for the lost
And the lonely
Her job is entertaining folks
See your songs and town jokes in my club
Piles a singer
She stands up
When she plays
The piano
And the lonely
Her job is entertaining folks
See your songs and town jokes in my club
She stands up
When she plays
Her job is entertaining folks
See your bow
Telling to do
Yeah, I'll be there
And I close
It's been decades since I've heard that song
Came across that of my first gen iPod
Which of course is still here at the Curry condo
Works
Spurles a singer on daily source code episode 728
It is the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
Edition
Curly educational
And I can remember exactly where I was when I heard the song
How about you?
I got no money
I ain't that close for my daughter
I'm around
Yes, got no money
But they're always seeing the legend
Nothing to spoil
Cause I'll never see you anymore
And I need you nothing
That's all I'm living for
Yeah, yeah
I need you to picture your pain
But I love you
I won't let you do
I'm so shy Yeah, but with you, I just go out
Woo, woo, woo
I just want to pressure your pain
I'm laughing for one and a half years
I want to hear your cry
I want to hear the pain
You come from me
I want to hear your cry
Oh no, I can't stop
This usually makes us perfectly through the controversy
From the days before it was fashionable to like friends
I want to be your lover
You know, I've slept around
I've slept around one stack of vinyl albums my entire life
Or at least since my 20s
And it's all prints
Never played them to completely virgin
I got to tell you
That's probably the guy I
Waffner can't be the guy that I respect the most
The music business
But
Gosh, do I love the stuff he does
So for those of you not quite familiar with the concept of
The soundtrack of our lives
The idea is when you hear these songs
And you think about them
You're like, oh man
I know exactly where I was when I first heard that
And it doesn't have to be the first time you heard it
Because when I hear this song
I always think of
The time I was in Minneapolis
The Twin Cities
Manyapolis St. Paul
Of all things
Of course, the Mall of America is there
And I was shooting a commercial for
Sam Goody's record stores
So they still exist by the way
And so they had it, you know, we're doing the shoot in
In the Mall of America
And I was staying there for a couple days
And the second night of the shoot
I remember I was in my hotel room
And I was just watching the Tonight Show
Maybe it was a Letterman
And the phone rings
And it's midnight
I pick up the phone
And voice in the other and says
Yeah, um, it's Adam
Yeah
Listen, prints wants to invite you to a party
Paisley Park Studios
Are you interested in going
And I said
Are you kidding me? Yes
Says good because the car's out in front
So I throw on jacket
Going downstairs
It's about a 25 minute drive
From the hotel I was staying in
And you roll up on the highway
Passed the Paisley Park Studios
And it's completely illuminated in purple
It was just phenomenal sight
You know, rolls up
Walk in the front door
It's all pristine white except of course for this
Uh, for this purple glow
Over the end and you got this
It was just so spooky, you know
Really dark and just this purple building
Which was illuminated
Go through a metal detector first
Which was kind of funky
Excuse me and I walk in
To this room this huge room
Which consisted of it was just a big white space
Along one side was just about the
The longest
Buffet snacks and dinner
I'd ever seen
As a DJ
In the middle with
You know it's into that typical DJ set up
Actually none of the middle but over to the other wall
With with speaker stacks
And he was playing this this print stuff
These tracks that I never heard before my life
It was like this
It was just unreleased stuff, you know
And I was wow I can't believe it
And the most beautiful boys and girls in this place
All kind of dancing
And
You know so I hung out and actually
One of the extras who
Who was on the shoot
What was her name again?
Um, willow I think her name was
I guess right willow because I remember
My sister's name
And um, I don't know if she was an extra on the shoot
I'd met her either
Earlier or the day before
And you know so we're talking a little bit
And like wow this is pretty cool
And prints is standing over in the corner
Next one of the speaker stacks
And so I say to Willow
Who I think he actually went out with her for a while
I don't know if it was during that period or before
After whatever
And I said oh I got to go over and say hi to him
Because damn yeah this is very cool that he invited me
And there were a couple people standing around
She said oh no no no you shouldn't do that man
Is it well why not?
Oh you know because you're really tall and you're white
I said I kind of bullshit is that
If he's got a problem with that then I'm leaving
I'm leaving
So I walk over to him
First thing I noticed he's not all that small
He really isn't
Maybe he was wearing some heels but didn't you?
He's not like a midget
Not a big guy
So that was the first thing I noticed
I say hey you know I want to thank you very much for inviting me
And he knew everything
He said oh yeah you know
I'd seen that Halloween episode you did on MTV
And yeah I didn't knew about my daughter
And we talked for I don't know
15 20 minutes and it was just you know
I was but I'm not a fan boy
But I was completely blown away by that
And and then he kind of disappeared after a while
And then probably
I'd say around 2015 to 30
The whole bunch of guys and black suits came into the
Into the into this white room that we're all in
And they started flashing flashlights on the ground
Just like click click click on and off
And everyone just you got it
It was the signal
It was like the bat signal
Everyone got their coats
Put them on and left
It was definitely
Definitely one of the
The coolest show business moments I've ever witnessed
And obviously
A cut right at the beginning
To the soundtrack of my life
You can try this cowbell out
Let's don't give up night
To the hardest work
And lawyer
He's trying to tie
Yeah
Oh yeah
Oh
How's it going Adam it's jersey time
The official musical just of the chat chat
Hey dude, I know my week off of Valentine's Day
But I wanted to bring you something really nice
For a football Friday
You see on the positive music network
Is a song by David Martin
And the interesting story about David Martin is
That he met his wife when he was 15 years old
And he recently put out an album of
Ten songs all dedicated to his wife
It's an absolutely beautiful album
And he actually calls it the ultimate love letter
I think this is a really really special song
And I think it really really is going to break out
As a mainstream kind of hit
Check this out
It's called Something Your Eyes
The notes this guy hits
He's jersey time
I'll check you next week
There was something in your eyes
And now I see
It was your life for me
There was something in your eyes
And what I saw
Still holds me in your eyes
Spend your life with me
Until the end of time
Yeah
We will make more memories
And we will share the stories of the way we want
And we will share the stories of the ways we want
And I see it was your life for me
There was something in your eyes
Come on, it's all to hold me in love
There's still something in your eyes
Come on, it's all to hold me
There's something in your eyes
Oh, Todd, man
You did it again
David Martin, something in your eyes
From the pod save music network, fantastic
I think I'm going to add that one to my personal soundtrack to my life collection
Cool, man
That was good, that was really, really good
So I'm going to do some extra work on today's show
And I'm going to find links to every single song I played
And with those in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
So that you can go and purchase them
Because I know what always happens when I play some of these tunes
Just people say, oh, man, I love that song
How can I get a hold of it?
So I'll put in probably Amazon links
So I'll see if I can find MP3s because Amazon sells them
DRM free
And if I have to, I'll resort to the iTunes music store
So it looks like the weather's going to be pretty bad
Tomorrow as well
But Monday, when the week starts off again
You know what happens, right?
You know what happens after the big rain storm
When the sun comes out
From behind the clouds
It's when you see the rainbow, my friends
And that is something you want to connect with
And here's a frog to tell you about it
Why not?
There's so many songs about rainbows
And what's on the other side?
Rainbows are visions
But only illusions
And rainbows have nothing to hide
So we've been told that some choose to be like
I know they're wrong way to stay
Someday we'll find the rainbow connection
The lovers, the dreamers
And me
Who said that every wish would be heard
And answer when we should find the morning star
Somebody, follow them
And someone believed it
Look what it's done
So far
What's so amazing
That dreams are star-facing
And what do we think we might see?
Someday we'll find the rainbow connection
The lovers, the dreamers, let me
All of us under it's known
We know that it's probably magic
Can you then have a free
And then we'll find the rainbow
And I've heard them calling my name
Is this a sweet song
But only illusions there
The voice might be one and the same
I've heard it too many times
Do it, ignore it
It's something that I'm supposed to be
Someday we'll find the rainbow connection
The lovers, the dreamers, let me
Doesn't get much cheeseier than that
And I love it
And I'm not ashamed of it
Come with the frog
And the rainbow connection
Rappin' up episode 728 of the Daily Source Code
Links to all these songs that show notes
at dailysourcecode.com
I hope you enjoyed listening to this program
on your Saturday night or your Sunday morning
Or, of course, if you're down under on your Wednesday lunch break
I'll be back on Monday for sure
With another edition of the Daily Source Code
I hope you tune in then as well
Adam at podshow.com
Dailysourcecode.com
Live your life with passion
And enjoy your freedom
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear