Imagine headphones without wires.
Now their Sony's Bluetooth wireless headset, a rechargeable listening experience with 11 hours
of music playback, so you and your music are free to move.
Pick up yours at Sony.com-headphones, Sony wireless headphones, your music are unplugged.
You are listening to a man crazy enough to fly without a business card, Adam Curry.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass, to the next generation renew
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this journey.
Don't care about it, crazy me, won't scream, where my words they cut short like a demon
decision, I was chillin' my friends with my bad religion, when I was left talking
on my television, some me overheat you with this bad religion.
While they gathered and screamed and gathered in the place, all he'd better be careful
with my pop-up thing, no matter what he says, I don't feel forgive him, somebody, you
have him, please, he got some bad religion.
I want you to scream, I just have to be right, what the earth in front of him, I've
been a queer, I'm never meant to end it, I've been walking, told me my love and I've
been a man, I've been a man, I've been a man, I've been a man, I've been a man, I've been
bad religion and I've been a man, I've been a man, I've been a man, I've been a man
Zero, six, like Jimmy Branch are kicking on on this Tuesday, January 8th, 2007. Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Oh my goodness. Uh, this is almost the official start of the new year for me.
You hear that?
You could...
Sorry, uh, got some flim in your ears there, didn't mean to do that.
Yeah, it's Tuesday, missed out on yesterday, spent most of the day in Los Petales here in G-Town.
Nothing serious, but also nothing I'm allowed to talk about.
The lady Patricia doesn't want me to say anything.
But I'm sure... I'm sure she'll give you details. Hopefully later on in the week as to what was going on.
But everything is fantastic. I'm all alone here in the the curry manner.
Another crappy day, unbelievable. It's just... it's just been... it's been shit.
Oh, maybe it's, uh, let me see. Oh, yeah, it's winter, almost forgot. I kind of forgotten what it was
like to have really crappy crappy weather in the UK, because we've had such a, such a great summer
and almost an Indian summer and man, it's just wet and rainy and Christina went back to school today.
After, uh, what is it? What is it with, uh, with these, uh, with these vacations, with these holidays,
unbelievable? I don't, I think she'd been out of school for almost almost a month. Of course,
Christmas and New Year's fell on really strange days this year. So, um, I guess that's why stuff
just kind of closed now. But I haven't been able to have a decent business meeting, nothing at all
until finally starting out this week and, uh, and, uh, well, here we are. I feel like crap.
I got to tell you this, uh, this flu, which, uh, had had, I guess it's still kind of reaching
epidemic proportions. It's the, the no-row virus, or, um, as some would say, the Norwalk like virus,
which usually attacks people on cruise ships. Uh, it's just running rampant. I mean, you can't
get a single person on the phone. They're all sick. They're all home and, uh, and, uh, it's, uh,
it's messed up. And I've been thinking that, uh, in this new year, um, I want to do a
couple of things differently with the show. I'm, uh, it's still kind of running shit through my brain,
trying to figure it out. Uh, obviously the topics that we've been hitting on in the past, uh,
a couple weeks or actually a couple months have, uh, have really increased the, uh, the, uh, the
the listenership, the audience has grown significantly, um, you know, the conversations have been, uh,
turning to, uh, well, I want to steer a little bit away from, uh, from the conspiracy theories. I,
you know, when I was ill, uh, if, if you heard, um, uh, Noah Jenda, uh, the one that, uh,
John DeBorek and I did on, uh, on Friday, he even warned me. He said, you know, you really got to
watch out watching all of those, uh, conspiracy videos because you can really go nuts. And I think I was
kind of going just a little bit freaky, uh, because you get into this, this spiral of, um, my god,
there's no fixing it. There's nothing we can do. And, and actually there's, uh, there's a lot
of hope out there. There's a lot of amazing things happening, uh, throughout the world. I also want
to concentrate a little bit on the UK. Um, in fact, uh, I, I got a, uh, I was nice to see as I went through
the, uh, the voicemail, uh, messages that, uh, there were a lot of calls coming in from, uh, from the
UK. And this is one that I kind of expected a while ago, but finally someone's asking the question.
I add, um, it's, uh, Adrian Pack from London here, a very long time listener. I was just wondering
if you might, um, do as a big favor for your non-American listeners, and, and explain how the American
race for the White House works. I mean, words like caucuses and primaries, they don't really mean anything
to me. And I, and I, and I, I'm really very confused about who's competing with who and whether it's
Democrats looking for a representative of the Democrats or whether they're all fighting each other
or I'm where was wrong polling. I, well, I don't get it. Uh, can you, um, can you, can you help me out
here? Um, and get well soon. I hope you feel better. I love you. Bye.
Hi, I love you, too, Adrian. Thanks, man. Yeah, you know, it is extremely confusing. And quite
honestly, I think that a lot of people, uh, Americans probably don't understand. In, in fact,
I'm probably not even qualified to explain exactly how it worked, but, um, the main thing that's
going on right now is that, uh, and this is just an observation from my part, is that the media has
grabbed onto this primary in, you know, like there's nothing else going on in the world, um, and
by the way, there is quite a lot of shit going on in the world, um, that it almost feels like we're,
you know, we're going to be, uh, electing a president next week, you know, and, uh, and, and
almost feels like, oh, well, the race is over. It's clear that, uh, Obama is going to be the winner.
That's, it's just the way it comes across. And, and I think that, uh, the sooner we all realize that
this is a very long process. In fact, it's the longest process ever I believe in history,
because all these primaries have started early. Let me just try and give it a, uh, a brief
stab. Essentially, the United States has a two-party system. You have the Democrats, and you have
the Republicans, two different, uh, I mean, really, the same two different sides of the same coin.
I guess you could almost say, um, but they're two parties, and they stand for different things.
It's, uh, it's kind of hard to even, um, segregate the two these days when you listen to all the messages,
almost sounds like everyone is saying pretty much the same thing. A change is always the big
word. Everybody wants to change. But, um, you know, in a contrary to, uh, probably popular belief
around, uh, most of the world, the, um, it's not a popular vote. So it's not like whoever gets the
most votes wins the presidency. Uh, it, uh, it's divided up by, um, by delegates. And, uh, each state
has a number of delegates assigned to it. Uh, uh, that is determined by the size of the state.
And, um, you have, uh, uh, I see, I'm, I'm, you know what, can somebody please explain this to my British
friends? But anyway, the idea is that first, each party decides who their, um, Canada is going to be.
And once that is done and this, uh, essentially, uh, this process goes all the way through, uh,
well, through the next several months, I think it even goes, uh, well into the summer, uh,
where, uh, states will be determining, okay, this is our guy from the selection of guys for this party.
And so what we should wind up with somewhere around November is, uh, two tickets. Uh, one ticket will be
the, uh, Democratic ticket, one will be the Republican ticket. Uh, excuse me, you can tell
up so aggravated, just trying to explain it to myself is difficult. Uh, and the ticket will consist
of a presidential candidate and a vice presidential candidate. Now, you can imagine that you have all
of these, these parties and all these states and these are basically little clubs. And, uh, there's
a lot of backroom, you know, jocking back and forth and, um, to essentially come up with the, um,
with the right amount of votes to present the candidate. Am I butchering this? I think I am actually,
and maybe I should just stop. But right now, we're just in this primary and the primary, um,
the whole point is to come up with the candidates for each party. There can also be a, uh, uh,
you couldn't have, be an independent candidate. Uh, I don't think we have any, uh, at the
moment. I'm sure there are some, but the whole thing is basically messed up because what you're
seeing is without mainstream media exposure, you're, you're almost irrelevant in the conversation,
even though when it comes down to the votes, that's really all that counts. So when you look at,
well, uh, obviously, uh, there was, uh, very little about Ron Paul in, in Iowa,
although he did get 10% of the vote. Now, let me just explain, I'm just going to just take a
step, man, I wish I had someone to help me with this because it's such a complicated process.
Someone's got a call and be able to do this in three minutes or less to explain how it works.
So all of these states have to make their decisions for their candidates for, for each party.
Some states, I think it's five of them, uh, have an old fashioned way of making this determination.
Instead of just going in and, and, you know, just having a regular vote, you go into the voting
booth, you say, here's the guy that I think should be, um, the nominee for the party that I'm
registered to, which is another whole, uh, part of the equation. You have to be a registered
Republican if you want to vote, uh, to choose, uh, the Republican candidate or Democrat, obviously.
Uh, some of these, uh, some of these states have an old system, which is called the caucus.
And I think really it stems from, you know, way back in the day, uh, when, uh, when people would
sit around in a room and they, uh, you know, they go back and forth and, you know, when things were
much, much smaller and they'd have a specific way of choosing. Uh, and it was basically like, you know,
if, if you're for this guy, you stand in that corner, if you're for that guy, you stand in that corner,
and you have to come up with the majority. If you don't come for the majority, then you could change
your vote. It's, uh, it's a, it's a very convoluted system. But in general, for most of the states,
it's just based on, on pure voting and depending on the size of the state, that is the amount
of delegates that will be voting in the presidential, uh, election. I think, had Jesus, I don't know.
At the end of the day, when you win, you get stolen away from you. So, uh, but it is fascinating
to watch how it's being covered, and particularly was not being covered.
Adam, during Chris and Levittown, first, you need to stop it. The caucuses were a huge success.
10 percent, uh, nobody, somebody completely, utterly and totally ignored by major media.
Intentionally blackout by major media got 10 percent of the vote in the first caucus. That's
phenomenal. I was hoping for 15 percent, the 10 percent is still incredible. Think about that.
With no support from major media whatsoever, we were able to convert online presence is with 10
percent physical vote in the caucuses. That's incredible. That's amazing. I have huge high hopes
for the coming New Hampshire election. I don't think you'll win it, no, of course not. But I think
we're going to build on it, and I think it's going to work good. And you've got to push.
The online presence can be a finicky presence. We have to continue to push to convert the
online presence into a boots on the ground presence. Major media is not going to help us. They're
going to actively fight us. They're going to actively ignore us. They do not want wrong calls
away. They want to blight him out as much as possible. Every time you hear them on the news,
what's more of the things you hear every single time. So, they're going to run as dependent.
They've already put forth the notion you've lost, you have no chance that you're going to
run as dependent. The message is starting to people. The message is that you already have no chance.
So, we have to do with the brute force way. We have to force people online to motivate,
to mobilize, to try to get this guy elected, but see on the way it's going to work.
10 percent in the Iowa caucus, only 300, 56,000 people voted. That's amazing. That's absolutely
incredible. Over 11,000 people came out for those who are on ball in what 10 below zero
weather. I am very, very impressed. I think it's a win. A huge win. And I think you and Ron Paul
make it a big mistake if you push it as such. It really is a win. See you later, Ron Paul.
That's not true. Out of pressure. Oh, man. You're way into it. Yeah. So, you know, so that is what
really a big part of, is really a big part of the problem is that the zeitgeist or or what is
top of mind, what is being discussed is really the only thing that seems to matter. And it's
hard for me. This is what I struggle with every single day. You know, if it's not on television,
does it matter? Does it make a difference? And I think it does. And honestly, I hope that we see
much bigger, much more than even the 10% in Iowa. I have no idea this being Tuesday morning in
the UK. I have no idea how new Hampshire is going. But again, these are just two of the 50 states.
You know, so there's a lot more that's still to come. But what does happen in a lot of these
a lot of these primaries is this is where, you know, the men are separated from the boys, so to speak.
And, you know, candidates that get absolutely no traction at all, a lot of them will drop off some of
them. You know, I mean, look at what's happening right now with the Democratic party, where Obama
just seems to be, you know, pulling ahead like a bad out of hell, just completely on fire as,
you know, hope, I think people are on the Democratic side are putting, you know, a lot of energy
and a lot of hope into this candidate. And it's just phenomenal to watch. And the media takes this
and spins it in a way that, you know, makes it look like Hillary Clinton is, you know, is almost dead
in the water and ready to drop out. I mean, to me, it is convoluted the entire process and
honestly, I really don't know what to think myself anymore. The end of the day,
it's got to come down to the votes. And the only way to, you know, I guess to really get the votes up is
to have a presence. And, you know, stuff like the Ron Paul money bomb gets, gets press, it gets people
interested. People start talking about it. But even here in the UK, you know, if I walk down the street
and I ask 10 people who was Ron Paul, I bet you that 10 out of 10 have no idea who he is.
No, I don't know, it's Mike Turner here, currently in Swindon. He is a go-mem. No,
there's a lot of people with go-mem. Do you have politics? Listen, I'm ready to form a radio
five and whatever, the world service. No mention of Ron Paul whatsoever. Absolutely not the
soul. It's in Barack Obama, this Barack Obama, this, and the, and what is an
idea that he's a who's in X, anyway. First, I thought for the BBC, there's no mention at all
of the, of Dr. Ron Paul. What's going on with the BBC, if it's just mainstream,
very crap, I take it. There's a, or BBC talk, like the red, and fixing things.
Obviously, BBC don't have a BBC, you have to have on the US elections. There are a people
listening out of it, or you're suddenly at the, on the United States side.
Uh, there's just a thought, not the sound of you. Uh, I can't gag. Yeah, fine.
Oh, oh, you, you're this.
Man, I don't know if I can complete a whole show. You know, I want to do some live shows this year.
I really do. I got a look into my streaming setup. You know, I'm kind of tired of the delayed
response. I just want to talk to people live. I feel that I'm much better when I'm in conversation
with someone. Whenever I'm talking to Patricia, whenever I'm talking to someone like John C. Devorac,
it just, it seems to work a lot better for me. So, um, if you're flexible, I'm certainly flexible.
We can, uh, we can figure it out. We can do something with some live streaming and recorded for, uh,
for the podcast. Um, yeah, going on. I think you're right. You know, it's, uh, it is just a
bunch of mainstream crap. You know, the, the news only has so much time that they're willing to
devote to, uh, to talking about stuff. And they only want to talk about stuff that everyone else is talking
about. And, uh, it, uh, I'm really disappointed with just how it all fits together and how it all works.
And I'm becoming a little bit, uh, cynical. I think about the entire process. Uh, so we have to continue
to, uh, to work very hard. Uh, I, as you know, I believe in the, uh, in the constitutional message of
freedom that Ron Paul is, uh, is preaching. So, I will continue to, uh, to support Ron Paul continue
to motivate people to read about his message. Even though it's not on mainstream, you know,
go to Ron Paul 2008.com, read some of the articles, read what he's about, learn about the
constitution. Um, even if you're not an American, you know, it's, uh, it behooves you to understand
what the country originally stood for only, uh, 200 plus years ago. And, uh, definitely the direction
I think we should look at taking again. What's kind of nice to see that, uh, how it's stern is now
catching on to, uh, to Ron Paul. I'm, I'm sure, uh, most of you know who how it's stern is, although he
hasn't been on terrestrial radio for, uh, well, what is it now? Like two years at least,
he's, of course, on satellite radio in the US, check this out. This came across the
whole party. He used to be welding. I don't know if he really wants it. Ron Paul, I'm going to
tell you about this guy, Ron Paul. He's fantastic. The Republicans for some reason, they laughing
them all the time, but meanwhile, he did pretty good in Iowa. This guy is a Republican, and he says,
listen, I become president. I'm taking us out of Iraq. I'm taking us out of everywhere in the
world. He goes, what good has it done us? Being in this, and these fucking Middle Eastern countries.
They all hate it because they hate us. I'm taking us out of all these wars, and we're done. He goes,
and I'm not an isolationist. I'm not afraid to use the military where it's needed. But he said to
sit in here and these extended fucking wars, train the economy and he goes, and if we stay,
or we leave, the same guy damn thing happens. Nothing. So let's leave, and people love this guy
when he talks. He's makes sense. Well, we're, we're the votes. I don't know who this guy is.
I heard him speak. I heard him speak. I heard him speak, and I said, this guy should be
getting more airtime. Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel. On this week's show, the first of the
new year we'll be looking at Uncharted, Drake's fortune on the PlayStation 3. Lego Star Wars,
the complete saga on the Wii, we'll be giving away B movie game for the Wii, and we'll look forward
to some games coming up later in the year. That's all like Gamesweasel.btpodshow.com.
I am a bitch. I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I know what I want, i'm a bitch. I'm a bitch overall
like a prince, I've guessed it down. I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch. I'm a bitch,
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch. I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch. Alright, now unseaved and get some
Some earplugs, I've got a microphone.
Oh.
Excuse me.
That's my butt.
You're commenting on funny.
I don't recall asking for your opinion on my body.
Get your words off of me.
Now.
I'm a bitch.
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch.
I work for your company here.
That's my desk writing the corner.
I make 10,000 less a year.
Then my mail partners.
Is it because of the bra that I wear?
Hey, me groidly now.
Now.
I'm a bitch.
I'm a bitch but now what do I want?
I can't step down.
I'm going to say, I'm going to say, I'm going to say, I'm going to say, I'm
from my toes.
Like a man, like a man, I'm going to let the whole world know.
And I'll be labeled, do you know what my people are scared?
But I've got to speak up anyway, because I don't really care.
It's a woman.
I'm a woman.
I know what I want.
Then I won't let myself get stepped on.
I'm a woman.
Then I'm going to make myself know.
And I've been inviting all the people to share my life.
Bye, lifelong.
Hi, Kristen Kitko.
The bitch song.
Thanks to Sir Jersey Todd for pointing that one out to me.
He actually sent in his email, he said, hey, this could be a great one for a Hillary Clinton.
Oh, like a no man.
I just kind of like the song from The Pod Safety Music Network, of course.
And you'll find links to that in the show notes at DailySourceCode.com
Well,
I'm kind of empty, you know, I'm lacking inspiration today.
All that's going on in the news is frickin' presidential race,
which is just driving me up the wall, driving me nuts.
I want to talk about some other things.
That's some just some general stuff.
Is it just me or is the world spinning three times faster than normal?
Maybe it is just me.
But I'd like to make some changes in 2008,
just in our own little world here.
Let's talk about some other shit.
Let's have some fun.
Let's get creative.
And what I'll do today is I'm going to look into different ways
to doing some live streaming,
so we can take some, well, not live calls,
but we can do some kind of live conversation.
Just not quite sure how I want to do it yet.
There's a number of different technologies available.
Well, let me work on it.
Let me figure it out.
If you have any ideas posted in the comments,
at dailysourcecode.com,
let me know what you think might work.
One thing's for sure.
I'm going to have to announce when I'm going to actually record,
so that folks can hop on and get involved.
And let's just give it a try.
Let's just do some different.
I just really want to do something different.
Something different, for instance,
like rolling out a jersey Todd song,
even though it's not a food bar Friday?
You're on her.
I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out.
Please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give up night.
To the hardest work in law here.
It's jersey time.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You're on it.
What do you say?
Yo, how's it going?
Adam, it's jersey time.
The official musicologist of the Chacha.
So, dude, big man.
AC, dude, dude, dude.
Have I got something for you right now?
It's one of my all time favorite bands.
I'm flipping out that they're on the pot safe music network.
The black crows.
That's right.
The black friggin' crows.
It's time to shake your money,
make your and tell them work or that you love them.
I am thoroughly psyched that they're on the PMN today
because they've got a brand new album coming out in March.
It's called Warp Paint.
I'm really looking forward to it.
It's their first studio album in seven years.
And they posted a track on the pod safe music network.
I'm telling you, the revolution is here.
And this is the black crows with goodbye daughters of the revolution.
Check it out.
The black crows on the DSC can't beat this.
Do you see me are there?
There sure will be me, I got a can come back there.
Ah, the right and the right kid home.
Ah.
If you see me, there's no way they'll be there.
It's all right.
I've got something for them.
Ah.
I can't help but chance I can't
Don't you want from a nifty bed but now
Take it easy, to avoid it, it's next
Because I'm not a summer ever mission
I can't even see your future
I will know you come, God, to kill me
Keep on, I'll run into the gate of the city
Give up now with me, sir, to pity
Don't you want to see the ship go down with me
Where are you?
I can't do it for me now, go to your side
I'll come around midnight to your back door
I'll run into the gate of the city
I'll cross your head
Run you, run into the edge of your age
When the sun goes away, it's gonna snow, your stage
Give me help, leave the guilty group of the shock
And see the ship go down with me
Because I'm not a summer ever mission
I can't even see your future
I will know you come, God, to kill me
Keep on, I'll run into the gate of the city
Give up now with me, sir, to pity
Don't you want to see the ship go down with me
Keep on, I'll run into the gate of the city
When the sun goes away, it's gonna snow, your stage
I'll be around, go to your side
Keep on, I'll run into the gate of the city
Give up now with me, sir, to pity
Don't you want to see the ship go down with me
Keep on, I'll run into the gate of the city
Keep on, I'll be around, go to your side
Chris Robinson, the only guy who has to run around
I'm the shower to actually get wet
Black pros
Goodbye daughters of the revolution
Unbelievable, it's Podsake
Love that
That's right, the revolution clearly
It's well underway
As the music business changes right before your very eyes
The smart guys are doing it
All right everybody
I'm just gonna stop the show right here now
Because I'm empty, I'm done
I have no more energy left
Let's think about some ways we can change this show
For the coming year
I want to keep the conversations going
But I want to talk to more people
I'm tired of speaking to myself in a vacuum
So let me, yeah, give me your ideas
Adam at podshow.com
DailySourceCode.com
Tomorrow I'll be back with another show
Just for you
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Make a statement with Saudi stereo ear buds
Sleep metal housings that reduce vibration
Delivering killer sound from a tiny package
Buy yours at Sony.com slash headphones
Sony earbuds
Where style meets sound