I should be really happy and I just should be bouncing off the walls which of course I am but I'm extremely troubled by fellow charcoalheads.
I'm really concerned about what's going on and somewhere in September is when the war will start involving the United States Iran Israel and Pakistan.
It seems like in a way we're awakening, we're becoming aware of things, things are happening around us and the worldly powers that they are fighting it.
The first time I've been tracking oil prices, you know, this is almost the hobby of mine.
In fact, today being Wednesday, 253 p.m., I saw the oil go down yesterday drastically.
That sounds like 135 dollars a barrel which to me meant something's up.
In low and behold, just as I thought this morning, where it comes that Iran is testing missiles and there's a rumbling in the Gulf.
Of course, oil starts to pop up, it is now at 8.53 a.m. in New York.
Oil is almost up to $2 a barrel.
There's clearly things going on that Iran just never wanted to play game with the dollar currency for oil.
They've threatened to flood the world markets with cheap oil and paste that trading upon the euro.
It seems like the only answer, the only solution is to come up with a reason to go to war and then actually go into it.
Do you feel a repeat if there's a days of who has been in your mind at all with the Iran?
One and two, the disastrous, disastrous decisions that are being made towards fellow men, women, all the majority of them are under 30 years old in Iran.
It must not be.
It's kind of scary, but it's kind of scary.
You're supposed to add $0.25 to the iron.
You know, they've been through this journey for your claim that you're in prison.
You worked for it.
For the attack, I run.
Played this year.
It's talked of a meeting.
It's clear.
Program's folder.
No echo, probably.
You know, all the file on the clock.
Coding is really national rating.
For it's something that ain't completely clear.
He's political up to you.
You don't need one of more to the attack.
For it's day to day was present.
I'm glad he ended his last day in August.
January 2019.
You know, Ronald Reagan and his efforts to bring the ring here.
They won't forget what they'll see.
They didn't finish the discharge.
And it can be pretty good.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I never thought I really would.
Coaching life.
And when you said it, no, maybe I ran in.
From time to time, I think it's true.
But when you told me, no, I think you won't be.
I know it's time for me to go.
Coaching life.
And when I think about it today,
My mind is about it's time to think about it.
And when you said it, no, maybe I ran in.
Coaching life.
No, I think I don't.
You were saying, I've never listened to it anyway.
You said you love for me was disappeared.
Just like the clouds of sunny days.
I want you by.
No, I want you by.
Oh, man, I've always been a fan of these guys.
It's the fire range.
Of course, they are entirely pod save from the pod save music network,
find it at podsafemusic.com.
I want you back kicking off for the triple seven edition of the Charlie.
Hey, everybody, how you doing.
Welcome to the daily source code coming to you.
Once again from the affluent suburb of Surrey known as gulford,
where it's 27 degrees centigrade today,
even though there's no sun shining.
It's a ball me, so you can probably hear the fan that I've got running
to the background because it's going to kind of hot up here in the attic.
And that to start off, I want to say major major thanks to our buddy Ray Raymond,
who has been a charcoal head and certainly elevated to savon status
of the the daily source code for a number of years.
He created that entire opening and I got to tell you, I love that stuff, man.
I love it, particularly how you.
How you basically are mashing me up into something completely new,
a whole new product, if you will.
Excuse me, a whole new show, which of course deserves to open up a daily source code.
And I just wish I had, I love doing that stuff.
I wish I had the time for it, man.
Fantastic.
And he came like that, you know, you make my day.
So Ray, thank you once again.
But spending some time looking around some stuff as usual.
What I did yesterday, for most of, like for hours on end,
I went through all of the voicemail comments on multiple lines
for the past week when I was on vacation.
You can imagine just the volume.
And obviously, you know, I want to listen everything
because there could be that gem could be sitting in there
and I don't want to miss out.
So we'll be listening to a number of you guys calling in today.
Some funny, some sad, some happy, some some glad.
Also, I bumped into a video that I guess I had seen a couple of pieces from me.
I thought I'd pretty much seen every 9, 11 truth video out there
that matters or that seems to have, you know,
some real journalist equality to it.
But that probably don't.
And this is 9, 11 press for truth.
I don't know if you ever seen that one.
It's, you know, it has interviews that were made with the jersey girls,
these four new jersey women, young women who lost their husbands
and one of the lost their son in the twin towers.
And it's a really good, just a fantastic journalistic piece.
And of course, if I remember, I'll put a link in the show notes to it.
But you can Google it 9, 11 press for truth.
It's pretty simple to find this kind of stuff through the tools that we have
at our fingertips, I might add.
And from that, I, even though, of course, I was aware of the 9, 11 timelines.
I'd never really, you know, spent any time looking at it.
And a couple of things dawned on.
I mean, at the original 9, 11 timeline,
which I believe was published as a book as terror timeline,
was done by Paul Thompson.
And this 9, 11 press for truth, you know,
it's a lot about this timeline and how all the pieces were put together.
And it really started to dawn on me.
What is actually going wrong in, in our understanding of what's happening
in worldly events?
And at first, I was probably of the journalism sucks school, mainstream media blows.
And that's not entirely true when you look at this 9, 11 press for truth
because although you don't have the ground swell of the importance
of Britney Spears shaving her head, the words are out there.
And this, you know, basically by using a very simple database structure,
Paul Thompson started off by putting together mainstream news reports.
So that's newspaper.
Oh, online stuff, of course.
But mainly online newspaper stories,
accompanying stories that go with video for news outlets,
like seeing any international and, of course, video clips.
And you really get a whole different picture that is pieced together
or what happened, of course.
We pretty much have a good understanding of it at this point.
At least we know that it's completely different from what was portrayed
in the 9, 11 Commission report.
And I'm thinking, you know, so this means that the mainstream is getting the news out
there, but it's actually one step above the journalists.
Okay.
It's probably a couple more steps above it if you really think about it.
And I've witnessed this myself when working for Viacom,
indirectly, of course, for MTV Network.
I'm sorry, even one level below that.
MTV, you see how all those levels, how they're important and how
the, and it's obvious, by the way.
And a lot of it is profit driven.
It has nothing to do with patriotism or lack of patriotism.
It's what a, what a company does.
A company is there to protect itself from losing.
So, and of course, then, you know, that comes from really, really top levels
where, you know, advertisers pull out and all kinds of crap happens.
So that's why we don't get that groundswell of news.
I said, you know, when Lindsey Lowhand gets busted, booze
and up and drive around town again.
And that's, that gets all the attention because it's safe.
It's completely safe.
That's why it gets propagated so far and wide.
But there are a number of, let's just call them massive points of light
that are out there reporting the, the truth reporting things
that may not be popular with the typical news desk and their editors
out there that are letting it go through.
And I'm seeing it sometimes even in letters to the editor.
That seems to be a very popular pace or certainly not on the front page.
It's always buried down a little bit deeper.
And if you can really start to pull all these things together,
then, you know, you get a real true story.
That also, of course, is the way that the 911 truth movement
has started and I see it moving globally.
I really can feel the movement on this.
And we just have to keep copying pasting.
Copy, paste, copy, paste.
Get the word out.
Let people know.
And please send messages to your representatives.
It actually does work.
And this 911 press for truth even shows you how it works.
When the, the presidential daily briefing had to be,
the classified and released.
It was because of severe pressure from the public writing their senators
in the congressmen or, you know,
it might be your minister of parliament or your prime minister.
Or your queen or your king.
You've got to keep you got to keep the pressure up because the one thing
these guys and they're not, they're not really the ones who are the bad guys.
They're just robots in between.
You know, we're too lazy or we decided a long time ago that we want someone else
to do our dirty work for us, basically run shit.
So they do whatever they're told.
And if we're not telling them, well, someone else is clearly telling them.
So you just gotta keep the word out there and gotta keep telling your representatives.
It is not futile whatsoever.
I know sometimes it gets tiring and you just want to have a happy little life
for the white-picked fence and a ta-da-da-da-da-da-da.
I'll have to work the apron.
But life just ain't like that anymore now is it.
Hey Adam, this is David.
Long time listener calling from the Brooklyn Keys Express way
and downtown Brooklyn.
You're in traffic.
Getting all bummed out, burning my fossil.
You're listening to you talk about the world bank
and the big conspiracy.
You're bumming me out, man.
No blue pill.
No red pill.
I want the shiny happy yellow pill, man.
I want to live like an ostrich with my head in the ground and be happy.
I tried to yellow pill once.
It's overrated.
Come on.
What happened to the good old days?
What happened when you were living in Amsterdam still
when the show first started and the simple shows
that you'd put your mic to the door and listen to you
and even sleep to the arrow.
I missed the simple days.
I missed the strategy.
Yeah, baby dude.
My brother.
I missed it too.
I really, really do.
I'm telling you.
But I feel so much lighter and so much better.
Now that I've awakened and I've seen what is actually going on.
I think I found something to do.
Of course, I got three jobs.
I got plenty of work.
But really a passion, something I really want to work on.
You'll feel great, man.
You just got to kind of get through it.
You can see everything.
Then even the news becomes great because you hear the keywords.
You have the information.
And there's action you can take.
You can do something with everything that's bothering you.
And we'll get back there, my brother.
We will.
And by the way, I had a great week off.
Yeah.
I followed the news.
But I had a great week off.
You can shut it off.
Once you're awake, it's easy to shut it off.
I'm not really complaining.
I do like the show.
I listen every day.
But man, the world's bombing me out.
Dude.
Oh.
I got to go home and go ride my motorcycle.
Hell yeah.
And some fossil fuel.
It'd be.
Burn it with some fog.
Yeah.
He's out.
All right, man.
Yeah.
They work for me.
Hell yeah.
You know what they do.
That's right.
We just got to remind him from time to time.
That really, that really will work.
I'm convinced of that.
And I go ahead and burn some fossil fuel, man.
Don't worry about it.
Let me check oil for you right now.
Oh, boy.
Something's going on.
I love it when this happens.
Let's see.
Only a couple weeks ago, oil was at $146.
It is currently.
And today is Wednesday, the 23rd of July, 2008.
It is currently down $220.
It is at $126.
It's at $122.
It's at $840 AM.
Yeah.
Eastern time.
That's $20 in the span of less than a week.
$20.
Only in in four or five trading days.
Look at this.
Now, what does that mean?
First of all, it means you should go ahead and burn some damn fossil fuel, my friend.
Go ahead.
Because clearly, there's no more supply and demand issue.
That seems to be dwindling pretty quickly.
We'll talk later about what that could actually mean.
I don't want to bum you out while you're thinking about hopping on your hog and going for a ride.
Although, don't tell me you might have a rice burner.
Yeah.
I have them questions.
Thank you.
First question.
I think you might possibly have been on something when you were talking about the British possibly
taking too much alcohol and things like that.
The report just came out last night.
800,000 cases of alcohol related illnesses in hospitals.
In hospitals.
Yeah.
And I think that was in the past year.
That's almost a million people in hospitals.
Only 60 million here.
And that you know a lot of them just aren't going to drink, although you don't know.
But you think really old and really young, like babies.
800,000.
Yeah.
That's pretty concerning.
I'd say Chris.
That's okay.
It's just a blue pill, man.
You can take the red one.
And then you can take a blue one whenever you want.
One, you got to take the red first though.
You got to wake it up.
You got to stop numbering yourself.
Okay.
Look at me.
I'm totally self-medicated.
Anywho, I'm called a number of my phone telling them,
I'm quite a big secret.
I can't remember who it was.
Some kind of thing I saw in my phone book.
It wasn't you who I called was it.
No.
If it was, but in the ringback, you know my,
well, you know my email address.
Yeah.
It's the same email I'm at.
Okay.
That's a fuck, that's hope it wasn't.
Skype.
And a phone together will mix it alcohol.
I do not go.
Do not get this any Skype phone.
Do not drink alcohol.
This is a good sign.
The sign, good suggestion.
Anyway, I don't see a PSO at the SD.
They're supposed to go and not say if you're a fucker.
What do you think you're a fucker?
That is a...
I'm lucky.
All right.
I mean, no.
I'm drunk.
Yeah.
Yes.
Good night.
There's some about people when they get plastered
calling me up, I like.
You check this guy out.
Hey, Mr. Curry.
Oh.
Yeah.
This is Jason the truck driver.
Hey, man.
I'm sitting in Oklahoma right now.
Backbone of America, my friend.
The truck drivers.
And dude, I love the daily source code.
Man.
From those first time I heard it, it's been awesome.
That's coming for you, my friend.
That's a huge compliment.
I really appreciate it.
You've been traveling around the great states of America.
And you have a lot of choice of stuff you can listen to.
So I take that as a as a big one.
Your audio quality is what got me.
I mean, although you're on a Mac now again.
And you should switch back to the bio or you should donate the bio to me actually.
Yeah, man.
I do another laptop to one I have.
Did he just built?
Do I have to solder the power back?
The power cable back onto the board.
Because I accidentally ripped it out of the machine.
I hate it when it happens.
Yeah.
That is kind of the cool thing about that.
Magnetic plug.
That shit doesn't happen to me anymore.
And believe me, it's not only happened to me.
My daughter is the champion of tripping over laptop wires.
I'm 36.
I'm white.
And not gay.
I'm on the straight.
Other not homophobic.
Right out.
And.
And you've got men.
I'm gay right.
Fucking.
Oh, bro.
Can you probably figure that out right now?
I feel so much a part of your family.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I love it.
I got a ping from Yon Poletti said, you know, dude, you were on vacation.
Then we didn't hear anything on Friday.
It was the deal when I said to myself,
Well, crap.
That's right.
Yon still has a hit test.
Ready for me.
13.
I'm proud of your casting.
We're hungry.
This is the hit test.
Yon Poletti.
Hey, Adam.
How are you doing?
I'm good man.
I'm ready for it.
You see this number 130.
You're going to start right away with intro number one.
All right.
Rock.
What?
It's not going to be no one.
These obscure years that I know nothing about.
Is it?
Okay.
I'm have to give up on that one.
Number two.
I know this one.
I know this one from my Z100 days.
It's a Jodie Wattley.
I'm looking for a new log.
Unmistachable.
And number three.
Yeah.
Telling low.
Easy.
Wild thing.
What is that like 89 or something?
It must be 87 or 88.
Yeah, 87 or 88.
I think.
That's it.
And this week's answers are all from.
98.
Oh, no.
Just.
What the hell is this?
It's a number one.
Wets, wets, wets, wets.
I never looked at those guys.
Not never got into wet wet wet wet wet.
Well, this won't be included on the soundtrack to my life.
I can't sing along with wet wet wet.
Sweets are in.
Resents number one.
Oh.
There we go.
Resents number two.
Jodie Wattley.
Hell yeah.
Let me use the pump this out over New York City.
Real love.
Got to have me.
But it was looking for new love.
Jodie Wattley.
Former member of Shawlamar.
Real love is on number two.
Plus.
And this is answering number three.
Also from 1989.
Wild thing.
Yes.
It's so long.
Working.
Oh, we.
Not five.
Oh, my money.
So on the weekend comes.
I go get live.
We're not honey.
Wild thing.
Answer number three.
Don't look.
And that's it for hit this number 130.
So at him, how did you do this week?
Well, I thought I did better.
But I did three out of possible six.
You are because I got Jodie Wattley's title.
That's better.
You hit this.
That's me.
If you don't come, it's the place to find the answers to this hit this.
And any older hit this as well.
And also to find the links to iTunes.
So you can find.
Bye.
Sorry.
All the tracks featured in the hit this online.
Alrighty.
And thank you for playing.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I'll be back for another hit this.
So until then take care.
Have fun.
And try to think with your heart.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you, man.
Another Dutch guy who just does a fabulous job on putting stuff together for the Charlie
and of course much appreciated.
Y'all pull out there with hit test number 130.
Check it out at hittest.mevio.com.
More awakening stories coming in through the voicemail lines.
Which you can find in the show notes at dailysourceco.com.
More of course crossposted at curie.com.
Hey Adam.
This is Chris and Philadelphia.
I have a comment on FOIA.
It's one of the things that you're opinion on something I've been dealing with.
I feel like a bit of a hypocrite.
You know, I really care about the environment.
I don't want to waste.
You know, I turn off my lights when I can.
I bring bags to the grocery store.
And yet when I go to work, I take.
You know, I screen print logos on to pieces of plastic that come from China.
And we ship them off.
And we import, you know, watches.
And ship from China and all this mess.
And it's reading that article about China in Africa on the drop.
It gets me worried.
Like how can I, you know, go home on one day.
Like I'm running a bike to work and take public transit.
And then go to work.
And then, you know, fuck around with all this acrylic.
Oh, man.
All right.
Hold on a second.
First of all, look, you're, you're just getting by, man.
You got a job.
You got to do it.
Do what you got to do.
And at least you're not chained to the machines yet, right?
Yet.
And, and, and, and, and, and, you know,
there's people just like you in China.
And in Iran.
And in Australia.
And we have a lot of things in common.
And yeah, we're.
Yeah, we're.
We certainly may not be doing the best at working within the environment.
And it, that is mother earth, but get on your bike, man.
That's not just good for her.
It's good for you as well.
But it doesn't mean that you're a hypocrite.
You don't want, look, we've been, we've been thrown shit into the earth's atmosphere.
Ever since we could walk up right.
And probably pooping away with CO2 before then.
Which, by the way, is apparently the biggest source of CO2 is cowfarts.
And of course, it's been a lot of lie and going on.
And the biggest part of feeling hypocritical is between your ears.
And you can change that at any moment.
You can change and feel happy whenever you want to.
Think about it.
There's, there's no one poking you with anything.
There's no physical weight on your shoulders.
There, you know, there's, there's nothing physically happening in your physical world.
That you can see touch, feel, taste, or hear.
That is actually making you unhappy.
It's all between your ears.
You can change that.
Just think.
I'm going to be happy now.
And let everything else drop away.
See, you can do it.
Just think of something happy.
And whenever you want to feel happy, you think of that.
Maybe it's a moment with your kid, a moment with your wife or significant partner.
You know, maybe it's something you accomplished.
Let it make you feel happy.
And don't worry about it.
We're going to work this out.
We just got to remove some of the evil shit at the top of the pyramid.
And we do that by not being depressed and just refusing to be enslaved.
No matter what happens because we can't change this.
Oh crap.
That wasn't a line from Obama.
So instead of just talking about it, do it.
You know, if you feel shitty about what's going on,
then take charge with your personal actions.
But don't forget to let them know.
They work for us.
And have you ever felt that, you know, what you're doing to things that seem to be
Dude, every single day of my life, are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
This show, which I've got to skate around, you know, the commercial aspect of it.
It's totally in conflict with my commercial interest.
I'm like, Jacko and Hyde, every single day.
Nothing.
But that's life.
That is life.
MTV, Jacko and Hyde.
You know, we suck up to the record companies on air.
And we slam them off air because we weren't allowed to do it.
Couldn't even make a freaking joke.
Contradictory.
We're trying to get the word out.
But I'm not using anything.
But I love, I love your opinion.
I had a deal with self-apocracy.
You know, because I'm, I'm struggle.
You know, I'm like, should I just quit the job?
I don't know what I'm doing.
No, no, no.
But anyway, man, good show, keep up the good work.
And daily source code.
Hey, it comes out on some day.
There needs to change, you know, just roll with what you got.
Wait, we don't mind the lapses.
Quality over quantity.
I'd be.
Thanks, man.
I appreciate that that seems to be pretty much the consensus, by the way.
A lot of people respond to that through a voicemail and email.
A like and also on the drop drop.au slash daily source code.
Saying, it, you know, just call it daily source code.
We don't care.
It's like our little inside joke.
It's not daily.
Okay, get it.
So, yeah, man.
I absolutely, I feel like that.
Of course I do.
That is the constant struggle.
And if you add to that, that there used to be severe ridicule.
And there's still is, of course.
You know, if you're a truth or if you wear a tinfoil hat, or if you have your wallet
in a fairer day cage, or if you even mentioned that you think you actually might believe
that you are full stuff could actually be true.
All of that stuff?
Of course it's in total conflict.
But that's okay, because you can also feel like this.
Hey, Adam, there's a parent from a green pod.
I'm feeling that the awakening.
Let's do it.
Let's get all over it.
Okay, I think there's a new media revolution awake in the people.
And we're in a circle.
And the time when we're all alone.
And the time when the shine goes to the sun.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh I, oh, oh, oh, on, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh,
We're not falling over right,
We're the leaders here,
Fromalu to the whole of your world,
Where have you my happiness?
Strnd fountain is a bad one.
I am free, you're hiding,
Don't I die by your side,
Just like yesterday,
You're my fundamental warrior.
We don't forget, oh, now we're going in
Now, now, now, now, now
We're going in
I hope we live
Of whom I end the love every single other
Make me at the limit, give me a medal
My heart feel hot, pull me loose my heart
And just toss it over and be with you when it's time
It's time to fly
Say my love
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, oh, you know the world that she for a reason don't you?
You can probably relate now.
Now you listen to it.
We'll be full again.
Brought to you by Van Halen on daily source code.
Episode number 7 7 7.
Oh man.
Fantastic track.
That is.
Hey, got a lot more calls to get through today on today's episode, including from a fellow
chucklehead sales guy, you.
Hello there, Adam.
Sales guy, you've determined he's been a long time.
Amazing thing happened today.
I'd rise up to the gas station to fill the car up with diesel.
Diesel right now.
You're a 50-meter.
That's what it calls to.
So I've filled up the gas station lot of money and I'm aggravated about it.
I walk in to the gas register.
You know, give the guy my credit card.
You know, it's about bitchening complaining to him.
Yeah, as one does.
Just morning.
You know, I'm Dutch.
So with a morning complaining.
Yeah, true.
You know, the Dutch are like, right?
Yeah.
Behind me, there are still a few other people waiting.
One guy starts bitchening.
He also starts complaining.
Well, it's ridiculous.
It's way overpriced.
Stupid.
You know, I'm going to try to get my bike and go to work with it.
I don't want to drive my car anymore.
I start feeling really bad for the guy behind the register.
It's nothing you can do about it, right?
You know what he did?
He asked me to say, hey, people, nothing I can do about it.
And they will go up more.
And we just received words from corporate adolescents that we have to increase pricing.
So basically, over the next couple of weeks.
And you know, for us all free ice creams to make up for the rising gas prices.
You know what?
I kind of sell for it.
So here's a tip tool that the gas station is out there.
Also free ice cream.
People of it.
We're losing day work for us.
Ice cream.
Time's the correct.
Oh, boy.
Five times.
Nah, ice cream.
It makes you feel good when your tank costs too much to fill up.
You know, that's kind of interesting.
You say that sales guy, you because here in the UK,
we now have a minor price war going on.
Now that the price of oil has dropped by $20 since we checked the last.
Let me just see how we're doing right now.
Hold on.
Let's see.
Last time we checked it was 12622 actual retail price.
Now of 12671.
Okay.
So when I'm just a little bit.
But it still means down 20 bucks from, you know, less than a week ago.
That's just pretty amazing when you think about it.
So in the UK, there's a little bit of a price war going on amongst the.
The grocery store stores here like Asda and Tesco.
They usually have a gas station on premises.
And so they're not lowering by five to six pence a liter.
Excuse me.
So, well, they're calling it a price war.
But they should really be dropping into quite a bit.
And, you know, I'm talking like significant penses.
If the price now stays down this low.
And you should see that same happening all across the world.
If not, well, that would be a big flag right there.
But I'm thinking something else personally.
Now think about the timing of all this.
So everyone's pretty much on vacation now.
Or a lot of the West is on vacation.
By the way, all of your tickets, all your travel.
It was all booked on the high oil prices.
Now, if the theory is correct.
And I'm talking about multiple theories here.
But kind of the one I'm shaping in my head.
But it certainly includes the most recent book I read on vacation.
Shocked doctrine by Naomi Klein.
If the shock theory holds true, then basically we were shocked.
Right?
So we were, in fact, you read it everywhere in the newspapers with the oil shock.
So we're shocked by 146 dollars of barrel of crude oil.
Now it's dropping down significantly.
Usually, if the theory is correct,
this is the moment when shit starts to get slid in.
Like the removal of double jeopardy.
And other interesting things.
And that's kind of the way advertising works too.
First, you got to scare someone into saying,
let's see, if you don't drink this beer, you'll never get laid.
And then you give them the information.
And make them feel good.
If you don't use the Zid cream, you'll never get laid.
And then you give them the information.
Isn't that, what does David Ike say?
It's a problem conflict resolution.
So we should be seeing some interesting things happening.
And I want all chuckle heads to be on high alert now.
Because now is the not the time to kick back and say,
oh, finally, you know, things are getting better.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
If the theory is correct, we'll test this within the next six weeks.
We're going to see something happen.
Something will change.
Some walls will be introduced.
We may even have a double whammy.
Have another to shock it us.
And I got to thought about that, which we'll talk about in a little bit.
Yeah, I got plenty of thoughts these days.
This one, this two, contact contact.
Contact.
Yeah, the movie with Joey Foster was coming.
That's what I was talking about there.
This is going back to 775.
A lot of people misconstrued me explaining the new brew theory with,
with me believing in all of it.
I'm not saying I don't.
But I'm certainly not saying I do entirely.
Yeah.
So I'm not, well, here we go.
Thanks.
You're talking about a UFO.
Yes.
You're talking about here, calling from sunny Southern Germany about 775.
Good job.
Adam, you're a little concerned.
I've been with you since 2004.
Yeah, we've been together a long time, my friend.
Uh, we've been through red tills and rabbit holes and scrunching and folding.
We've been through banks and teagulls and now different types of looking at oil,
eating oil, eating babies, you name it.
I've been on board.
I'm on the bus taking the red tills, drinking the coolade.
But UFOs.
Yeah.
Me, the wacky weed is providing you with a little too much research room up there
in the old nagging.
Yeah, that would be the desired effect, Chris.
Anyhow, it's funny.
I just saw Indiana Jones, the latest movie wasn't that great.
And then two are exploding the whole UFOs thing.
And, uh, don't even have a query.
Anyways, good luck on your walkabout out there in research land in the Controversial
City world.
I'm still in board.
But definitely looking for the escape exits in case anyone moment.
The ejectum.
You're wacky weed gets a little too strong.
Uh, wish you well.
Nice air.
Hope you win.
They win for us.
They work for us.
Hell yeah.
And, uh, cheers.
No, man.
I'm not wacky.
I'm just a free thinker.
Um.
Actually, Johnson and Warwick had a theory about that on the most recent no agenda.
I think, uh, so number 39.
Check it out no agenda.neveo.com.
He said, he thought that this could easily be.
And, and his theory's not bad, by the way.
This could easily be a whole PR campaign for a movie.
These UFOs.
CNN, Larry Kings, been on it all week for two weeks now almost.
Um, of course, we just had, uh, so we had Indiana Jones.
Uh, we had the expiles coming out.
So it could also easily be that this is being propagated right now.
Although, if you think about all the sightings, including the Yorkshire police.
I believe it was the Yorkshire police.
Um, I don't know.
Maybe it feeds off of each other.
I don't know.
But at the end of the day, my friend.
Look around you.
And I don't mean in front of you.
Look up and tell me that in all that space.
They're in room for some other people.
Hey, I don't know if this is in here.
No.
First time call us.
I know.
With our whole word for the new D and the SC.
Okay.
And that word is demonstrative.
Uh-huh.
All right.
Just a quick look on the, uh, dictionary.com.
And, uh, definition for you serving two demonstrates.
Extraordinary three.
Or it is translated three.
You are demonstrative.
Your survival.
Our demonstrative.
Is showing us how to live on my.
That's, yeah.
So, uh, that's my little contribution.
And, uh, I hope that helps.
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
Uh, just one of the many comments.
I told you earlier of people, uh, looking to help me replace the daily and daily source code since it just ain't going to be that way.
And for a number of reasons, not just because of, uh, my, my real jobs.
Uh-huh.
Uh, but also because of, um, you know, it takes time to produce.
It's really just a time factor.
And, and not just a time of, I got to think about stuff too.
You know, I just don't, I got to have the time to think and digest and do research.
And every single waking hour is taken out by this show.
Every, every other piece, every minute, every second that, uh, that I'm not doing something else.
I'm doing this.
But demonstrative, uh, it doesn't quite roll off the tongue very well.
Does it?
Adam, this is a little from Westport again.
Um, I get cut off.
I think it out with ECS4.
ECS4 disinformation.
Okay.
The back.
I'm Paul is not a senator.
He's a congressman.
Yeah. That's just a mistake.
Okay.
Uh, you can call the disinformation, but that implies that I'm trying to say something that is incorrect on purpose.
So, me, a culpa.
The congressman from Texas, he does not get on the floor of the Senate and apply not any topic.
Right.
But did you hear what he said?
I think it was the actual content of his message that I played on the show that was important.
So, sorry about that.
He gets on the floor of the house.
Yeah.
Get edition.
The fact that Iran is even talking about flirting the market with, uh, low parties or
a denomulating in euros.
Frankly, is a canard because there's an exchange rate that is a canard as in a duck.
It floats between the dollar and the euros.
And as a result, the price will reach equilibrium regardless of what the currency is.
Oh, my friend.
Oh, you're missing the point there.
No, no, no.
If they start selling their oil in euros, I said trading.
But if they start selling it in euros, the dollar will be not unnecessary.
Then all of a sudden, there wasn't going to be looking to unload their dollars and buy euros.
You can't tell me that doesn't make sense.
That's the problem.
It's not just the cheapness of it.
Of course, that's equilibrium.
In fact, the equilibrium seems to be unequal on the US side.
But yes, there's equilibrium.
And everything's related.
You know, uh, you're the European Central banks.
They pop up from 4% to 425 on their interest rate, controlling the market.
Book dollar has to go up.
No way, man.
Dollar has to go down.
But then oil goes down.
Dollar goes up.
It's all related.
It's all, it's all a part of the same system.
But it's about the euro price, the pricing and euros.
That's what it's about.
If people have to buy it with euros, then there's not going to be a need for the dollar.
That would kill the dollar.
That's the point.
Because you have to look at all economic transactions in terms of a basket of what different
currencies and different commodities trade at against each other.
So enjoy your vacation.
When they get back one chip, give a call.
And we can talk about this.
Um, I have a way to keep operating officer for an investment management firm in New York.
And I had to do a lot of stuff at 30 some odd years.
So we can talk.
All right.
And I hope you have a good vacation.
I'm in.
Hey, listen, that's cool.
I really appreciate that.
So taking when I just said, would you mind calling back in and tell me if I'm totally nuts?
Because when you get into baskets and all that stuff, you know, it's like, oh, okay.
Uh, then all of a sudden, I mean, I'm in CNBC land and my eyes start to glaze over.
But I have a suspicious feeling that this is pretty much right.
If it's sold in euros, which means other countries who are buying oil, including the United States,
will have to get euros.
So you buy euros.
There becomes a supply and demand.
You don't need the dollars.
Just drop them.
The dollar drops in price.
And it's all over.
The world worth three.
It's arm again.
Or you could take your hard earned euros and go to e-music.com.
I actually want to do this endorsement for them after Van Hayland.
We won't get fooled again.
But I overlooked it.
So I apologize.
You can get 33 songs.
Free.
Okay.
As in as in free beer.
All you got to do is you got to go sign up and get your 30 songs.
And if you don't like it, if it's not working for you, then just unsubscribe.
It's okay.
I'm out.
Won't cost you a penny.
You keep the 33 MP3s.
Go to e-music.com slash daily source code for your 33 MP3s.
E-music.com slash daily source code.
Hey, Adam, what's up?
What's up?
This is Eric from Portland.
Just going in.
I saw this link.
Freak me out, man.
Faceless people.
Yeah.
We're open.
So that too.
Yeah.
Freak?
Yes.
They were for us.
They sure do.
Yeah.
This is a great campaign.
This is the Lotus Car Manufacturing Company.
And they've got this really, really scary looking kind of like plastic masks that
these people put on.
It's like a buzz marketing campaign.
And I heard about it.
And I immediately was thinking,
the UFOs aren't sitting there.
The aliens aren't there at Wimbledon.
But you go to it's facelesspeople.com.
I think is the website address.
Pretty cool.
Yeah.
But the campaign is great.
Hey, Adam.
Can't pick up on the air.
Thank you.
You know what I'm thinking about the D&DFC.
And I was thinking, you might want to just make it the Delta source code.
Delta.
That being of course an aviation term.
And it represents change.
That's medically, I guess.
And we've managed to change the minds of a lot of people.
My self included.
And also you've changed your format over the years.
You haven't been afraid to experiment a little bit.
So I'm with the Delta source code.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Tell when's back out to my friend.
I don't know.
I'm thinking maybe the D just stands for whatever you damn well decide.
Hey, Adam.
A gorephobic mic here.
A gorephobic mic.
I was listening to the past few DSCs and no agendas.
It appears that you're going down the old camera foil halfway.
Yeah.
I know you said it just theories.
And you know, you're just doing your research.
But it appears that you aren't really looking at any of the sources that refuse these theories.
Yeah.
Go on.
Hold on a second.
Yeah.
I am looking at the sources that refuse the theories.
I look at them all the time.
Are you kidding me?
I don't report on them.
You know, I come up with what I think is the story.
Yeah.
And I'm out of journalism.
I'm a disc jockey.
I'm a VJ.
That's the lowest drug on the show business ladder.
So, you know, I'm just a guy who's just passing on what he thinks is right.
I'm doing my own translation.
I'm aggregating information.
And people send me lots of stuff.
I have to say though, most of the stuff that is the anti conspiracy stuff.
It's just not as entertaining.
So I have a humble request.
Try to spend equal notes of code.
I'm not going to spend equal notes.
Because there's not equal amounts of anti conspiracy stuff out there.
It's all the conspiracy stuff.
I'd be looking forever and coming up with no results.
I'm on pro and anti conspiracy website.
I'll just even, you know, quarter of the time looking at what the skeptics have to say.
And I'll be happy.
I'm just asking you to apply a little reason and critical thinking to, you know, determine the validity of the series.
I suggest skeptic.com, skeptoid.com, you know, quackwatch.org, skeptic dictionary stuff like that.
These guys use logic and critical thinking to find a supported conclusion.
Not the justification of a preconceived conclusion.
And that's, I think, is the real bread pill.
So give it that a shot.
Okay.
Well, they work for us.
Yeah, they do.
All right.
But, you know, I don't know much about you, my friend.
So you got to tell us a bit more.
You got to point us to some actual stories.
You know, don't just say you should be looking at both sides of the story.
Because that's like knock talk, okay.
That's Mr. Smith talking.
Does it show me some?
And by the way, those anti conspiracy sites, they don't have any cool videos.
That's not your bummer.
Yeah, that's just words.
Show me some videos.
Show me something that is proof of the 21st century, like edited video.
I love that.
That's the real truth.
But, you know, point to some mainstream stories.
Don't just give me some scientific evidence.
Point to other reporting.
That's what I'm liking so much about this stuff.
Is it a pointing out reporting from mainstream news media?
Remashing that into a story, which, hell, you know, it's certainly better than
veging out and zoning out to desperate house wise.
Hey, Adam.
Yeah.
The monetary scientist.
Actually, I'll get to the monetary scientist in a moment.
I wanted to say that I had looked at a couple other conspiracies.
And actually, not so much conspiracies.
But, uh, refute this for me.
The codex elementarious.
I'm just going to run through a couple things because I think they're going to start heating up.
And it's going to be really important to look at these.
The codex elementarious is literally the food law.
We've talked about it before.
And I found, uh, was this Health FreedomUSA.org, which you're probably familiar with, has actually
the summarized, some of the codex elementarious summarized in seven points.
And, uh, to the points are starting to 62 by the UN imposed by World Trade Organization sanctions.
Uh, number two, nutrients are toxins is junk science.
Number three, not consumer protection.
That's propaganda.
Number four, codex, serious threat to health and health freedom.
And, uh, five serves economic interests of sickness industries through the World Trade Organization and
Napoleonic Code.
This is a big one because it's the pharmaceutical companies who I believe are a part of the big,
big problem.
We got going on or the one that's coming.
Uh, all the way down number seven, your action is needed now.
So I'll put a link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
I want you to take a look at that because there's no way I can explain exactly what this is other than,
uh, the government of the world wants to determine what you put in your body and what you eat.
By literally outlying certain types of food, certain types of nutrients.
Uh, they've already done it with tomatoes.
We talked about it, uh, with tomatoes.
Now there's a code for what a tomato can look like.
What it's, you know, the four kinds of a tomato.
And now they're going to do that with the, what is it now?
There's a new health care with the jalapeno peppers that have made, you know, one jalapeno pepper,
made 1200 people sick and, uh, it's so it's just done there from the same.
I think it was Mexico again.
Uh, which is probably in American corporation.
Um, and now another form of, uh, what is it, uh,
you know, the chicken stuff, Salmanella, Salmanella.
Now, the first on tomatoes, now Salmanella found on jalapeno peppers.
You know, this could be part of a shock, but all I know is that, you know,
we had that big scare with the tomatoes in the US,
not even putting them on our, on our American hamburgers.
And also, and there's rules about what a tomato can look like.
Uh, I'm just saying.
Uh, let me see what else that I have.
Oh, yeah, talking about the big, uh,
the big pharmaceuticals.
Here's a cool one.
Have you heard about this yet?
The New York Times reports that the American Academy of Pediatrics
has issued new guidelines this week to, quote,
aggressively screen and Medicaid for high cholesterol in children.
Yeah, now you're talking.
Let's not, let's not, let's not, uh,
try and feed our kids healthy food.
Let's, uh, feed them crap and put them on cholesterol, uh,
medicine statements.
Uh, boy.
Do some research on this and please whatever you do.
Don't put your kids on cholesterol medicine.
That's nuts.
It's absolutely nuts.
You got to feed them healthy food and healthy food.
I'm pretty much convinced.
Doesn't come from the grocery store anymore.
And then my favorite.
This is my absolute favorite in the past two weeks.
Not one but two companies.
Um, in San Diego and the other one.
I'm, I know West Coast.
Have claimed that they have an effective
vaccine against the dreaded avian flu.
H five and one bird flu virus, which, of course,
will be the root of the pandemic.
Which is going to kill us all.
We've been, this has been building for a number of years.
Now we've had SARS and, you know,
and of course, it's all based on,
and you really need to look this one up.
Uh, it's based on, um,
what happened in 19.
Uh, was it 18, I believe?
Uh, no, 19 13.
Just before a world war one, um,
they sent, uh,
American soldiers over to Europe and they
inoculated them.
And, uh, when those guys got over there,
they said they had a virus in their, uh, in their body.
And by the way, uh,
uh, the anti-dote for virus is actually part of the virus.
You got to have the virus, you know,
you've seen that in movies, right?
You've got to have the virus or patient zero's, uh,
DNA in order to create the antidote.
So, first of all,
there's two companies who say they've got the,
an enoculation for this means that they've created
the human to human version of avian bird flu.
That's the only way I can look at it, you know,
from my limited scientific knowledge.
So, um, if you've never heard of the Spanish flu,
this is what happened in, uh, in the early 1900s.
So, they sent all these GIs over there.
Now, when you have this, when you have a virus in your body,
you know, you've got a lot of viruses.
It doesn't actually activate unless A,
you're in reasonably poor health,
like, uh, you're eating shit from the supermarket,
and you're full of stress,
like, uh, you can't afford to fill up your car.
That's when viruses start to, uh,
start to live in the body.
So, if you were, if these GIs were
inoculated with, uh, some horrible virus,
and God knows, well, you can look it up
there's lots of theories about where they purposely injected
with some shit or not.
You know, you, you, you put them on some ships,
uh, you know, food is probably minimal, uh,
in quality.
Are they stressed?
Let me think going off to war?
Yeah, I think they were stressed.
So, it was, I think was like 40 million people died
of the Spanish flu.
40 million people.
And these statistics can be found in large
pharmaceuticals and you'll reports
with their product pipeline saying, hey, you know,
we're getting some shit ready for the A,
and flu, of course, you've heard of Tamiflu,
which, uh, is now no longer considered to be valid
for this horrible strain of the H5 and 1 virus.
But these two other companies,
this is like $100 million on order
by the US government.
They've reserved $3.9 billion to stockpile
a vaccine for a disease,
which does not exist as far as we know,
unless, of course, they've built it in the lab,
which so far is only in 10 years,
is only killed 200 people.
And you have 100,000 percent,
100,000 times more chance of being struck
by lightning in your bed.
So, what is up with this?
Is it possible, maybe,
that now that the lever has been pulled back
on oil that we're going to get scared by something else,
maybe terror doesn't do it for us anymore?
Is that possible?
Maybe, um, it's time to, uh,
bring that back into the fold.
Two things I'd like to say.
Keep your eyes open, keep your ears open,
and don't let anyone stick a needle in you.
Or any reason.
Hey, Adam, this is the monetary scientist.
Um, Jason didn't hear indie Mac,
the second largest bank failure ever in US history,
has been on Friday.
Yeah, it's not like we haven't talked about this,
that, uh, you know,
when, when, when, when they,
when the financial sector was saying,
oh, you know, we're getting over this,
you know, we were talking about maybe
second or third inning.
And I think we're not even half way there yet.
And so I bet a lot of the DSC listeners
are wondering, you know,
is my money safe in various banks or whatnot.
Yeah, let me, uh,
let me just, for people who may be new to this conversation.
Um, so this is really almost
at the bottom floor of the entire credit crisis.
So here you have two companies,
Freddie May, Freddie Mac,
and he may Freddie, Freddie, Freddie,
and he may Freddie,
Freddie May, John Boy and Mary Ellen.
And, um, they, uh, these are banks,
commercial banks.
And they hold about six,
trillion dollars worth of mortgages,
which, of course, are to being defaulted on,
and, you know, people can't afford it anymore.
And, and they also, you know, took that debt,
and they, they've traded on it.
They've barred against it.
They, they, with that as collateral.
That's basically how the banking system works
by the way.
It's, it's always pretend money.
You know, just because you have, uh,
like if you have a million dollars in the bank,
you're allowed to lend out nine more million dollars.
That's money that never existed.
You just created it because you got a million in the bank.
That's the way it works.
That's what reserve banking is.
That's the law.
That's how it was all set up.
That's how we get ripped off.
And so these guys look ready to fail.
But of course, they've always been very sturdy players
because it has been implicit.
This is the word that they're using.
It's code implicit that the US government would always stand behind them
and that these are institutions that are,
quote, too big to fail.
So that means they won't fail because America will just,
well, you know, it's like printing money,
but it isn't really.
It's just putting out the zero behind this elementary and the spreadsheet.
But of course, that will devalue the dollar and cause a whole
another economic shift.
So that's what's going on right now.
Anyways, the F-E-I-C has about 52 billion in assets.
And Indy Mac is estimated to cost between six hundred billion
of that 52 billion.
Right.
So let me just explain that.
So this is the guarantee that if you deposit money into the bank
that to a certain amount, which is different.
Not quite sure.
Is it now 100 grand in the states?
I think it's been up to 35,000 pounds in the UK.
And I don't know if that's per account or if that's just per depositor.
So, you know, because if there's a run on the bank or the bank fails,
you know, you don't want everyone's money to be gone.
Another thing that is insured by the government.
So they've got 56 billion, okay?
So F-E-I-C insurance, I don't know if I can count on it.
If I were anyone.
And a couple of banks that look like they might be having some trouble.
And I've actually written about, remember, before our Wacobia and
Washington Mutual.
So, you know, just make sure that your cash is safe and run to gold.com.
Anyways, I've bought about a lot of these issues there lately.
And some of the latest articles I think would be good reach for people.
Especially like the snow sticks.
That's a good one.
Anyways, I hope all the BSC listeners are safe with their money.
Keep up the good work.
We'll be your hair.
Great job.
Now that's us.
Yep.
Excuse me.
Run to gold.com.
Some good advice over there.
I have not bought into gold myself, but I have put everything into euros.
And I guess I'm considering filling up the ice box with some cash.
I don't know.
I'm not really seeing an impending doom, but it is for real.
These failures are for real.
And if the FDIC only has 56 billion to guarantee these banks.
You got the May and the Max.
And they could fail for trillions.
Yeah, we're not going to have enough money.
Of course, we can just print it up.
But that, of course, is a bad idea.
That's why they're put some European stuff.
Hey, Adam and Michael, listen up from Germany.
I have a lead for you, which when you might be interested in.
I just found this guy on YouTube.
His name is Nigel Ferrage.
Yeah.
He's the last name he's pronounced.
He's an MEP, a member of the European Parliament.
And he's very outspoken about European issues.
And go check him out.
And maybe if you happen to be in the yet.
Maybe you should.
I think he's a like guy for the program.
Thank you.
Yeah, you know, it's funny.
Because I've seen his videos on YouTube.
You can just go to YouTube or do Google video search for Farage.
F-A-R-A-G-E-F-X-T-L-F-R-O-R-O-M-O-L-F-G-O.
And you'll see this guy talking some real straight talk
in European Parliament.
Now, in the UK, though, people are like against the guy.
Like, you know, it's from the independent party.
And then, and not quite sure, I don't have a handle
on the vibe of the UK political landscape yet.
But whenever I say, hey, I've said to people at the office here.
I said, yeah, this guy's pretty interesting.
Oh, yeah, but he's a UKIP.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It sounds like he's making a lot of sense to me.
Particularly when it comes to the Lisbon Treaty,
which I will say once again,
do not let this get jammed down our throats.
No is no.
And they work for us.
So you've got 27 European members of Parliament
in each of your, in your countries.
Right to them.
Tell them that you want to respect the Irish vote.
Respect it.
And if there's no Lisbon Treaty, then it just remains
as that as quo as the Treaty of Nice.
Which is nice.
And just keep it rolling.
Leave it at that.
Respect the Irish vote.
Please.
Famous middle-aged, rock-and-roller called me last week
to thank me for speaking out against the war.
Only to go on to tell me that he could not speak himself
because he fears repercussions.
If you oppose this administration,
their can and will be remediation of the picture.
And the picture of the picture of the picture.
By the name of the world Abundance and the definition of the word.
By the name of viewers of the world Abundance and the community of the world,
tennis-and the toughest life for women.
I choose to beat everyone.
But I miserable.
I understand the complexity of freedom of women.
But life is notbilir in a reputation
as Marx and the political PM-Ran,
no more tires.
I'm allowing women to play rugby.
I'm awaiting that.
Finally, we are again.
We've played on some dances.
And today is the first time I watched swan.
And I'm going to show her the interests of both the women.
There should be no more leads.
So, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what
I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do. What do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, like do I do, like do, like I do I do, like do, like do I do I do, like do I do, like I do, like do me, like, do I do, like do I do, what do I do, like do I do I do, like do I do do I do, like do I do, like do I do, like do I do,
And then justansa
I remember
The world filled with
I'm watching so quickly in one shot for no
Someone watching TV is watching so far
Someone watching so quickly in one shot for no
Someone watching the TV is watching so far
CHARACTERS
There's no good things to play me
What's wrong with you & what's off and running
What is the forbidden walls?
What is the forbidden wall?
But once I know you make it, once it's a hell.
I like the way, the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it is.
The way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it's the way it
was the couple days away.... I can't resist. I love that track how cool is that. Alone everybody we're at a
Oh, man. Long show today. But oh yeah our in 10 minutes, we're all righty, gonna leave it at that which means
probably after all the preparations that'll have to do after this one, with all the comments,
everything coming in will be all set for a football Friday. Then again, you never know, do you?
So so until we meet again, live your life with passion and while in last,
Enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medial presentation, stick it in your ear.