Delta Shara Charley, 7-4-2.
With $16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio contenting my ears.
We don't need not seeking forgiveness.
I like to think I'm flying to the future.
I guess it's a happy curry.
Come on, they're more on its brand new day.
Come on, they're
I really needed to play something that reminded me that I'm free.
Good morning freedom.
And good morning.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
Hello.
Good day to you tomorrow.
Daily source code episode number 742.
Coming to you from the affluent suburb of Surrey.
In a cloudy and an overcast killed for it.
West Side of Gtown.
Wow.
I've always missed that part on that record.
Hey, everybody.
How are you doing?
Folks listening to the podcast version of the Daily source code.
Those of you checking us out live on live 365.
Having its usual problems.
People not being able to connect.
Kind of pisses me off because I went for the 99 dollar a month option.
I actually paid a year in advance.
Could I figure, you know, well, it's a little bit cheaper.
Why not?
I've used them before.
But I've never seen these problems with these guys.
Last time I used their service was pool.
I don't know.
Maybe a year and a half or two years ago.
So they're with me hanging there.
We're doing the best that we can.
I feel kind of anxious today.
And, you know, woke up and I don't know.
I'm just feeling restless really.
It's an unrest throughout my entire body.
And I'm trying to pinpoint this.
You know, I'm examining these feelings.
I think what is really going on with me.
And I think there's a number of things.
And a lot of it is just the conversations we're having on the tanty source code.
A lot of this stuff was really freaking me out.
I mean, not like I'm tripping.
But just, you know, my mind keeps on going.
It's very, very hard to stop thinking about all these different conversations.
And, you know, it's a fact.
I feel, or at least for me, if you start to get some information overload on particular topics.
Those of the complicated kind, or perhaps even those of the conspirator kind.
Your mind starts going pretty far.
And luckily I've been getting a lot of, you know, a lot of the contrarian views.
And a lot of these topics we've been talking about the multicultural society.
We've been talking about, well, that's why I played Good Morning Freedom about our own freedom.
How free are we?
What is the status of our freedom of speech and freedom of expression?
The financial crisis.
You know, thoughts of taking DNA from kids in a term if they're going to be troublemakers later on.
I mean, just saw this stuff and it's very hard to weigh exactly what is happening.
What isn't happening?
What's true?
What's not true?
Where the half-throughs?
Where the word of the half-truths intersect?
It's complicated.
So luckily, though, today, we're going to get through a lot of this with some excellent feedback
and some great comments and some good questions, which is really the best thing to do, I think, at this point.
And it'll really come down to education, I think.
Remember, this is a political, politically correct free zone on the daily source code.
This is where we talk about anything and everything and everything goes, no name calling alive.
Hey, Adam, this is Jared from Washington State.
That footballer Friday was fierce.
Way to kick him in the teeth.
Taking a pass on important issues because they're difficult and messy is totally chicken.
That guy with the hard pronounced name from the Netherlands may be a little over the top from an American or Canadian point of view,
but he should say whatever he thinks is right.
That's what freedom of speech is about.
The importance of freedom of speech is why political correctness is so dangerous.
I hate political correctness.
It limits every discussion.
The sense is conversation and it makes topics and ideas off limits.
This is one of the problems with the public schools.
It pre-programs kids that some thoughts are just not acceptable.
That conformity is key and that is part of the reason for the lag in maturity of our own country.
I want to even start an American news.
I watch BBC America because they seem to have a brain in a couple of balls.
I totally disagree with the constant demonization of the rich.
Thank God for the well to do.
You know, those guys didn't just bingo and win this money.
Most of them worked very hard to get what they have.
I don't know about everybody else.
But I am not employed by the poor.
A rich guy who worked hard to get where he is has given me the opportunity to make a living.
Wave that rich guy flag and tell him to shut the fuck up.
I'm not rich, but I want to be.
And so do all those antiest bastards who are giving you all this shit.
It's all I got.
Jared from Washington State.
Oh, Jared.
No kids.
Got a dog.
Go time.
See you later.
I love you meeting that.
Yeah.
And this is one of the things that I struggle with all the time.
I mean obviously I was born rich.
You know, comparatively speaking to the entire planet born very, very rich.
But I've also been monetarily rich myself.
I've been, you know, ever since I've been a millionaire since I was 23.
So for 20 years I've been in a very small percentage of the world.
You know, that can say that they're that wealthy.
And of course there's many, many people much wealthier than I am.
But it's hard, you know, it make it, how do you put things into perspective?
And I think, I think that, and wow, it's already becoming hard for me to start to formulate a lot of this stuff.
That we really have to caution ourselves each as an individual.
That we're responsible for everything and anything just as much as anyone else.
You know, at the bottom basis of it all, one human is exactly the same as the next human.
And this is kind of my Dutch upbringing that comes out by saying that, you know, we all get out of bed.
One, one leg at a time.
We all put on our trousers.
One leg at a time.
Of course, I'm Bruce Dickinson. And when I do that, I make hit record.
Sorry, little throwback to the cowbell.
So, you know, no one's better than another person or no one's worse than another person.
But it is our responsibility. And I think maybe that's where I want to go today.
I think it's our responsibility as, a lot of us here in the chucklehead group are parents.
Or in your parents to be, or it will soon be parents, or at least have some responsibility over more than just yourself.
There's someone else in your life more than likely.
That could even be an aged parent for all I care.
But that's pretty much just looking at the basic demographics of the show.
That's who we are.
And I think that we're doing the world a huge disservice by, and this goes across the board.
And of course, I'm putting hand on my heart.
You know, I'm doing the same thing.
It's very easy to complain and yell at the man at the government at them.
But they, we should actually, we should outlaw the word they on the show as well.
I really despise that all my life.
I remember them TV, Steve Leeds, my good buddy, would say, hey, you know, they really want you to cut your hair.
So who's they? Well, you know, they up there at the office.
Fuck that. They can come down here and talk to me about it.
I never did cut my hair. By the way, I got fired seven times. They hired me back each time.
But the responsibility is ours.
And I think we're probably not doing a very good job with our children.
And that's mainly because there's so much distraction going on in the world.
We're creating a lot of it, by the way, ourselves.
And we're, we're falling into a number of traps that we actually have set ourselves.
And we've set ourselves up for partially through just apparently the way human humans work and the way our, what's in our DNA and what we crave and what we strive for.
But we are missing a lot of the, the important things and we're certainly not questioning them.
Enough ourselves and we're definitely not opening up dialogue with the next generation is to what this is all really about.
And by the way, kids are not stupid. You know, has my daughter heard of the credit crisis?
Does she know what it is? No. Does she care? No.
Because it's not a topic of conversation. Well, it is actually here. But in general, that's not a topic of conversation.
I was shocked yesterday. Absolutely shocked.
Christina says, Dad, Dad, I finally found a great way to get songs on the internet.
Oh, well, what is that? She says, look, it's this thing called a zurious. Oh, my God.
She says, yeah, I have to do was find a file that says to rent, which was kind of cute, you know, because she's never, she's clearly never had this conversation in her own community or maybe only written, but we call it a torrent. She said it to rent.
And he can just download this music.
And I said, well, dude, this is problematic. And you know, and I started the dialogue with her first all about copyright and these bands.
And actually the way she founded was I had told her about the radio head album that she could download that one for free or she could contribute whatever she thought was appropriate. Of course, she downloaded it for free.
And that's how she found this whole Victorian thing.
And of course, now I know exactly when it's on because the home bandwidth and the entire house slows down to a crawl. She doesn't really understand what's happening.
I did walk her through it and I told her about copyright and how, you know, her favorite bands, you know, how she's basically taking money from them.
And you know, suggests that some alternative ways and easier ways to get music on to her computer.
Because that's really what it is. She buys CDs quite frequently.
But she finds that a pain in the ass and the ripping and she just doesn't want to do that. She just wants to have an instant gratification.
And of course, I also would letter her to the fact that, you know, this is trackable and that you could wind up with no internet.
With no internet service whatsoever. But I was kind of disappointed. I was severely disappointed in myself.
That here I am, a guy who knows a lot about this has grown up with this has been a part of this file sharing and the internet in general.
And I'm just flabbergasted that my knowledge and my values towards this and I do not download songs off of the torrent.
And, you know, in fact, I tried to reverse the process and I tried to give music exposures for people go out and buy it.
I'm flabbergasted that none of that has passed down on to her. So we got to talk about education.
Because, you know, let's face it. You know, I got a lot of living left to do and I'm going to enjoy myself. But I don't think I have.
It's a young man's game, you know, to go and prove stuff and change the world. I can certainly facilitate and do all I can.
And I do that in many different ways.
But we really have to start this educational process at home. And that goes across the board for all groups, all race, all religions, all creeds, everything.
And I know I'm not alone. And this is good, man. This is really good that we're starting.
By the way, if you're listening on live 365, it's very possible that the stream is going in and out.
Because I'm quite sure that my daughter is downstairs with her azureus P to P on.
And I think I can even see nice cast telling me that it's messed up. So, sorry about that.
But here is someone who is incredibly smart, who I've known for almost a decade actually.
Yeah, maybe even longer than a decade. But we've been good friends, certainly intensely for the past a couple of years, Andrew Grummit from Pachio.
And he has some questions that just, you know, for someone who's very, very smart. I'm like, okay, wow, we read none of us really understand the basics of what's in front of us and how things work in the world.
And I have a sneaking suspicion that this is not being taught properly in school. And if it is, it's probably only very superficial,
I'm not going into the real meeting potatoes, which, of course, is the interesting thing about how our world runs and who does the running.
Hey Adam, it's Andrew Grummit here, checking in from HQ.
Actually, this time, I don't have an HQ update, but rather I wanted to check in on the money system conversation that has been taking place on your show.
So, I'm not in the economist, but I've been really interested in this stuff. I think it's fascinating.
And I'm trying to wrap my head around it. So, I wanted to pass a couple of observations by your listeners, hopefully get some stuff on level feedback.
Okay, by the way, I love that. That's right, calling out on the savants. Hey, I wonder if nylon's okay in the middle of all of this.
Excuse me, you are a New York financial guru, savante in London, the nylon.
I hope he's still got a gig, you know, we don't know exactly what he does, but I think he's in the financial sector.
Yes, indeed. We need some savants on this. Bring it on.
The first one, the gold standard, right, this is part of Ron Paul's platform. Something you've mentioned before.
And there's something about it. I can't quite get my head around. So here it is. It's a thought experiment.
We know that there's only so much gold in the earth, right? There's only so much gold you can dig up.
So let's imagine a world where we have 100 people and 100 gold pieces, right?
So basically, let's say we start off with each of those 100 people having one gold piece.
Okay, now, you know, some time goes by, people have kids and the population doubles.
So now there are 200 people and only 100 gold pieces. How do we, you know, how do we handle that?
Does each person on average, now maybe has, you know, half a gold piece.
And effectively, if we use the, you know, the weight of the gold as a measure of currency, suddenly, there's, you know, more people, but just the same amount of money.
So how does it work, right? Because generally speaking, prices go up.
People's incomes go up for better or worse. You know, there's this feeling of progress as time goes on and people's wealth gets larger.
Hopefully. So I don't, it seems contrary to that trend that you would have a fixed amount of money and that generally speaking on average,
people would have less money with each successive generation.
So I, I just don't know how, how do you apply that thinking to a world where there's increasing population and, you know, maybe we're nowhere near it, but a finite amount of gold.
So I don't, I don't know how to square the, the gold standard way of doing money with those facts and maybe somebody in the audience does.
Okay. All right. So here's what I've learned Andrew and it may not be correct, but first of all, I think you're confusing two things.
The gold's equating the gold standard to the way money works in circulation.
So let's just remove that for a second and just say, we have want them, you know, or sticks or whatever.
And these sticks are attributed to value and everyone agrees that, you know, a stick has an intrinsic value either by its length or perhaps if we use paper sticks by the number written on it and it was, you know, and there's a known amount of this in circulation.
So what you say, I have to agree that if we all have an equal amount of sticks.
Someone's going to wind up with, as we start to trade and buy goods and services from each other, you know, at times you'll have less and then if you have some good services or products, then you know, you'll make more.
And I think that this is exactly where a central bank comes into play because in order to manage that economy, depending on how hard this economy works and what they produce or if they're mainly consumption focused.
And, you know, this, of course, is now now you're getting into some heavy shit economics because, you know, that it then imports and exports come into what this leave all of this to the side.
This is just a village.
You probably could get around, you know, just with the sticks, right, but that would depend on if you wanted to buy something that you didn't have enough sticks for.
And so that's where banking comes into play.
So when you have a central bank, then there is an entity, a force, a regardless of who it is, that manages a lot of that economy by putting more sticks into the pool.
And this, of course, is extremely interesting because how many sticks do you need to have to lend, how many sticks can you lend out to someone based upon how many sticks you have.
So immediate conventional childish thinking as well, if I have 10 sticks, I can lend people 10 sticks.
Well, that's not exactly what is going on because we have fractional reserve banking.
And I bet you that that's going to be Andrew's next question.
So the gold standard is a different topic altogether, Andrew.
I believe that, you know, okay, so I believe that the reason why we don't just live in a society with an equal amount of sticks for everyone is because society grows.
And because of that growth or, you know, with international important exports balance has to be, you hear these words all the time, you know, nice start to think about what they mean, right, what is the trade balance, well, it's an important part of the economy to understand the value of your sticks.
Inflation of prices, et cetera, all of it really there's an equal and opposite reaction for everything that is done.
And this, of course, is what all this interest rate talk is all about.
To now on to Andrew's next question.
And then there's the second one, which is the, the fractional reserve lending system.
I want to say that you said on yesterday's show that a bank could lend 10 times what it had, which it's kind of misleading.
I think that I've done some reading about this and I think what the role is this for each hundred dollars a bank receives into posits.
It can turn around and invest something like 90% of that.
So that's a fundamental difference the way I've read it and I and I also have looked around and again, I could be wrong.
It is my understanding that fractional reserve banking works by you have 10 sticks and you're allowed to lend out 10 times that amount.
So you have to have at least 10% of it in or that whatever you have in deposits, you can lend out 10 times that.
And I presume that only works if your bank is ensured of the some other deal going on in the background.
You know, of course, that's exactly what happens when there's a run on the bank.
There's a run on the bank then, you know, all those 10 other people come running and say, hey.
Wait a minute, I'm saying it the wrong way.
See how fucking complicated this is.
There's a run on the bank then all the people who've actually deposited money start taking it out, but that has a like a multiplier domino effect on what you have outstanding.
And of course banks don't just lend out, they borrow all the time.
That's the business.
The business is borrowing and lending of money and arbitraging.
So in other words, bilo sell high and this can be thousands of percentages of dollars.
But if you have enough of them, they start to add up.
And of course lending at the end of the day is always based on trust.
Right, that might be where the 10 to one number comes from, but there's a limit.
The Federal Reserve sets a limit on, you know, the fraction of that hundred dollars at the bank and then turn around and invest.
And it kind of, I mean, it makes sense to me in a certain way that the bank should be able to take that money and essentially make money from it, right?
That is, well, not make money in the printing money sense, but rather make money in the be profitable sense, right?
A bank is a business.
They have, they've got to, you know, run the ATM machines and then the bank branches and whatever else they do.
So in order to make money, they essentially take your money and they invest it, right?
So you give them a hundred dollars and if they were required to keep that hundred dollars in their safe, they wouldn't have a way to be profitable, right?
So I guess the question is, you know, how much of that should they be able to invest?
And where do the limits come from and what are the implications of that?
So those are kind of my two points in this discussion.
I'm really curious to see if anybody out there has some thoughts about anyway.
Thanks for having the discussion, really enjoying following it.
And that's all for now.
All right, bye Andrew.
And by the way, you know, I know you don't call it an orphan Andrew, but come on, get with it, man.
Do some of the official sign-off, Lingo, will you?
Yes, so you may have received this PowerPoint that's been doing the rounds on the internet, which explains the banking crisis.
And it's kind of a humoristic cartoon, essentially showing how all of these lending and borrowing institutions.
And by the way, that includes us.
You know, what Andrew would call investing, what a bank does, another would call borrowing or, for instance, if I buy a house and I have a mortgage, I put down 10%.
Right?
So if it's a hundred thousand dollar house, I put down ten thousand dollars.
I borrow ninety thousand dollars.
The house goes up in value.
I've just doubled my money.
Yeah, as sure there's a little bit of a loss for the interest that I've had to pay, but that's exactly what banks do.
They do it with all kinds of things with the exchanging of money.
They do it with investments.
They do it with all kinds of financial instruments.
It's coming up with different ways to borrow money at a lower cost than you can lend it out to someone that's the basic business.
So anyway, so I'm amazed at how people, particularly with a couple of visual aids, are able to really explain this quite succinctly.
And in fact, I got a voice comment here, which kind of explains the Federal Reserve in under a minute.
Hi, Adam, Eric from Portland.
This whole Federal Reserve thing is a little complex for some people to get their minds around.
And I've found a nicer way to an easy way for people to understand it is to just pull out a dollar bill and look at it.
It is not just a dollar bill.
It's a contract.
If you look at the top of it on the face side, you look at the top of it.
It's going to say Federal Reserve, Federal Reserve note.
That's the lender.
Down there, there's little signatures at the contract signing for the American People's
at Treasure and the Secretary of the Treasury.
Those are the borrowers and they're signing on our behalf on the American People's behalf.
So look at a dollar bill as just a simple contract.
And you'll realize that that contract is just paper and it's not backed by anything.
Hope that helps.
It certainly helps for some part.
Why is it that our political leaders?
Why is it that why don't they just take the time out?
Take five minutes and explain in simple terms because this stuff is simple.
I mean, yeah, it seems very complicated because there's lots of zeroes and it's, you know,
and it's intricately linked to all kinds of other systems and issues.
But I think basic economics is, it wouldn't be bad.
You know, well, we can't expect that from President Bush.
But why doesn't Obama take some time and just say that or Hillary?
Oh, she really understands it.
Just explain how it works where the money comes from, you know,
explain this situation to the people so that we as, as a world population,
because it is interlinked throughout the world.
This is not just a problem in the United States.
So we can all understand it and then we can educate ourselves.
And then stay away from the pitfalls in the future, which in this case in the subprime mortgage crisis
was that we didn't understand exactly how the adjustable rate mortgages worked
and that refinancing is only possible if the housing value continues to rise
and it's not a set given fact that house prices always go up.
Very, very simple things.
You know, so instead of people saying, we were dupped by them and they screwed us.
Now, you've got to educate yourself.
But I think we deserve some of that from our leaders.
And I don't mind being patronized a little bit like I'm some idiot because clearly I am.
I don't understand this stuff.
No wonder a lot of smart people I know understand it.
Thank you to the BBC who had a fantastic program on last night,
called the Super Rich, the greed game.
And you can get on the BBC eye player if you're still in the UK.
It's good for another six days.
I hope that although I don't like piracy, but I think it's such a good piece of work.
And of course, it has been paid for by the British populace.
I hope someone puts that out there like on YouTube or Google video.
So that other people can see it all hunter-round for it.
But it's just a fantastic show.
A little over the top about the super rich.
It's like blah, blah, blah, whatever.
But just understanding what happened and why the system broke down.
Then all of a sudden you can put it in perspective.
And you see all these bank guys, the guys in the strip bars.
I understand that they just overplayed their hand and overplayed the game.
And there was not their own elders and people responsible.
Played along and did really educate them as to what could happen.
And we screwed up.
We'll get out of it.
I do like this news that I saw from...
Who sent this to me.
I think that Naly Cruz, of course, is the...
What is her exact title, the competition minister?
She's the one that makes sure a company says play honest.
She is now starting investigations into the state bailout of Northern Rock.
Because there are European rules against doing this.
We can't have all of individual member states of the European Union.
Just willingly going around and bailing out whatever and whatever they want.
And of course, that's where a lot of the dissatisfaction comes from.
And that is just the anger that builds up inside of us.
But if we understand better what's going on, then we'll be able to combat that in many different levels, including political.
You know, your kids can run for office, you know.
It's not too late to let them know that.
I don't know where I was going with that crap.
So I almost want to rewind what I just said.
I was on the roll.
Anyway, we'll work on it.
I need your help, those savants.
Let us know what's going on, okay?
Hey Adam, it's Jack.
Are the multiculturalism discussion?
I think it's a dangerous to lump a whole group of people based on the actions of a few violent,
so-so-siffrous minority.
As it is dangerous to lump all journalists based on the faux-siffrous idiotic Glenn Beck.
Okay, point will made podcaster for me to know in his Jack.
Actually, it just came to me when I was talking about,
thank you, Jack, for kind of jogging my memory there.
So what really gets people angry is you see these crises brought on by big institutions.
And yes, in some cases, very wealthy people.
And it hurts everybody, but the people who get helped by the government, for a number of reasons, not just altruistic,
but a number of reasons, seem to be these large institutions and wealthy people, and seemingly they therefore have no risk to taking even greater risks.
There's no downside. There's no repercussions for them taking that type of risk. Of course, in recession, the little guy and we all get fucked.
And that makes you angry. Angry. So you want to we all get angry, but at the same time educate ourselves on what the hell is going on.
We understand that we can definitely change it. And you can do that because at the end of the day, who is it based on?
Right? Who was the subprime mortgage based on? Who was the housing boom based on?
Based on us. Based on us borrowing to buy.
Selling at a profit, going back, refinancing, borrowing to buy, buy sell, buy low sell, high, make money, party, party.
We did it. So within we can stop it, right? It's that simple.
You know, but this whole day thing is just, I should stop that myself and I think you should consider it because it's just going a little bit out of hand.
Now, of course, to educate yourself and this is something that I've been working on as a personal mission.
It's, you know, there's so much information coming in. And in fact, I use Google News as an example of this.
If you just go to news.google.com, you'll see a whole bunch of stories in different categories.
And these are all aggregated and supposedly the the hot stories bubble to the top, but they've got a whole bunch of different things.
Different, like, showbees, entertainment sports, etc. Now, I really look at sports ever.
I saw on the page. But what I'm trying to do now is when I see a headline.
The first thing I, I, before clicking on it because that's where you go down the rabbit hole.
Before clicking on it, I'm like, do I really need to know this?
Will it enrich my life? Will it make any difference to me at this moment?
I mean, unless you're in like a major major leisure time moment.
You know, like, here's one, Britney, anything Britney Spears. You know, those headlines are, are you just want to click on like, oh my gosh.
And you know, instead of going into why I want to click on it.
It's like, what is the benefit going to be? I'm not even just not going to click on that link. You know, it's all right.
So I'll sound stupid by not knowing what happened to her.
You know, I'll live with that. I'll know, you know, I'll click on things that I really evaluate for second.
Because when you click on like a Britney link and this, of course, is what publishes are very good at and what I try to do myself is,
you know, they draw you in and here's another link to click on it. Get more info and see more pictures before you know it.
What the hell was I was trying to get the news? Wasn't I? So evaluate this stuff. You know, don't just click Willy and Lily.
That's probably not a very good idea.
And sometimes, of course, you just have to be in your leisure time mode and whether you're watching, whether you're clicking around and Googling things or whether you're watching certain types of television.
Well, you know, that's a moment where you can, you know, you think you're resting your brain. You aren't really, but at least you can put some different impulses in there.
But when you're really focused on getting some information and learning something or when you're just just news in general, this is a good thing.
Anything you see evaluate why you're going to click on that link.
It would probably boost our economy by a trillion dollars if you all did that.
It would save us a lot of time jerking off doing nothing.
Adam, it's Chris and Nashville.
I've been listening to Noah Jen the number 24 and the park where John is saying that these shows are detrimental to our mental state of being.
He's absolutely right.
I'm sick and tired of all those big brother, you know, all this reality bullshit.
It's just,
I only played a little bit of that for one reason because for those, and a lot of you listened to Noah Jen does well, I know.
And we kind of had a cliffhanger that we left on the last show.
So of course, a new one coming up this weekend.
And I need to provide a rebuttal because, and this is why I wanted to just say this for a second.
I did not say I'm a fan, because this is, we had a whole conversation.
And I said, I was a fan of a certain type of reality programming.
Namely, the talent contest with voting and honest judges.
And that and, and there was one specific example of honesty.
And that'll be part of my rebuttal, which was Jerry Springers, nothing but the truth.
I just want to say this has nothing to do with big brother, although that, I can say a lot about that as well.
But in general, I will be talking in my rebuttal about reality television.
And why I do believe that there is value to that genre.
And it should be an interesting show.
So Friday or Saturday, you never know when we released that.
Hey, Noah, let's play a song.
Something I found on the podcast music network just uploaded this morning.
And there's nothing better than the Rolling Stones than our Rolling Stones tribute band with their own material.
And they have the only one going without giving up.
Straighten all my hands at the end.
You're gonna ask a pause and you're gonna...
Let's go find where the old drone.
And I just stand with different lines.
I'll figure out where the river is.
My shows are ready to die.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
Ah.
Oh yeah.
Oh yes.
Oh.
For the chamber of the smaaaight
You're probably scared of past me
Let the show with perfect size
And I'll come back to your body
Let me summon you
Get it out for me now
Just for me to say
Okay, I'll come home from
I just need your help
Oh yeah
Oh
When is the minister
Of the moment you raise
And these objects are self-known
Self-love
Self-righteousness
Why the victim is convicted
Running out to steal them
I guess you're falling into the moon
And your flesh rip by your chain
Oh yeah
I thought that was kind of interesting
The name was really what caught my eye
The power goats
Deep love
That attention to potting music
Now we're going to force I will share the location of this band
And their music on the PMN
Through the show notes at the daily source code
At daily source code.com
Actually
Okay, I think we're going to leave it at that for today
Because it'll want to think about
And I'm still in the middle of my learning journey
And my quest
So I will turn it over to the sabons
You know how to reach me at
Adam at podshow.com
Of course if you look at the show notes
You can find the
Phone numbers to call in
And leave some feedback
Keep it short
If possible
In fact, can't someone out there
Describe how our economy works
And how the Federal Reserve works
And how certain elements or discussions
We've talked about in under 60 seconds
I mean, that should be possible
Something that I can just
Fire off an MP3 to my daughter
And she'll understand it
Wouldn't that be amazing?
Wouldn't we be doing something interesting?
All right everybody
Thank you very much for listening
I think the live 365 stream
Wasn't too great today
I'm not quite sure what the problem is
Also our bandwidth here as you know
Is severely hampered by the
The illegality of a teenager
Who needs more speaking to
Before I start closing a port
Because that of course is the ultimate
Why to get whatever I want
Tomorrow I have some more dental work
Being done so I don't know if I'll do a show
But Friday definitely full on
Fubar I hope we'll have the stream up
And running perfectly so get your songs in
Early so we can crank it out
Have a maximum music good time
Live your life with passion
And because that is something you control
And while others don't control all of it
Enjoy your freedom
Another pop show podcast
Stick it in your ear