Hi everybody, this is Adam, sorry to interrupt a daily source code feed, but I have an announcement
to make that I want to share with you.
Yeah baby, you just got Rick Roll.
That's right.
If you need to know what it means, go to RickRolling.com.
Meanwhile, enjoy Rick Ashley, never going to give you up.
Part of the soundtrack to our lives.
We're no strangers to love.
Do you know the rules and so do I.
The story begins, while I'm thinking of you.
When you get this wrong, any other guy.
I just wanna tell you how I'm feeling.
Got to make you understand that I'm gonna give you up.
We're gonna let you know, we're gonna run around here, we don't do.
We're gonna make you cry, we're gonna share you that I'm gonna tell you my love.
We're gonna let you.
We know each other, so you're hot to be naked.
You're too shy to say it's safe, so we won't know what's been wrong.
We know the game I'm gonna play and you do ask me how I feel
Don't tell me you're too bad to see
But I know the game you are
I'm gonna run to you now
I'm gonna make you cry
I'm gonna say goodbye
We know the game you are
I'm gonna run to you now
But I know the game I'm gonna run to you
I'm gonna make you cry
I'm gonna say goodbye
We know the game you're too
I'm gonna give you my gonna give you my gonna give you my
We've known each other for so long
You'll have to be making hard
You'll just have to say
It's like we've all known what's been going on
We know the game and we're gonna play
I just want to tell you how I'm feeling
Y'all who make you a misunderstanding
Give you our gonna, let you down
From the long run, me, that you
Has made you cry.
From The shame of the poor
I thought, give you our wanna to know
From the long run, I've got to
This rig roll is brought to you by Emusic, get 35 free songs with absolutely no obligation
go to emusic.com slash daily source code.