This is the daily source code, the daily source code.
For $16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not seeking forgiveness.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I'm casting this battle curry.
This is finished later in Fort Lagerdale,
and my dad says,
that I'm curry kicks ass.
So I say Adam kicks ass too.
You're listening to the DSC 751.
We don't need not seeking forgiveness.
They are the answers to why it's called 420.
I'll hook a little bit, and then they all grew up, and as they grew up, they all went their
separate ways, but they also did a lot of plots of 420 and get out every morning, and
tow kept 420 so they could all be together, like a lasting friendship, just so I could
do the update on that, and I'm a 3-dayer for the week, I mean, and the folder, thank you.
Oh, I'd forgotten about that. This is, this is that news report that's been circling
around that says men who masturbate at least five times a week have less chance of getting
prostate cancer. So I know I'm certainly going to be okay. Now I do question if it can
just be sex, and if it doesn't have to be necessarily sex with yourself, if any kind
of sex qualifies. In fact, John C. DeVora, can I talk about that on yesterday's No Agenda,
which might want to listen to? Three-timers, well man, you got to catch up. You don't want to catch
nasty stuff. So up the quota a little bit, my friend.
Hey Adam, it's East. You've got to go.
Ah, Shabbat Shalom, my friend.
Ah, so just listening and hearing about voicemails from Ms. Geller from I need you. Oh, yeah,
man, big knee a culp on this one. I'm sure that's what you've thought is calling about.
All right, hit me, man. It's Masha, yeah. Mike Alpha Sierra, who tell Alpha.
I know. I really messed that up.
Castale's Weasel Greg was listening and he says, dude, dude, you know her name.
I don't know. What can I say?
Yes, Masha Geller. So the whole point was she called in once going to be on a panel at
I media, and I said, and I don't think anything has really happened. I don't think the
charcoal heads had taken any action because I have not heard from her or nothing has come
back. The whole point was, if she sends me, you know, my favorite kind of picture I'd
be willing to accept her, her offer.
She has no Romeo in her first name, and Dan, she is fine looking.
At least that headshot they have on her website.
Hell yeah. Yeah, good luck with the, I would tell him, make a picture for the panel
thing. Anyway, love you. Hope you win fantastic care. Shabbat Shalom.
Shabbat Shalom. You have to thank very much, buddy. You should be our, you should be
our, are you disappointed? I got, you know, I got to talk to Jeff Smith. We have spoken
a couple of times over, over email about a couple things, but I think what I should do
is I should get a list together of the current savants we have, you know, a monetary
scientist. I got to get some jingles, and that means work for Jeff, and that means I'm
going to pay him, obviously. But we, I think we should just do a one big session, we
do like four or five, because we are lacking in a couple.
Hi Adam, it's partially checking in. I just wanted to put you right. It wasn't me that got
both of them. Unfortunately, it was Paul Nichols, and the really sick thing was that you
was done over again four days later. So, you know, my heart goes out to Paul. You've
been voted twice now, and I hope they catch the bastards and rip their arms and make
so I'm going to take it.
All right, Barkey, thanks, man. That really sucks. But hey, you know, that's what all those
cameras are doing, right? Aren't those cameras supposed to bring down crime and, on
the, especially at two times in a row, within four days, you'd expect that these millions
of cameras in the UK would stop crime and it's tracked. Of course not. That's just there
to spy on you. Oh, man. That's pretty disappointing, actually. I mean, I don't know what
the situation is with his house, but clearly, that surveillance system isn't working. Unless
of course, they're using it for something else other than actually surveying crime.
Let's have a word with the Nile on. Let's break the news with the smile on where the
wrong old right. We go for light. Let's listen to the Nile. Oh, yeah, he's back and he's
changed his tune. Adam, you know, it's the Nile on. Let me stop by saying this is a
seminal moment in our relationship. That is because I totally agree with you only issue
of China. Oh, wait, I think I should just replay that one. I just want to hear him say it
again. I totally agree with you only issue of China. Nice. Now, at a conceptual, metal
level, I agree, which is the point that if you wish no man woman or child is free, until
every man woman and child is free. So, you're right. Why are we just focusing on China?
There is inhumanity across the world. Has anyone ever heard of Lake Providence in Louisiana?
Has anyone been to Mississippi? The poor state in the USA? Lake Providence among the
poorest places in America. 75% of people below poverty. Highest levels of mortality
and drug use, teenage pregnancy in the US. Hmm, I think I should put this on my vacation
destination. With demonstrating to help those people, who is in Mississippi to help
radio levels, which is remaining the poorest state since the Civil War, where the protest
is in America, where the protest is in the UK for chef field and hull among the most
oppressed places in the UK. People out of work, drug use, violence, teenage pregnancy,
unemployment. Who is complaining to disrupting things, get politicians, get on things
in their own backyard, and that's why I agree with you. So, Lake Providence, Mississippi,
chef field, and hull until the Americans and the British take care of their own backyard.
They shouldn't be going in there worried about the debt. In fact, probably most people within
five seconds couldn't put their thing on the map and find where the debt is. Symbarway, Sudan,
North Korea, where are the protest? Where are the non-African people protesting Symbarway? I've
not seen one protest of people of non-African descent talking about Mugabi, not one. Maybe I'll be
out there, I haven't seen it. So Adam, I agree with you. It's not about China, it's about
four-old. No one is free until everyone is free. So we protest things in our own backyard and
fix our own backyard. Let's not be going into other people's business. We have no license to do it.
I agree with you. What can I say? Even a broken clock is right twice a day.
Oh, and I see still gets this slam in there at the end. Even a broken clock is right twice a day.
Nylon, I appreciate it, man. Absolutely. Of course, I agree completely with that.
And this talk about China, not just on this show, but also in no agenda has resulted in a lot of
conversation. I'm going to play a couple of them. Don't worry, got some other stuff coming as well.
But this is top of mind. And in particular, what hit a lot of people, and I'm just, well,
I'm going to play a couple of pieces of voicemail and it really freaked me out to hear this.
I coupled the, it's an age-old proverb. I don't remember who said it. I'm sure I could look it up
and find it. But the statement is, every country gets the government, it deserves.
And wow, you know, the response is to this, particularly as it pertains to China,
have been pretty unbelievable. From people who I consider to be my friends by, you know,
osmosis or by email or because their chuckleheads or contributed to the show, whatever.
And my opinion in my friendship doesn't change, but man, we have to rectify some thinking here.
We kick it off with the guy who I respect enormously, who does a show called hoothype.com.
He's been calling into the Charlie for a couple of years. Jay Mack hit it, man.
This would carry Jay Mack from hoothype.com. And I got to be honest, I was putting mulch in my yard.
This I love. Here's the big hip hopper. And put mulch in his yard. And of course, every single time
you think of mulch, now we have to think of the daily source code. Because clearly,
there's listen into it while he was mulching. Yes, I run hoothype.com and I put mulch in my fucking yard.
Yes. Anyway, I was putting mulch in my yard and I hear you talking about the Chinese government
and how the Chinese get the government they deserve. And if they have a problem with it, they should
revolt rise again. You know, not at all. The problem is, is that China is not like the United
States. And I'm sure you're well aware of the fact that China is a communist country.
And I don't know that I need to remind you about a Tiananmen square. I mean, when people attempted
to do that, was the college students or a thousands of them there, thousands. And what did the
Chinese government do to payment with their tanks and mold the fuckers down?
Oh, man, you think we're that far away from them? Do you think the protesting in the United
Kingdom is pretty much a band any legal? I don't think we're that far away from their so-called
communist government. Yes, by the way, the guy, you remember the student who stood in front of the
tank? I think that was there was a very, I think he was very successful with what he did.
Those pictures were broadcast to the world and it changed opinions or refreshed memories for
lots of people. So of course, that is important. And yes, it did make a difference. One step in
perhaps a long path, but you can't say it was a complete failure. Here we are talking about it.
All kinds of people die and to this day the Chinese government denies it even ever
happened. So my point is is that you can't just tell the people of a country that you can just
up and rise against when you're in a communist country, it doesn't work that way.
You know, the idea, the... Yeah, how Jay Mac, my friend. I know you don't mean it this way,
but this is almost a slap to every freedom fighter. Every member of any resistance in any
occupation or war from an outside or internal source, there have been hundreds of thousands,
maybe millions of extremely brave men and women who have fought against oppressive governments against
Hitler. Come on, if people didn't rise up and didn't fight, then we might be, you know,
I don't even want to go there. But the things that could be happened right now,
the world would be a very different place. So, you know, the only way to fight is not by just
voting or just yelling. Sometimes you gotta get up and you gotta fight. The government holds the
stronger man. They've got the weapons. Select these people can organize and revolt.
Oh, that is so untrue. This is what history is almost based upon and revolt uprising.
It happens all the time. And by the way, look at the French. Look at the French.
You know, you can... Yeah, sure, they may be a republic and have a democracy or be democratic
thinkers. But if the people don't get what they want, they rise up and burn the shit down.
And it works. I get weapons and, and, and rise against and, and take over so the government doesn't
work that way, man. It's sure does. And I think there's more Chinese who are not in the army than
Chinese who are in their vast military structure. There's no way. It's just, it's not logically
possible. Then you need to think about it. I don't know. And that's just the way I feel about it.
Maybe I took your words incorrectly, but they kind of caught me out of the crowd. They've seen
like a very educated individual, especially when some two countries abroad were not. But
that really caught me out of God. It just doesn't make sense. There's no way that a country,
especially with China, with all the poverty they have. And, you know, then at the time in this
government, there's no way they would be able to overthrow the country. So I disagree that the
China has the country, the government that they deserve. disagree, man. All right. That's cool.
That's cool. But you are wrong, unfortunately. Because again, the country gets the government.
It deserves. Governments sometimes are installed. The old governments are overthrown.
Governments are removed. New governments are put in place. And the United States of America,
its government was created as a revolt against the monarchy in England. People said this
ain't working for us. Well, let's think of something. What can we do? Well, we could
try and overthrow the king. Or, you know, why don't we go start our own country and run at the
way we want to? And have the government we deserve? That of course was the original intent.
And some of that is slipped. And again, we here in the United States have the government we deserve.
The government, by the way, I heard to both candidates for the Democratic nomination,
Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama, saying that, hey, we have the nuclear weapons to
what was the word obliterate Iran? Do who'd what kind of crap are we talking? Of course we do.
But man, what is that talk about? Shiver me, Timbers, well, there's more people who
misunderstood or I think are probably just misled. And and have to understand that, you know,
it is we the people in every country. It's absolutely true. And you know what? People probably
will have to die if you want to change something. That's just the way it is. But we're like
pussy's over here, man. Oh, the only way you can change something is by voting.
You know, it doesn't seem to be working too well. My friends, that voting thing.
I'm Chris and I'm down again on social day of 70. There's a fundamental flaw in your statement.
You say the people fundamentally get what they deserve. Now, I said they fundamentally get the
government they deserve, but okay, I'll let you slide. But there's a significant flaw in that.
The individual does not get what they deserve. The people as a whole get what they deserve,
the kind of that ignores manipulation. So without manipulation, that statement is correct. It
changed people to a society. For example, me as an individual. Right now according to your logic,
the proper action for me to take is to drive down the Washington B.C. walk into the White House
place, place under arrest and you share the government in this place. No, I never said that.
I never said that. That's your interpretation of what I said. But, you know,
marches on Washington have been quite successful in the past. But you got to go do it. Someone's
got to organize it and go march. What's the result of that? I go to jail. Tell you in simple.
Oh, right. So stay home and do nothing. It doesn't matter if I'm right at all because they
have a bigger stick than I do. No, he's got a bigger stick. So I can't come up for what I think is
right. And visually, we can do almost nothing. It's at a whole that we actually have the power to do anything.
Do you have any idea how difficult it is to organize a group of people as a whole to do anything?
Yeah, absolutely. It is very difficult to organize a group of people who are so hypnotized by
mainstream media stories about Nicole Richie, Britney Spears, Lindsey Lowhan, Amy Weinstein.
We argue about DRM and how evil it is while kids are getting shot and killed in the desert.
Yeah, I understand it's very hard because we have all these much more important things to talk about.
Like my iPod doesn't work. Please.
Leave under the current moniker of this country that no one else wants to do it.
Why am I going to stick around it down? But of course, everybody thinks that way. So everybody says nothing.
So listen to it. Right. Yeah. Well, it starts with talking about it and from talking we got to
get this action by friend. That's for sure. Because we're just being fed a big pile of bull crap
from from news organizations. And the go back to what the nylon said. You don't hear about
Louisiana. You don't hear about, uh, she was at Shepherd's Bush. Is that what he said? And how?
Because that's not what is important to the politicians at the moment.
That, therefore, it doesn't get reported on. Luckily, though. Thank goodness, we have what I would
almost want to, it's like a first time caller. But close enough to reaching savon status immediately
from New York Bulls, I Johnny. Adam, it's Bulls, I Johnny from New York City. Hell yeah.
It's just something I'd share with you. This whole thing with the government. We deserve the
government that we have right now. This is our fault. It's something I like to call the devolution
of the American man. If you look at our fathers, I think you and I are about the same age Adam.
Our fathers had a whole different life than we did. They fought in battles. They lived through
a depression. They stormed the beaches of Normandy. That was just that tougher generation.
Well, what did we have to do? The toughest thing I had to do when I was a kid was figure out
which led Zeppelin out in the by. I had no worries. I mean, we came from a middle class family.
I had everything I wanted, wasn't like luxury, but it was a stress-free childhood. Now our children
are like real. So the Americans things have to get really, really bad before they get any better.
That's how this country was founded. So when the oil runs out and the shitty little gadgets from
China start to break, then all hell is going to break loose. It's time we need to organize it
now. You're right. We have to rise up and we've got to figure out a way to get back to that
toughness of our parents generation. And we've got to do it now for our children's sake.
So get together and organize. When gas hits four dollars a gallon, you happen to do something
about it. Stop driving your car. Figure out a different way. Do it now. We'll be about
me 43 public relations professional in New York City, two kids,
folder and scruncher. I'll go both ways with that one. Thanks Adam. Bullseye, Johnny Man,
love you. Thank you so much for calling in. And the only person who could say it better is the guy
that just turned 70 years old. And when I'm saying that, I'm purpose because when someone turns 70,
you know, this is how someone's been around for a while. They, you know, you should listen to
what they have to say. You know, remember this whole respect, your elders thing? Well, this guy
just said another HBO show, another show for HBO, I should say. One of his infamous routines and
John C. DeWire, DeWire, I turned me on to it. He actually burnt it to his DVD for me, but it didn't
work. And he told me what it was. And of course, it was very easy for me to find and just went to video.
Google.com and those intellectual property thief's over there. Of course, had everything nicely listed.
You don't hear about that anymore. Do you, you know, when there's stealing content left and right
and it's been up there for a couple months, you know, nicely categorized, not hard to find anything.
It's probably crossposted on YouTube. But anyway, this is the guy who without doubt
has pushed his finger right on the open wound of the postification of the United States of America
and probably countries around the Western hemisphere. Listen to a couple minutes
of George Carlin on our kids. It focuses bad for you. It's all bullshit. That's what you have
to remember. You go through life in this country. It's all bullshit and it's bad for you.
Now speaking of parents, speaking of bullshit, two ideas which aren't always mutually exclusive,
by the way. I'd like to mention a special kind of bullshit that has taken hold in this country
in the last 30 to 40 years. It's a form of bullshit that really only can be called child worship.
It's child worship. It's this excessive devotion to children. I'm talking about today's
professional parents. These, these obsessive, diverse sniffers who are over scheduling and over
managing their children and robbing them of their childhoods, even the simple act of playing.
Even the simple act of playing has been taken away from children and put on mommy's schedule
in the form of play dates. Something that should be spontaneous and free is now being rigidly planned.
When does a kid ever get to sit in the yard with a stick anymore? You know, just sit there with a
fucking stick. Do today's kids even know what a stick is? You know, you sit in the yard with a
fucking stick and you dig a fucking hole. You know, and you look at the hole and you look at the
stick and you have a little fun. But kids don't have sticks anymore. I don't think there are any
sticks left. I think they've all been recalled because of lead pains. Who would have thought that one
day the manufacturing of sticks would be outsourced to China? But you know, something a kid shouldn't
be wasted as time on a stick anyway. If he's four years old, he should be home, study in for his
kindergarten entrance exams. You know, but that should only happen now. Yeah, yeah, there are places
that have kindergarten entrance exams. The poor little fuck. The poor little fuck he can barely
locate his dick. You know, and already he's being pressured to succeed. Pressured to succeed
for the sake of the parents. Isn't this really just a sophisticated form of child abuse?
Speaking of that. Speaking of child abuse. Speaking of child abuse, next stop. Great school.
Great school. Who won't be allowed to play tag because it encourages victimization.
And he won't be allowed to play dodgeball because it's exclusionary. I have provoked
aggression standing around is still okay. Standing around is still permitted, but the won't be
for long because sooner or later some kid is going to be standing around and his foot will fall
asleep and his parents will sue the school and it'll be good by fucking standing around.
Now fortunately, all is not lost. All is not lost because at least we know
that when he does get to play whatever games he is allowed to play, the child will never lose.
We know he'll never lose because in today's America, no child ever loses. There are no losers anymore.
Everyone's a winner. No matter what the game or sport or competition, everybody wins.
Everybody wins. Everybody gets a trophy. No one is a loser. No child these days
ever gets to hear those all important character building words. You're lost Bobby.
You're lost. You're a loser, Bobby. They miss out on that. You know if they tell a kid who
lost these days, you were the last winner. A lot of these kids never get to hear the truth about
themselves until they're in their 20s when their boss calls them in and says, Bobby,
play the shit out of your dressing. Get the fuck out of here. You're a loser.
Man, George Cardano, I love that guy. He's so incredibly on the ball.
If you don't have HBO and you can get it, please go and get HBO. I'd love to support them
for bringing great stuff like this to television. There is still hope, even though it's not
publicly accessible television. Unfortunately, there's just no other way to get it if you can't get
HBO, but man is that guy awesome. I love it. Listen up, so go ahead. This is for us from Washington.
Clicking over the DSC. Listen up. We have a low-than-off opportunity. You know, that has
re-establish this human connection through the voice, it's through podcasting. And our global forum
isn't the DSC. We need to start giving solutions. We have to give ideas, have big ideas.
It doesn't matter. We have the collective dollars to make things work. That is step one.
Be proactive in what we think. Step two, we have to implement those ideas and report back
and only through this two-step process. We even begin to take back what is ours. We do not
have to live in a macavillion world where the few and corrupt are the only ones competent enough
and willing enough to make the world their own. We can do this. We have the power, but we will
be nothing but servants, dogs of the elite if you sit here and listen to Adam and the savants a year
out what the world is in this current status. That may not be good to understand the future,
but the future will continue on its current path unless we make changes and the changes will
come from the people. Adam is behind us, the savants are behind us, but that is not enough. We must
make ourselves known. We must put the power back in our hands. Now, what do you want to do?
You want to listen to me and you're going to think to yourself, what can I do? Because until you do,
nothing will happen. And once you think, you must now act to tell us,
talk about what we can do. And then we must, as listeners do, what is said, try what is said.
This is a daily source code.
Adam, hey, Dave Jackson from the Musicians cooler. Wanted to give you a special heads up about this
week's episode. I mean, can anyone say bummer the charts 2008? Because I'm interviewing
Shannon Curfman. This is an artist who had a major deal at the age of 14. And this powerful
vocalist, hugely talented guitar player, had her first album go out toward the world when she got back
in the infinite wisdom of the major record label, tried to turn her into Britney Spears. It's
like turning Led Zeppelin into the back street boys that ain't gunna fit. And you know what,
she stuck to her guns. And even though they held her career hostage for years, she came back in 2007.
She is rocking harder than ever on her own record label. You can check out our new album,
fast lane addiction at emusic.com forward slash music news and get that album for free.
If you are a musician, you need to stop by musicians cool.com as I interview Shannon Curfman.
It's time to bummer the charts, man. Oh yeah, I'm forcing the force to grate here,
hope you win. I love you no home home. Oh yeah, scruncher.
Oh, for this is just like professional lives, you know what I'm saying? Wow, wow, listen.
It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga.
It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga.
It was your nigga. It was your nigga. It was your nigga. Was your nigga. It was your nigga.
For my people survival is self-steam
I want your fight for racist churches
We sound fun, they're good
I'll be fighting and keep the hockey pace out
My nigga, whoever clocks someone who talks shit
Look at your bowl and imagine if they shot at you
I was raving with your moms
And of course that I'm insane
Had chemical weapons we sold in that shit
Have the Ronald Reagan's election
Most of every contract is fighting
And we have a former military bank
And all the war on terror
They control in the ghetto with the fear of attack
Trying to strike the fact that they engineer in the crack
So I'm scrap-likely malvo
Holding a sniper rifle
These bullets are touch of kids
And I don't mean like microwave money
You send to the wall, strip down
And cycle that fire on a house
Because that's what you would like
You was innocent people get murdered in the struggle daily
And poor people never get shit
Struggle daily
You say no alien, conspiracy, dirty shit is real
Written on a dollar underneath
The Masonic seal
I don't rap to get presidents
I'd rather see the president dead
It's never been said
But I said presidents
I didn't blow a project
It was your nigga
Tell a joke, nigga
Stocked down, nigga
I didn't blow a project
It was your nigga
Tell a joke, nigga
It's an eight seconds away
From the side of some cops
From the front building
They hit the head out
Was it a hit-out?
Must have a mortal technique
And M&M tell the truth
Had just scraped that one off of YouTube
and I realize that's not such a good idea because, well, I knew this sound quality would be inferior, but it's also mono.
But it's good to hear protests alive and well in hip-hop, bring it on, bring more of it, please.
Hey Adam, this is another hit test and we're going to start right away. We're going to throw number one.
Hello.
Are you kidding me, Adam?
That could only be EWF, earth, wind and fire with September the month I was born in.
Number two.
I know that one too.
One of the few concerts I went to as a teenager, all in oats.
I can't go for that.
And number three.
You know, the young always has to put one in that I absolutely know chance of getting.
It looks like two out of three stars for today's show.
And time's up.
And these are the answer for this week, hit this.
I love this song.
Answer number one is from 1979.
This is earth with fire, a September.
Number two.
Can't believe it's a timber.
Filled anything.
Number one is 25.
This is answering number two.
You're coming to the room.
In 1982, all in oats.
And I can't go for that.
I can't believe it.
You're going to stop when you're down.
I need to throw the line.
I can't go for that.
You're all in oats.
You can't do it.
I can't go for that.
You can't really.
And all in oats has answered number two.
No, what was this?
Answer number three.
From 1983 unique.
Oh, God.
What's your name?
Of course.
What I got is what you need unique is answer number three and that concludes hit
number one hundred and ninety yeah so what I'm how did you do this week well two out of three
on I never would have gotten unique that's just not one embedded in my soundtrack
if you want to review the answers to this hit this or any older hit this or if you want to buy
the tracks featured in the hit this online through iTunes you can go to hit this.mevio.com
nice there you'll find everything you need all righty Adam thank you for playing everyone else thanks
for listening next week I'll be back for another hit this so until then have a very nice week
and remember try to think with your heart bye bye
come extra come extra come extra come extra come extra come extra come extra come extra come extra
hello Adam mevio carry here is your European correspondent me this is me so do you remember your
old car the Trinity well European Union is back pedalling down on biofuel because
as you might know or not increased demand for biofuel in EU and USA has caused hunger in poor countries
before saving planet we have forgotten about people the biofuel do good as actually did
evil the and the by the way I have heard that curry fort is nowadays less popular in UK
I mean I think for some people they think what is actually British food kibab well it's not
a terrorist or curry it's not in fact curry is fallen out of favor curry's are going out of
favor now nobody's really interesting curry's any more the interest is is tailing off of rake
which is a shame so Adam please ensure and the same will not happen to mevio in
you media arena you I'm sure once you get that RSS feed implemented for comments in
on each episode I'm sure that will be guaranteed a long life and lasting future come extra
blogger our EU correspondent then of course a bunch of the charlie everybody nice to have in back
I disagree though I think that just like we're being gained and being ripped off on fuel prices
and oil watch for the announcements now it's earnings time once again and look for the big
billion dollar profit announcements from the oil companies they are ripping us off big time so I
kind of have to believe that the food importers or the growers or let's just call that industry
are probably taking advantage of this exact mean that you've grabbed onto com extra blogger
I have yet to see some real conclusive evidence of this that's just not enough people driving
on bio fuel yet for the price to have multiplied by it's in some cases 10 times in a very very
short amount of time I think it's again people are just ripping us off I have absolutely no belief
that is taking place at this moment I really don't think that's uh that's the case
and we're just being ripped off we definitely have to revolt against this this is uh
ah boy well anyway I got a company to run and then we'll go save the world and win
valuable cash prizes I guess hey Adam it's uh I've been the uh I guess the blind listener of
DSC oh man can we have a blind survivor now as well I mean I just I got Jeff Jeff man we got to talk
uh and uh I just wanted to uh hey say hey you got a great show why do I listen to the daily
source code I know it's kind of a little topic but still why do I listen to the daily source code
because it's just it's a great show full of information about technology and uh just when you
have a lady pion it's even better but also I wanted to express my appreciation
uh to you for playing the movies for the blind promo when I heard that I immediately got excited
and uh went to the site and uh subscribed and it's just a great it's a very great
feature for us visually impaired people because I am visually impaired and uh it's just a great
it's a great service and you know a lot of people think visually impaired people are retarded or dumb
and no only dumb people are dumb if anybody here on the DSC thinks so it's bullshit we are not dumb
we're not stupid we're like everybody else without a sense it's like deaf people they're not dumb
you know anyway thanks a lot thanks a lot Adam appreciate it and um love you great
and bye bye bye bye bye bye. I'm happy very much sorry rong one there we go that's better
the only thing I wish I could do for uh the the blind audience is I wish we could
get our accessibility fixed up on our site man it's so much crap when you're dealing with
JavaScript that's a whole new site that has to be built I need to calm down that I need to
to do it with some music from the soundtrack to my life.
You have just yourself grey, a puzzle pool, by any other name.
You love no, you love no, you love no, you love no, you love no, you love no, you love no, you love no, you love no.
I'll cross again.
Nothing but the best for you would do.
My love was finished one.
Now you're just a memory you've gone from me.
Just so much wasted time.
You can rest assured that I cry.
The best for you is one never quite my style.
I stop crying.
Won't go away when I feel it all the way.
For real I'm from my mind.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You love no, you love no, you love no, you never closed it.
You love no, I'll cross again.
You love no, you love no, you love no, no, you love no, no.
We'll count higher and higher.
Hold the dime
You have just to say I'm to blame, I'm to the blue, I'm by any other name
You have no one more than blame, you have no one else
You have no one else, you have no one else
Yeah, that's one from the soundtrack to my life, all right?
Presented, of course, by the organizers, for the preservation of the soundtrack of our life under its educational auspices
Because we need to share these memories amongst ourselves, friends
I think it was a young poet who sent me this, could have been rare, not sure
But thank you anyway, high gloss from my high school days when I was on pirate radio in Amsterdam
You'll never know, and it was exactly what I needed to wrap up the show for today
Because I just needed to calm down a little bit
Hey, I'll do another show for you tomorrow and Wednesday, maybe even Thursday
Friday, maybe a problem this week
Because I'm accompanying the lovely lady Patricia to her first live show
Which will be broadcast live Friday night
So I'm a little looking forward to that, this should be a lot of fun
Anyway, we'll talk more tomorrow, you know how to reach me, it's adamatmevio.com
The show notes, of course, dailysourcecode.com
And there's my weblog, curie.com where I do post things from time to time
That are outside of the context of this program
And I look forward to talking to you guys again tomorrow
So please, I hope that I've fired you up, you got to live your life with passion
And you have to, you must absolutely enjoy your freedom
Another fine, medium presentation, share it with a friend