This, you think it will be so it's cool.
It was $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm sorry.
Almost people are looking forward to the weekend.
Looking forward to Friday the day before the weekend.
Chocolate heads are looking forward to Friday.
Maybe Thursday because the next day is Friday.
Either way, it's because of the football Friday.
And here's Adam Curry with your football Friday for the DSC.
$7.66.
$7.66
$10.66
$7
$7.66
$8.66
$8
$7.66
$9
$6.66
$7.66
$8.66
$9.66
I mean, is this thing on the radio?
I think I've heard this before.
I've sourced it on the podcast,
I'm using network, electric, soul,
but I know I'll place a link in the show notes
and if I get to it.
I am so personally full of artists
as the outrageous, what a week it's been.
And then I find out today that the Builderberg Group
is meeting in Virginia, the Builderberg Group.
Of course, started by Prince Bernard of the Netherlands,
which is rumored to be the secret meeting,
annual meeting of all the world leaders,
mainly people from royalty and the financial world,
also a big media moguls are there,
but you never read anything about it in the press anywhere.
And so I kind of got sucked in a little bit.
Before I know it, there I am.
I'm on Alex Jones's site and I'm reading up on it.
And I'm spiraling down into Build Giltner's videos
about 9, 11, that they were no actual planes.
Oh, man, it's like, oh, my brain just hurts.
Oh, but I've got a fantastic football already for you.
Of course, this is the Daily Source Code 766 coming to you
from the affluent suburb of Surrey, often known as Giltner.
Good morning, Prince Giltner.
The spending of I'm Arno here to Giltner.
The town's first recording is in the 9th century,
when he actually views Giltner,
there's a base to launch his attack on Danish health London.
He's only managing to reach the outskirts of the city
and messes him six hours.
The feet occasionally match to the stage, right?
Yeah.
Nice.
I've been holding him back on this one for an entire week.
Happy once again to say hello to the one-on-one he surges he took.
Yeah.
To make a motion to rock this mother out.
Your honor, please don't bang that gavel.
You can try this cowbell out.
Let's all give a night.
To the hardest work and lawyer, he's charging time, yeah.
He's charging time, oh, yeah.
You're out there, what do you say?
You might, yo, how's going to Adam and Jersey time?
The official musical just of the shot shot shot.
So dude, I've got to give you somebody big this week.
One of my all-time, all-time favorite potsafe artist is back with her brand new album.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm feeling a little horny this week because I got blue number nine.
Stephanie Saskin and the gang is right out of Jersey City, New Jersey, and they are just
absolutely a lot of fun.
Check it out.
It's a brand spanking new one from blue number nine called I like the way you move on the
daily F and source code.
Check it out.
I used to spend my time just keeping busy not to hear the nagging voices side by head
with my friend love it's no brand new.
I know one will understand your whole jaw hand with fake controls so just give it up.
There is no hope get used to being alone but then you walked into my world with a
sweet smile upon your face and I got dizzy when you told me not to worry about the past.
And the nagging voice announced that there was no way this could last but I was swept
away by love and hoping to take a chance because I like it I like it, I like it
with you, I like it, I like it, I like the way you move, I like it, I like it, I like it
with you, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like the way you move.
What the honey move it ended like honey moons always cool little irks and things you did out of the blues
and the wangers turned my cheek to see just good all the way I felt miss on the stud and when you asked me what was wrong I couldn't tell you what I should
said I like it, I like it, I like it with you, I like it, I like it, I like the way you move.
Said, I like it, I like it, I like it where you, I'm doing it, I like it, I like it, I like the way you were born.
Falling down, I came falling down, getting through the kitchen, fading, crashing around.
But we held on fast and it turned back around.
And now and forever I will sing it about it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it where you, I like it, I like the way you were born.
I like it, I like it, I like it where you, I like it, I like it, I like the way you were born.
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like the way you were born.
I like it, I like it, I like the way I'm kind, I like it,, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like that, I like...
You like it, I like the way that that makes it and it does, it's the jersey grows into work, of course.
Number nine source from Surgeers, he taught the official musicologist of the Charlie.
I like the way you move baby.
If you've never checked out all that pod safe stuff, you really should.
It's a good shot going on there.
Oh boy.
You know, I do want to talk about a couple of things even though today is a football show.
I'm going to keep it relatively short.
And it's coming up a little bit later on because we got lots of music to play.
Lots of music to share, soundtrack from our live type stuff.
Come up in a little bit.
But of course, this being a Friday, you know what that usually means.
It's the hit test.
Brought to you by Young Pullet.
Oh, I'm casting with Adam Curry.
This is the hit test.
Hit it test.
Young Pullet.
Hey Adam.
How are you doing?
I'm doing great, man.
I'm ready for the hit test again.
Okay.
I'm going to start right away with intro number one.
Let me.
Oh, shit.
I know this one, Young.
Oh.
I think I might be too fried to play today.
I can't come up with the answer.
Number two.
It sounds like I'm every woman, maybe.
Maybe, maybe chuck a con.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to say one.
Number three.
Boom, boom.
Check it like a boom.
That one I know.
Uh, I'm going to do everybody walk the dinosaur.
Was not was.
Oh, gee.
Maybe we got one out of three this week.
And that's it.
And all of this week's answers are from.
Of course.
Hit me.
And answer number one.
What's this?
It's by Lionel Richie.
Oh, well, gee.
I don't mind losing a point on that.
You look sometimes.
I sit in the wonder.
Without you six.
You say I.
Say I.
I remember it now.
It's not on the soundtrack to my life.
Say I buy Lionel Richie's answer.
Number one.
And this is answer number two.
By Rick James.
Yeah, I could have known this one too, actually.
Great James Glowers.
Answer number two.
Okay.
I got that one right.
And this is answer number three.
Was not was.
I like this.
For a million years ago.
I'll need a single bit.
Pick up a monkey.
Everybody walk the dinosaur.
Open the door.
Get on the floor.
Everybody walk the dinosaur.
Look at like a boom.
Open the door.
Everybody walk the dinosaur.
Answer number three.
Was not was.
And what to dinosaur.
And that concludes.
It's number 125.
Don't even ask me on.
How did you do this week?
Let me see somewhere between really bad and sucks bill.
One right out of three this week.
Like always hit this up.
Meet the other corners.
The place to find the answers to this and any older hitists.
And of course, the links to what I do.
So you can buy the tricks featured on the hitists online.
Adam, thank you for playing.
No, thank you.
Yes.
Thanks for listening.
Next week I'll be back for another hitist.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And try to think with your heart to come out.
We'll be back.
To test at gmail.com.
info.
youngpool.com.
Jay and BOLVT.
Got to go.
All right.
The maximum music freight train continues here on the full bar Friday.
It is yours.
Spectacular with the Danny Warhols.
Now pod safe as well.
Valerie Young.
We'll be back.
Note here from Thomas Nyberg, hello Adam.
You seem to enjoy having samples of fresh human insanity
and evil delivered directly to your doorstep,
so I thought I'd share this with you.
Rick Falkfinger, the leader of the Swedish pirate party.
The skust a wire tapping bill called,
better adapted military intelligence gathering
that soon may hit hard on the privacy
of anyone relying on any electronic communication
routed through Sweden.
Check this out.
At about 20 points in the national information
infrastructure network, all traffic is spliced off
and fed into the fierce pirates of Adirn Staten agency.
These points are placed as to catch all traffic
entering and leaving the Swedish borders.
But we'll catch much if not most domestic traffic as well.
So, you know, you know, you sure could all go on.
You got to ask yourself, do they really work for us?
That almost hurts.
Man, those guys are nuts.
The Danny Warhols, they put this like a tracks up on the Pods head music network.
That was Valerie Yum, holy moly.
Those guys are pretty out there, I'll say.
I learned something really interesting today.
Remember I was talking the other day about the possibility of RFID chips being located in 510 and 20 Euro bills.
Well, you know, you think why would that be?
And of course you can test this yourself.
If you have a Euro note, 510 or 20 in Denomination, just pop it into the microwave.
And you know, turn it on for 10 seconds within a second or two.
You'll hear a pop and there will be a hole right off the center of the bill.
Now, I've been talking to some people.
I talked to a guy from the RFID platform in the Netherlands.
And he said, oh, no, I've heard that before.
That's just a little piece of wire they weave into the fabric there.
Like, well, yeah, but why would you put a piece of wire in there?
Well, you know, but that's one of the ways you can tell if it's counterfeit or not.
I said no, because I looked it up, you know, the European website.
And there's five ways you can tell if a bill is real or not.
And it has to do with the hologram, you know, some raised bombs.
But no mention of a piece of wire, which by the way could act perfectly as an antenna.
And I've been reading up on RFID chips.
These things are actually pretty interesting.
They don't really transmit anything.
What they do is they respond to what is known as an activator or a combination RFID reader.
But basically, it sends out a magnetic signal.
It hits the chip.
That's enough to power the chip, the send back a little signal.
And, you know, there's different frequencies.
And, you know, it really depends on what your what application you're using.
And for you'll get anywhere from a couple of centimeters distance range to actually a red reports of three to 500 meters,
which seems like an awful long way.
But, you know, it could be an active RFID chip.
But anyway, so I learned today by complete coincidence that as of June 15th,
so that's was at nine days from today.
And I've read nothing about this.
Go ahead and Google it.
Do a Google news search for this.
And then once you Google it like in the regular Google search,
it'll show up to get the European website laws.
But as of June 15th, no person may transport 10,000 euros or more than 10,000 euros in or out of the European Union.
And the reasons for this according to the law, which, actually, I think I wrote that down somewhere.
And let me see.
It was like 1899.
I'm sorry, I can't recall it.
I thought I had my browser history.
Anyway, you have to declare, which is very similar to the United States by the way,
except there it's less.
It's now $10,000, which is significantly less than 10,000 euros.
You have to report it, which I'm sure not many people do.
Interestingly enough, now, at most major airports, already, they're using money sniffing dogs.
Now, they say that this is to combat whitewashing or laundering.
Whitewashing, this would be a European version, but laundering of money in particular for funding of terrorism.
That's why they say they're doing it.
So, I'm just putting a couple things together here, like one and one, that all of a sudden,
or some reason, this RFID chip in your money pops onto my radar screen.
When at the very same time, they're starting to put sniffer dogs out there to sniff money.
And if you don't declare more than 10,000 euros, then they can confiscate it.
And they can find you, you know, I've seen some numbers of 16,000 euros.
They can find you for not declaring your money, your own money.
And I'm thinking, you know, what is more efficient than a sniffer dog?
Hmm, could it be perhaps an RFID chip embedded into the money?
Yes, he gets another star for answering the question correctly.
And is the food bar Friday, my friends?
And this is Go Home Productions.
you. There's often you've expressed a complaint before about how the web repeats bad
information and how it's all a bit terrible and no one does near original research.
Well it occurs to me that maybe that doesn't actually matter. It's like the gutter
press and Britain exists, but it doesn't mean that everyone believes everything
that's in it and it doesn't mean that the good information isn't out there if you
wanted and the the upside of course to the easy replication if the net is when there
is good information that is also easily replicated. So maybe it's not so much
worth worrying about. Maybe just be happy that we gain the things that we gain and
rely on people to use their nons to decide what information is good because I
think most people will only accept bad information if they don't actually care and
they're not actually going to act on it anyway. Anyone who's actually going to do
anything will go and find out the truth like you and the European Parliament. You
find the bad information and then you're going to talk to the right people and you
discover that it's bad and the net result is positive. I like that. I hope that
contribute something to the conversation. I love you, mean it, no home, great hair, hope you win.
They work for us. Yeah, keep out the good work. Yeah, thank you. Man, I appreciate that.
Whatever you're on, you better be sharing that. But you know, this is exactly what's gone through
my head, you know. I'm starting to see some really big pictures again and maybe it's just for
you know, it's a very, very much red pill stuff. You know, I'm seeing an overview. I'm looking
into people's eyes. I'm listening to how they're speaking. I'm seeing things happen around us.
There's no coincidences, you know. And it's just like, you know, more and more people are
tuning into this, they work for us thing and do they really work for us or are they working for
themselves and stick in it to us? And I'm conflicted about it. I really, really am. You know,
on the one hand, it seems so totally easy for all of this to be true. All the conspiracy theories,
you know, that Brussels is trying to take over the power on their end and that, you know,
there's all kinds of secret seeds and secrets and clubs and moneymen and powerful people
who are pulling strings all over the place and got a little bit out of whack with that credit
crisis, but they're re-adjusting and I don't know. And on the other hand, I'm thinking, you know,
we're just a bunch of fucked up humans on this dumb earth, you know, trying to figure it out
and we're probably all evil in our own little way. So yeah, sometimes I struggle a little bit.
I got this awesome, awesome email. I'm very excited about it. I want to share with you guys
crap who sent this to me. Oh, shit. I didn't do very very good on my, uh, on my prep today.
Anyways, from Russian to date, RAU. Russian geologists have discovered a new mineral, which absorbs
radiation from liquid, liquid, nuclear waste. They're now striving to chemically clone it in the
hope it may help solve the problem of radioactive waste disposal. So this new mineral was tested
and named at the Cola Science Institute. And let's see a quote here. It's nature that is showing
us a way to solve the problem of preserving those radioactive isotopes. That's what the, uh, the
geologists have discovered. His name is Jaco Ventuch. This is big news. This is really too,
atomic rod, uh, the big savant, uh, for all things nuclear. He got to get on the case man. I got
to figure out what's going on. This is really, really awesome. I'm excited.
Um, let's see, uh, let's get back to the music for a second here. Um, and I don't usually play
songs with intros, but uh, with a hell. It's a special food bar. Bernie hit it. Please.
Hey, Adam, this is Bernie. World of Bernie.com, you remember we used to talk when you were with
Pod Show. Yep. Now I know it's been a while since I've been in touch, but I've been working really
hard to bring new artists onto the Pod Saves scene. I mean, this week, I got four terrific artists,
and it was hard for me to choose which one I was going to get in touch with you about. I got
to tell you that there's a couple people doing this now who are like independent promoters for
Pod Saves music artists. And, you know, and they're starting something. There's something going on
with this. It's very much, uh, it's very analogous to the, uh, the old music business. Only,
it's like people working directly with people, independence, you know, trying to make some
shit happen, uh, hopefully making some muddance of money together, and Bernie's one of them.
And, uh, that's why, you know, I'm happy to make an exception for the intro. So I went with one
that was close to home. My uncle, Brian Kane, has been on the professional music scene for a while.
And I know, especially when it comes to food bar, you love hard rock and tunes. I got special
permission from him to play this Pod Saves and to share it with you so that you could play it on
the Charlie. This is a tune off of his new album called Haunted and the tune is,
you can't stay here. All right, let's hit it.
Oh, go, where you going? Go back to you.
And it'll do the flow. What you're going to do, babe, with me up some more, I don't care what
you say. Leave it enough to the sky. I know the sides are far away, but taking the road so it's all the same.
We got to be all by the end of the day.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh,
I said you can't say it, I can't say it
You know it's got a little bit of easy top and down, but it's fine
Oh no, don't have to worry
Is it a rubbish out to hurt me?
So it's taking me with you to worry
Yeah, I'm on my way for the same
I can't say it
Oh, I am an honest person
Bernie, you know me so well
I prefer to try like this on a footballer front
I guess what? I'm actually staying home this weekend
Go figure, Billion
Say the lady Patricia and the princess will be off
On a little trick for a couple days
So I'll be home alone
Up until Wednesday
That's a secret message, all the girlfriends
I'll be all alone, which will mean plenty of Charlie to be done
That's for sure
I cannot wait
If it's a Friday
We should be doing some music from the soundtrack to my life
Well, this is what I've been thinking about
And this is what I want to play and dedicate to the lady Patricia
Bad company, feel like making love
If I had those golden drinks
Of my yesterday
I would have been in the heaven
But till it I am in all the way
Feel like making love
Baby, if I think about you
I think about love
Darling, if I live without you
I live without love
And if I have
The sun and moon
And if I shine in my heart
I would give you
What night and day
The sentence fly
If I had those golden drinks
Of my yesterday
I would have been in all the way
Feel like making love
And if I have
Those golden drinks
Of my yesterday
I would have been in the heaven
But till it I am in all the way
Feel like making love
Feel like bringing love
Feel like getting love
They won't get their Tammy flew.
Oh my goodness, I think if we can wrap up the conversation
we've been having over the past week or two about the price
of diesel, actually when talking with nuclear, of course,
just to talk to you, we just talked about that new mineral
that absorbs all the radiation.
Wouldn't that be beautiful if that's true?
Oh man, being out of sometimes it's hard.
The figure out what's true and what's not true,
but I'm going to stay on top of that one.
A great article in GQ about nuclear power.
I think it's available online as well.
You might want to check that out.
And then this showed up on the daily source code drop,
which, of course, you'll find at drop.io-slash-d daily source code.
I don't know who it's by, but man, it sure does ring true.
There's only so much oil in the ground.
And it's kind of like a really bad 70s Charlie's Angel soundtrack
to them, but I'm digging it.
In a way, it's retro, and it fits right into the Fubar Friday.
The festivities are definitely all.
There's so much oil in the ground.
It's what a little bit won't be in much round.
Tell that to your kids right from the ground.
That's all because it's only so much oil in the ground.
We can't get loose without that juice.
We can't buy anything when things are showing out.
Because the fact we just didn't got some things you can't get loose.
Because there's only so much oil in the ground.
So let it don't be in, not around.
All the nightzones is out, power must be found.
Because there's only so much oil in the ground.
There's a fact of the nightzones.
So what is worth something a little girl?
Unfortunately, no sense for it.
If there's always so much oil in the ground,
there's no use for our views.
No, it's use for our views.
Because there's still not what we use when I see that awesome sky.
But it's an end of the world where it'll wash away the ground by.
There's no use for our views.
No, it's use for our own views.
Because it's just assumed that what we use when I see that awesome sky.
But it's an end of the world where it'll wash away the ground by.
Because there's only so much oil in the ground.
So let it don't be in, not around it.
You can tell that to a shield and why you're probably been brought that out.
There's only so much oil in the ground.
Because there's only so much oil in the earth.
There's a bank of life.
What is worth something a little girl?
Unfortunately, no sense for it.
There's always so much oil in the earth.
We can't lose.
Now that you can't lose.
But that's your one.
We can't buy everyone.
Things showing that we're cool.
And the fact we just ain't got a picture.
There's only so much oil in the earth.
Could you imagine?
If the mineral really is for real?
Damn, when that be awesome.
Only so much oil in the ground.
And again, I'm sorry.
I don't know how to perform that.
Maybe next time someone who dropped that in the drop can just leave a little tag.
And tell us who that was by.
So I can put something into the show notes.
So normally we do a final thought of the week.
I'm not actually going to do it this Friday.
I'm going to let one of these comments that we're sending
do some of the talking.
It kind of reflects how my week has been.
Hey Adam, this is Leslie from the Daily Christian Show.
Daily Christian Show.
I'm just plugging my podcast while I'm at Daily Christian Show.
That's because I can't.
About the European Union Constitution, sorry, 3D.
Obviously it's written by some folks who don't understand the origin of rights.
In the Declaration of Independence, Thomas Jefferson pointed out that we the people are endowed
by our creator with certain unalienable rights, life liberty, and the pursuit of happiness and
all that.
I know the Daily source code is a no religion zone, so I'll stay in terms of everyone can
get behind.
Humans have natural rights, we're born with them.
They're a part of our being.
Government doesn't give rights to people, they simply recognize rights that are already
there.
Now the problem is that not everyone thinks the same way Thomas Jefferson did.
They can't see how rights are a natural thing, so they think they're an artificial
thing.
They think we made them up.
The problem is that if we made them up, we can also take them away, or we can decide
that someone else's rights like the rights of a government are more important than the
rights of an individual like me.
And that's what you see in the Lisman Treaty, we have a right to life unless it gets
in the way of the government.
We have a right to respite, unless it gets in the way of the government.
That's definitely not the language you see in the U.S. Constitution.
Our Constitution avoids exceptions because look what happens when you allow exceptions.
The Constitution makes an exception for habeas corpus and now look how President Bush
is abusing the hell out of it with Guantanamo Bay and Secret CIA presence.
The Constitution says your stuff can't be seized without due process, or bought out by
eminent domain, and if it re-adact passes for due process, and eminent domain abuse is
running rampant as rich people use local governments to take over the land of four people.
That's what happens when you make exceptions for government.
They government always takes advantage of those exceptions, always.
Now look at all those exceptions in the Lisman Treaty, why even bother to list rights?
But you see the exceptions are there because the writers that the EU Constitution don't
believe rights are natural.
Well, some of them might, but those people didn't put together the final draft.
The draft reads like EU government is more concerned with its rights than ours, which
it is.
Except the government's rights are artificial, not natural.
Governments aren't made by nature.
By nature, well, you see nature on the nature channel, right?
Only the strong survives.
It's a rival of the fittest.
Well, we don't want that, so we make governments.
Governments are manufactured, not artificial.
So since their manufactured, they have no rights.
My laptop has no rights, my wristwatch has no rights.
My government has no rights either.
Stalling out of governments rights in a Constitution means you don't understand the first
thing about where rights come from.
If you think rights are granted by a government that you've just taken the first step towards
totalitarianism, because of the government grants it, the government could take it back.
Back to Thomas Jefferson.
Governments get their power from the just consent of the government.
If the government abuses its power, it's our right to overthrow it.
It's not a person, it's not an entity, it's a machine that's gone wrong and when that happens,
you pull a plug.
Anyway, that's my rant.
Thank you for watching Show.com.
Demographics 37, starting somewhere between Diddley and Squat, single White Nail, love the
show, love the hair, love you, man it, your wife is hot, the folder, six times, they'd
better work for us.
I'm Laces where you used to be, it wasn't inside of you, but the way you looked at me,
you're getting a close test, so many mistakes, it wasn't inside of you, like it always
is, it's me, talking to businesses, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me
it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me, I feel like a
It's the world.
You've been in your summer, but you don't ever find me home.
What don't get up in your town?
I do what I need, and you won't keep doing it.
You're doing it, you're doing it, you're doing it.
We are wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up.
Come here to love you, you're free.
Come here to love you.
Come here to love me.
I know what I don't know, I never waited with the night
I know how hard it is to always walk out in the light
And it's an ensign job
To load a bad book in vain
It's an ensign job
To hang on to the jail, I'll never hear
Don't know if I would you give
They know your mother's late name
And what you have for breakfast
What you have never met
It's an ensign job
To load a bad book in vain
Let those words be the final thought of the week, my fellow charcoal heads.
Donamently knows it.
As those Sean Pan has those Rosio Donald and the Baldwin brothers.
They work for us, don't they?
Or do they?
Until we speak again.
Live life with passion.
Enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medial presentation.
Stick it in your ear.