DeltaSharrade Charley Seven Niner Niner.
All right, everyone!
A one, two, zero
I like to think I'm flying into this journey
I'm testing this very great
Ow!
Oh, youогоz!
Eat it, yeah, eat it well!
Whole bit of trash on a needle!
Always only, just fly behind the wind
I'll dare to see a little bit of nell over there
I'll do fine
id struggle may, If you must freakin' run out of who you haw!
Don't let me feel it, take both
Ouch!
It's in this room
Can he?
I'm called the nation
It's in this room
I thought you'd have a sailor back to
Rock my soul
No, no, no, no, no
Who's that?
That thing
I'm like a mini mouse
I'm real
Oh, nice
Ready, oh
Keep all of this through
Go back to the room, so
Oh, not that as
You're waiting
On that door
And a heart of rain
You might have to walk my life
Into a big hole
But every night is waiting
Over time
Should we get away from
Yeah
I'm alive
It's in this room
Yeah
I don't have a sailor back to
Oh, I'm alive
It's in America
You may not be
Looking farther from a flame
But you might not escape away
On that door
And a heart of rain
I'm alive
It's in this room
Yeah
I don't have a sailor back to
I don't have something
I don't have anything
It's in America
I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I
I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in sini and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night, and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night and I'm in the night
was a killer, particularly because I lost two full days in travel.
And well, here we are, it's the third day of the week, I'm sorry.
It is, of course, Friday.
So it's a footballer Friday on the Charlie,
extra long show for you.
And I'm in the curry manner here in good ol' blighty.
Only for a bit, though.
I'm kind of on a massive swing around.
There's a, I can't tell you what it is, because it's,
I, anyway, it's someone might be listening.
I can't really tell you what's going on, but there's a family thing we're doing.
So that's why I came back.
So we're traveling just a little bit over the weekend.
Then Monday, back to San Francisco,
because there's still plenty of work to do.
Plenty of things to see.
I'm going to be in Los Angeles the weekend after next.
Oh, man.
It's, it's, it's crazy.
But, nonetheless, you guys have once again prepared a fantastic show for me.
I feel extremely privileged because, oh, wow, I see that,
oh, this is not good.
The, it looks like the battery on my, my fader fox.
That's the, that's the, the MIDI controller I used to control the Ableton live software,
which by the way, I'm finally getting it around to showing you guys exactly how all that works.
I think the batteries are low, so everything's like flashing.
I hope it'll make it through this show.
In fact, I might have to even have to run downstairs and get some fresh batteries.
Anyway, a proper food bar Friday.
It's all lined up.
This is the stuff that you guys have been leaving at the drop.
The drop.au slash daily source code.
Some good comments.
Lots of individual really cool YouTube videos to play for you.
Of course, as it pertains to the financial meltdown.
And, you know, it's listening to that song.
And actually, I chose living in America because it kind of reminds me of a time that we won't see again for a long, long time.
Remember how carefree we were when that song came out written by the way by Dan Hartman and Charlie midnight.
Song by, of course, Mr. James Brown himself.
Remember those were crazy good times, right?
And we, it was a living in America.
Couldn't be any better.
Well, those days are definitely over chocolate heads.
Because I see nothing but hard times ahead.
Not, not something we can't overcome, but with the bailout bill,
which of course is blossomed, I should say, not even bloomed.
But blossomed from a mere 700 billion to it's probably probably a wind up around three or four.
Maybe even five trillion is what is going to cost us.
This is of course, brings with it inflation.
And don't take it from me.
Take it from the expert to be hearing from later on on the show.
All from mainstream media.
Nice little bits aggregated for your convenience.
And of course, we also have our European correspondent here with us.
The tell us how the situation is in the EU.
Comics trip.
Come on in, CSB.
Who are them?
And you're the carry.
Yes.
So EU, it means European Union is light in darkness.
And become of freedom, a force for good in the world.
And new EU directive prescribes that manufacturers of electronic devices should offer.
I quote, readily removable batteries.
No, I was.
Yes.
Also Apple.
The iPhone.
The company.
It's before us to offer extensible batteries in iPhones and iPods.
And otherwise, they can forget about 400 million customers of EU.
Cool.
You.
Yeah, I heard about this CSB.
I read about that.
I think a week ago.
And it was actually was a conclusion that was made.
I saw it first in the Netherlands.
There is a very strict directive on batteries and how disposable they have to be.
So that you need to be able to basically throw a device away without throwing its battery away.
Which indeed does mean that technically the iPhone and the iPod touch could be in violation of European Union law.
But that really doesn't matter too much because particularly when it comes to laws, it looks like the United States of America will be.
You know, I thought that the EU with the Lisbon Treaty and all that that it was going to become the United States of Europe.
But really the United States is becoming the United States of Europe.
We're becoming a complete socialist state.
It's it's crazy.
I'm going to get to some of these comments kind of fast here.
So we can get back into the music.
This is I might actually have to cut this one off a little bit.
It's DSC from Oregon, but you make such good points.
I definitely want to give him a voice here for a second.
Yeah, I'm DSC out of Oregon for now.
To call and listen to the daily source code on Saturday.
And I got to say,
I've been right so far.
I think everybody's it's been watching this unfold.
It's been kind of all I don't want to say patting ourselves on the back.
At least doing I told you.
I'm trying in affirmative response to what we knew was coming.
All these people that are denying it are simply again still still living in the bubble.
There's still hoping somebody's going to pull it out.
I got to interrupt you.
Meanwhile, I'm also replacing batteries in the this is the UK pronunciation.
You've noticed batteries.
We don't say batteries.
We say batteries.
Replacing the batteries in the fader Fox here.
Yeah.
Gosh.
Let me just back that up for one second.
I lost my train to Thought Hold on.
Again, still still living in the bubble.
There's still hoping somebody's going to pull it out.
Come on.
No one person can save this.
Yeah.
This is what's what I've noticed is that the Dow Jones industrial average, the index,
has pretty much become the public bell weather of whether the economy is going well or not well.
And it's stupid.
It's like a chart.
Graph, you know, which by the way, is being highly manipulated by the so-called plunge protection team,
the president's working group on financial markets,
Ron Paul keeps calling for transparency on that.
He says it's easier to get information about the CIA and what those guys are doing.
So a lot of this is manipulation.
But it's said the money's gone.
It's gone and nothing happened and nothing will happen.
You know, what will happen is a lot of people are getting bailed out.
But mainly banks and not small banks, but the big banks, Goldman Sachs,
where, of course, the Treasury Secretary is from.
And also his, his, his little PA, what's his name, Neil Cache Curry,
which, of course, everyone's laughing about.
I mean, what a perfect name for the guy.
Neil Cache and Kerry, who's been handing out money.
And of course, we didn't want to.
And you always, we didn't actually want to inject money directly into the bank.
So no, no, that's un-American.
Now, here we are.
We're doing it.
That's what the Europeans are doing.
Everyone's calling now for a new global financial order.
Listen to Gordon Brown.
This links in the show notes a deadly source code dot com.
That's how you do it.
What you do is you pull together all that you grab all the money.
They're going to, you know, have control of all the banks.
And of course, we actually have control.
We actually own it, but look at what government has become in the United States.
It literally is what the EU is becoming.
Or has the EU, the EU was a couple of steps ahead.
And from the helicopter view, I have today, you'll see later on in the show
that all these things are taking place simultaneously.
All nicely coming together.
All these horrible crises with oil and the climate.
And we're all going to die.
And then the financial markets is going to kill us all.
And actually it will kill a lot of us because we are going into a severe depression,
not a recession, but a depression.
But the lady P and I were in the city today looking at some houses.
She and Christina definitely want to move into the city.
I'm cool with it.
You know, I only have a couple, a couple of things.
I want to be able to stand up straight in these London houses.
By the way, that one you can check off the list.
That's box one tick.
Got to have good broadband pretty much throughout all the burrows,
the two burrows of London.
You can get massive broadband tick that box.
And we're looking to be kind of the southwest side.
Relatively easy access to an airfield.
It may even have to be big and hill for me.
I don't know what other choices there are of small airfields.
I'm probably not going to stay at Fair Oaks.
So tick that box as well.
But talking to the real estate agent.
By the way, the agents all over our ass.
This is calling every single minute.
You know, their signs all throughout London.
And actually this guy was talking about a couple of his clients.
He was trying to because they couldn't sell their properties.
And they were trying to rent it out.
Like 1500 pounds a week.
I mean, these are some serious properties.
But in actuality, what house needs to cost?
6,000 pounds a month.
And please, how rages.
But these were the prices in London.
UK where typically people spend six times their average income.
They're yearly income on their house.
In the US, it's only about 4.2, 4.5 times the annual income.
So you should know the credit crisis is hitting much harder here.
And so this guy was actually, I was trying to get these.
They have a sales on a rental apartment.
So he was trying to get them rented.
And he actually went to get the keys for two of them.
Just this week.
And they were sold.
The bank had already repossessed.
They weren't sold.
The bank had repossessed them.
Took back the keys.
He has to relocate another client of his.
Who was actually.
Who had rented a property.
And now that one got repossessed by the bank.
And the renters get and kicked out.
This of course is what's happening all over the globe.
This is just the beginning.
There's so many things going on.
Let's listen in there with DSE for Morgan.
Oops.
Sorry about that.
No one person can fix this.
No one person.
Taking off this somewhere is going to have a solution.
That's going to resolve this.
Absolutely.
That's the big.
The big thought mistake.
I mean, of course, when a new president comes in,
the stock market will probably go nuts.
He ain't a good way.
But now the the only thing that that someone could affect is
Will this be a long drawn out painful 10 years,
which is exactly what is going to happen the way the
Treasury Secretary is taking care of things.
Or do we want to go through a couple of years?
You know, really, and still going to be two to five, I'd say.
And it really is.
We're all going to have to take your step back.
We were all living above our means.
We have to take a step back.
And it'll work out because the housing prices will come down.
We'll have a little less to spend.
We'll still be able to get good houses.
But in the meantime, lots of people are going to get fucked.
The or should I just say, food bar.
Now, food bar, Dan.
We have to crash.
Yeah, people still want to accept that.
We don't want to sit there and say,
Hold, but I have X amount of this, X amount of that.
I still see on the news that they're still blaming the housing.
Even with the two to three million houses.
Yeah.
That have gone bad.
Paying off the mortgage isn't going to fix this.
Is it going to fix problem?
Yeah, it's, uh, you're right, man.
It's, uh, it's really the derivatives.
And this is what has to unwind.
It's just just no other way.
It has to come apart.
There's, uh, it's like probably $600 trillion of derivatives.
They're trying to figure out.
And again, I know I'm almost not like a broken record,
but I worked on a trading desk for these guys.
It's, it was all phony.
In, in, in, in, in the respect that there were actual trades going on,
but it was nothing more than a facts of a promise of something in the future.
10, 20 years out.
And that was that being valued is actually something valuable.
It was all done completely off the, you know, over, over the counter.
So, um, no, um, um, no exchange, no transparency, no reporting.
Of course, that's really where it all went wrong.
And, um, and just creation of money, blatant creation of money.
And it's, it's interesting to see that now that, that it, of course, is too late.
Still with the speed of the internet, people are catching on.
But as you point out, people really just don't want to hear it.
You know, they, they want the soft landing.
The mainstream media is telling us, oh, you know,
how do we make this into a soft landing?
And we can do this.
No, it, we're going to, it's crashing.
It's completely crashing.
And it's going to hurt.
And it's going to hurt a lot of people.
And I believe no exceptions.
So, we'll get hurt more than others.
But at the end of the day, no exceptions.
We're all getting hurt.
So, I, we are only seeing one show.
Uh, one quote unquote news show.
Talk about the default credit spots, which have actually caused all this.
They were actually people were actually betting on it to fail.
So, they could pay doubt.
You look at AIG, the insurance company.
Now, why do stocks need insurance?
Well, they don't want to pay for the,
Well, it wasn't the stocks, but it was insurance for,
for basically people defaulting on, um, on the mortgages.
There you go.
They don't want to pay when they lose.
Uh, I do have to agree with that.
We're in, uh, oh, everybody's a winner to my mentality.
Yeah, that's right, man.
That's another thing.
You got to have losers.
And, you know what?
We've been in a horrible job teaching our children that sometimes you just lose.
Sometimes you get full barred.
It just happens.
And then you got to pick yourself up and get back in the race.
And we have not been teaching our children this.
And these children, many of them went on to run Wall Street.
No losers.
Only winners here.
You're only, you only, you were seventh.
You were the number seventh winner.
Johnny.
Instead of, uh, son, you sucked.
That's all right.
We'll get a bit next time.
Practice hard.
That's what America was made up.
And we've turned into a nation of posses.
And, uh, and so has most of Western Europe.
Just posses.
No losers.
Only winners.
We've forgotten.
Again, our past are the 1893, 1927, 1929, 1929.
1907, um, 1773, uh, 1980.
You've been around.
Look at it.
It's, it's all, 1999, 2000 with the bubbles.
Yeah.
We, we, we over and flake.
Everybody that can't take advantage of it.
Don't us.
Try to, try to surface to get him.
It tries to get him on the ground floor.
Only to realize that.
Oh, it's already too late because they're about four to five years too late.
Absolutely.
Uh, actually this comment is on the drop.
Uh, it's another two minutes.
And it is for our Friday.
So I do want to get back into the music.
But I appreciate all the feedback.
Really got me started there.
Uh, DSA listener from, uh, from Oregon.
And of course, um, although I will be talking about this over the weekend with John C.
Tovorek on No agenda, which will be recording on Sunday, by the way.
Due to my, uh, travel.
Uh, so don't expect it Saturday.
Uh, of course, October 14th came and went.
Uh, prophesized by many on the interwebs.
As the day that, uh, an alien ship would surface for three days.
And as I said, I was very open to this.
I didn't prophesize it, but I was very open to it.
But at the end of the day, I pretty much looked like a dick and I realized it.
So we'll talk more about it on Sunday.
I do have some thoughts and some theories.
But unfortunately, yeah, I'm just a douche.
Shouldn't have bought that one, huh?
Open mouth, open smash mouth.
Come on, come on with that in him.
If you've got fun, go tell me about it.
Just stay in my clinic.
So don't you make, act now.
So fast and run, and out.
A lot with your skill, a lot.
Six two eight years to the right.
And you can follow me.
Be out to all of all it.
Be out to the shun.
And my eyes will be walking on the sun.
Twenty five years, I'll go.
Thanks, bro.
Calamate, bro.
Calamate, set shun.
And I'll press shun.
And together they took.
And they pulled down.
With good toss.
Oh, round of all, far just.
Sing and make happy men.
What the hell happened?
Yes, I'm with the hell.
So, where help?
Bells and they fell down.
So yeah, back up.
And on, back it's a little too.
And they came for him.
They chicked.
So him, boy.
Crits.
Because fashion is fashion.
All too.
Made anything of it.
So don't you make, act now.
So fast and run, and out.
A lot with your skill, a lot.
Six two eight years to the right.
And you can follow me.
Be out to all of all it.
Be out to the shun.
And my eyes will be walking on the sun.
And I'll show you when I'm almost there.
Coach, you feel so.
With the tears, because I've been as loud as been ran for.
The bond is broke.
Got felt you're open for.
Yes, I'm not close up.
This always I can't be full.
No God, I can't be full.
So don't sit in the back kick.
I can't watch the world get most wack.
You can't stand your name on it.
It's on the right side.
And I put away the crap that fall the crack.
But you will wait.
Your needs are be that way.
And your baby is older.
Now tell me.
Hey.
She don't do it.
Act now.
So fast and run, and out.
A lot with your skill, a lot.
Six two eight years to the right.
And you can follow me.
Be out to all of all it.
Be out to shun.
You might as well be well.
You know the sun.
And you might as well be well.
Be all the sun.
Yeah.
And you might as well be well.
Go the sun.
Ah, someone.
It's not me.
Wow.
Smash mouth.
Might as well be walking on the sun.
And double share Charlie seven nine or nine.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, what a disappointment that was.
Well, anyway, I guess we're just going to have to do it all for ourselves.
There's no quick fix coming.
Coming.
The aliens aren't going to save us, which means we'll just have to keep on going with many
daily source code to help you awaken your friends.
Turn them on to the show.
Hopefully they can.
They can get through it and start to see some light at the end of the tunnel.
Because we'll come out of this.
You know, how effectively we come out of it.
I just wish.
Yeah.
I just wish I had been able to start years ago and maybe affected more change.
And somehow, you know, was able to stop some of this because it's, it's not going
to be good.
It really isn't.
I have to say right now, it looks like Barack Obama is going to be the next president
of the United States.
It seems like a nice guy.
Very charismatic.
Anyone who listens to the DSC knows.
I would definitely not vote for either candidate or any candidate of either of those
parties.
It would have to be independent because they're run by.
Basically, the shadow government.
Let's call it that.
Call it the new world order or whatever you want.
They're being run.
And it's nice to see that finally all over the net.
It's dawning on people that the.
The big new Brzinski is indeed.
The brains behind Obama's campaign.
And there are some things.
And I'm going to leave that for the daily source code for no agenda.
Because John and I will definitely pick it up again.
The 95% you know, the tax cut for the 95% of Americans who pay taxes.
The refundable tax cut I mind to I might add, which basically turns America into.
A socialist country like many that I have lived in or actually currently live in.
Where they easily hand out money to people who don't do anything.
That is just not the American way.
The American way is you stimulate business.
By the way, in America, 75% of all business is small to medium business.
That's everything from the one man store stall.
I should say almost to, you know, a small family store.
To me, you know, and even even bigger than me, view.
These are small businesses.
We are really what the economy is in the United States.
And we're getting fucked.
So typically what you do is you help those companies so that they can keep more money.
Higher more people, which is called job creation.
Because, wow, man.
We could see eight, nine, ten percent joblessness in the US.
That's a lot of people.
So there are a couple of links I want you to read in the show.
No, it's a daily source code.com.
One of them is this article.
It's titled as a big New Jersey.
The real power behind the, and Obama throne.
Good read.
It'll definitely tell you where the, the Obama policy is headed in the,
Man, the sky looks scary.
Excuse me.
And by the way, four of his sons are also in the campaign or involved with the campaign.
It's a family.
It's one of the, it's one of, it's a family that's in there and is running the show.
And you can read his books and you'll know exactly what's going to happen.
So as I've stated before, I think that there will, you know,
there will be joyous, joyous feeling in general.
There will be no revolt if Obama wins.
If he loses, I think people will take this streets.
They'll be severely pissed off already.
And again, I don't want to give away too much because John and I are getting some deep info.
There's a lot of worry in the Obama camp as is about a potential recall.
They're already saying no matter how many points he wins,
there's going to be a recall that preparing for it.
They worried about the Supreme Court.
I mean, all kinds of stuff that's going on,
I still believe that the true powers that be the true owners of the earth,
these are the families that are essentially behind the failure,
this financial failure.
They do it to grab real assets.
You know, they have, they have the hands and all these banks.
And so when you lose your house, they get it.
And they don't care about the house.
They're probably just care about the land or redeveloping entire neighborhoods,
their bastards, total bastards.
And they've done it before and they'll continue to do it unless we wake up
and stop it.
But this time, we're going to witness it.
So I'm pretty sure I'm going to be doing the show for at least the next 10 years,
maybe not daily.
But I'll certainly be doing the show.
Excuse me.
Meanwhile,
now I did not see the debate.
That'll be something we'll talk about over the weekend on no agenda,
no agenda at mevio.com.
I basically got a European update upon arrival.
Of course, it took place in the middle of the night.
Excuse me.
It's finally all loosening up that cold,
that sinus thing I had.
But now I've just got this cough.
I got to get rid of those kind of gnarly.
Anyway, I'll give you the details of that.
It's all a big show.
And the show continues fantastic YouTube clip,
which I'm going to play a little bit for you right now.
You'll see how well this is done.
Obama is an actor.
And a damn good one.
And you can feed him almost any line.
And he can deliver.
If you see this YouTube video,
which is the the Al Smith dinner,
I think it was in New York City.
Obama has his notes.
And he's looking at points.
He's almost reading them verbatim.
You know, he keeps looking down.
And even though his timing is kind of funky,
he hammers at home.
But the jokes are just so well written.
This guy has got some major lead people behind him.
Listen to this.
Thank you to Alan Tam to your Eminence.
To Governor Patterson and Mayor Bloomberg,
to Senator and Mrs. McCain.
By the way,
this is a white tie dinner.
So everyone's got white bow ties.
And McCain is right there.
And like everyone's there.
Hillary Clinton is there.
This is a big to do.
The Alfred East Smith Memorial Foundation dinner.
I don't actually know what that's about.
But it doesn't matter.
Listen to Obama reading his lines and just killing.
You know, you at the end of the day.
Any any project, any creative project,
like a movie or TV series or a book,
of course,
you know,
it all comes down to the writing.
Which is why these writers straight to strikes are always so debilitating.
Listen to what these guys wrote for him.
This is better than Saturday Night Live.
My wonderful colleague, Senator Clinton and Schumer,
to all the distinguished guests.
There is no other crowd in America that I'd rather be
pounding around with.
Writing.
All right.
That was good.
I'm sorry it couldn't be here.
I do send regards to my running mate.
The writing or has Senator McCain noted.
He now actually likes to be called Joe the senator.
All right.
So first, you know, so he's hammering the cane with these jokes.
So the first one is, you know,
of course a reference to paling around with terrorists.
And then Joe the senator versus Joe the plumber.
So that's two for two, I'd say.
And he's just he's reading it right off of his paper.
I was thrilled to get this invitation.
And I feel right at home here because it's often been said
that I share the politics of Alfred East Smith
and the years of Alfred E. Newman.
Oh, good self-deprecating humor.
Awesome.
Which by the way means he's wide open for ear jokes now.
Come on, man.
We just recycle those Prince Charles jokes.
Come on.
Get him out.
You liberal media.
Don't be such chisters.
Even he's making fun of himself.
Let's have some fun with this guy already.
Can we?
But I have to say tonight's venue isn't really what I'm used to.
I was originally told we'd be able to move this outdoors to Yankee State.
That's a double joke, of course.
Yankee Stadium being demolished.
The original Yankee Stadium.
Good New York Joe.
Can somebody tell me what happened to the great column?
He's reading it.
He's just reading the jokes.
He's reading the punch lines even.
It's great.
I do love the Waldorf Astoria, though.
You know, I hear that from the doorstep.
You can see all the way to the Russian TV.
Oh, my goodness.
That's awesome.
That is what I call a show.
It's not going to be here with El Smith.
I obviously never knew your great grandfather,
but from everything that Senator McCain has told me.
I got to stop.
You got to see this whole thing.
It's phenomenal.
And that is some awesome writing.
I mean, you know, Letterman has been hammering McCain.
And of course, McCain was on Letterman the other day.
I didn't see that, unfortunately.
I saw some quick reviews here and there and it looked like nothing too spectacular.
But this is better than the shit Letterman's coming up with.
Who the hell writes that?
And how can I hire that person to write for the daily source code?
I'd love that, please.
Oh, man, phenomenal.
phenomenal.
We'll talk a little bit more about Obama and McCain and the financial situation
and their policies coming up.
First, those switching gears to one of the most controversial topics on the Charlie of
late.
This, of course, is regarding Gardezill, the HPV vaccine.
In some cases being given.
Mended in some places in the world, mandatory.
Also, a mandatory for anyone immigrating into United States.
I would like to point out.
Which, as you know, I believe is extremely dangerous.
It hasn't been tested long enough.
It's brought to you by the same people who brought you viox.
Took that off the market only just a couple of years ago.
Another one of those grand, you know, who cheated and tested out two well schemes.
And it's really not a short deal.
You know, and it's very expensive.
And just look at what these farmer circles are doing.
They're scrambling hand over foot to find anything they can.
Anything to fill up their medicines that, of which the patents are expiring.
Which means they need billions of dollars in their inclusion with, with our government.
Worldwide, our government's to be fast tracked and mandated.
And, you know, price points set enormous amounts.
It's, it's, this is how the, this is really how the lobbyists work.
They'll say, oh, let's say, get this mandate.
It's mandatory.
It's good.
We've got studies.
We've got tests.
The PR machine cranks up and man, they're doing overtime.
It doesn't mean that it's all good, though.
Hey, Adam.
It's Michael Cole and Matt.
Some Chicago again.
Maybe.
First of all, I was one who said you were sometimes crazy like a shit house rat in that
Chris and Seattle.
Yeah, no, no, no.
I know he was just repeating it.
But that's okay.
Because I like it.
Sometimes crazier than a shit house rat.
But I said sometimes.
And I missed Don Lafantaine.
You'll be perfect saying that in the world.
Where sometimes he's crazier than a shit house rat.
I miss him.
And I said, I love you, brother.
I'm a great show.
You're talking about, and have been about Cardis Hill.
And the way they're injecting it into, um, into our children.
And I'm my children.
But, you know, people's children.
I agree.
It's pretty shady.
It hasn't been enough time.
I mean, I think we're probably all someone's child somewhere along the line
Aren't we now?
There's something that the, uh, the drug companies are doing because they're, uh,
losing their patents.
And there I is.
And they need to come up with the next big thing.
Yep.
Uh, you were talking about, um, uh, using Flood of Might as a comparison,
which was, uh, something done back in the 60s.
And in Europe.
And I think it's still done in Brazil.
I don't know.
Yeah, this was, uh, this was a horrible horrible mistake.
It really fucked up a lot of babies.
I don't know what the stats are on, um, you know, how often,
or what the results have been.
Uh, but as you said, it produced a lot of birth defects.
And I thought, uh, as I'm Michael from Chicago of Opera Now.
Uh, there's a guy, uh, singer, a base baritone in Tomas Quastoff,
who was a German, who was a, you know, a quote unquote,
with a might baby.
Um, he has very small, uh, very, very short legs,
and very, very short arms.
But, you know, like a fully developed torso and head.
And he is a very, very successful singer.
Um, obviously he doesn't do much opera.
Um, uh, although they wanted to hit somebody wanted him to play.
We're going to let out.
Who is supposed to be a dwarf?
Yes.
We're going to let us an upper by very.
That's fun.
Uh, he, he turned it down.
Yeah.
I mean, my man's got integrity.
You know what I'm saying?
The operatic dwarf.
Now, be funny, man.
That would be cool.
I'd watch that.
I'd go see that show.
Have a huge voice come out of a small guy.
Or whatever, it doesn't matter.
I love people who are weird.
No, I'm one of them myself.
I got my own weird shit.
And what's normal, by the way.
Huh?
What's the norm?
Is that what's on Vogue Magazine?
Is that what's in GQ?
Is that what's supposed to be the norm and how you're supposed to be normal and good?
That's the beauty of it, man.
We're all messed up.
And if we can just stop with the political correctness and just call the spade,
the spade, the spade, call the nutball, the nutball.
And not take such a fence and light knob.
That would be a pretty good start, wouldn't it?
Before they start putting in rules, laws generally accepted across nations,
where you can't say these words.
Yeah.
Hey.
It's all coming.
If we don't watch it, buddies.
Why is we probably?
But I thought it was interesting.
You know, this guy who came into this world with a, you know, up against the
C.A. Ball and he's been able to be very successful with his life.
Yep.
And he's a good singer, two good boys.
And teams are putting in this guy.
There's a lot of teaching as well.
So, gotten it that way.
Being sting, the chuckle has out there to hear about.
So I take it easy brother.
All right.
And I'm sorry to think you're getting less crazy like a shit.
That's right.
Let me know.
Don't worry.
That plenty of crazy still left to me.
I promise you.
Love you too, man.
I'll just stay on the shots for a second.
This, and all these links, of course, in the show,
know today at resource code.com.
I'll see.
Scroll up to this.
Yeah, this is happening in New Jersey.
Now, we talked about this a couple weeks ago that New Jersey was mandating all
preschoolers and kindergarteners.
Have to get a, a flu shot in order to attend school.
And parents, thank goodness,
bless all of you are protesting this.
Now, my belief is that, you know,
the flu is not comfortable.
It does suck,
but it does build up your resistance.
You know, there's no reason with, you know,
the basic over-the-counter medicines we have.
I really don't see much of a reason.
Not to just let kids get the flu.
You know, it has to happen.
But this, of course, is all a run up to the avian bird flu.
And, and, and I can feel it in my bones.
They're going to come out when they're ready.
They're just in, whether it will be true or not.
And they're already talking about getting flu shots in preparedness for the avian flu.
Again, it's a combination of,
how, well, I hope that all it is is really just,
um, government complicity in,
in, in helping big pharmaceuticals and make billions of dollars.
I mean, already these companies have this in their pipeline.
You can read it in their corporate annual reports.
They're projecting one to two billion dollars per company,
depending on what virus or vaccine they have.
And then literally saying avian bird flu.
So they're going to, the government's going to scare you into taking these shots.
And I just don't buy it.
You know, where is the damn bird flu?
Oh, oh, it might, it might go from birds to humans.
Well, in 15 years I've been hearing about this thing.
It hasn't really happened yet.
Yeah, 150 cases give me a break worldwide.
So good on these parents because, of course, it should be freedom of choice.
And when it comes to the flu, please.
I mean, polio.
Yeah, these things were, you know, there's no patents on these.
You know, it's a very effective and cost-effective vaccination.
But that was really made before big pharmaceuticals were in there.
And would do anything including kill our children to make a buck.
So I advise you to do your own research,
but I would fight against it.
Of course, a lot of people.
And I think there's, there's some truth in this,
because there's traces of mercury in these shots.
They claim that one and out of every 94 kids gets autism
because of these vaccinations,
genuine McCarthy even.
And we'll see on people magazine that a big stink about it.
Good on her.
Don't let the government inject shit into your kids.
Not unless you've done so much research
that you really feel confident that this is the right thing.
And I had a conversation with Patricia because she keeps saying,
you know, she's kind of on the fence and I said, you know,
honey, please, don't get the flu shot.
And she usually does get the flu.
And she's had really bad flu.
She's had pneumonia twice.
I said, I'm so worried.
I'm really so worried about you getting the shot.
And she said, okay, I won't take it this year.
I said, but the other children should be dropping hands like,
well, I hope it don't get sick.
Yeah, so of course she's going to get sick.
And then, you know, she'll blame me and I said, no, please,
I want you to decide.
You do the research.
Please, don't take it from me.
And if you want to take the shot, it's okay.
Yeah, you're not going to die immediately.
I at least I hope not.
But who the fuck knows?
And you know, maybe you should try and just be strong and
and get through one or two of these flu's.
So I'll let you know what she decides.
But that, of course, has her totally her personal choice.
Just how I just worries me.
So anyway, to these parents in New Jersey.
True Americans.
We've lived up, figured through the King of England.
For the dollar coming from the India.
We call our five, he comes in our hands.
We'll hit for our home.
We'll go next and dedicate it to Neverday.
Just as dirty call and make a book that we didn't know.
It doesn't look that way to me.
They can still got no.
Listen up now, for you who I am.
Just to know the stupid American.
You don't want to make it to one or two.
You don't want to understand.
So finish up the drink and go home.
I can't follow the man up.
It's like plenty.
Clean it from where I want with it.
Oh yes, it's ready.
And they turn it.
The country that I love.
But in the land of Australia.
And I want to close the land.
Hey, fucking quiet.
And I'm a free person.
Don't let caught these fears in.
They can joke I know.
Listen up now, tell your who I am.
Just to know the stupid American.
You don't want to make it to one or two.
You don't want to understand.
Come finish up the drink and go home.
I can't follow an essay.
And before the drive, you got to know the people who support you.
Hey, little guys.
You've got to know the dude who fought your head.
Everyone, catch up on the ocean, catch them on the sun
Break the hell we go
Listen up, man, I'll tell you who I am
Just another super, man, I'll make it
You don't want to let them do what I understand
So finish up the drink and go
Listen up, man, I'll tell you who I am
Just another super, man, I'll make it
You don't want to let them do what I understand
So finish up the drink and go home
Finish up the drink and go home
Yo, descendants, just another super-American
It's daily source code, we are at 799 or 9r
Oh, that'll be 8800 next week
And not quite sure when I'm going to do it
Traveling Monday, board meeting Tuesday
Maybe Tuesday to Wednesday, something like that
And as I said, going to Los Angeles
But in two weeks time, it probably should be a little easier for me to create
More shows during the week and also working on a video show
Ha ha ha
Yeah
If you're not in the United Kingdom, then you've probably seen
a mevio.com or cranking up these channels, techs,
I've been doing some video stuff for that
We've got the Lux channel up and running
And I want to do something with something about tech
But probably really broad base
And I got some ideas, but that's all in the hopper
So I'm looking forward to that
I'm also looking forward to talking to you guys more
And even another video show that I'm thinking of
Now that I've got some
Now hopefully I'll have some time and some capacity in the edit suite
I want to do it kind of like a daily thing
Not quite sure when they're calling it yet
But there's so much video from Seek span
Maybe just a daily rant that's based around some piece of video
Something outrageous happening in the world
I know there's enough material I won't have to search too far
All I need is Obama's writers and I'd be completely set
Well, I don't understand you from Seattle
It was a nice rant you gave on 798
And pretty exciting episodes
I was listening to your podcast
From a couple years ago, which I had caught
Weed onto a CD and happened to have in my car
Yeah, do people actually do that?
You go back and listen to old shows
Like five night, it's two 300 episodes ago
That's pretty wild, man
Thank you
And listen to the five 90s area there
And man, your podcast has changed over time
As I watched you awaken
I remember you
In 798, you mentioned that you wish you'd known this when you were younger
Well, I was kind of taught this stuff when I was six back in the early 60s
That's so cool
Of course, my entire family was part of the machine
So that was kept to carefully hidden from me
But there were enough clues that
I kind of have some knowledge of what actually happens
In the true reality of the universe
A lot of those pieces of the puzzle snapped together for me
So in a way I've had benefit from it
And I have watched it happen
And I've watched every step happen
And I've tried to wake up people for years
And years and years and I've been calling it
And then nothing like you have
And not to
And
Although you see Dr. Ron Paul, right?
The who even Johnson of War
I called him a Cooke or Cooke or it doesn't matter
And now the guys everywhere
I've even got some bits from one of his recent appearances
And everyone's like now he's at the authority
Because of course he predicted this shit
But 23 years ago is when he predicted it
It's been heartbreaking
I can't get my own family to follow the stuff
And listen to it
It's too hard, listen to
And that's kind of depressing
But you are doing something
It's truly inspirational
And thank you for having inspired me to make a
A blog which you're a podcast
If you like it and you can you can mention
As your friends, friends, friends and liberty
Add blogspot.com
I had some technical problems getting on the pot
So it's network
But
On there as well
And so I just want to say
You're doing a great job
And thank you very much
It's a hard thing to come to reality with
For everyone
And it's been really neat to watch your awakening
Oh I'm out
Thank you, Sandy, I appreciate it
Is that Sandy?
I think it was Sandy wasn't it?
Let me just check
Yeah, Sandy
A quick interlude here
I want to remind you about the sponsor
of the daily source code
So I'm going to embed this into your mind
Thinking of taking a trip
Thinking of driving somewhere
Budget rental cars
It's pretty much the way I'm going to be going
When we're in the city
Why have a car in the city
If you need to drive anywhere
I'm just going to rent one
And there is a budget
Right around the corner
You can book online at budget.com
If you go to budget.com slash dsc
You can get up to 30
Dollars off weekly budget rental cars
I think they do translated for a Europe
Or 10% off any amount
By using my checkout code dsc
All the links in the show notes
A daily source code.com
Just scroll down to the bottom of the show notes
Everything's there
Of course
We also have the ongoing go daddy discount
You can get 30% off anything you buy
By using my code dsc3
Any total package of a domain name
Quick blog, free hosting
All that stuff
And one thing that
I'm sure the economic crisis
Is not helping
I personally can see it
In the people who are using my code
For Brooks Dome.com
This is kind of like the
I call it the sharper image for outdoors
Man, I got almost zero sales last week
And you can get 10% off
Anything you buy
Just go to the links in the show notes
A daily source code.com
Of course there's also e-mmusic
We got some other stuff on the way
But the ones I really want you to try
Check out budget rent of cars
Because you probably will be renting a car
One point is pretty easy to remember to use my code
And of course go daddy at 30% discount
Over your entire order using dsc
Number 3, dsc3
So as Sandy said the show is definitely evolved
But some things
They've just got her a main the same
Certainly when it's a football Friday
On California casting
With Adam Curry
This is the hit test
Hit it test
Young pole net
Adam, this is hit test number 143
Adam, start right away with intro
Okay, let's go
I got to hear that one
Um
Okay
Foo barred up front
No idea
Number 2
Oh, of course
Dan Hartman rely my fire
Ah, I must have given you some kind of inspiration
With Dan Hartman last week, huh?
Easy one, what's next?
And number 3
I think I'm sexy, Rod Stewart
Okay, I'll say
I think I got four out of six this time
I'm very curious to hear what that first one was
Though that was completely foreign to me
And it's time for the answers
And this week they're all from
Hit it test
And this is answering number one
This is Bobby Thornton
You've got what it takes
I'm sorry man
Where was I?
Never, huh?
Ah, okay, I remember this
It's what to me, it's a silly song
All right, I'll see you on point
Number 1
And this is answering number 2
Um, uh
This is Dan Hartman
Relight my fire
I'll make you sleep everything
I'm looking to get you
Reactor
Relight my fire
Your love is the only desire
You're the answer number 2
Dan Hartman
And this is answering number 3
Rod Stewart
Do you think I'm sexy?
Um
Tell me so honey
Just reach out of touch
Answer number 3
Rod Stewart
Do you think I'm sexy?
And that concludes hit test number 1
So Adam, how did you do this week?
Well, I'm not too bad
I mean the first one I don't I barely remember the song
But four stars out of a possible six
I'll take it for a food bar Friday
I'm pretty happy
I'll write you that concludes this hit test
As usual, the place to find the answers to this and any other hit test
And also the links to iTunes you can buy
The tricks featured in hit test online
Is hit test.mefio.com
Adam, thanks for playing
Yeah, thank you young
Next week I hope to be back for another hit test
So until then take care
Have fun
And remember to try to think with your heart
Bye bye
And be OLDT.com
Oh man
It's gonna be another one of those long shows
It's already a quarter to eleven Friday evening
So we are rightly food bar
But there's just so much good stuff I want to share with you
And let's get into the financial meltdown here for a second
This is a piece of video I wanted to share with you
Of course you can find the link at the dailysourcecode.com
In the show notes
This is from TheRealNews.com
Listen to this, you'll like it
The US economic meltdown has sent shockwaves around the globe
European markets are no exception
The real news spoke to author and economist William Engdahl
About the trouble on Wall Street and the European perspective
The United States economy is going to go through a hell
It's begun already
That's going to be worse than the Great Depression of the 1930s
Goldman Sachs is Paulson
By the way, in this video you can see Paulson
In the Secretary of the Treasury chambers
You know he's got the American flags and he comes through a door
Which has like six flags behind it
It is like he's literally the Wizard of Oz
Comes from behind the curtain
This is the man who's doing a lot of evil to us
The point of Treasury Secretary
To bail out Wall Street and his colonies
This is the real colony capitalism
To bail out his colonies in the financial community
So with taxpayer money
After they've loaded the coffers dry in the first place
With the huge profits on the real estate
Securization asset pack mortgages and so forth
This whole multi trillion dollar charades
Just loans sky eye
Nobody knows what they're holding in terms of the papers
It's just as I guess you didn't hear
This is William Engdahl
He's an author
He's well, you can imagine what kind of books he's written
But he's a political economist
I think he does know his stuff
Probably better than I do
Absolutely madness
It's been supported by the chairman of the Federal Reserve
In Greenspan it's supported by Wall Street
When I can say about the European reaction
And this is unprecedented
The German finance minister got up in the parliament ten days ago
And said this is the end of a Mac
As the world's financial superpower
We are going to see a whole series of regional financial centers
Emerge out of this crisis
There you go
As predicted
Regional financial centers
There'll be regional there'll be like all of North America
All of Europe all of Asia
Three will go into maybe two
But certainly eventually into one
And they will own all your money
And of course they own your money
They don't even need to make up the laws
But they'll they'll take over that as well
This is the stuff we have to stop
This is the enemy
And I'm glad we're getting pissed off
Because it's just the beginning
Worldwide we're going to have to get extremely pissed off
At our governments and we're going to have to show it
And we're going to have to vote them out when we can
And we have to show our
Our pain but we're going to have to show it to them
Because the politicians they don't
They don't know what's going on
They're being threatened for entirely different reasons
They're being threatened with
Marshall Law
Stuff like that taking place
Never again will America maintain that status
It's the sole financial center of innovation in the world
They are primarily serious
I've heard them comment
Banking events over the recent months
They're absolutely serious
At the corruption and fraud
That's come out of the New York financial community
Selling as as AAA rated
Securities to European banks
Something that is now properly named
Toxic waste
Yeah
Of course that of course is totally true
But you know the European banks
As much a part of it
It's not like a US thing
Not just a US thing
Everyone was partying
And the blame you know we have
People blaming
Regulation
The regulators so that's where the Fed comes in
They have people blaming
Poor people
I love that
Poor people did it
We have people living beyond their means
We have 29 year olds driving
Mazaradis
It was all there
The true fault is the system
The system of central banking
Where private bankers
Control your money
And my money all of our money
With complete go ahead from the government
That is the problem
No one really brings that up
And we'll just have to keep hammering away at it
Because you know
And there are some proposals
Now in the United States
Dr. Ron Paul has put a couple in
Audit the Federal Reserve
Of course it's one step onto abolishing the Federal Reserve
It may take a while but I think eventually
We're going to get there
But I've realized it is going to be a five to ten year plan for sure
So they regard
The American financial system is not worth
To be trusted to
Walk you dog across the streets
There you go
Go watch that entire interview
Link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
And regardless of who wins our election in the United States
It'll just be more of the same
They're their liars
They will lie about anything
And I think McCain lies
But his lies are Obama lies better
I gotta tell you
He does make you feel good
But they're literally liars
You know and we could catch them on so many different things
I saw saw I was reading something about Joe Biden
Remember he was talking about that restaurant that he went to in Scranton
Turns out that restaurant has been closed for five or six years
I would have been funny if Sarah Palin had that knowledge
You could have really nailed them on that one
But of course the cutest actor of the bunch is actually Sarah Palin
But I think in all it'll probably be more interesting to have Obama's president
And I'll be pointing it out along the way every single step of everything that happens
Including the massive buildup of what we're going to be doing in Afghanistan
All to run drugs into our own countries and communities
That's where we'll continue to wage war against the mythical Taliban
Or the mythical of the Taliban is real the mythical al-Qaeda
And it's just liars
And you can pat it away as much as you want
And we all really want change and hope and something different
And that's good now I want it to and maybe if we feel better it'll change a little bit
But at the end of the day we'll just get more of the same probably five times harder
Hey Adam it's Dave from California
I did so I wasn't sure and I know you're mentioning that
Ron Paul was voting was up that king
Chuck Goldman
Yeah
So I have a question
And now I'm looking at the constitutionalist party website
And I was looking at the issues and the points that they bring up
And then I went to Chuck Baldwin's website
And I was looking at his issues and who supports him and who likes him
And all the things that he's back at
I thought one major discrepancy that always concerns me
All right now I'm a gay man
And I'm shocked
Oh no
It's a gay man
He's calling in the show
I'm shocked
A lot of people and I'm pretty shocked
Because everybody's against this whole gay man
It seems like everybody's against gay marriage
Now I'm a constitutionalist site
They say that they find it unconstitutional
To regulate marriage in any way shape of form
Yeah
I got a Chuck Baldwin site and he's very pro-traditional marriage
Now I've never looked at a lot of other issues
I've really researched
Much aushes
What is attacking is
That's just the first one
I look at because that's the most important to me
Yeah
I want to get your opinion
What do you say?
I mean, should this
How far off from his
From the other point that he's going to be
If this one is so drastic we different
You know, I want to know your points on the whole situation
As well, I think that would be interesting to find out
And what you think of him taking a stance
That basically goes against everything that is part of stanceful
No, not true
So that's all I want to know
All right so
Okay
That's a very interesting question
I'm glad you bring that up
So first of all, when it comes to the constitution party
And also Dr. Ron Paul, it's really easy
They have a pamphlet which you can pick up
At any library, probably any bookstore
You can find that all over the internet
It's not even that big
It's called the constitution of the United States
And those guys pretty much stick to it
And it took me a while to get over a couple of things
The way Ron Paul, for instance, spoke about abortion
So
As I believe
Certainly Ron Paul and
99% sure the constitution party
Believe that there should be a separation between church and state
And that the government
Nor lawyers or Supreme Court or whatever
Should decide
Anything about marriage in any religion
Whatever
So that first and foremost
So that's what those guys will tell you
And I believe them
They mean it
So if your church wants to have you married a goat
Or allow you to marry a goat
Or a woman or a man or whatever
That should be you and your church's business
And between you and your church and your God
And that's what Ron Paul will say
That's what Chuck Baldwin will say
That's what the constitution party will say
Now that they personally
And Ron Paul is very good at separating this
That they personally
Have different views about what should happen in the church
It's a separate matter
And I believe that every so
Let me just get to the abortion part
Because that's where it kind of fuck with my head
So Ron Paul says, look
Killing people should be illegal
But abortion you should be
It's your body you should you know
It's up to you what you do with your body
So then it only comes down to a matter of
Is an embryo
Is that a person is is it life at
At conception
And that I believe
Is something that is really kind of
Still undecided
So what Ron Paul is saying
And it's it's still hard to wrap
My head around he says, look
I'm against abortion
Because I'm against killing
And if you kill someone then you should go to jail
And really what he comes on the saying
Is you know if it were my American
He says the way it would happen
Is of course abortions would take place
But the person who performs the abortion
Would probably be at risk
I'm not saying it's an ideal solution
Okay, I'm just saying that he's not lying
And he says, look I think marriage
Should be a man and a woman
That's up to him
God bless him I don't care
And I really don't care
You can marry whatever you want
I'm happy
In fact I think gay people should definitely
Be able to marry each other
It's crazy they shouldn't
And I wanted to have all the joys of marriage
I want you to have kids
You know I want to have all the responsibility of kids
I want it be easy for you to
To adopt or conceive with the surrogates
Please I want you to have the joy of kids
To my pain a little too
And I want you to enjoy the joys of divorce
All of it all of it
And the love in front of you
Your church and your God
It should absolutely
We all should be equal in that right
But you know whatever club you belong to
Which are their rules
Now
Obama, McCain, Palin and Biden
And of course we both heard Obama
Sorry, Palin and Biden say quite specifically
No, they're both against gay marriage
Against it
And you know why they're doing that
Because even if they don't believe it
They're lying
They will lie to you
Stone face
Because they know they need the religious
The religious voters is very important
So these guys
And I don't know if Obama has cited it or not
And believe me
I'm looking at Obama and there's lots of stories out there
You know he may be bisexual
Why wouldn't if he had some experimentation
No one's ever asked him
But you know and so what
Good looking guy
Fine
You know but he'll never say that he agrees with gay marriage
Because he has to lie
He has to lie to get the religious vote
So that shows you right up front
These guys will lie in your face
Stone cold
And you think because you think
Well they get points if he said hey man
I think gay marriage should be fine
Can I say that
Never
Because they know it'll blow their chances
Entirely because the religious vote is huge
You get it?
These guys are just fucking liars
And they're good at it
So I don't think it goes against
The constitution party
Doesn't go against the constitution
As long as
The government and the courts are not allowed to decide
Who marries who for what reason
It's a private matter between you
Your church and your God
End of
And I'm pretty sure that's what they're saying
When they
Well what they're saying in their materials
Let's see another YouTube video
This is Dr. Ron Paul
I think this was on was this on CNN
Drone is now from clue text as Republican congressman
And former presidential candidate Ron Paul
Thanks for joining us this morning
Now I want you to listen to what he's saying
I mean I can almost
I can almost say it before he does
But he's so good at it
And so now the guy is mainstream
I'm blessed him
He's 70 years old he's out there every single day
He's doing this is tiring shit man
He's all over the place he's doing these interviews
He's getting the word out and he's being taken seriously
Finally
Remember to keep promoting this guy
He's a United States congressman
He's been doing it for over a decade
More than that I think
God I don't know how long he's been doing it
He voted against the bailout bill
Our two main candidates who of course are two sides of the same coin
McKenna Obama voted for the bailout bill
Because their shields for Wall Street and liars as we just established
Congressman great to see you
Thank you
Last time you were with us you explained why you were against the government's bailout plan
While you were voting against it and you didn't believe that focusing on
Buying these troubled assets was the smart thing you do
No sense then they've sort of tweaked it if you will
And now have decided to buy stakes in some US banks
I think that's a better strategy to help heal the economy
Now they tweaked it up
You know it started off as a three-page document
It ended up 450 pages
Instead of 700 billion it's up to $150 billion
Rorders had a story out this morning
Today they estimated it's going to cost the American taxpayer
About five trillion dollars
There you go. Just telling you that number was night
And that's from Reuters five trillion dollars
That's what it will probably take
So now it's tweaking in the wrong direction
And I don't think it's going to do any good whatsoever
Well the credit markets are starting to loosen up a bit
At least from what we've seen this week
Is that a sign that maybe it is working?
Remember this what we were talking about this
So the numbers on the big board on CNBC are going up
Does that mean it's working? Is it all fixed?
Are we going to be saved? Are we going to have a soft landing?
Huh huh huh huh Ron tell us
We're going to have a soft landing
Well maybe to some degree on the short run
But that just means that
We'll have more inflation
You can't create five trillion dollars on a thin air
And not expect inflation
So although the dollar may be up a little bit right now
Because the markets are a little calmer
This just means that in time
We're going to all suffer and pay for this
And we're going to pay for it with higher prices
And this is the serious problem
It's the attack on the dollar system
They're trying to save the dollar
But this system that we've had since 1971
It's coming to an end
That's what this whole story is about
The end of a monetary system that we've had since 1971
And something has to give
You just can't create more money on a thin air
And popping up everybody
It's an immoral system
You're asking the poor people to bail out the rich
You're asking the innocent people to bail out the guilty
You're asking people to just totally defy the constitution
Because there's no place in the constitution
It says that we can do these things
That's right
There's no place in the constitution of these United States
Which is a republic
No place does it say
That you can regulate the money
Certainly not
A bunch of private banks
It's economically
It's a disaster
This is going to cause a great deal harm
Even it's like a drug addict
Taking a strong fix
He feels better for a day or two
But believe me
We're going to kill the patient
And the patient here is the dollar system
And our entire world economy
Have you heard anything?
I would say let's get off this addiction
And congressman have you heard anything from either the presidential candidate
About their economic plans that you think are good things that need to be implemented
Now this was kind of interesting when I was listening to this
Because he does actually and surprisingly
So he does give a McCain some props
Even though of course it's his own party
But he'll just credit McCain right along with Obama
Let me just see if he says what I think is going to say about Obama here
No, not really
But it's tough to find out the good parts
I did think that John McCain has a better approach
To the medical problem
And Obama has a better approach
Trying to save some money by coming home from Iraq
We're spending ten billion dollars a month over there
So we could save a lot of money
That money should be spent back here
But quite frankly, how can we trust anybody
Because when it comes to the bailout
How do they differ?
Was McCain and Obama comes rushing back to Washington and vote for the bailout
Are they both in the public in it?
And in a proof both houses I know you voted
She interrupted her she interrupted him
That's right because he was saying some really beautiful there
Yeah, they ran back to Washington to make sure they cast their vote
To bail everybody out because their overlords their masters told them to do so
Tens of millions of dollars donated by Wall Street firms to both candidates
At least the candidates that are allowed to debate on television
Not truly all candidates
Since there are at least four independents who are worth looking at
Against it, but that leads me to another question
If Barack Obama does end up winning, it looks like the Democrats would really have a
Trifecta in Congress both houses and the White House
What does that mean for the American people
And also for the GOP?
Let me answer that in my way
Imagine that if the Democratic Party had the House, the Senate, and the presidency
Oh man, the big new Brazinski you'd be having a field day
We're going to turn into we'll be more socialist and communist than Russia ever was
Well, I mean it is a disaster for the country and everybody
Because even with all the shortcomings of John McCain
His strong argument to be present is keep the Congress and the presidency and separate hands
The American people are going to be a lot better off if they're fighting a little bit
Instead of just having no restraints whatsoever
And that's interesting
Now are you for the case?
So we're arguing for him McCain, but I know what you're saying
Staff members actually writing on your own websites
Either the Democratic takeover of both houses of Congress and the White House
This November would be a quote, reputation of false conservatism
Of the Republican Party
How do you get back to some of those fiscally conservative ideals?
Well, it's going to be tough because you have to convince the American people
That's what we need
And everybody now
I'm doing my best man every single day
We're going to try and convince the American people
That we need to stop this idiocy, this lunacy
We've got to stop this central banking crap
I was realizing the country is something seriously wrong
With our whole financial system and our governmental system
But the big question is
Dude, does the majority of the American people believe
The government can still take care of us
Or should we get the government out of the way
Quit spending money, balance the budget, bring our troops home
Yes
In Latin American people keep the money they earn
That means drastically reducing taxes
Getting the government out of this over regulation
And give up on this idea that inflation solves everybody problem
Let's roll up our sleeves and get to work
And by the way, Europe, you can do the exact same thing
Let's get to work, let's try and create some shit here
Let's try and get some going, let's work
Let's not sit around to our government, please help me
And want you to help me with everything
This is what you do when you create this kind of nanny state
And that's exactly what's happening
But it's going to be nannyed on their terms
Not on yours or mine
Inflation, that is the creation of new money
Could solve everybody's problem
Which they're claiming right now
Nobody would ever have to work again
If five trillion dollars could save this economy
Why work?
Just put money and everybody will be happy
So they don't understand
They don't understand
That's exactly the plan
That's the Obama plan
And that's mainly McCain's plan too
Print money, make everybody happy
Why work?
Dude, and do debts
And other transgender people's of earth
I've seen this happen
I've seen countries that give away money
Oh, you got another kid
Well, here's another couple grand a year to take care of your kid
Which, of course, makes people have more kids
Come to our country
Come hang out with us
We'll give you a free money money on the streets
Yeah, you used to be money on the streets
If you're worked for it
Now what do we do?
This is insulting, it's so insulting
Damn the idea that people have to work
People have to save instead of consumer spending more money
The market is saying you should back off
Spend less money and save money
But anyways, oh no, don't save money
You're supposed to go out there and spend money
People who have saved the last five years
Have money in the bank
And cash is good right now
They're going to buy up the bargain
They're going to get a good deal in the house
This is so beautiful
This is being, this is really
Dron Paul encapsulates the slavery right here
Certainly for the American economy
We're slaves, we're buying machines
We're supposed to go buy more, buy more
911, what does the president say?
Go out, shop and go buy more
The economy has to move by buying more
Nothing, work your ass off
Save some money, buy something nice
A nice house, an affordable house
No, buy more
We'll feed you with credit
It just ran out
It's obvious that that system ends
And when it ends then
You just got to print up more money to make it work
And that's when it really really ends
That's what Ron Paul is saying here
The prices of houses should come down
We shouldn't argue if I'm artificially high
We shouldn't try to stimulate housing
There are too many houses
We should let the market make these decisions
It's arrogant for the politicians
And the bureaucrats, the belief
They can plan the economy and sort this all out
We've been doing it for all these years
And the monetary system is so confusing and so corrupt
The sooner we get back to believing in ourselves
Believing in freedom, believing in sound money
Believing in the constitution
We're going to solve these problems
But right now there's a fight going on in this country
Our numbers are growing
Yes, the majority, but our numbers are growing
Yes
And as this situation deteriorates
More people are going to say hey
Maybe it's right
Maybe limited government and freedom works
Maybe freedom is popular
And maybe freedom really works
And this idea that we have to depend on government
For all these programs is an illusion
We're not going to leave it there
Excellent
So sometimes the wage jokes are really funny
And we're hammering McCain on how old he is
And that's a ha ha really funny
We're nice and ages which is no better
Or worse than being sexist or racist in my book
We're all going to get old eventually
So here's a guy who's 70 years old
You can learn something from someone like this
You can learn something from old people
And when are you old?
Is 44 constitute old?
I used to in my book
I've changed that tune
And yeah, Rompall 70 is old
Sounds pretty fucking switched on to me
Here's another old guy who knows what's going on
And he has some wise and happy words for you
I know it's going on here
Ain't no great mystery
Y'all love faith in yourselves
Is clear as it can be
You can wear all you want
Drining your misery
But you can listen to me
Listen to me
Never have it
Hope you ever wear a front
Don't let the bastard drive you down
Never have it
But they need you
Even your brain
And your dreams will come true
Feel free red sunshine
The sky's so beautiful
Like the same dream
You will sound like a devil
Me and you
Listen to me
I'll be
It's you don't take everything
Come and let my daddy lie on the table
Why can't I hold him for no more
Won't see you back in holding him
Why can't I hold him back in all more
Let him stand there for a bit
Don't you have a way up front
What a delay
No no no no
Thought that was over
Oh we ran into my last happy
From his brand new album
It's important that I want to the late night shows
Well I was in San Francisco
And thought, ah yeah, it's pretty cool
Actually bought the whole CD
or the whole album
On iTunes
A couple of good tracks there
Lath M Be happy
little message. And you know what? We might as well laugh and be happy because we're all in together. We're all getting fucked at food barred.
News from around the world, things that that happened that didn't get a chance to talk about.
First of all, I'm sure you heard about, or you know, your hider, your hider, the extreme right politician right wing politician from Austria,
who a lot of people equated to a frightening Nazi type dude.
Honestly, when all of when he was really really riding high and a lot of people were talking about him,
I wasn't paying that much attention. And so I totally, you know, I certainly had face values like,
I had the guys in Nazi, whatever. You know, coming from Austria doesn't help.
But of course, I never actually looked into what he was saying. And in many cases, you'll find that someone who might be saying something
really pretty smart and decent, his words can get turned around again.
I don't even have the time to do the research into what he was actually saying a couple of years ago.
And it's kind of a mood point because he's dead.
A horrific car accident. Now, what's interesting about this story is it comes on the heels of
him at saying in a television debate. And you can Google this. There's, and also there's links in the show notes,
maybe source code.com, and it crossposts that at curie.com. He was essentially, in the debate he was saying,
Hey, you know, this banking mafia, it is a mafia. We've got to bring these guys down because they're really,
they're screwing us. You know, kind of like when I was saying, except this guy's a politician.
And he's, and when he says something, it's big news. Well, very suspicious circumstances,
regarding his death in this solo automobile accident, particularly the picture is a rather peculiar
hole in the on the driver side on the roof. You can see that picture in the show notes.
And you could be a number of things, but I don't even have to, I don't even have to see the
hole or any weird pictures to know that this sounds like a hit, particularly, you know,
37 hours after he basically said, we got to bring these banking mafia down.
He called on the mob. He says, organized crime taking place before our very eyes.
So let's hope I never get into politics because that looks like ultimately you suicide yourself.
Or you get suicide. That's what happens. Now let's take a look at the Australians.
This is something that's happening in the United Kingdom, and it will happen worldwide.
We're talking about filtering initiatives. The Australian government looks like the Australian
cyber safety plan, which aims to block, quote, illegal content from being accessed within the country,
as well as pornographic material inappropriate for children. Interesting.
So there goes my porn. If it's inappropriate for children, then it's not appropriate for me.
If I'm an Australia, if I'm an Australia, if I'm down under, yeah, Australians, by the way,
horny bunch of people, they like getting it on, getting it leg up.
They like a little bit of porn. Maybe a lot of porn.
Hey, is there any Aussie porn? Could someone please send me a link?
I'd be kind of hot. Oh, yeah. I'll just think it.
What that sounds like.
Hmm. Come to think of it. I've never really seen porn from down under.
Okay. Chuckle heads down under. Looking forward to your submissions.
And fight this. Please fight this because once they get their food in the door, and that's where they're making such a big deal of porn.
Once they get their food in the door, you know, basically that destroys your free speech.
And, you know, what's next? You know, then it'll be something else that's illegal or bad for children.
And you just can't let this shit go by. It doesn't mean that, you know, we don't have a job to do as parents.
And as human beings and as citizens.
The internet network citizens of the globe doesn't mean that we don't have some responsibility with our freedom.
But don't let the government tell you what you can and can't see.
And please send me Aussie porn quickly before it's out of bounds.
Plenty of people drop this link into the show notes as well as email that to me about the giant database.
They're planning in the United Kingdom. Now, of course, this is only for your protection.
And we're not necessarily going to keep the content of your email message.
Just know only what time you sent one and who you sent it to. Oh, like that's okay.
And we'll throw out the actual message. Yeah, right. Like I'm supposed to believe that.
The BBC calling it an Orwellian plan.
Say, funny for them to say it.
Here it is. Communications data. That is data about calls such as the location and identity of the caller.
Not the content of the calls themselves as used as important evidence in 95% of serious crime cases.
And almost all security service operations since 2004.
Sure, let's try to prevent crime instead of making taking away our freedom to solve it.
Let's try and prevent it by getting people jobs and getting them giving them hope and let's give our children some hope.
Let's give them something to look forward to. Let them laugh and be happy as the song says.
Anyway, here's Jackie Smith, the home secretary.
Of course deals with all security here in the United Kingdom. This link in the show notes as well. Just look at her.
She's, she's a total reptile.
Ugh, you know, let's see what she has to say.
Our ability to intercept communications and obtain communications data is vital to fighting terror.
I just had to back that up. I was going to say it's vital to fighting terror.
Of course, fighting terror.
We're also terrified. Please read my email.
Oh, and by the way, I did not be sending any sexy pictures with my email because that would be dangerous for the recipient.
It could be intercepted by the children.
Some out of combating serious crime including child sex abuse murders and drug trafficking.
Of course.
Communication's data. That is data about calls such as the location and identity of the caller.
Not the content of the calls themselves.
You know what, Jackie Smith, you think you're smart, right?
You think you're doing the right thing here. They're coming for you.
They'll get you to.
Do you know that you send fucking naked pictures through email?
We all do it. You know you say sexy shit.
It's hard to believe looking at you and I'm sorry to go there.
But I'm just so angry at what you're doing.
You're already so easy to get a phone tap here in Britain or email tap.
And they're they're sponsored. They're teaching our kids how to paddle tail on the their own families and neighbors and paying them for it.
Calling the little cyber cop brigades.
People like Jackie Smith are sitting all of that up.
It's horrendous. Get rid of her. I wish I could vote here. Get rid of her.
Come on. You can't chuckle heads. Get rid of her.
If used as important evidence in 95% of serious crime cases.
Again, can we just let people be free and go and fight the reasons for this crime?
Fight the crime itself?
Prevention?
Anything. But taking away our freedoms.
Because, you know, then everyone's going to break some kind of law somewhere somehow.
Because it'll be dangerous and inappropriate for children.
And in almost all security service operations since 2004.
But the communications revolution has been rapid in this country.
And the way in which we intercept communications and collect communications data needs to change too.
If it doesn't, we will lose this vital capability.
We're going to die.
And that was certain extent. We now all take for granted.
The capability that enabled us to convict Ian Huntley for the same.
For what? For Tara?
That enabled us to achieve convictions for those responsible for the 217 terrorist plot against London.
What?
The 217?
Does she mean 777? What's 217?
It's not that again.
The action of the technological and behavioral changes that the growth of the internet brings.
Once again, it is not a government policy, which is somehow optional.
It's a reality to which government needs to be able to respond.
This is just despicable.
This is so disgusting the thing she's saying.
We are taking away your freedom because it's our duty to do so.
The changes that we need to make may require legislation.
The safeguards we will want to put in place certainly will.
And we may need legislation.
That's right. The safeguards. The same ones that protects our data, which you seem to lose every other week.
You're losing our data. That's the safeguards you think.
That's a standard that you're going to live up to.
Test what a solution to this problem will look like.
But before proceeding to legislation,
unclear that we need to consult widely with the public.
And other interested parties to set out the emerging problem.
Okay, this is important because I believe we get to have some form of a voice here, listen up.
The important capability gaps that we need to address and to look at possible solutions.
We also need to agree what safeguards will be needed.
In addition to the many that we have in place already to provide a solid legal framework that protects civil liberties.
Yeah, how about this? Don't read my email, okay? How about that for a framework?
This consultation will begin in the new year.
I mean, I have conversations with my lawyers over email.
That should be private. You should have, you have no right.
You have no right whatsoever.
Yeah, before you know it, if they want you for anything.
If you've got a big mouth, for example,
you know, then it's going to be like, well, you know, you have cyber sex.
And you're downloading naughty things and you're looking at web pages that are anti-government.
And you're a bad dude. That's how it happens.
That's how it works. That's how the police state goes.
And then they're not going on your door.
No, then I'm going to knock the going to ram it in.
And they'll come and take you away.
To the funny farm.
To be combined with a well informed debate,
characterized by openness rather than mere opinion,
by reason and reasonableness.
In this, as in the other work that we do,
my aim is to achieve a consensus.
And I hope that others will approach the serious issues
posed for our national security capabilities in the same spirit.
So let me set the terms for that open and reasonable debate.
Now I'll be clear on what we're not going to do.
There are no plans for an enormous database,
which will contain the content of your emails,
the text that you send or the chats that you have on phone or online.
Okay, so right there, there's not going to be the content,
but they're going to know who you chatted with and when you chatted with them.
Who you called? And of course, they'll actually have that information,
but they're not going to store it, at least not for a long time.
You watch.
Nora, are we going to give local farted the power to troll through such a database?
No, the authorities already have the power to actually listen to your conversations,
as well known and documented its legal councils in the United Kingdom
can ask for a wire tap either for the internet or for telephony.
So it's not, yeah, because then no,
so maybe they don't get to troll through the database,
but they can do whatever they want.
They can build their own database if they wish.
That's how it'll work.
Interest of the investigating lower level criminality
under the spirits cover of counter terrorist legislation.
I'm sick of this.
If you want to see a go to the show,
and check it out.
Well, you know, I was just singing that song.
I'm thinking, I got to see if I can find that.
Let me see.
There we go.
That's right, Jackie Smith.
Everybody, here's what she's doing us.
Remember when you ran away and I got on my knees
and begged you not to leave because I go berserk.
Yes?
Well, you left me anyhow,
and then the days got worse and worse,
and now you see I've gone completely out of my mind.
Come.
They're coming to take me away.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, uh-huh.
To the 25 where life is beautiful.
All the time, then I'll be happy to see those nice young men in their green light.
So they're coming to take me away.
Uh-huh.
You thought it was a joke and so you laughed.
You laughed when I had said that losing you would make me flip my lip.
Roller.
You know you laughed.
I heard you laughed.
You laughed.
And you laughed.
But now you know I'm utterly mad.
And they're coming to take me away.
Uh-huh.
They're coming to take me away.
To the fucking bottom.
With trees and flowers and chirping birds and basket weirder to sit and smile and twirl and come and tell the existence of your way.
Uh-huh.
I thought you're fooled.
I couldn't your house and this is how you pay me back for all my kind on selfish loving deeds.
Uh-huh.
Well, you just wait.
They'll find you yet.
And when they do they'll put you in the ASPCA you'll manage it.
Uh-huh.
They're coming to take me away.
But funny harm.
We're life is beautiful all the time and although the happy to see those nice young men in the Kuwait White coast and they're coming to take me away.
Uh-huh.
The hair will be free because of love and the jeeping birds and basket.
We made this very young wild and beautiful image and so on.
They're coming to take you away.
Napoli in the 14th on the spur of the moment. That was cool. I could find that they're coming to take me away
That's exactly what's happening. They are coming to take us all away. You got a big mouth
They'll find something to take you away. Hopefully. I'll just be so old by the time they come to take me away
That they'll take pity on me
All right, I'm gonna wrap this up. I do have one more song. I want to play in conjunction with this next story
which is Canada. It's quite an amazing amazing. Amazing place. I saw that
Historic record low turn out for their most recent election
Very very low turnout for them
Which just shows the apathy, but one thing's and maybe this is related
Something very interesting about Canada in many provinces. They're pretty laid back when it comes to marijuana and
There's this lively video titled pot 2008 that I wanted to share with you
The system designed to protect individual liberty will have no fun. It's unbelievable even this story about Canada starts with Dr. Ron Paul
Listen to it though. There's some funky stuff going on up there
Particularly when it comes to our own drugs are in the United States
But of course Ron Paul lays it out flat out first and tells you that it's bullshit the war on drugs as we know
It's well documented many many places the governments of the world are running the drugs
What do you think we're doing in Afghanistan?
95% of all of the poppy is
grown there heroin comes from there cocaine comes from there as a whole bunch of reasons why and how the cash flows into wall street
You can google that there's many and look at the daily source code drop drop dot IO slash daily source code many many good stories
detailing you know whistle blowers
You name it it's there crashes of big planes filled with cocaine government planes
And that's why they I think the U.S. doesn't want and they don't like marijuana at all
Cuz it's you need too much of it to make money to make any serious money and anyone can grow it
So they want people hooked on their shit not the the stuff given from God the holy herb that job put on the earth for us to smoke
Now they want us to have the evil shit. They make up in laboratory
For any group and no
Privileges today. I think inner city folks
and minorities are punished unfairly in the war on drugs for instance
Blacks make up 14% of those who've used drugs get 36% of those arrested are blacks and it ends out the 63% of those who finally end up in prisons are
Blacks
This has to change we don't have to have more courts and more prisons. We need to repeal the whole war on drugs
It isn't working
Dr. Ron Paul he is blacker than Barack Obama listen to that man. He's so right
He really gives a shit about people
Stupid war on drugs and
By the way our prison system completely commercialized that'll happen everywhere else. It's already happening in Europe
Commercial prisons they get paid for prisoner. Let's just pick people up and throw them in jail
We make money that way. It's just like the pharmaceutical industry. They make money by injecting bad shit into our kids
It wasn't long ago. They Canada was on the brink of decriminalization
We will soon introduce legislation to decriminalize position of small amounts of marijuana
God smart start to smoke right away
There's a feeling that the serious threat posed by marijuana and the particular company Canada is being ignored. I think
Um
joking about it
Makes that worse John Walters the White House drugs are himself was dispatched from Washington to personally deter us from legalizing pot
Lordy Lordy the anti-Christ himself is coming to Vancouver. Good god John Walters the White House drugs are from the imperial
United States
Did you should see this video the guy stood behind a desk with a pile a weed on an unbelievable pile of birds
Arriving in Vancouver next Wednesday. I would legalize this and I would tax the live and hell out of it
Larry Campbell met with the drugs are when he dropped in to visit Vancouver
The drugs are is idiot
A complete and totally idiot
I mean he tried to explain to me that marijuana was the
Was the most dangerous drug and was the most addictive drug
Any idea
And I didn't understand how that was
Yeah, you know, absolutely really my friends. It's a dangerous drug because you start to think straight
And start to tell people about the true privacy
The sun for me
I'm going to Canada
This
I'm not much with you, it's in
It's real, oh, magic round
There's no cut, call us, oh, raising up on the steering
And round those magic on
But you'll never live so long to her
For her callable in room
Holy snake tales, but just the few
Get ready to sing along, you love it
She likes wings
There is it to grow
Is it to grow in one morning due
She likes wings
There is it to grow
And there is all that
Every well when she needs a view
But she also keeps a kept awesome
And the miles fire in screaming
Raven, a magic stick, a flying broom
I'm just a few things
That she feels in her room
She likes wings
There is it to grow
Is it to grow in one morning due
She likes wings
There is it to grow
And there is all that
Every well when she needs a view
She likes wings
There is it to grow
Is it to grow in the morning due
She likes wings
There is it to grow
It was a super smash back in the 60s
I think it was actually 68
Maybe it was a huge on all the pirate radio ships
And the North Sea, the T-Set
She likes wings
They are easy to grow a Dutch band
And of course they didn't actually write lyrics
They just put a whole bunch of songs
Works together that rhyme
But considering it is this song about being hammer
Kind of works
Alrighty
And that will do it for episode number 799
Well hit 800 sometimes this coming week
Again no agenda being recorded on Sunday
So if you are in the states it will be somewhere
And the morning slash afternoon
That you will be able to get the show
And of course just appropriately
For your time zone
Please feel free to send me porn from down under
Very curious
And even better if it is your boyfriend or girlfriend
In the picture
Or the two of you together
I'm just hinting it some suggestions
I mean we might as well take advantage of our freedom
While we still can
We know what I'm talking about
So bear that in mind
Put your freedom to good use
And live your life with passion
Another fine medial presentation
Stick it in your ear