This podcast is brought to you by Pawn Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-1-4.
Yeah, it's Fumar Friday.
With $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
It's Fumar Friday.
Get your dance and shoes on everybody.
Time to kick out the jam from the trotting.
Are you ready?
Battle of the Hattle! Let's go!
It's Fumar Friday.
With $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
With $16 million worth of airplanes strap to my ass.
With $16 million worth of
All that'll point you good good.
With $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
With $16 million worth of electronic strap.
With $16 million worth of airplanes strap to my ass.
deceased athlete нам typically leaves the자
But a feedback, it is later a Friday night.
His James King, gold for the P.M.
Hand.
Got a look into my subconscious and no, I'm not playing, I believe this role was meant for me.
His my time, I've got this job, it's my time to move, can't hold on to what's gone wrong.
His my time, I've heard what they say, it won't get in my way,
because now it's a new day.
His my time, I've got this job, it's my time to move,
can't hold on to what's gone wrong.
His my time, I've heard what they say, it won't get in my way,
because now it's a new day.
His bikint was a new day.
His inner heart and my arms.
So those wishes were fine enough to me.
Because I had to hold my hands in one of the next gifts,
This can't be all you'll ever be
Gotta look into myself because I know
I'm nothing, I believe this role was meant for me
Yeah, yeah, yeah
It's my time, I gotta be strong
It's my time to move on
I can't hold on to what's going wrong
It's my time, I've heard what they say
It won't get in my way
Cause now it's a new day
It's my time, I gotta be strong
It's my time to move on
I can't hold on to what's going wrong
It's my time, I've heard what they say
It won't get in my way
Cause now it's a new day
Cause now it's my time to move on
It's my time, I've heard what's going wrong
It's my time, I've heard what they say
It won't get in my way
Cause now it's a new day
It's my time, I gotta be strong
It's my time, I've heard what they say
It won't get in my way
Cause now it's a new day
It's my time, I gotta be strong
It's my time, I've heard what they say
It won't get in my way
Cause now it's a new day
It's my time, I've heard what they say
It won't get in my way
This is the Charley, sir Jersey Todd, who of course should be hearing from later on in the program.
Oh, nice ending there dudes, they're from Ontario, Canada.
Hey everybody, it is late, it is completely, in my days, full, full, full, full, full, full,
bored.
I'm trying to be upbeat, but I got some kind of disturbing bad news when I got back in the
condo this evening.
My dad's in hospital, and I'm still trying to figure out what's going on.
He, I believe he's being operated on.
Nothing I can do right now, and I didn't feel like going to bed.
So I figured I'd bring you a show.
I'm going to be kind of low key for today.
Mainly because I'm a man physically tired, and now obviously just a little bit emotionally tired.
However, I do have the bomb diggy show lined up for you, including young polettes.
It's a fun crowd casting with Adam Curry.
I Adam, who are you ready to be stumped?
Yes, he is.
Bring it up with the young polettes.
Hey Adam, this is hit us number 106, and all the tracks this week are from 1983.
So here we go with intro number one.
Biggest.
Yeah.
That's it.
Is it, uh, was it, uh, Craig, uh, right next door?
And this is number two.
Okay, that's an easy one.
That's why we Michael Jackson and beat it.
Pretty short isn't least.
And the final one is number three.
Uh, uh, must have been love.
Yeah, I'll track from 83, darn.
And time's up.
There we go.
And these are the answers.
Oh, it's not John Craig.
Robert Craig's number one is Katie Grant.
Oh, this is Grant to know you.
Oh, man.
That takes me back on the soundtrack of my life.
And number one, Katie Grant and glad to know you.
And this is answer number two.
I knew I could, this was a run.
And this is Michael Jackson and beat it.
Anyway, hey, let's get started.
Michael Jackson is answer number two.
And this is answer number three in a test number one of six.
This is Roxette.
Roxette must have been love as answer number three.
And hit test number one.
Oh, six.
Okay.
I really blew the first one.
So what am I, did you do?
Yeah, I screwed up number one.
I'm the answers to this hit test and also the links to iTunes.
And the Instagram.
Online want to be found at hittest.botshow.com.
Thank you for playing Adam.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening.
And next week, I'll be back for hittest number one of seven.
So until then, take care and bye-bye.
Well, I'm not just thanks for playing, but thank you for putting it together once again.
Yeah, that's bugging me.
I was so convinced that first one was Robert Cray.
Well, let me just listen to that again.
So here we go with intro number one.
Oh, wait a minute.
It does sound a little bit.
You know what?
Let me just try something here.
Did you hear about the lawsuit that Warner Records has put on against seek pod?
My favorite illegal music site?
They're seeking like, oh, I think the typical $150,000 fine
were statutory compensation per violation.
Which I think would put seek pod considering it's popularity.
I had to probably put them down one or two billion dollars.
Let me just find it here.
Let me see Robert Cray.
I'm pretty sure what's right here.
It is.
Oh, man.
Does that sound the same or what?
Hold on. Let's listen to the listen to the intro.
There we go.
So hit test number 106.
And all the tracks this week are from 1980.
Listen to that.
So here we go with intro number one.
Okay.
It's a little different.
I agree.
You're all mixed.
Yeah.
That's the big master.
Let's play the song.
What the hell?
What is what helps you?
See you, Robert.
And we'll find it right next door.
The ring we were, it sounds empty in the walls
The round midnight heard a shout on three-core One.
And I knew I'd be in the saxophone.
It was because of me.
It's because of me.
I heard him shout, who is he, his mum would love
He said, the baby don't you lie, I'm here no more
And I'm listening through feastin' walls, silent shame
As he called out my name, I was right next door
Because of me, it's because of me
It's because of me, it's because of me
Oh, she was right next door, and I'm for such a strong persuader
She was just enough, and I thought my guitar
She's gonna lose a man that really loves her
In the silence, I couldn't hear them written parts
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
The Robert Cray Band in probably the worst quality recording I've ever heard of today.
Next door on the Davis Horse Code episode number 714 coming to you from the Curry Condu.
I was like going to have another, well it should be a very interesting week depending on what's
going on back in the lowlands of course I'll update you on that as soon as I can it's kind of weird
doing the Fubar Friday without having the type of mixer control that I'm used to of course
I'm still using the new mobile setup rocker now with Ableton Live with soundbite and thank you very
much a lot of people sent in some really good suggestions for MIDI control surfaces that will obviously
work with Ableton Live. So what that essentially would do is it would give me faders and a little
mixer to work with which is basically virtually controlling the software. It's it's freaky to watch it
because you move a fader up and then you see the faders on the screen move up and down. So some really
good suggestions the Jeff Smith actually checked in a suggested Apigee do-et which is indeed a
beautiful little device so perfect for portable recording but the the absolute most fascinating
best suggestion came from Alan Pine located so actually let me see to see he is located somewhere
near Paris and he sent me a link to this thing called I guess it's I'm not sure what the name
I 3L I guess is the name of it and what it is it is this is this is phenomenal I'm
definitely gonna put a link in the in the show notes daily source code.com for you to check this out
it if you're into this stuff you're gonna freak out it is a controller a MIDI controller that you
can load onto your iPhone or iPod Touch and so essentially you have the faders on your iPhone
or your iPod Touch and then through Wi-Fi there's some configuration of course you basically need to
you know you basically need to hack your your iPhone or or iPod Touch with the was it the
jailbreak software but then remote completely wirelessly you can control these faders just by
holding the iPhone in your hand can you believe that how cool is that I mean so I could literally just
be you know kind of like fade and stuff up and down with my left hand while I'm controlling the
other stuff with my right hand really really awesome of course unfortunately my iPhone after it
took after it took that that bath in the toilet the the the the the most important part for this
experiment doesn't work which is the the touch screen but wow it would be great to have something
like that on on the Nokia on the 800 and 10 I wonder if anyone's done any software like that
because that also has a touchscreen and that would be a phenomenal use for that device which of course
you can buy at a 15% discount you can't get a cheaper anywhere in the world just go to the show notes
the daily source code dot com and there's a link right there if you're in the US or if you're in the
UK more countries coming online soon I use the code daily source code and here's a guy we haven't
heard from in in a couple of weeks partially my fault he's also been very busy but of course
what expect guys a lawyer huh you're on her I'd like to make a motion to rock this mother out
you're on her please don't bang that gavel you can try this cowbell out let's all give a
night to the hardest work in law here it's Jersey time oh yeah you're on her what do you say
yeah how's it going Adam it's Jersey time the official musicologist of the Chacha so dude
I don't just sing it every week I bring it and this week is no exception because I've got a
band for you that is really really interesting in fact I didn't know anything about them they come
from the pharaoh island the band's name is eager to please now I had never heard of the pharaoh
island so I went over to Wikipedia dot org and this is what they have to tell me the pharaoh
islands apparently are group of islands in northern Europe between the Norwegian sea and the northern
Atlantic Ocean the roughly equal distant between Iceland and Norway they're an autonomous
province of the kingdom of Denmark and in fact other than their legal system foreign affairs and
defense they are completely autonomous from Denmark I never heard of these guys and you know what
these pharaoh islands apparently rock because this band eager to please has completely completely
throw me this week you got to check this out they are just perfect for a food bar Friday they're
big they're loud and they're a lot of fun and they also got a huge intro check this out it's
eager to please with two time and lady yeah we're out nothing like a big intro for a food bar Friday
Help me
you
don't think I know what you're all about
You're the cheating guy, and you always take the easy way out
You ain't fooling nobody, you're fooling yourself
Oh, wake up baby, I'm with my lower Michelle
Two times a day, just get away from me
You're on me, and you're awake
Through the night I'm leaving
Just get out of my face, don't want to run away
Get to the end of this maze
You fall around and you're taking me for a ride
I can see it in your eyes, baby, what you try to hide
Two times a day, don't try to play your games with me
Yeah, oh baby, baby, you make it easy to see
Two times a day, just get away from me
You're on me, and you're awake
Through the night I'm leaving
Just get out of my face, don't want to run away
Got to get out of this maze
Two times a day, just get away from me
You're on me, and you're awake
Through the night I'm leaving
Just get out of my face, don't want to run away
Got to get out of this maze
All right, definitely put the Ferrell Islands on the list of places to visit
You're gonna please, two time and lady
Surgery is he Todd, when the man is back, the man is definitely back
I got a great song lined up for you from the Italian variety
I was listening to episode number 30 of my sister's podcast
From the hills of Florence, Italy
She hadn't done a show in a long time, but of course I have her show on my on the go channel
So it popped up automatically, and so I listened and it was really it was a great update
In fact, I should put a link in the show notes to give her a little link of
She talked about, well, essentially the past couple months, although we're back to August
So it was real cool because you know, I caught up on a couple things that I knew that she'd been up to because she was actually a vacation with us
When we were in the states member Fire Island
For those of you who've been hanging around the show long enough
And she played a song by her husband, so my brother-in-law who is a well-known actor, director, producer, all-round entertainer
And he's a great guy, I really love the guy
And he, I've heard him sing before he, when we Patricia and I renewed our vows, or basically got remarried in Italy
A couple years ago, and we had the whole family over, and it was really cool
And Alessandro got up during like after dinner, or best
We were still kind of at the dinner table, but after dinner he got up and he had that we had a piano player there and he started singing
And the guy's just a great entertainer, and he has this classic song called Karina
Which she played on the show, it's not part safe, but I begged her and she gave me a copy, and I think you'll like it a lot
That's coming up right next
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Game's Weasel, coming up on this week's show
We've got a review of roleplaying game, Kingdom and the Fire Circle of Doom on the 360
We also shoot lots of stuff with geometry walls, galaxies on the DS
I chat to the team behind first person shooter, conflict denied ops, and you can win one of five copies of the club for the Xbox 360
That's all at gamesweasel.btfodshow.com
Hey Adam, we're in here from the World's Wayne podcast, the World's Wayne podcast
I hate it when that happens
Let's just pretend they didn't happen, I'll just take it back, okay
So it didn't actually happen what you just said
Don't come
Karina
You're 20, you're 40
My fondore is always a bandina, that I don't know
She's the hero of love
Grazieza
Mezzuna, don't you dare to take it back
Karina
You're the hero of love
But with the bro, I'm always the best
You're the star
Karina
My fondore is always a bandina
That I don't know
She's the hero of love
Grazieza
Mezzuna
Don't you dare to take it back
Karina
My fondore is always a bandina
That I don't know
She's the hero of love
Grazieza
Mezzuna
Don't you dare to take it back
Grazieza
Mezzuna
Don't you dare to take it back
Karina
My fondore is always a bandina
Grazieza
Mezzuna
Karina
Why don't you dare
Just inspire a bar
Your band screaming
She's the hero of love
Grazieza
Mezzuna
She's the hero of love
Grazieza
Karina
My fondore is always a bandina
Grazieza
Mezzuna
Darida
Marisa
Mezzuna
Karina
You're an engineer
No one wants to play anyơi
did have to give you an audio comment.
You see, this one just really affected me.
You see, in researching this week's rumor Friday,
I don't know why, but I came across the history
of CBGBs.
Don't know why, I was just surfing around.
And I never really knew this.
If you don't know CBGBs, it was the legendary
legendary club in New York City.
And I'm the sign underneath CBGBs outside.
It said, I'm fug.
And I never knew what that stood for until now.
Because I'll just read you this interview with Hilly Crystal.
He says that the question most often asked
to me is, what is CBGB's stand for?
And I reply, it stands for the kind of music
that I intended to have, but not the kind
that we became famous for, country, bluegrass blues.
The next question is always, but what is omfug stand for?
And I say, that's more of what we do.
It means other music for uplifting gourmandizers.
And what is a gourmandizer?
It's a voracious eater, in this case, music.
Man, oh, man, oh, man, if there is ever inspiration
or a mantle for the pot-safe music network to assume,
it's that omfug of the music for uplifting gourmandizers.
You see, the listeners of pot-safe music network,
we're some gourmandizers.
I'll tell you that.
I want everything out there.
And the artist that are on the PMN,
man, we got some great, great chefs.
Well, that's just my final thought of the week.
What's yours?
Well, I got all kinds of thoughts running to my brain
right now, Todd.
I'm fug, we're definitely going to keep that in the show.
Hey, thanks to everybody for sending in your demographic
information.
Indeed, I was right.
It seems like we got a bunch of middle-age, middle-class dudes
listen to the show.
And I love you all, no homo.
By the way, just to make it clear, homo loves loud, too.
Got no problem with it.
This is from South Africa.
This is Derek.
Derek, the bandit versus James Nelson, featuring Marseille.
It's on the pot-safe music network.
Total chill out.
It's a little uncarturistic for a fubar, but...
I think we can all handle.
During the car, be careful you might start to speed up the end.
If you're on the train, be careful.
It might be late in the, a little bit too close to that person next to you.
I wish they'd love you.
You, while you're making my sense.
And I'll have to give you a hug.
Oh, oh, oh.
I wish they'd love you.
You, while you're making my sense.
True, I must have love.
I must have carried all the time.
It's on the theory of the way we're trying.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I wish they'd love you.
Oh, oh, oh.
Just for a day.
I wish they'd love you.
You, while you're making my sense.
True, I must have love.
I must have loved you.
You, while you're making my sense.
True, I must have loved you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Just for a day.
I wish they'd love you.
Oh, oh, oh.
Just for a day.
I wish they'd love you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Just for a day.
You know what I mean, that's just one of those songs that you can have that on in the car
and you turn it up really, really loud and just kind of start to space out and then you
forget the speedometer and then before you know it, you're doing 70 clicks.
Nice.
Very, very nice.
Hey man, what would a food bar Friday be without our EU correspondent, huh?
I'm all thank God he checked it.
Comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip.
Hi, I'm Adam Ferricari, I'm here with your EU correspondent.
So, as you know, EU, I say, is going towards recession and in result, well, you know,
a whole month as a second CSP, it's not officially a recession.
I think there's a, there's a, where the hell is nylon?
I have all these financial questions.
We know that he knows what's going on.
He is the Savank du Finance.
What is the official definition of a recession?
I don't think we're in one yet, but okay, CSP I'll play along with you.
Financial situation worldwide is more and more volatile.
So, EU countries are now intensifying efforts, meetings and, you know,
behind the scenes stuff, stabilizes the financial situation, but clearly in the
so-called Eurozone, it means 15 EU countries with 320 million people
that use Euro currency, that is, by the way, now getting stronger and not only against
US dollar, but also British pound.
So, maybe we all should switch back to gold standard as a whole, comments, recommends.
Well, great here you have Adam, what condition are you using?
Yeah, yeah, very funny, but of course, it's officially, it's love you,
mean it, great hair, hope you win.
Thank you very much, comics, trip blogger.
Yeah, I know, I just can't, my brain's motion, I can't get into all that stuff.
Ron Paul did put out something interesting, I got an email about it, let me, let me find it for you here.
What is it called exactly?
It is the four point plan, there you go, it's the comprehensive economic revitalization plan,
you can find it at RonPaul2008.com, four points, tax reform, spending reform, monetary policy reform,
and regulatory reform, just the highlights, tax reform, reduce the tax burden, eliminate taxes
that punish investment and savings, including job killing corporate taxes.
Nice, spending reform, eliminate wasteful spending reduce overseas commitments,
freeze all non-defense, non-intitinal spending at current levels, monetary policy reform,
expand openness at the Federal Reserve and require the Fed to televised its meetings.
That's very interesting, because up to now Ron Paul has said, we got to get rid of the Federal
Reserve, and I think he's taken a very wise step here by essentially putting in, I would call it a
phase-out step, but to require the Federal Reserve, which, by the way, please remember the Federal
Reserve, who prints our money, who determines in the U.S., who determines the interest rates is a
private commercial organization comprised of commercial banks of which the complete member list is unknown,
and it's a black bark, black box, a dark dark hole, so the idea of expanding openness and requiring
them to televised their meetings is a great idea, and he says return value to our money.
Of course, there's a, on this page, it's all expanded so that you can see exactly what it means
by that. So return value to our money legalized gold and silver as a competing currency, man.
This is big, this is a really big idea, subbullet here, level the long-term boom and bust business
cycle by passing HR 4683. So there's all these proposed bills or laws, or whatever we could
call them, that go along with this, with this four-point plan. So pass HR 4683, which would repeal
provisions of the Federal Criminal Code, relating to issuing coins of gold, silver, or other
metal for uses current money, and making or possessing likeness of such coins. So I guess indeed
it's illegal to pass off, to make your old gold coins. Wouldn't that be cool, though, if you could
make your own gold and silver coins? Awesome. And then finally the fourth point is regulatory
form, repeal sarbans, oxly regulations that push companies to seek capital outside of U.S.
markets, stop restricting community banks from fostering local economic growth. So sarbans, oxly,
or sarbox, as it's known, has made the public going public-basic or being a public company,
very burdensome, very, very complicated. So damn, comics are blogger. You got me to do it after
all. I talked about some finance shit, even though really actually too tired to do it.
This song, my friends from the Pod Safe Music Network, is nominated for an Academy Award.
I couldn't be happier, so should you.
And games I've never amount to, more than they're meant, will play themselves out.
Take the sink in both, and afford it home, and we still got time. Raise your old
full voice, you have a choice, you make it now.
Falling slowly, I stand only, I don't try to go back.
Just let it take me, I'll never erase me, and I'll pay too much.
Will you have suffered enough, and what with yourself is time at U.S.
Take the sink in both, and afford it home, and we still got time.
Raise your old full voice, you have a choice, you make it now.
Falling slowly, I stand only, I stand only, I don't try to go back.
Take the sink in both, and afford it home, and we still got time.
Falling slowly, glad answered, Marquetta Aglova, is from the original version picture soundtrack for
the movie once. It's nominated for Best Original Song and nice to have that on the
Podsake Music Network. Also has two Grammy nominations. Awesome.
Oh man, I am tired and I'm bummering out. You know, my dad and I don't really talk at
all. In fact, the last time we talked was that our big family reunion in August and
you know, a year could go by and we don't talk. There's a whole bunch of reasons for that.
And now of course, you know, now that things aren't, well, things weren't going too well
with them for a while, but you know, now that whatever has happened has happened, I was like,
you know, it's like, oh man, all these things we should have been talking about and, you know,
you always get a fatalistic view and crap, I don't know, my head's just spinning.
Ah, I need to, I need some to cheer me up. Let me see. One more song, which we do that. I figured
out by the way, how in Ableton, though, how I can find the time, where at what 48, 49 minutes
now, perfect. Just great for a footballer Friday. Here we go. These guys always cheer me up.
Whenever you're kind of down, you can always crank up the fire apes.
Still, I'll always wonder why. Oh, I couldn't take it anymore.
Just to know, let's be for a no more.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
They take it, he's way, I'll take it all too late
I've been no take thinking of you, we thought the thought you could be through
I've been no take you for days and days, I could only stand up
Oh, I can't take it anymore
Just to know that we've fallen no more
Take it, he's way, I'll take it all too late
I'll take it all too late
I think it's that last tone that last chord that just hits me in the right spot
Fire Apes, hey Kate, wrap it up the Fubar Friday edition of the Daily Source Code episode number 714
Hey, that's a lot of episodes
All right, everybody, tomorrow I'm sure I'll have an update for you
I'll post something on the blog about the situation back in the lowlands
I try to get a hold of JCD John Cdvorak
We were going to do a Noah gender earlier today
And I did ping him on Skype, but I didn't get back to me
I was much later than I expected
So maybe we'll do one tomorrow morning
Which would be kind of interesting because I'll be here in San Francisco in the condo
And he'll be in the Devorak mansion somewhere in San Francisco
And even though it's called Noah gender, I think he wanted to talk about a specific topic
He mentioned it to me in passing on the street and I was excited about it
Uh, for now, uh, Adam at podshow.com, DailySourceCode.com
And, uh, of course, uh, I'd like to say
Love you, mean it's a great hair, hope you win
Live your life with passion
And, of course, enjoy your freedom
Have a great weekend, everybody, bye-bye