With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I guess it's Adam Curry.
Is the evil Adam Curry from the brass guy?
And you're listening to the Daily Source Code, D-S-C-7-3-0.
More.
Whatever I like, whatever I like,
If you don't want to lie, come every time you go.
Come on, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take,
let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let
it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it
take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, put it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, Let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take take, let it take, let it take, let it take take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it go, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take, let it take
But cause I'm the same, don't be happy in my life
But your feet, you didn't want to get a chance
I'm forgetting me, you know?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
That's a kind of tune that just kicks off the week and all I'm saying, excellent.
Party Bands, genius of London, thanks to a mainland, our very own genius in London, running
the Podshow UK office, actually sent this one name for a Friday's footballer, but you probably
figured out by now that I just didn't have the energy to get into it and do it.
Ah, fully well knowing that Saturday was going to be a Noah gender day with my friend
John C. DeVorex, so I just had the slip and slide it over to Monday.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's a daily source code episode number 730 coming to you from the curry manner on
the west side of G-town, the affluent suburb of Surin on his Guilford.
I have some kind of high pitched, some thing, that my wires are all messed up, just when I
started perfecting all of the software on my new setup, which by the way, a lot of you emailed
me that the previous episode from San Francisco had some kind of weird sound distortion in it.
I heard it at the time when it happened, we just turned this down a bit, so you thought,
it works any better.
There we go.
Yeah, I heard it at the time and I just decided to ignore it because I'm sure by now,
most people are pretty fed up with listening to me complaining about the sound setup, but
I knew it was happening in Franco from Rockhouse to Talia sent me a couple of tips for those
of you who were interested in basically had to do with the Mitch Matt mismatch of bit rates
on the aggregate device that I set up in the Mac.
Anyway, I still got to document everything every single day.
I get a little bit closer to this thing being one stable operation that I can just fire up.
In fact, now I'm still firing up like four different apps to make it all work, so once
all of this is stable, which is starting to look like the next step is going to be to create
a script, an Apple script that will essentially boot everything up and configure everything.
I guess if not almost completely automatically, and document that's where other people can
set it up as well.
It's not a cheap setup, but man, when you get it running, that was of course was the beauty
of Cass Blaster, which unfortunately only runs on Windows, but you could rely on it.
You fired that puppy up.
You still can, obviously, Cass Blaster.com, you just fired up and it works.
It just always works.
Even with the USB headset these days, as I found out recently, the Candyman ran into trouble
and figured out that it does work.
Sorry, so now I've got all the software stuff working.
It sounds like I've got some kind of ground loop going in my, I don't know.
It can only be the microphone in the preamp to the microphone, so I'm not exactly sure what's going on.
Um, but I guess that's Murphy's law.
Once you get the software side, fix the hardware failure.
Hi Adam. My name is Anna from Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.
Well, I just wanted to say that I love listening to the daily source code,
but I love it so much more when Patricia is there participating.
We've used so please, Adam, bring her back.
Hi.
Yeah, I just asked her, actually, and she said, what now are you kidding?
I show now.
There was a, I had, I had to represent for Patricia yesterday in Amsterdam.
It was her, one of her best friends is this Ku-3A, which is like a fashion dude.
He makes clothing high and, um, you know, not, uh, old cootures, so not off the rack.
And he does, uh, obviously does this fashion shows four times a year, and Patricia often works.
They're best friends, so he, uh, they often work together on what the hairstyle is going to be,
uh, she even gives him ideas about the clothing.
He's very close relationship, and, uh, and, uh, they enjoy doing that stuff a lot.
And so Patricia always goes to the shows, and this time she said, look, you know, please,
will you come along? Uh, it would be fun, you know, it'd be good for you to represent,
for the family, for Paul. That's his name, Paul Schulter.
And, uh, well, you knew I, if you listen to Noah Genda, you know, she already bought me a,
a pre-produced, uh, the buying of a suit before I got back from San Francisco.
And then, uh, Saturday, uh, bless her, man, she, she made me feel welcome. Let me tell you,
there was a big welcome home party. And right after all the good stuff, she said, okay, now,
grab your coat. We're going to go shopping for a suit.
And I have to say off the rack almost at Ted Baker, fantastic. I got a couple. Really, uh,
really happy. Anyway, so one of those was for the fashion show. Now, Patricia had some other
business to do. So she left on Saturday, uh, evening. She flew to Amsterdam with EasyJet.
And so she was there, uh, a day earlier. And, uh, so I flew over yesterday, uh, Sunday.
And, uh, as you know, uh, the lady Patricia loves to fly with me, but she won't fly across the English
channel, um, unless, uh, I have a safety pilot. So I had Captain Dan with me, who she, uh, she loves
Captain Dan because besides him being a, uh, a certified diving instructor and, uh, rescue swimmer
and, uh, he is obviously also a certified pilot and instructor. Uh, he is really not needed,
because I can do everything. But I understand if it makes her feel more comfortable. So Captain Dan and I,
oh, by the way, she loves Captain Dan because he's kind of heavy. And she knows that, uh, if we go into the
sea, that she can always hang onto him because she sure he'll float.
Um, and it was, uh, the weather was, um, interesting. A lot of wind, uh, the skies were generally good
and there was no rain and, uh, and the cloud base was pretty high, uh, but we did have rather strong
winds. In fact, we were doing about 200 knots going over, uh, uh, on the way over from, uh, from our airport
over to a hill versus, so right under Amsterdam is a little airfield I like to use when I fly there,
much less hassle and, uh, you know, you're supporting a community of people I always buy fuel
from them if I can. Uh, and it's, uh, and it's just cheaper, uh, everything's cheaper there.
And they have a great little restaurant that has opened six days a week and it's right on the air
field. So it, it's a great vibe and, uh, I've flown there a lot when I was, uh, uh, learning how to fly.
So I love to support them as much as I can. Um, um, but I even called them. I said, hey, I'm coming in.
I want to park the plane overnight and then like, wow, you know, it's really windy.
You've got crosswind, uh, which means they don't have a, uh, a runway, uh, which you can use to land
on, which you'll be heading directly into the wind, which is what you're trained for, obviously,
because, uh, you know, you should be able to put this thing down anywhere regardless of the wind
if necessary. So you train for a lot of weird situations, but it's a little more work, uh,
when you're doing a crosswind landing. And this kind of, uh, brings me to a video that's been
circulating around the net. And many people sent it to me. I posted it over on, uh,
curry.com on the weblog. Uh, you see, uh, airbus, uh, a 320, uh, landing and essentially performing
a pretty much a textbook go around. But it was great because, um, you know, you, the way people
talk about this video is like, wow, man, these people are almost dead and, uh, the pilot only
barely averted a crash and, you know, as airman and dad and I looked at this video and, you know,
it's, it's, it's very dramatic to look at, but probably no less dramatic than if, uh, if
couple of pilots were to, you know, or as dramatic, if a couple of pilots were to look at open
hard surgery and see how close the surgeon came to sniffing some, something he shouldn't, you know,
but even though there may have been no danger at all and it may have been very standard procedure.
If that makes any sense, that kind of, uh, analogy. And you should really check this video out
because I just wanted to mention a few things. First of all, um, a lot of people said, wow, look
at the angle of the plane coming in. It's not aligned with the runway and this is true and although
you rarely ever notice it when you're in the aircraft, uh, as a passenger, um, you know, typically
if there is some kind of crosswind, meaning wind not coming directly up the runway, um, that plane
is going to land, uh, with its nose into the wind and kind of moving sideways. It's a bit like sailing
on the ocean, if you will. Um, and although it looks weird, if the most comfortable way, really,
I mean, there's another way to, uh, to land in a crosswind and you can basically point your stick or your
steering column, if you will, into the wind and then, uh, depress the opposite pedal, um, and,
you know, the plane will then, uh, basically fight the forces of nature and stay on a steady course,
uh, however, whichever side you, um, depending on which side you depress the pedal and, you know,
opposite, uh, opposite stick, uh, the plane is going to tilt and that can make passengers kind of uncomfortable
because it can, uh, it feels really, really weird when you do that. Uh, so typically that's not done,
but at the last minute, what you do is then you straighten out the plane as it lands and then you get
or with a nose straight on the runway. And now there's a couple of situations that we're at
at play here, um, partial wind shear, partial crosswind, uh, wind shear is a situation that can, uh,
the most, besides the fact that it's, uh, that it's wind coming from the side typically,
the most devastating effect is that you lose altitude very, very quickly in wind shear and that you
can drop down significantly. And I think that's what I'm seeing on this video, uh, as you see,
the aircraft seems a bit high on approach, but again, you have no context because you're, you know,
you're looking at video and you can't really see the distance as properly. It's just kind of
a guesstimate. It could be completely off. So it's just, you know, my opinion from what I'm seeing,
and all of a sudden you see a rapid descent and then you see the pilot, uh, the pilot in command
turning the plane, uh, aligning with the central line on the runway and then the, um, the wing
that's, uh, into the wind raises up, of course, pushing the opposite wing very close to the tarmac.
Now I would say it's, and it's, again, you can't see it from this video, but when you're landing,
you know, you want to have your stick into the wind. Uh, you know, certainly with taxiing,
any, any, any time you've got an aircraft out, uh, out and about, you want to have, uh, you want to
be pointing your stick or your column into the wind because that's exactly what can happen. The wind
can catch underneath your wing and then it'll want to flip you over. So he may not have had, you know,
maybe because there was some wind shear. He drops significantly. He was concentrating on pointing
the aircraft onto the center line. Didn't have enough sticking to the wind. And then, uh, the
unfortunate happened is when the wind blew his wing tip up, the other one down, and of course,
he did exactly what you're supposed to do is hit the throttle full and perform a go around. And it
just looked kind of weird because the minute he, um, he was on the ground only for just a few moments
and then he hit the throttle and he, um, and the aircraft took off again, but of course, you know,
this wind was so strong that it blew him right off the center line and he recovered. It's kind of
weird to see because the engines are making all kinds of smoke and you can't, you know, it almost
looks like he's scraping the ground continuously, but he isn't. So, um, pretty textbook stuff.
I'd have to say, it looks much scarier than it probably was. Anyway, long story to get us to the
fashion show. Uh, it was great. Uh, had a great time, actually. So I was wearing my new suit,
funky, uh, had my, uh, my darling wife on my arm. Um, it was a great show. I have to say this was one
of the better ones. And, and I really do carry, and I care about how the models look. I care about
the clothing they're wearing. You know, in Patricia and I will talk about, you know, the shoes
as they're coming by and what goes with what and how it looks and how it falls. And I've paid
attention, you know, for 22 years, I've been hanging out with this woman. So I, uh, I kind of know what's
going on. Had a good time. And, of course, we were going to fly back today. And, um, weather was,
for me, to take a passenger along, it was just on the edge because I knew it was going to be a
little bit bumpy because all the advantage we got from, uh, coming over, you know, doing 200 knots,
which is well over an excess of 200 miles an hour. Uh, now we were going to pay for it, uh,
by hitting straight into the wind on the way back. Um, and so we were going probably 120, three knots.
Yeah, something like that. And, you know, you mess around and find the right altitude where
where the wind is a little bit, you know, less strong or gusty. And then you can pick up a couple
knots. So we were kind of figuring that out as we went along. But it was bumpy. It wasn't
extremely comfortable because some of this wind was gusting up to 33, 35 knots. Patricia's a trooper.
She said, okay, you know, after like an hour and a half, which is what it normally takes,
she's like, I'm ready to land. So we made it into our field, um, just about an hour and 55 minutes.
I think it just took us a little bit longer. And a crosswind as well. And I have to say a little
bounce, uh, on coming in because the wind did catch underneath the body of the plane and push the back
up. And I just, uh, I wasn't fantastic on the landing, but not bad because as you know, when you
go walk away from the landing and the aircraft is reusable, you've done a great job.
Hey, Adam is a David and so these Texas calling again about the iPhone and the water thing.
Uh, today Apple released a technop that the iPhone has an indicator at the base of its head
on Jack that is normally white. As a phone, it's been submerged in liquid or had liquid damage
apples, as that it's half of the dot becomes red or in kitchen color. When the phone has been
submerged in liquid, see Apple document for image they have an insert. You know, that's,
so this is, uh, I guess proof of what we've been talking about, that this, uh, indicator really
does exist. It does exist in the Nokia phones. Uh, but what's amazing is, um, I'm looking into the
iPhone, the one that was submerged and it's really not easy to tell. I don't know if they, they might
have a special instrument or some kind of microscope or some kind of magnifying glass they have to
use because it's just not that easy to see. If the dot is red or I think it's color, the repair
is not covered by warranty. And, uh, so there you have it. I guess, uh, when yours landed in the
toilet, it must have gone head sewn down and it must have been an air bubble. That kept it
from getting wet through those, but anyways, there you go. It's the announcement, uh, nine. So I
thrown at was dot com. Bye. All right, man. Thank you. I appreciate the update. That did happen
last week. God, man, that that little high frequency noise is irritating. Can't wait. My father
and law, uh, is custom building from me, uh, an old school microphone preamp. And then I'll have
all my shit set up. I only have two external boxes. I'll have the MIDI controller for, um, you know,
for my faders and I'll have the, uh, the mic pre, which I've specified. I wanted to be, uh, with a nine
volt battery. So everything is completely either powered from the laptop or powered by battery.
Of course, the next thing actually to do would be to use USB power for that, but, uh, we'll have to
think about it. Oh, man, you're going to love this. Listen, it was back.
Adam, it's the nylon. Find that jingle. Oh, hold on a second. Oh, I thought I had the jingle. I'm
sorry. Uh, let's so he read for the nylon. Dun, uh, wait, the here it is.
Right. He's back. I haven't gone anywhere. Well, listen to each one of your shows. I'm
Ron Paul on down. And it's a similar Godfather. Just when I was trying to get out, you pulled
you back in, baby. So this is only a warning, because I'm finishing up performing devices
in my team for the next week or so. So not a lot of time. For those of you just checking in the
nylon, uh, our New Yorker and London, um, works in the financial industry apparently. And so
it makes a lot of sense. He's doing performance reviews. He knows a lot about banking and about money.
And he hates me. But he is my threat. Next week, I'm going to do your performance evaluation.
See a 2000 and seven. See what I mean? Um, you too need to have your performance evaluated.
And, um, I've been giving some thought to it. And over the next coming days, um, I hope to give you
some feedback. Meanwhile, um, pleasing you, pull me back in with this stupid,
democratic survey. Here's my problem. You get this whole fucked less thing over the summer,
with you got, you know, everything down to, you know, the size of my underwear knickers on this
hole on a second. Hold on. What happened here? What's going on? Why do I have this? Oh, man,
hold on. Something's very wrong here. Okay. All right. I thought, well, nylon was talking
I have to be honest. I was thinking of myself, hey, maybe I can fix this home.
All right. Back to the suckless data. What was your problem survey? Yeah. I got no feedback. We got
no feedback. Nothing's changed. And now you do this in a graphic survey. You know, one point of
the fuck less, you know, all you keep doing is collecting data data data data data data data data data and
new data data. The engine, a good no agenda that revolutionary news show that you do with a friend, um,
that was great. Oh, thank you anyway. I'm not getting any information on it. You know,
it's too much fucking less. Okay, next week. The dubie back. Alright, it's good to have you back
back nylon. Very, very happy about that. Well, you know, we have released a
cyclist data to our producers, which was a main point of the exercise, so that our
producers could actually understand a lot about the audience. If you took the
cyclist survey, you will have known that it was a lot more about particular types
of advertising. And this for the, and also, if, if you hadn't noticed, and I know
you're very busy with the performance reviews, the daily source code,
listener audience data is public data. You can view the results right online. And
if you go look at curry dot com, you can see that I released a beautiful
presentation, uh, done by one of the chuckleheads. So it's a complete community
project, which shows, uh, the, uh, the report. And it shows information about us. It
was really a, uh, really a community deal, man. Nothing more, nothing less, no need
to get your panties in a bunch. But welcome back, can't wait to hear from you.
Hi, Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel on this week's show. We've got a review of
Unreal Tournament 3 on the PlayStation 3. Also, the club on the Xbox 360,
find out what happened when I went to Amsterdam, for an exclusive look at Sega's
condemned to. And you can win. I don't think that for the Xbox 360, that's all
the game's Weasel dot beaty for show dot com. Oh, man, Matt Kotlin on in Amsterdam.
I can only imagine what kind of debauchery that might have been. So normally, uh,
a lot of the, what I had prepared for today's show would have been out on Friday.
So what is it you missed for your weekly wrap up?
That's right. Y'all, let's hit test.
Hello, Adam, this is a hit test number 111, the triple one edition.
And if all went well, I'm in New York City right now. Excellent. Therefore, this episode of
the hit test has been recorded. One week ago. Okay. No problem. If you're ready, we're going to
start right away with intro number one.
Ah, the dungeon. It's a, uh, brother's Johnson, win a stop on in the neighborhood. Yeah.
Number two.
Ah, Billy Joel, uptown girls. Come on, y'all. Man, make a part on me. Nice intro, though, huh?
And the final one is number three.
Oh, crap, that's hard. It sounds like it might be talk talk, but I'm not sure.
And times up in these are the answers. Yeah. Answer number one.
From 1980, these are the brothers Johnson.
Here's a stop.
Number two, from 1983. Billy Joel, this is uptown girl.
Number two, Billy Joel. And this is answering number three from 1989.
And a diva.
A diva and respect as answering number three.
In the triple one edition of the hit test number one hundred and eleven.
So Adam, how did you do? Well, I'm two out of three on the last one I would not have gotten.
The answer said to this hit test. And also the iTunes link, so that you can buy these
tracks online not to be found at hittest.butchio.com.
I don't exactly know when the page will be updated because like I told you, uh, at the beginning of
for the hittest, uh, as if I went well, I'm in New York City enjoying my ass off.
So next time, I'll be, uh, semi life again. So thank you for playing Adam.
Thank you for your health. Thank you for listening. Next week, I'll be back for number one hundred and
twelve. So until then, take care. Have a nice week and bye bye.
Oh, young. Thank you. I was actually watching his Twitter feed. I think, uh,
I think young is already back and he made it safe. And I hope you did have a good time and part of your
ass off. Um, let me see. Okay. For the past week or two, uh, certainly a lot. Unfortunately,
while I was in San Francisco, and I just didn't have time to set up a live DSC, I'll, I will get to
one later this week, although I have a lot of stuff to do in London as well. Um, I want to hear
from the Brits at a time when they can actually participate in their wake to joining on the show.
Um, I, the main focus, I think, well, two things, one of the Northern Rock bailout,
which, you know, and all that stuff, and actually there's three things in non-domiciled
tax status. Okay. But the, uh, the one that is really quite important, uh, is this red pill moment
we've had about what's going on in the UK. And now the, uh, the government has come out with a campaign
where they're actually asking Brits to spy on each other, uh, in a, in a fashion that, uh,
is a really three areas. One is, uh, if you see someone taking a lot of pictures of public buildings,
you should report them, uh, if you see something suspicious going on in someone's home,
in or around someone's home, which to me is the most concerning. And the third one is, oh,
if it looks like someone has too many, uh, mobile cell phones for their own good, because, of course,
terrorists use cell phones to blow things up. Um, so it's a, a massive marketing campaign, uh,
which is going out on outdoor posters, radio commercials I played one. Um, and I, you know,
there's mixed reactions, uh, I must say that looking back and I have done a little bit of research
in the meantime, that when the IRA was blowing up places in London, uh, there were similar
type of warnings, some of the languages, in fact, exactly the same. Uh, but I do believe personally
that this is a little different this time, because, uh, this type of terrorism has a face and that
face is also a face that is just a part of the population of the United Kingdom, uh, apply this
situation to your own home country. It works almost everywhere. Uh, I got a great comment that I
want to share for you with you. I had a new from underneath, uh, um, uh, long time listener, and been
listening since that 2000, full December 2004. Yeah, beginning of 2005. Um, um,
I just read those adverse from the net police about spying on each other. It made me feel
physically sick, man. There's a rule, not in the stomach. Oh, uh, uh, it's just horrible.
When, um, when I was a kid, it was all about, yeah, there was stories to it about,
for sure, being like that, you know, neighbor spy on neighbor, you know, default mode is fear,
fear of everybody and everything. You want to live like that. These are host, yeah,
that was, that was what we always told the Russians like that. How will our comics work? We're,
we're like based on a world world too, and they're all about coys and things and those band
traitors who they were the ones that self scared and they were watched and they were hunted.
You know, this is really interesting because, uh, I remember a lot of those comics too. We had our own
version in the United States and any boy, any man actually who's listening to the show and hearing
that high pitched wine when I talk. Um, you'll, you can immediately teleport yourself back to your
youth when you were a kid. And the comic books, I had like battle of midway, um, you know,
where the Japanese were the bad guys and all kinds of comic books. So that really hit me when I
heard you're talking about this. And, uh, you know, we were the plucky brits who substrate to
it on the chin, but also it's down and just come on with it. And I was proud of being British,
you know, and I was proud of being British during the IRA campaign. So we know that
those sort of scary, because that always went off to work and, you know, if we're going to get
a ship or on the tele, something like that. Exactly. However, uh, but it was always business
is usually, you know, they weren't going to, they weren't going to change our way of life. And
then people actually said that, you know, on the tele and, and, and that on the radio and, you know,
face to face. So take note of that. People actually said that. And you hear something very different
today. You really do. It's a very, and I'm, unfortunately, I just wasn't around when the IRA
activity was at its height. So I'd love to hear more from the British listeners to the daily
source code to find out what that was like. And do you feel that there were differences between
terrorism, then, which is exactly the same thing, blowing things and shit and people up and tubes
and buses and threats of all kinds of, but basically the IRA as far as I know, they were all about
bombs. Whoops. This show just got picked up by echelon. Um, so yeah, I'd love to hear from the
British. Um, please, please, please call the call the phone number. If you don't have the phone
number, by the way, and I haven't talked about this in a long time, you might just want to consider
putting it into your cell phone. And, uh, so here's what you do in the UK. You do a plus four four,
obviously. That's the international cell phone code. So you don't have to, you know, you can even
call us from America. So plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three
plus four four two zero seven six eight one three seven five three. Okay, let's continue.
I think the terrorist of one or, frankly, still have a lit. We're a bunch of craving keeps, you
know, said, um, we're just being fed on like groom's fairy tales and whatever to keep us in line
and the fight of our shadows. Uh, you know, I do wonder what my daughter's gonna think of.
Of me in my generation, that in this happened. I'm gonna use it so I'm up for a flashball man, you know,
um, yeah, it's gonna be done. We go. So, um, the flash mob idea. I still got it out there, you know,
I will do anything I need to to support the flash mob to help to propagate the word, but I need
someone else to step up and coordinate. And so far, no one has presented themselves as the
person who's saying, look, I'm willing to give those some actual time because it does take time
to think about it, figure it out. But I think a lot of it can be done from your computer and your cell
phone and set up a flash mob. So, the, and the idea is to get in front of the right cameras,
cameras that will also, um, if not the actual footage, if we can, you know, shoot our own footage,
which will be pretty easy of just hundreds, if not thousands of people wearing t-shirts or holding
up signs to the government saying, you work for us. That's the basic idea. Someone needs to step
up, though. Someone with a really stiff upper lip.
It was something. Um, 37 on married, uh, I've got one kid, I've got another one on the oven.
Obviously not in my oven anymore. I'm the eldest of seven kids on white. I'm an atheist.
I think one is in traffic jam. Oh, damn. Um, I can't remember the rest.
Right, man. All right, all right, all right, all right. Was it folder? Yeah, I hear. Yeah,
hope you win. You caught a nice chap. Yeah. I hope you win. All right. And I can't remember the rest.
Ah, it's good. It's good, man. Thank you. Appreciate that. You really opened up, dude. That's cool.
And see, normally I wouldn't play anything that long, but that was just full of all kinds of
golden nuggets. And I'm going to listen to that again, because I think it really hit home for me,
certainly. Uh, something I haven't had written down in my, uh, in my own personal production notes,
and again, I'm using Omni Outliner, really loving it. It really works for me. I have to put that in
as a piece of the whole production tool, uh, because it actually does integrate quite nicely on the
Mac. Um, that I want to tell you that this is for those of you who purchased an Nokia 810 internet
tablet, or even if you have the end 800, and you're using the, uh, the new updated OS OS 2008,
you can get this program called Kanola. And version two, I think is now in beta. Oh, sorry, beta.
That's a beta in the UK. Uh, excuse me. Um, uh, it's a great way to manage your media on the, on, uh,
on this internet tablet. I used version one quite extensively. It does podcast, but it also will look
at your drive. If you have a, what is the PNP router, thingy, thingy mobabi, UNP, whatever element
OP, uh, if you have a media drive that's serving up media, it'll automatically connect. So it understands
all that stuff. It's very, very cool. Uh, and I just want to make sure you guys knew that because, of course,
you can purchase the N810. You can't get a cheaper anywhere, but through pod show currently, uh,
with a 15% discount, just go to podshowoffers.com, uh, use my checkout code, which is daily source code.
There's a couple there. If you see your show, you like more than mine than for all, you know,
wrong tends to purposes. Please go ahead and use their code, but I will track you down. Um, and you'll
get a 15% discount. It's a great deal, and it's a fantastic device.
Actually, I'm, I'm having kind of a bad hair day. I've got it, uh, headphone hair.
And I didn't, uh, I didn't fix myself up for you guys. Hope you don't mind. Yeah, that's dreamtoon
or I've heard about that. That, that looks pretty cool too. I'll definitely have a download, uh,
speakin' of, uh, of Nokia, the candy man checks in. Hi, I'm just a candy man again with some, uh,
positive feedback this time. Oh, for once, right? Yeah, really. Um, I just wanted to say that
I'm really happy with the way in which this, um, aggregation functionality is now working at Port Show.
So, um, besides aggregating audio podcasts, I've now also started to aggregate some,
HD video content into one XML feed, which I then, uh, play or, or I use, uh, an application called
middle or my row to, to play the HD content on my computer. And, uh, this, this aggregated
Port Show HD feed, which has, uh, both Port Show HD and non-port Show HD content is really, really
good way to, to manage and, uh, control the HD content. So, if I don't like a show, I can just, uh, drop it
out or if I find a new show, I can just, uh, drop it in and it will automatically be updated in the,
in the XML feed. So, I automatically get the new new feed also in my, uh, let's say, HD player,
whatever, whatever that may be. And, uh, yeah, I think that's, that's a very good development. So,
thanks for, for getting that back into order. I'm really using that on a daily basis. So, thanks.
Bye. Okay. Now, candy man, you may be handing out free phones to everybody, but, uh,
doesn't mean you can get away without the official sign off of the Charlie. So, next time,
let's just slide this time. But next time, please, think about telling us, uh, if you are into
the red pills, the blue pills, the folders, the scrunchers, if you love my hair, if you're no
homo, if you, uh, if you, uh, I'm sorry, that wasn't the correct. If you, if you think I have a great
hair and hope I win. Uh, but yeah. So, what, uh, what the candy man is talking about is, uh, the channel
functionality at podshow.com. It really does work. Now, we've got it tweaked and tuned and, uh, streamlined.
So, you can build up a channel. You can even determine the order in which the shows will
poop out of this channel on the back end in, uh, in the RSS feed. And, of course, in RSS feed,
you can put it to anything. You can put it to iTunes. You got to think you can put it into
Tvo these days, even though we have a specific Tvo channel, but you can still, if you want, you can put
it, um, uh, one of these aggregated of your own personal channels into, into Tvo, uh, or Miro,
what, uh, the candy man was talking about, or even, uh, canola, a little work, as well.
There's a lot of functionality, a lot of power in, uh, being able to manipulate the, um,
the way the order in which, uh, the episodes will pop out. So, for instance, I have, uh, at the
beginning of my feed for my, um, on the go channel is what I call it. You can see it at atom.podshow.com.
You can even subscribe to it and then you can follow along. So, you know, you want to check out
candy man stuff because you can, uh, I, I guess if he has a public, you can use his channel and be
watching the same HD content. He can be doing all the work. And you can just be enjoying it and by
the way, he becomes kind of a podcaster in his own right. He's aggregating things together.
He doesn't even have to make a show. He could make great channels. And I, I would love that. I want
to check out the stuff that he's finding in HD. I'll be happy to promote that. Lots of people out there
who want to get HD content. So, think about the power of that. And of course, you know, it is a pod
cast because it's an RSS feed with enclosures, only it's generated dynamically,
based upon what you tell it to do. Another example, I have the weather report first and I have the
New York Times front page podcast. And I, I, I select the depth, which means I always want the,
the two most recent, and you can select one, two or three. I always want the two most recent
episodes to be in there because sometimes I miss a day, but I still want to catch up on it.
Now, I'll do the same with tech five, but then buzz out loud. You know, I don't care if I miss one,
so I just want the most recent one. It's, it works. I think you find it pretty cool. I don't think
many people have, well, I know a lot of users have discovered it, but not a lot of people in the
Twitter swoopsphere, if you will. And the bloggo sphere on the technical side because it,
yeah, there's a lot to it. It's, I think it's some good, some good site actually to be quite honest.
Oh, man. Oh, you're not going to believe this.
Oh, I thought I'd have to wait at least a week.
He's back. Adam, it's for nylon. I couldn't wait any longer. I have to comment on this
nationalization of northern rock issues. I like your financial support, but you've simplified the
issue there. Sometimes happens. Let me just make some quick points because I actually have worked
it. One. Yeah, I do. You have in the US something called the FDIC, the Federal Deposit Insurance
Corporation. Simply what they do is they ensure everyone's deposit up to $100,000. That's $100,000
insured. In the UK, you're insured up to 2,000 for $1,000. Wow. Okay. This is a big piece of information.
This I didn't know. And actually, I did know about the $100,000 limit that isn't sure
by the FDIC, but I was, I, I, I, I, I, I, I have to admit nylon you're right. I was thinking,
you know, that money's just insured. And I kind of presumed it was the same here. I did not know
that it was only up to 2,000. So now this does make a lot of sense to me that there was probably
a lot more money on deposit or, you know, they have it on deposit doesn't actually mean they
have to have it in their, in their accounts. That's kind of the whole banking trick. So yeah,
it makes sense that a bailout was needed to save the bank because if they could, if they're only
going to ensure up to 2,000, I'm sure a lot of people were going to get burned big time. But then
the question is, you know, why not ensure up to $100,000 or a million? I mean, they're doing it anyway.
You know, they didn't stop at the 2000. They went above and beyond and wrote another 25 billion
check to ensure the bank could stay in business outside of what was on deposit. I think that's
what we're looking at. So let's see you if nylon gets to a point. So clearly, if you have a
problem with your bank and the UK, you're rushing out. In the US, you sit back because you got
a $100,000 guarantee. Now, you may not call that nationalization and indeed the FDIC is separate.
However, the president and the Senate does approve the five people on that board of directors.
It is paid for by the banks. The last thing on nationalization is, during the financial
sabronico back into the Great Depression, most people will tell you it's because the federal reserve
refused to intervene to the Great Depression that had happened. It refused to lend money to the
banks. It refused to get involved. A lot of reasons legal and otherwise. So anyway, not just
to find that situation, but as usual with the US in UK, you're separate by common language.
There is no deposit insurance in the US in the UK. Sorry, there is a $100,000 in the US at the
FDIC. So, the issue is on that simple. Because bank failures in the US don't have the same
impact, whether it would have had here. And the government would have had to step in. I.E.
Look at the Great Depression as a lesson from history. I'll see you soon. But nylon back.
Anyway, that nylon back in my life, back in our lives. So happy about that nylon.
Okay. Well, that does put a new perspective on things. I appreciate that. So, I still remain
at my point that the government wrote some pretty big checks to save the bank. Yes.
It avoided perhaps something like the Great Depression, but don't we?
Well, I'm starting to maybe revise my thinking on this. We do have to go through
something so that a pain has to be taken somewhere. The only thing that is pissing me off right now
is the pain doesn't seem to be with the people who caused it, namely the banks. And they're just
right and shit off left and right. You know, I'm sure it goes way beyond the subprime cart crisis.
This is banking in general, which is all about credit and debt. And I think that just
washing everything out as quickly as they can. But there's some huge, I saw an estimate over the
weekend in the paper that it went all of a sudden done. 600 billion, I guess it was pounds.
I'll just say dollars to be on the safe side because I do mess that up a lot. 600 billion of
anything is a lot. But that's probably the amount of money that will just have been destroyed,
just written off and then everyone would be kind of back to a new basic level and we'll all trust
each other again and we can continue on banking is usual, I guess. I love to hear more, nylon.
As always, it's highly appreciated and you know that I think you have great here. I love you,
you know, homo and I do hope you. Hey, Adam, what's up? It's Monk and Phil Monk. He's a testimonial
to the power of podcasting. All right. Cool. And in audit of digital distribution for my
releases through December 31st, 2007, I was shocked to find 12,151 purchased downloads have been registered
12,151 for me in unsigned, independent artist. Now we're talking about international digital
distribution like iTunes, iTunes, Europe, iTunes, Japan, iTunes, Canada, Rhapsody, Napster,
Sony Connect Verizon, music match, music blah, blah, blah, blah, I'm not saying music and a bunch
of me leaving out. Now I hadn't released a record since 2003. So I'm wondering where the hell did
these numbers come from? Where did they come from? I'm fine. Podcasting, my brother. All thanks to you,
Marc Yoshimoto, NMConf, CC Chapman, and the Army of Podcastors all over the world who took my
music under their wing and exposed it to quite literally the world. It is because of every single
one of you that I now release my third album, Modest Among the Living. The physical CD is now available
at CDbaby.com and will soon be available in all the aforementioned digital distribution outlets I
rattled off. There are also new tracks in the PMNs that check those out. Modest Among the Living
is a big, huge, thank you to the podcast and community. You've all honored me with the home.
Thanks Adam.
It's not to say that I don't take chances of at my share of the ledge, but all these steps
are not repetitive dances. I'm pouring me to jail. It took three days to float this night.
Now I have to definitively decide what to do in the days of hate.
I try to take my try to plan a new life, but I just can't scratch that edge.
I watch another episode that I take a lot of plan life has on the couch.
Why can't I grab the remote and change the channel on my hold of time?
We're headed to 30 days to float this night.
Now I have to definitively decide what to do in the days of hate.
Now I steal, breaks myself again, but I don't want to make it.
It's not to say that I don't take chances of at my share of the ledge, but I just can't touch it.
It took three days to float this night.
Now I have to definitively decide what to do in the days of hate.
It's been 30 days of hate in my life. Each day is the same one for me.
When I'm hanging on my dreaded, make it all out, make it all out.
Now yeah, that's Mark from the pod save music network 30 days on the daily source code.
Episode 7 30.
The ketchup edition, there you go. Oh man, awesome, so happy it's all going so well. This is it.
Man, this is how the music revolution takes place.
It's all about the promotion of the marketing my friends.
That's what the pod save music, that work is for. You've got to get the word out.
If there's someone doing some shit you like, you've got to play him. You've got to let people know.
You've got in bed, you know, players. In fact, I'll put a link into into monks player on podshow.com slash music.
And you can embed that. And it's configurable.
All kinds of stuff you can do with it. This is how it works.
And then let it just be available anywhere. Let people pay for it.
I mean, this is one of the few guys I can listen to a whole quote album of his.
I mean, I can listen to a whole playlist of songs and just doesn't get boring for me.
In fact, this is the kind of guy I think Patricia should be working with. He does.
So he's got like some throwbacks, 60, 70s vibe in there. He's got some real hard edge rock.
I think that I think that really worked together well.
I'll have to work on the lady Patricia.
In fact, yeah, I have to work on her tonight anyway.
All right, I'm going to get out of here. It's been way too long.
Hopefully, as he tomorrow is going to be a little tough.
Wednesday, I'll have a show tomorrow starts at 8 a.m.
For me, and it goes until well into the hours of the morning.
So look for another show Wednesday.
I appreciate you listening. Sorry.
It took so long to get another Charlie out for you.
My bad.
Adam and podshow dot com daily source code dot com for all the show notes.
Of course, go daddy dot com.
Use check out code DS 3DSC 3 if you want a domain name for under seven bucks.
Don't get much better than that.
And please, whatever you do, live your life with passion.
And while it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.