Delta Shara Charley's 7-9 or 5.
We died, and mine's working, and the tears are rising.
Cause, great father, why'd she show that it is?
You know, we're getting more mean, not too sad to say to their minds.
Cause of what we had as we were.
You're why, more things of no one else is there, babe.
Everybody get rid of the time we survive.
All it has to be sure is for my eyes.
We'd be clung up with it, and that's what we died.
Why's more things of no one else is there, babe?
Yes, I'll tell you the chance you are.
Don't like that she's kidding, her name won't move on.
My heart has been glad, but she'll start next door.
Why does it not work?
Just standing here for...
When my country and people come to our country, the bridge is famous.
And at the same time, these people don't understand.
The way they partner with hate us.
But there's this love that's gone too good job, it's feel like a place to think.
But I'm really great, it's that's it.
They're not a crime.
But we get a guy that's helped us survive.
What did my English name strike on my eyes?
But I've been in this dimension of mine.
My book and this vision of mine.
We can't even take destruction from both sides.
Destruction of people, destruction of life.
I'm a horse of four, the hungry sick and greener.
I don't want the house, but I'm a need.
Yeah, getting angry.
It's a beautiful emotion, bit of anger.
We could use some more and I'm pretty pissed off myself, my friend.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
A daily source code episode number 795 coming to you from The Curricondo in San Francisco, Northern California.
California. It's Wednesday evening. Um, or as we call it at, uh,
mevio HQ, we, uh, speak of the Wu bar.
So we have our company meetings used to have them on Fridays.
Food bar Friday now. It's a Wu bar because we do my Wednesdays. And I'm dead
tired. Really am. It's, uh, 840. Uh, yeah, 845 PM. Uh, but I am officially
calling this Thursday show. Which means I know there will be a Friday
show only a lot of you might not get it until Saturday because of the
time differences. Um, I got a head cold. Uh, it's been running at, you know,
we get like a Petri dish, a situation in the office right now. Uh, so my
nose has been dripping all day. I got a headache and they're within
incredibly busy. I'll be talking about that later on in this program.
Not not, um, um, um, this may not be a very long, uh, D. S. C.
Only never know. I seem to, uh, have a knack of expanding on things a bit.
But there's really just a couple of things that we have to talk about.
But of course, right off the bat, um, we know now that the Senate has passed the
bailout package. I believe 74 to 25, uh, I think was the final count. Um,
so what a great strategy, huh? What a fantastic way to do it. First, we try to
we come up, uh, uh, we meaning, uh, the true masters of the universe trying to
create a fourth branch of government with a, uh, a three pageer that said,
hey, give us all the power. This is our real intent. Of course, everyone
walks at that and then we, uh, we adapt it. Oh, we got to hurry up. We got to rush.
We got to suspend the rules. That's a form of a martial law, uh,
under which the Congress, the House representatives were, um, we're operating, um,
this dispute over the actual term martial law. But there was a
suspension of rules. So there were no committees. It didn't go through the
typical process because if we don't get this thing signed, then we're all going to
die. Which, of course, hasn't happened yet, uh, even though nothing has
been passed. And, uh, yeah, sure, we saw a 778 point drop. But, uh, it's still
was above way above, uh, 10,000. It's still above 11,000, the doubt. This is not,
the, um, the stock market. I talked with Johnson to work about this all the time.
The stock market is not necessarily an indicator of the economy, okay?
It's how it's an index of, of stocks, of industrial stocks that make stuff. So that
does relate in a way to the economy. But it doesn't mean necessarily that, oh,
you, meaning you and I lost at over a trillion dollars. Man, the lies are outrageous.
The things that are being said is just, it's starting to really piss me off. So anyway,
so that gets beaten down, uh, by a margin of like 24, uh, votes. And, uh, so then, of
course, the strategy comes out. Here's what we're going to do. Now we're going to pull
in the senators. We're going to have another version of the bill, which I have not read.
I don't even know if it's available yet. Uh, I've heard bits and pieces of what is
supposed to be included in it. And, uh, and of course, we bring back the presidential, uh, candidates,
the two leading ones. There are more in case you didn't know. It's not just those two guys you
can vote for. There are some independence, okay? Cynthia McKinney, Ron Barr, Chuck Baldwin. There
are more people that, uh, Americans can vote for international listeners. Please take note of that.
It's not just these two. That's the way the media plays it. Of course, the media owned by the
very banks that, uh, that have, have caused this situation. No one disagrees with that.
Because they're all saying, well, this is Wall Street and Main Street and Wall Street and Main Street
and Wall Street did this and we have a Wall Street that then. So we're still bailing on a bunch of
bankers. And, uh, I have had some, uh, the, the source code drop, which is Drop.io slash
code. Man, this thing is a treasure trove. I'm, you know, kudos to the guys who make this stuff.
There are small company that got just a little bit of financing. I wish them so
such a successful future because it's just a fabulous system. It's not really complicated,
but it works and people are using it in such interesting ways. And it's the first page I go to.
Now, when I wake up in the morning, first thing I do is I hit drop.io slash daddy source code.
That's where I'm getting, uh, a good overview of news. It's really, that's when I start producing
the show. It's the mirror. I read that thing and it's updated throughout the day. And of course,
I knew that the, the savants out there and there are many and you guys are expanding. The group is
growing bigger. I knew people would find stuff. And there was a link, which was Drop there to a, a very recent
thing was only about a week old, a very recent conference at Harvard University.
And it was, uh, believe six economists or, um, yeah, economists, I guess you can call them, um,
one of them even a current professor, but there was, uh, it's pretty diverse. There was a guy
from the World Bank. You know, the World Bank guy doesn't care about, you know,
Democrat Republican left or right. You know, those guys are about taking money from every single
country in the world, including United States. Um, and it was great. It's about an hour and
thirty six minutes. You have to watch this. You must absolutely watch this. And you will, if you're
brand new to the daily source code, not all of what they're saying may actually make sense to you,
but I found that, and remember, I'm just a DJ VJ, you know, the, I'm no economist. I have no
college education, um, I have, uh, uh, LICM, which is a high school, uh, education from, uh,
from the Dutch schooling system. Yeah, I went to school, but I didn't learn any of this stuff. I
wish they had taught me some of this stuff. But even with the knowledge that we've gained over
the past couple of, uh, months, I'd say, but really in the last few weeks, as this has started to come
to a head, uh, we've been, uh, predicting and talking about, uh, the financial crisis that would
come, then man, so much has come true, so much more than I even imagined. And just listen to the
words they're using. I mean, it's, uh, it's, it's financial terrorism. We're all going to die.
Nothing will work. It'll all be broken. They're going to lose everything. We don't actually know
if this is going to work this way, but it's the best shot we got. Now, this is not about the money,
because $700 billion. Look, it sounds like a lot of money, but I know at least personally,
10 billionaires. So, you know, you don't need to, you know, you don't need to small multiple of that.
That, that money is not, that it, it, it gets it's a huge, unfathomable amount. And before we have
seven, a hundred billionaires, seven hundred, what is it? Yes, seven, a hundred billionaires,
and I got to get it right. You know, there's, there's work to be done there, but it's not like
this money isn't out there in the world, and this isn't an outrageous amount. Although, of course,
it is a 10% of the, the national debt that the United States has were wanting, increased that
effectively. So, um, so we all know a little bit about this. When you listen to this panel speak,
you're going to be blown away. And, and, and I really buy into what they were saying, and they all kind
of said different versions of the same thing, which was very interesting. And I want to paraphrase
and kind of sum it up for you to, to wet your appetite, but you wouldn't even have to watch it,
just as I give you this kind of breakdown and lowdown. So, first of all, this economic crisis that
we're in, which is really based on all this bullshit that the banks created to make money
and to pay themselves handsomely. I mean, just look at some of those pay packages or go to the
South of France and take a look at those apartment buildings that are called boats that some of
these guys own. People are making $300 million a year. It's crazy. It's totally crazy. But, you know,
that was their own industry. It's an industry. It's a called the financial industry. And,
in fact, more of the things that was said for a foreign industry that is supposed to operate
really lean and mean and and be extremely effective. A lot of money sticking to the wall on the way
in, before it goes out. But, everyone's blaming these, the subprime mortgages. Again,
I'm paraphrasing all of this stuff, but I pretty much buy into what I heard. These people are a number
of the list of 166 economists who are saying this is not something that we should let happen.
This bailout package. And, by the way, just because, for those of you don't know, it's past the
Senate in United States. Now, it has to go back to Congress. So, they're probably going to vote
on it again Friday in its new incarnation. So, now, you know, now everyone's been indoctrinated and
we'll get to the mainstream media role in all of that in a second. Okay, so back to these theories.
So, what a lot of people make it sound like, it's, oh, this was poor people. This is a big
meme that's out there. Yeah, poor people who signed up for these loans, they could never pay for
and banks who, who suckered them into it. That's not necessarily true. A lot of this was
second mortgages. And, of course, they had these teaser rates, which is like, hey, come on in here
and for the first 24 months, you won't let you pay a really low interest. And, yeah, then it'll
go up depending on something, whatever, just sign here. And, this is marketing and advertising.
That's where there was a lack of regulation, obviously. But it wasn't poor people, necessarily.
Other than the middle class in America, which is poor, because what are we using the second
mortgages for? Well, to get by. You know, like, well, 24 months, maybe some nice will happen,
or maybe there were some medical bills that had to be paid. This is why these second mortgages
were taken out. I remember very well. In 1998, I helped a couple people who were in really,
really bad trouble with credit card debt. And I said, you got to consolidate and what you got
it, because they were up to their next. And I said, take this credit card debt. You can get a second
mortgages. And that, I was only talking, like, maybe that was like $8,000. And they had
probably, like, $30,000, not $20,000, because they'd had their house for, you know, 20 years or
whatever. They just didn't know how to use the instrument. So this has been going on for a long
time. But of course, at a certain point, if the middle class is taxed and there's, you know,
effectively, no real wage increase versus the price increases of energy and food. And then,
eventually, it's going to catch up to you. So that's what happened. Now, here's the, here's the
main thing. And this was really an eye opener for me when they discussed this. Before we had all
these complex pieces of paper and, you know, bullshit derivatives and credit default swaps.
Basically, you went to a bank, you got a mortgage. And if you couldn't pay that mortgage,
if something happened, then you'd call up your bank and you said, hey, man, I got to sit down
with someone or the bank, of course, my contact. He was at, come on in and you sit down and say,
okay, here's the deal. I can't pay this mortgage. Here's what I can do. And then work with you.
Because of course, the bank would rather get their money than have to deal with a foreclosure.
And it doesn't mean that foreclosures didn't happen. But it was basically your bank and
there was someone there to work with you to work it out. What happened? And yes, this is a part of
deregulation and agreed is that the banks decided to split up these mortgages into little
bitty pieces. And I won't get into how those bitty pieces became even smaller pieces. And all of
sudden, you have hundreds or thousands of financial institutions, basically owning little pieces of
all of these mortgages. Excuse me. The direct result, of course, is when someone's defaulting,
who do you talk to? And in fact, the people who whose piece, little piece of loan was defaulted on,
either didn't know it because there were three stories removed in the house of cards in the
Ponzi scheme, they just, they would never actually know that that was taking place. But the bottom,
the bottom line. And by the way, the idea of distributing the risk of a mortgage is from a financial
perspective, not a bad idea, but not to the extent these guys took it. It's a bubble. I mean,
it's a huge, huge, huge Ponzi scheme house of cards, cards bubble. So there was no one to talk to.
So, you know, that's when stuff started to spin out of control. And of course, you know,
this is mainly because of these arm mortgages, adjustable rate mortgage. Again, with what they
called the teaser rate, you've heard all of these phrases. I'm sure. So these things, you know,
and after two years, or after three years, this shit starts to happen. And this has been happening
for a number of years. It's not something that just started to happen overnight. But all of a sudden,
if all these banks have built up the value of their company, and these banks have shareholders,
you know, it's, it used to be a really good idea to invest in a bank. Because banks are printing
money literally. And by the way, it's going to be a pretty good idea to invest in banks. Again,
depending on what happens, but you can already see Warren Buffett. And why is Warren Buffett putting
his money into banks? Okay. So he put $5 billion into Goldman Sachs. And today, he just announced
he put another $3 billion into GE. General Electric, one of their largest divisions is the finance,
GE finance. So basically, there's a bank. And they were also protected under the no-shorting rule,
which I think expires tomorrow or Friday or Monday or whatever. Now, Warren Buffett,
guy is not stupid. Why is he putting this money in? Not to help his cronies with like a
vote of confidence saying, oh, you know, Warren Buffett's, although I'm sure, I'm sure it's appreciated
that way. I warned Buffett, man, if he's putting money in, well, as Americans can certainly put
money into it. Yeah, one difference. Warren Buffett is a smart guy. These banks,
they need money. Okay. Now, it isn't the problem. There isn't money in the world to put into
these banks. So they can start lending to each other and lending to people and recapitalizing their
balance sheets. That's not the problem. The banks don't like the terms of the deal, because the
people that are sitting on the sidelines like China and their sovereign wealth funds are saying,
well, you know, hey, we don't mind putting some money in, but you're really going to have to
give up a piece of the pie. They don't want to do that. That's why they've come to the government.
It will just take it from those suckers. We'll take it from them people, one difference.
Warren Buffett believes me. The guy got an awesome deal. He's getting stock in these banks.
We are not getting stock in the banks. We are getting pieces of paper that if they can be
resold, yeah, we might make a profit, bloody, bloody, bloody, blah, but why didn't we get the same
deal as Warren Buffett? Why? Because we're being jacked around. It's financial terrorism.
In fact, the money that we're going to give is going to be given to the exact same people who
put themselves into this crisis in the first place. This is in the bill. This I do know
that the Secretary of the Treasury, Paulson, and Bernanke from the Fed, they're going to
hire Goldman Sachs, hire them outsourcing the work so that they can though buy up all of these
bad toxic assets, pieces of paper, computer entries, not even paper, computer entries.
They can buy that up and then sell that back. By the way, that's really true. They are doing
that in the Wall Street auction. It's something that, well, nothing ever has ever been done like
this. The government does know how to do auctions. They do it with the frequencies. They do it
with the area code. It's all kinds of stuff like that. Not for telephony, for phones.
I'd like completely like I'm so incensed about this. So that's the main. So again,
the amount of money. Yeah, that's a lot of money. And we should not be getting a possible
profit. We should be getting stock in these companies in these banks. We should be able to sell
back to them because we don't actually want to be owners of banks, although we already own a couple of
them. And we own AIG. Hey, 80% of that. You enjoy your insurance company there. Another version of a bank.
So it's really about the power. And if you look at the bill, at least the last version that I saw,
more bullshit, gaming the system of how decisions are made and the Congress will only have
10 hours to decide if the next 100 billion can go. It's all about power. It really is creating
a fourth branch of government. And again, the federal reserve is like federal express. It has nothing
to do with the government. It's owned by private banks. Oh, guess who? Let me see Goldman Sachs,
JP Morgan. They own the bank. They own the federal reserve. They've been given because of the federal
reserve act of 1913. They've been given the right to make and print the money. Dr. Ron Paul has an
excellent plan and a bill that he's putting together to abolish, well, at least they investigate first.
But eventually abolish the federal reserve. This should be Congress's job. We can't have and hold
anyone accountable at the federal reserve. It makes me mad. Okay. So now we're being sold, uh,
really sold into the idea. And this is what worries me because we had such a massive wave of people
calling emailing, writing, telling their congressmen or congresswoman, the representative,
no, no, no, no. I will hold you accountable for treason. And we have to do it again. We've got to go
right back at them. And we've got to tell them. And please, you've got to ignore all the bullshit that's
being told to you and put into your brain by mainstream media. Okay? Particularly, anything that has
the letters NBC in it. CNBC, MSNBC and NBC all owned by General Electric all owned by the bank.
You that what a huge conflict of interest. They're not even saying anymore. Well, uh, by the way,
we should point out that CNBC is owned by General Electric who has a stake in this whole thing.
They're not even disclosing it. So back to this, um, this panel, I was just one woman. I
think her name when my last name was Warren. Um, she said, look, what's really happening is you,
if you look at this whole house of cards, this Ponzi scheme, it's really like holding a thin metal
rod, if you will. Or maybe a saw, here they go, um, you know a saw. And you hold the saw by the handle
and you, and you, but you hold it flat. And if you shake the handle a little bit, what's going to
happen? The other end of it is going to go up and down and up and down. So when a couple of these
mortgages started to default, you know, that's like a little vibration. It's kind of shaking at the
handle into the saw. And then at the other end, at all the way down the line of these people who have
leveraged upon leverage upon leverage of little pieces of all these mortgages, it really starts to
shake up and, you know, up and down. And that's like a shock. If it happens again, then, you know,
while it's already shaking, you get another little vibration, what's going to happen? The other
end is really going to start going up and down. So they are fixing the problem at the wrong end.
Forget forget about all the power grab and forget it because it is a real problem.
Forget about the power grab and the money and the executives who will steal the money,
they will steal it. They'll all get, look, they've all got their houses in, in foreign countries.
I don't give a shit about you and I. This is going to take our money and get out.
This news about every single day. I don't even have to tell you. Just go look at the drop.
You'll see it all. So how about, um, we freeze the adjustable rate mortgage rate
bring them back to their teaser rates. That would be one way to do it.
Career, simple solution. It would even cost any money. It's a whole bunch of things that could
be done. But we're now being sold into this and it's, they're just propagating the hype
by companies who are, our, our licensed broadcasters who are now not even disclosing
their conflict of interest and what they're reporting.
It's almost like, uh, I don't know if you, you must have seen this. It's, it's all over the place.
It's like song for Obama. These kids, they're so called grass roots movement. It's funny.
It's almost like, I keep having to think of the new seekers. You know, um, I like to teach
the world to sing only when they did it for Coca-Cola. I'd like to give the world a Coke.
That's kind of this, uh, what this Obama video is, you got to see it. I'll put a link in the
show notes at daily source code.com. Um, this thing, uh, and this is why I bring it up,
is produced by professionals, including Jeff Zucker, the president and CEO of, oh, NBC
universal, pretending that it's a grassroots movement. That whole thing is filled with, with, with professionals,
professionally produced, misusing their kids. I don't care what it's for. That's why it equated
to selling Coca-Cola. Uh, uh, so, um, please, you must contact Congress. You must tell them,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Because now I'm here in these, these big grand turnaround. Oh,
where I used to, I was getting 5,000 emails that said, no, and only one or two that said,
yes, now it's like 60% of the people are saying, yes, I don't believe it. I do not believe it.
And you know what's even worse? I just found this on the drop. The House of Representatives
is limiting emails from the public. Listen to this. Listen to this. They're limiting emails to
the public to prevent its websites from crashing due to the enormous amount of mail being submitted
on the financial bailout bill. They are now censoring our true interactive wave
communing or communicating with them. Oh, this is so big. Oh, website to crashing.
Fuck that shit. That's such bullshit. I mean, even Microsoft can can deliver
incredible large updates to hundreds of millions of computers around the world,
but our government are all powerful government. Oh, and the website is crashing.
All they're doing is just shutting off the communication. That, I'm so angry at this.
How the hell can they even justify this?
Link to the show notes at dailysourcecode.com for that as well.
Oh, so angry. Yeah, I'm angry. But anger is beautiful. You're allowed to be angry.
Get pissed off with me and call your representative and say, no, no to the bailout fix it another way
at the root of the problem. Not at the branches of the money tree. Everybody knows things about it.
It's at the pression. Everybody's out of work. We'll scare you losing the job.
The dollar buys a nickel's worth. Thanks in going bus, shall give us keep a gun under the counter.
Punks are running wild in the street. There's nobody anywhere seems to know what to do and there's no
inventory. You know, there is a fit to breathe. Our phone is a fit to meet.
See, watching our TV's on some local of just a dozen. Today, we had 15 houses, 63, 500 trains.
As if that's the way it's supposed to be. We know things about it. We're so mad.
They're crazy. Just like everything everywhere is going crazy, so we don't go on anymore.
We're sitting in the house and going to the world. We're living in this getting smaller
and always says, please, at least leave us alone. And I'll live in the room. Then we have my
toast or my TV. My steel built in great deals. I won't say anything. Just leave us alone.
Well, I'm not good anymore. I want you to get mad.
I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad.
I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad.
I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad.
I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad.
I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad.
I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad. I want you to get mad.
I want to get mad. I want you to get mad.
Maybe she willm, nevin' a van, not for one-off-tri'ing.
It was his name.
I came out at the San Francisco to set up.
We've now implemented a wonderful device called the TriCaster.
It's basically television studio in a box.
Now our studio is not built yet, so we have basically hijacked a very small conference
room, which kind of looks like a closet, in fact, I've seen walking closets much bigger.
And we're using it as a studio.
If you've looked at mevio.com, you'll see we have these three channels.
We have Texture, we have Lux, and we have Bang TV.
And the first part, and really what I've done is I've said everything up to really
show by example how we want this network to really look and run and how anyone can
create in exactly the same network that will come later on.
But anyway, if you go to mevio.com or, and this is all really like data or almost
alpha testing on the fly, so take it with a grain of salt and forgive me if stuff doesn't
look right, function right, et cetera.
We also have TextureNetwork.com, something we've been working on.
It's not all updated right, but you'll kind of get a semblance and idea of what we're
going for here.
And it's basically the return of me to doing video segments, which is kind of interesting.
It's fresh every single day, and we're really bringing all of these programs and
episodes and shows together, including some that we've done some pretty interesting deals
with that haven't been announced, but you'll figure it out pretty soon when when you see
this all rolling.
So keep your eye out on that as I think we're on to something here, and something that
you can create at home using our entire infrastructure.
Enough said, more about that as it progresses, probably by next week, we'll have some more
conversations about it.
Tomorrow night, of course, in the United States at 6 p.m. San Francisco time, the vice-presidential
debate between Joe Biden and Sarah Palin.
Now, I'm very excited about this for a number of reasons.
First of all, I want everyone once again to understand, I am not a Democrat, I'm not a
Republican, I'm a constitutionalist, and that's why I supported Ron Paul.
I would have loved that if he could have been president.
He is now endorsed the independent candidates, Ron Bar, Chuck Baldwin, Cynthia McKinney.
They all represent individual parties, which I have not had a chance to look into entirely,
but I'm pretty sure that I will, and they're more independent, by the way.
I will make sure that I'm well informed before I cast my vote.
My daughter who is now 18 is also getting into the game, and she's trying to understand
things.
The way I view this, what we're seeing right now, is truly the world's greatest reality
show.
This is not a debate amongst vice-presidential candidates who are actually going to do anything,
who will run anything other than the taps in the Lincoln bedroom, same for the presidents,
by the way, for the presidential candidates, McKinney Obama.
No, it's a casting call.
Okay, we've had actors before, we had one of the greatest actors in America became president,
and we have an actor in California, although that's actually a guy who was more than an actor,
but McKinney Obama, Palin Biden, actors.
The true agenda, what really runs them are Wall Street, that's mainly in Obama's case,
although McKinney also has plenty of Wall Street money in his campaign.
It's the lobbyist, it's the special interest groups, it's the think tanks, and it's shadow
government, and I'd say evil people, they're running it, they're running it for their own
power, for their own good, and these people are just front men, and you can agree with
me or not, but I don't think any of these people would be fit to run, I wouldn't even
have run a company of mine, let alone the country of mine, but it's going to be very
interesting because I've been following, you know, that would so NBC as we know, they
totally love Obama, Fox, totally loves McCain, and you can see how there's so many
children think that gets me, though, is how can NBC, so as a, you know, all of the different
companies, but it all comes back to general electric, whoever's in all that, they're running
it, it's amazing to me how they say, well, you know, Palin, she's so stupid, she's not fit,
she should drop out, if, if, if they're so pro Obama, why, why would they want, to help
them, it makes no sense, on the other hand, Fox news, it's, it's so blatantly obvious, again,
it's, you know, I'm just waiting for the number to pop up on your on the screen, just like
big brother or, or American idol or X factor, they've been saying, Sarah Palin's got the X
factor, I, I, I, I want to call it right now, I think I really think that we'll be surprised
by Sarah Palin, again, I don't, I'm not a Republican, I'm not a Democrat, I don't want any of
these people to be in the White House, of course, we're going to have one of these teams
is going to be in our cage match at the world wide wrestling Federation of the United States of
America, so it might as well be someone who's pretty, I think that's what a lot of people are
looking at, I think Sarah Palin will surprise everybody, if they teach her to just let herself
go and just speak, because she's pretty good, she's pretty personable, now forget about if she
knows anything, none of these guys know anything, but what, I'm just watching it purely from
a show business perspective as one of the greatest television extravagances in the world watch,
this is truly, you know what they say, the economy awards, watch my over a billion people worldwide,
which is a lie, big lie, this is the reality show that really is watched by over a billion people
worldwide, this really is the big one, and so that's the way I view it, that's what I'm interested
in, and I think Sarah Palin might actually just echo head and might just actually beat out Joe Biden,
but purely on character and personality, and none's nothing will be about the issues.
They tell these people they're all at the same answers, McCain and Obama, they're all for the same
thing, the little nuances, there's no difference, and we as the American public are acting like
the same way we do with wrestling, I'm for this guy, I'm for that guy, I'm for the
hammer, I'm for the the pile driver, now I want this guy to win big brother, now this person
sing was much better on X-Factor, except we get a little bit more angry at each other, which is
very disheartening. So, John C. to work, and I really liked doing our analysis of the president,
the first presidential debate, so tomorrow after the vice presidential debate, we're going to do
special edition of No Agenda where we go through all the points, and of course, John will be looking
at everything from his vantage point, and he was probably going to be scanning all the channels,
and I'm going to be listening and watching as someone who's been in television for years and
in show business, and I'm treating it as a reality show, and you may enjoy checking that out,
so that'll be tomorrow after the debate, no agenda.neveo.com.
Okay, um, it's just one other thing that came in on the drop, dropped.au slash daily source code,
which freaked me out. It's a YouTube video of Cynthia McKinney, who I was talking about earlier.
This is from September 27th, speaking at the Critical Resistance 10 Conference in Oakland,
California, from two days ago. I had a woman in the wake of Hurricane Katrina. I had a woman,
I've never really said this in public out loud in front of a lot of cameras, and there's a lot
cameras in this room now, but I had a mother to a homey because her son had a very gruesome
test. Her son's charge by the Department of Defense was to process 5,000 bodies that had received
a single bullet wound to the head, and these were mostly males, and her son was afraid to talk
because he assigned a silence of her greener. So he only complained to his mother,
but the data about these individuals was entered into a pentagon computer, and then reportedly
the bodies were dumped in a swamp in Louisiana. This is as a result of the tragedy of Hurricane Katrina.
Now, I have no, and I have a verification from insiders who wished to remain anonymous
and who wished for this is true. I suspect that these were prisoners, and so you know this investigation
of the whole prison that doesn't come, is extremely important, and it should not end with just
a question of the nature of prisons in our country, but these 5,000 souls also need suggestives too.
There you go. The American government directly are indirectly killing its citizens.
Even if you're in prison, do you deserve to be executed?
The prison industrial complex commercial prisons, I'll venture this so get paid for those 5,000 prisoners.
This is me, my fellow Chaka heads. We're going to stick on it. It's an outrage.
I've got a man, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun
I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, and I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun, and I have got a gun, I've got a gun, I've got a gun emerge, I have a gun, I have a gun, I have a gun and I've got a gun, I have a gun, and I have a gun, and I have a gun, as I have a gun, and I have a gun, and I have got a gun, I have a gun, and I have a gun, and I have a gun,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, from Frenchenders.
That's what I got, they've all got to plant a loos at all.
Learning to preach on the daily source code, all, seven, nine or five, and that'll be it for me, I need to chill out.
Hey, please enjoy your freedom, you still got some,
and no matter what you do, live your life with passion.
Another fine, medial presentation, stick it in your ear.