This podcast is brought to you by Pod Show and GoGay.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
Delta Shara Charley, 7-2-Niner.
It was $16 million worth of airplane scrapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
I'm guessing it's a matter of curry.
I never thought I'd miss you.
Half as much as I do.
I never thought I'd feel this way.
The way I feel about you.
Soon as I wake up, every night, every day.
I know that it's easy to write me.
You take my blood to white.
It must be love, love, love.
Nothing won, nothing won.
How can it be that weekend?
Say so much without words.
It must be love, love, love.
It must be love, love.
Nothing won, nothing won, nothing won.
As soon as I wake up, every night, every day
I have the tissue I need to take the lens away
It must be the love love
It must be love love love
It must be love love
It's another one of those tracks, probably presented by the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
It must be love
Brought to you actually by Chief Gadget Guru Andrew Grummit who sent that one to me and he said he grew up on that song
So I figured I might as well spin it for you
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's a daily source code episode number 729 coming to you from the curry condo in Northern California
Current time 837 in the evening San Francisco time of course
Oh man, my back hurts
It's been a very very long day started way early this morning
You know, we have these conference calls on what does it choose what to say?
Mondays and Thursdays when we all the sales we still get together
And we chat but they have to start at 7 o'clock in the morning
And I'm not good without having my morning tea of course
Which has to be just perfectly made and I need to have a little bit of toast a little bit of breakfast
And I don't know it's just been a long long day
But it's still good being here even though I missed the girls back home
And plenty to talk about today the first thing actually I spent a lot of time yesterday
I can't remember what inspired it exactly but I'm really happy I got into it
I decided that I would take a look at Safari as it browser once again
Most of you probably know that I'm back on back on the Mac
And loving it very very much
But I was really getting tired of Firefox
You know it was hogging system resources
Taking a long time to you know to render pages sometimes
It's just I don't know it was I was getting a little little fed up with it
And said you know why don't I give Safari another try
Boy am I glad I did that
Man that thing is so blazingly fast compared to Firefox
And I started to do some calculations
Actually this is something that that I did with our previous company
Think new ideas which we had in the mid 90s up until 2000
We discovered that it would actually be cheaper
These are the days before video we were doing lots of website stuff
And actually lots and lots of rendering was being done by you know Photoshop rendering
And you know stuff like that and of course the power of the machines was much more
I would say it was always eight I think in those days for the Mac always eight always nine
And we discovered that it would be cheaper to buy honking fast super machines for our designers
Because the amount of time they spent waiting for crap to render was really a huge huge cost to us
And so I started to think about this I believe that on a daily basis
You know the difference between Firefox rendering and Safari could actually save me up to an hour
And think about it you know yeah it's just seconds
But seconds before you know it turned into minutes and minutes before you know it turned into hours
And well it makes a big difference something else I found by the way
Of course you know with Safari there's all with any new browser any new piece of software
There's all kinds of little nuances and things that do work and don't work and work a little differently
And you have to get used to it now I'm not a guy who has a shitload of extensions loaded into Firefox
So I really don't mind I just need a browser that goes fast and that I can manipulate with a keyboard because I'm a big keyboard guy
And you know the less I use the mouse again another time saver right
I discovered that you know sometimes it would kind of hang or do some weird stuff and I get these pub sub errors
And well of course I have not used Safari on this machine at all
However it comes standard with a whole bunch of RSS feeds that are baked in
And these RSS feeds are checked I guess by default once an hour or once every half hour
And what Safari is doing and remember this is out of the box that didn't configure any of this is it's aggregating you know news feeds
And it's storing these in some magical place on on your hard drive
Now again how long have I had this machine couple months it had a mast almost 30 gigs 30 gigabytes worth of disk space
With I guess sites that it's downloaded I have no idea how it got to that point
But you know it was hanging at one point and I just had to screw it. I'm going to clear out this RSS feed database
I'm going to turn it all off which you luckily can do and I'm going to empty out all these all these sites or these feeds or whatever the
Caches that it that it has
Thirty gigabytes all of a sudden reappeared on my drive and like okay, this is good news
So I'm really enjoying it the speed is astronomical and probably
When I get back to to the manner, I'm going to do a little ab testing and really see how much time it to how much time it says
But I'm pretty sure it's it's quite an astronomical amount
Today by the way we're doing another live version of the Charlie we've got plenty of chuckle heads who are logged in everybody waves say hi
They're all on the conference call and I will be coming to them later on because there's one big topic that I want to talk about
I'm promoting it throughout the day. I post it on my weblog and I sense some Twitter is out about it
So hopefully people will get into it and well and we'll be able to talk about some stuff
Hi Adam this is Cameron and I'm calling from New Zealand
What a wonderful show DSC 728 was I really enjoyed it and I loved it
And I just wanted to say thank you very much and all of your shows are fantastic and I do enjoy listening to them
I'm sure when you were recording that session you must have had Patricia on your mind quite a lot
And for me it also made me think of my wife. She's been overseas for several months
And I look forward to seeing you shortly
Right Adam, but thanks Adam
And I think that's enough of me kissing your ass
Oh never know one more time come on baby
Pack her up Adam
Here we go
Oh
Thanks mate
Well that you know what I'm so happy to hear that because then it hit home, you know you do a show like that which is under the auspices of the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives
But you're known as upsall you can find the show for upsall at upsall.podshow.com
Oscar Papa Sierra Oscar Lima
And if I evoke some kind of emotion just like me, you know your thousands of miles away from your better half
Clearly your better half and my better half and you get that soundtrack to your life and it just makes you feel kind of good doesn't it
So I'm really happy you liked it
You'll last night which was Sunday night, of course, it's what is it now in Australia?
Friday
The Academy Awards were on and I was actually pretty much prepared to watch
I spent you know because we're on the west coast and I think that show kicks off at 6 p.m.
Pacific Standard Time
And I watched I was flipping back and forth between the e-channel you know basically the red carpet and TV guide channel also was on the red carpet
And even ABC had some people on the red carpet and I'm thinking of myself
These guys have kind of jumped the shark on this whole deal
You know it's all about what you're wearing
Who designed your dress you know there's no more mystique to it
I can't quite put my finger on it but I know it's wrong
I really do I can just feel it you know it's like it's been over
Some things been over commercialized
It just doesn't have that mystique anymore and I was you know all prepared to
Kickback relax and watch the show last night and then we decided that Ron and I decided that you know we could do some work
And I went over to his house and the fur of Chris Mac came over and we were working on some stuff
So I didn't actually watch the show and it turns out I was not alone
The ratings the overnight ratings came out
And I'm reading this from
Where did I get this from CNN dot com actually but New York time a whole bunch of publications
Posted this news
In fact the headline here is Oscars are ratings dud
Newerson media research says preliminary ratings for the 80th annual Academy Awards telecaster
We're 14% lower than the least watched ceremony ever
The overnight ratings 21% lower than last year
That is that is proof. Well, you know what is proof of because once again on the red carpet
You hear all this hype and shit and
It's like the Academy Awards will be watched by billions
A billion people worldwide a billion
That's billion with a B I'm like fuck this bullshit
We know it's bullshit
I mean those are the days when you could still scam people into thinking that you know it's like
Well, we're going out via satellite and it's just not true
So again, I didn't see the show so I have no idea if it was any good
But I even Patricia didn't watch it
Of course it was it was on late at night
She did watch the red carpet she said yeah, I'm bored with it all
You know, where's the where's the glamour or where's the mystique?
Where's the the glitz that we're that we love to see from Hollywood and by the way
So that I don't know any of these movies
It seems like all really you know complicated difficult
People
I should really you know, I can't wait to do a show with Patricia. Oh, man
I mean so cold to do that with her again
Man, oh man, oh man
So I would have to say that it definitely feels like there was a little bit of a shark jumping going on there
And the ratings definitely prove it
Let's see we got the candy man hanging on the line candy man what you got for me brother
Hi Adam it's me again
Yeah, I really like what you are doing with this live shows
I think it could be a very interesting way to discuss certain topics
Definitely much easier to discuss in a live situation
And by sending voice feedback back and forth
Example is this my cranky geeks comment I mean it would be much easier to discuss my feedback
Let's say yeah one on one with you or with anybody else for that matter
But I'm just surprised that a lot of people seem to be dialing in
But then they don't provide any inputs so they don't participate in the live call
Or they they just seem to be hanging there listening
So I wonder what's the what's the reason is there's a technical reason
Or are people just I mean why do people dial in if if they don't if they are not ready to participate in the in the discussion
I'm just wondering what's going on there
I mean definitely if the times or not timing would be better for me
I would and I would have time to dial in I would definitely dial in and try to participate in this discussion to make this live
Part of your show a little bit more interesting
So it's yeah, that's just something I'm wondering about perhaps you have some insight into that thanks
Bye.
Of course I have some insight into that
It's really quite simple. First of all the timing is all off being here on the west coast
Benefit I get from being in the United Kingdom is you know I can do the show and it's morning for everybody and in fact I love getting the show out
You know around one or two PM
So one or two in the afternoon the UK which is a morning time for the for the east coast and of course folks on the west coast
Definitely have the show by the time they get up and
Well, unfortunately again, you know I guess people in Hawaii they're on yesterday's time
And also you know it's it's a matter of having a moderator or giving people a topic and we'll see we'll see how it goes later on tonight
It'll be curious
And
Absolutely there's the proof for you. I knew we were all being a little bit too politically correct
I appreciate that calm and really do that makes a lot of sense
Let me see how to couple thing. Oh by the way, of course now that I'm using Safari the one thing that I actually did use Firefox for which doesn't is not compatible in Safari
is
Google's notebook
And I was thinking yeah, I really need a way to
You know to organize myself and I was kind of using the notebook because it works on all different computers
But honestly I'm back to really one single device one computer
I do everything on at the entire show is created on and now
And I went back to an omni outline or if you ever seen this
Actually I was using this back in the days of the curry cottage
So that's what three years ago almost two or three years ago and
The program is a little bit more stable than it used to be. It's still a great outline
I spent some time yesterday and last night learning how to use it again
Because again I'm a keyboard guy. I love using the keyboard to navigate through everything
And
I might even you know there's a they have a great function you can export it
Gosh, and it's all coming back to me. I used to export as OPML files
And anyway, there's a
There's an export function you can export as dynamic HTML so it actually will export as an outline
And now I'm even storing the voice males and the promos and the feedback and all that stuff in there
It's pretty good. You should give it a give it a shot
And of course link links to everything that we discussed on today's show including
Omni Outliner will be in the show notes a daily source code dot com
I'm single girl in the city here to tell you about my new show getting single
My happily ever after story book romance kind of very unfairy town like ending
I'm 26. I found myself surrounded with friends who are happily getting engaged
Getting married getting pregnant and there I was getting a single
You can hear my not so Hollywood love story and all its great details at getting single dot
Potcho dot com
I know they're awesome show to check out on pod show
And something else you might want to check out if you haven't seen it yet
Have you seen this gene sim in sex tape?
Man, that guy's ugly
Don't know much about history
Don't know much about biology
Don't know much about science
Don't know much about the franchise
But I do know that I love you
And I know that if you love it too
Well I wanna pull around this for me
Don't know much about geography
Don't know much about history
Don't know much about how to grow
Don't know what a sky blue is for
But I do know what it's for
And if this world could be with you
Well I wonder for where this for me
Now I don't claim to be at a student
But I'm trying to be
For maybe about being at a student baby
I can win, don't know what you're about
History
Don't know much about biology
Don't know much about science for
But I do know that I love you
And I know that if you love it too
Well I wonder for where this for me
Let's talk, let's talk, let's talk
History
Wow, the G
Well, let's talk, let's talk, let's talk
Let's talk
Yeah, but I do know that I love you
Sing along
And I know that if you love it too
Well I wonder for where this for me
I'm in service
I don't know much about history
What I wonder for a world this would be
So of course I just checked in the chat room
While the song was playing
And no one from the UK on and no one
Thinking about talking too much
That's okay because I got plenty of stuff here
Cute up
We're gonna move over to the United Kingdom
And talk about a couple things
The first one is about the nationalization of Northern Rock
The Bank that was on the verge of going bankrupt
Of course due to the credit crisis
Which is turned into a global financial fiasco
Way beyond the subprime mortgages
The central problem is that banks just don't trust
Each other anymore
And so when there's no trust
There's no money being traded
There's no liquidity and it's a big ass problem
Now of course we have a financial sabon
To talk about the nationalization of this bank
And I got him right here for you
Adam, it's been smoking one of your recently pointed economics
Want to give you could go on just to the whole Northern Rock
And pretend nationalizing it
It's to that idea
Nationalizing a bank probably never
A good idea
However
Probably what they had to do
Given the situation because letting a bank fail
Is even worse
I'm a capitalist at heart
And kind of feel that businesses are there to make people money
And if businesses want to take risks to make money
They should do that
And if they fail at those risks they should go to business
So there's programming that says this bank should have just gone out of business
But the bank's failing has pretty wide reaching repercussions
Not just to the people that own the bank
And not to the people whose money is deposited in the bank
I'll just stop for one second there
I do believe that these banks are insured
So of course it has repercussions of the bank fails
Then the insurance that the government provides for all banks
Or all certified banks
I guess or sanction banks
That is going to be a big nut
So I totally agree that that's a big problem
But I think it has more to do with the psyche
But you're probably going to get to that
As I think we were talking about earlier
When some of your conspiracy theories
And the whole making money out of thin air
Playbaria
One of the things we saw is that banks lend money out
And they lend out more money than they have on deposit
So it's people make a run on the bank and take out all their money
It's tough to give them that because most of the money
It's not all from it is all lend out
So so many of the kind of step in and stop that
From having to kind of prop up the confidence
With in the bank so that people don't make a run
And if one bank fails and people start worrying about other banks
They make a run on other banks
And the whole system kind of collapses in on itself
So the nationalizing it
Probably in the normal situations
Necrash it happen
But given the situation hopefully it works out
But then that's pretty much my two cents
So have a great day
And keep up the good shows
Thank you very much
Well
One other thing that there's been a topic on the Charlie is about
The refusal of the bank or there was a paragraph in the documents for the nationalization
That the bank would not be subject to a freedom of information act request
And which of course is makes no sense
It absolutely should be wide open
Actually I got a comment about that
Let me see where is this
That's too long
I don't even go into that
However
A lot of people emailed me and said well you know would you want
People to be able to request information about your mortgage
I'll tell you people of the United Kingdom who emailed me that
If you're comfortable with your privacy being violated by
Millions of closed circuit TV cameras
Strong up all over the United Kingdom
And of course lots of people say I have nothing to hide
I'm doing nothing wrong
Why would you ever problem with the people looking into your private information?
Is that interesting?
Where lots of people will say
Yeah, it's okay these cameras
I'm not doing anything wrong
But yet when it comes to other things
And of course a mortgage you're not doing anything wrong with the mortgage
I'm sure you're not
Yet people don't really want anyone looking at that stuff
I just find that interesting
If you live in the United Kingdom
Here's what you will be hearing on the radio
I believe it starts this week
You'll be hearing on the radio
I believe there's also going to be television commercials
And also print campaigns again
If you haven't seen this go to curried.com
I posted about it quite extensively
Fellow Chuckle had Paul Parkinson parkey
sent me actually he notified me of this
He sent me a comment which I'll play in a second
But first let's listen to the radio commercials
Which will be playing
Starting this week in the United Kingdom
How to tell the difference between
How much is videoing a crowded place
And someone who's checking it out for a terrorist attack
How can you tell if someone's buying unusual quantities of stuff
For a good reason or if they're planning to make a bomb
What's the difference between someone just hanging around
And someone behaving suspiciously
How can you tell if they're a normal everyday person or a terrorist
The answer is you don't have to
If you call the confidential anti terrorist type line on
0800 789 321
The specialist officers you speak to
Analyze the information
They'll decide if and how to follow it up
You don't have to be sure if you suspect it
Report it call the anti terrorist hotline
0800 789 321 in confidence
So that to me is is pretty darn scary
Our Nate is on and as raise his hand
Want to say something Nate go ahead you're on the Charlie
Hey, so I'm gonna put up cameras
That's fine by me. Just put a camera's net office
What I can watch didn't do what they're doing to
Yeah, I'm not quite sure I understand what do you mean
Who watches the watches
Are you a second or suddenly violate my privacy
I expect the exact same privilege against them
I want to be able to tune to their website
And watch what they're doing whenever I want
That's a good point
You would need some kind of oversight
I guess I have no idea how it's done other than what I understand
Is that it's pretty low level people
It's pretty low level people who are watching this stuff
And when you think about it, you got millions of cameras
You know, you can't have
Super sleuths manning every single one of them
So I'm not quite sure how we would go ahead
I mean, I mean, like parliament or the center of the house
I want a camera in each one of their offices
Ah, well, of course the good thing about the UK
And I have to say I really enjoy as they do have
You know, you can pretty much tune into what's going in
In the House of Commons at any moment
They do put that on television
And in the states here we have C-SPAN as well
But you actually want to go into the offices
Well, you know, that kind of transparency
I don't think we're ever going to see that
Honestly
But your point is well, I
What's that
As an I would an exact public camera
Okay, yeah, where do you love Nate?
I have a day
Where do you love?
I live in center of the California
Camera's all over the place
Oh, really?
They've got cameras where you live?
I see cameras on and in buses all over
And they've got little tiny cameras on those
The pool on top of every street life
Really?
Yeah
Ah, you know, those cameras just to watch the traffic
Or you know, or to catch speeding
Speeders or people who pop through the red light
Or what do you think?
I have no idea what those little cameras are for
But they have a couple of steam cameras
That they stopped using several years ago
Hmm
Okay, I didn't know that
I mean, that's interesting
I had no idea that there were
That this was happening in the States as well
Hmm
There's not really as much
Like in other countries, but I do see cameras if I look
Huh
That's news to me
Ron's strupe is on Ron you
You're in Louisiana
Yeah, I thought Ron was on
Okay, I guess he's not
All right, we'll we'll get back to the live
Calls in a second
Ah, Ron, thank you
Go ahead Ron
I don't know
Okay, finally figured out what's needed
Ah, yeah, I'm in Shreveport, Louisiana
Which is right across the river from Bozier City
Which is right next to
Parkstill Air Force Base
And they're going to
And still or build a
Cyber Command Center here
Which will house
In the, I guess the spike of Dearest
Or all of the country
To find terrorism
And I'm not
You know, not too surprised
We haven't seen a lot of cameras come up
lately, but
Now they're going to be sniffing over
All the computers
All the internet connections
All right, well, I mean, of course
There's no illusion that isn't happening
Already
All right, that's true
They've been doing it for a while
But the problem is
It's going to be a huge facility
And it's not only going to be helpful
To local people as well as the Air Force
And
To the security of the country, but I think it's going to be
You're going to really increase the
Technology that they're using now
And probably we'll see something
Start happening in the next year
But wouldn't be surprised
That they don't start listening to podcasts
Well, I'm telling you
Just based upon the shows that I've been doing
I'm hoping I get back into United Kingdom
I'm sure they're listening to me, dude
Yeah, you better be careful
When you bring in and take out
Oh, no, no, I'm
I'm clean as a whistle, my friend
I may be radical
But I'm not stupid
Yeah, I understand that
Yeah, I understand that, I do understand that
Right now
I got one question about John C. The war act
Is that right?
That go ahead
You know what, what does his job
It's fine show
You know, that's a damn good question
I'm going to have to ask him out on Friday
I have no idea what he's doing
I will say there were a lot of people
You know, question
Why he still does cranky geeks
I'd rather strange and, you know, obviously
You know, there's a lot of people who are on the pod show
Now work with prior
Prior work or we're doing different things for other people
And, you know, I don't mind sharing the love, man
I don't want to lock everyone into doing one particular thing
But John is working on
A tech channel
There's a lot of stuff coming up here at pod show
A lot of changes that you'll probably see in the next 14 days
Primarily great news for people who
Produce shows
We've got some great camps
A great money making campaigns
Anyone can participate in
And we're going to open it up much wider than just people who are signed to pod show
So stay tuned for that
And I promise you on Friday
I'll ask John what the hell he actually does pod show
Okay
Thanks for checking in
Let's get back to the United Kingdom
Here's Parkie to talk to us about
In the UK, but privacy in general
And in particular
About this new anti-terror campaign
Which essentially, if you look at credit.com
You'll see the posters
They're saying hey, if you see someone taking pictures of public buildings
That looks suspicious or if you see suspicious activity near someone's house
Or
If someone has multiple cell phones
Which probably could be anyone who's sitting in the conference call right now
I'm sure all of you geeks have multiple cell phones
You're being asked to report them
And this to me is very concerning
Now, M spoke
Who left a couple comments on the blog over curry.com
He said hey man, this is nothing new
We had this with the IRA in the 70s
And I have to agree actually I did some Google work and I searched around
And it almost exactly the same words are used
So it does make sense
I think there's a big difference though
That with this terrorism, it has a face
And this face has been plastered all over
Newspapers, television, everywhere
And not fairly of course
But that face
Probably looks like a lot of
Legal, hardworking, honest, and often citizens of the United Kingdom
Who came in from Asia
And
I think that that's going to present a lot of problems
I'm quite worried about it. Anyway, I'm a lot of parky talk
Hi Adam, it's parky checking in
I'm coming back to you on your reply to my email about the UK's
Very Own Starsy Informant Service earlier on
And you asked me how I felt about it and to be honest
Until I'd read taking liberties, I kind of knew this was all going on
But I was asleep walking right into
My buddy Carl is my resident conspiracy theory in
Weird News 7 and he's regularly getting my head from completely going to sleep
I'm going to see various cars with news block
But he wasn't until I read taking liberties
That my eyes really own right up
And the book jammed a hand from those red pills right there
I got it
By the way, if you haven't seen it yet
You have to take a look at this documentary
Taking Liberty, so there's a post
I'll put it in the show now, but there is a post on
I'm curry.com where I put the first
I think it's 9 episodes because it's YouTube stuff
Right, so they can only upload 10 minutes
It shows that there's a lot of issues in the UK
That just aren't being talked about
So it looks like the red pill went down smoothly
He probably here in the UK is the vast majority of people
Still sound asleep and have no inclination, desire
Even a need to wake up and kind of smell the coffee
Let me give you a instance
I was talking to some folks about the whole CCTV
The other day and the line from the taking liberties
Book came to mind
When they said, yeah, CCTV
You've got nothing to fear if you've got nothing to hide
And the comeback hunk of from the book is to ask a very simple
Question straight back to them, which is, well, how much do you earn?
Yeah, there is nothing to be ashamed of
Question, nothing to be fearful of question
But it's personal and here's the thing
It's private and I have no need to tell people that kind of stuff
Yeah, and I had this conversation with the lady Patricia again today
That was talking about all these posters
And this whole anti-terrorist campaign
And she has a very typical view
And she says, look, I'm really happy about this
I'm happy that there's cameras
And I have nothing to hide and I said, okay, why do you close the curtains then?
You got nothing to hide?
Can people, you mind if people look in and see what we're doing?
She said, no, that's different, I said, no, no, it's not different
Oh man, I can't wait to do a show with her
It's going to be fireworks
And these idiots in charge are asleep walking themselves into a police state
I'm pretty sure there's no grand conspiracy plan here
I freaking out there isn't
But I'm caring government is doing their best to protect us
By a reacting like a 51st day of the union
adopting all George W. Bush's ideas
And be trying their best to protect us from terrorism
You know, stuff though
We had years and years and years of the IRA trying their best to blow us up
We don't need this additional surveillance crap to do that
We looked after ourselves perfectly well during the blitz
We looked after ourselves perfectly well during the IRA time
So get off our banks guys
You know, that's a very good point
I view the British public as
Amazing people
After 7-7 which is the UK's 9-11
7th July
Man, everyone was just like screw this shit
We're not going to let anyone bring us down
We're going back to work, we're not staying home
Even at the office, you know
We said everyone, hey, if you feel uncomfortable
And stay home and I was like, no crap
No, we're not going to do that
So I agree
If all those cameras are there, you know
How come we have to start reporting on each other?
You know, no good is going to come of it
By the way, didn't an innocent man get killed
Shot to death multiple times
Because he was acting suspiciously
I just wish they'd get over the nanny's state
And give us a lice back
I think once the British people wake up and realise
What's happening to them some of this
The trouble is murdering the sun, the times, and the news of the world
Right, something else, whoever's in power
Now hold on a second
I've got to go against that
Because what the sun and news of the world
and the Murdoch publications are doing
They are, of course, giving you what you want
You know, this is clearly the type of news that we want to see
For some reason, we desire it
I don't necessarily believe that there's some conspiracy theory there
And that the government calls up Murdoch and says, hey man
But it's a more scary shit in there
I think we actually want it
We want to be scared
Maybe it gives us a feeling of living
I don't know, it's something we should delve into
Oh, you know, I should get to
Robin from InsideWorks on the show to talk about that
He would probably have some good inside
Which, of course, is why it shows called InsideWorks
It doesn't matter whether it's labour or the Conservatives
Murdoch has supported the in power parties
In each train through his media interests
Being left well alone
It's about time we'd galvanize the British people
To take back our civil liberties
And that matters the American people while we're at it
Yeah, the yanks have got it just as bad
If not worse in some respects
At least we don't have the bleeding TSA
And depending on the opponents' security
To contend with
I'd have to say you're getting pretty damn close man
I go through UK security quite a lot
Which, by the way, is full of holes
If you've ever flown internationally
And I've made a sport of this now
If you fly internationally out of Heathrow
First you go through security
Now you don't have to take your shoes off
At UK security when you go through the metal detector
In fact, these days
You don't even have to take your laptop out
And I'm about to find out how that's going to be
And on a national flight tomorrow
When I fly to Los Angeles for the day
But then once you're through there
Then you hit kind of like a custom's exit point
Which is basically five or six
Rolls that you go through and then some
Clearly unqualified person looks at your passport
They don't check anything
They just look at your passport
Check the name against the ticket
And then you're supposed to walk through
Another line which is
Specifically meant to put your shoes
Onto another x-ray machine
But this is the way it's set up
You can go off to the right
Which is where you get there's the change bureau
So you can change your money
Or you can go off to the left and they typically have some monkey
Stand in there trying to ask you into this
Into this shoe x-ray line
So what I do is I get into the left hand exit row
For you know the so-called like passport check
And then if the guy or gal who's standing there isn't looking
I just walked to the left and walk right past it
I've done it three times in a row now
It's the stupidest thing in the world
So it clearly has you know has no official
Resonant for being around because they're not enforcing it
And how easy is it just to surpass it
So I didn't have to take my shoes off through the first x-ray machine
And I bypass the second one
It's clearly horseshit
I'm just saying
The trouble is there's so much to do
Where do we stop?
Let us step on brace ourselves to argue
So bear ourselves
But it's the brick empire
And it's commonwealth
Lost, brought by India
Men will still pay
Never give up
Never surrender
There you go then
I think a bit of Winston Churchill combined with
Galaxie Quest says, oh man
Pocky checking out
Take him and bye
Listen to this week in London
It's a bloody marvelous podcast
Lovely, Parkie, thank you so much
Men, I really appreciate it
You gave me some good fodder for today's show
So I'm going to open it up and I want to hear if anyone has something to say
In fact, I'm going to be screening myself during the next song
This is a song that I posted the YouTube video on curry.com last night
And I have the MP3 actually
Let me just see if I can give some prompts here
To the person that sent it to me
Here we go
Rick
Quality on teen, I think is how you pronounce it
He sent me the MP3 in the link to the YouTube video
It's hilarious
It is completely not safe for work
It is absolutely not safe for a young
Impressionable ears
But it's a hoot and the video is even better
It's the TSA gangsta's
Talking about
The TSA gangsta's
Check it out y'all
I walk into the Austin International and
Orpac trip
TSA gangsta's up in this arrow
You can't be bringing that shit on a plane
No more mother fuck
Get your shit right
War
Grail, buckle, money, clip, going keys
Wallet, bird, put some D-cell
Let run it through
Grail, buckle, money, clip
Goin, keys, wallet, bird
Put some D-cell, let run it through
Ooh, don't be choppy, good
I had it since Easter
And all my breaks I'm bangin' that star box
Paul Reaster
I think it's corkscrew
You like this in your mat
Books, damn it got enough
But I don't want it to save the fucking queen
Got this on the arrowhead
Give me all this spark lens
Call it so good, Paul, and Springs
Keep my little soul wet
Girl, I can't let you bring on
More than four ounces
Unless you want to show me how you're fat
Pretty boozy, we confiscate your lick
It's cause you know they pose a threat
I'll even confiscate your pussy if I make it through
Damn I hate to see that breast milk
Go to waste, but you can come right through
If you give me a tip
Be a buckle, money, clip
Goin, keys, wallet, bird
Put some D-cell
Son, let, run it through
Damn buckle, money, crib
Goin, keys, wallet, bird
Put some D-cell, let, run it through
I'm a knee, $50
If you know what I mean
I saw you bigger, still Momer and Traim machine
Motherfucker took these shoes off
Before you come stepping
Yo, I think this apple could be used
I don't care
I can breathe just down
Fouls and knives of every type
Even CBD, the blades doesn't work
Wethlessly snob
I'm checking gold, played in pen, not bitch
And that's reality, you better lose your pre
911 mentality
Hey, oh, look, oh money, crap, boy, he's wallet purse
Put some D's, oh, they're running through
Hey, oh, look, oh, money, crap, boy, he's wallet purse
Hey, oh, hey, oh, he's saying, yeah
And we don't break, says that TSA gangsters
No, we don't gangster, that TSA gangsters
No, we don't break, that TSA gangsters
No, we don't pizza, oh, hey, they're sweet, you fly to Paris with your mama
Tell the bridge to shape, and she's looking like no son
I'm even thinking, coming through with you a terror risk
We gotta say, he's bodybuilder from a male
Who bitch, how can I be sure you ain't a member of our kinda
Now excuse my wand, as I slide it up inside
I'm just a kid, I need a change in 2001
Let me squeeze them titties are the terror risk of already won
Oh, they'll block the money, crap, boy, he's wallet purse
Put some D's, oh, they're running through
Hey, oh, look, oh, money, crap, boy, he's wallet purse
You're running across some more Lego-rattin' duty free
Cause that Johnny Walker blew a stain in here, written me
Hey, hit me, you gotta suspicious looking face
Let me bump in that ass like maria full of grass
You got weed up in your shoe working, you're tainted in a locket
By the time you want the plane, I fall in the mall, he's in a mall, fuck
Yes, we, I score my girls, some Chanel, number five
Lady handle with a perfume, or you gonna have to dry
The leaves in five minutes and you're running late
I'm so fucking sorry play, I get your ass back in light
But what'll lead on the conveyor?
Rea, bak, homony, clip, going keys, wallet purse
Put some D's, oh, they running through
Hey, TSA gangsta's
Link to the YouTube system, the show notes, a Debbie Source
The first code dot com as gangsters, yo we don't gangsters. Thanks for flying Kanye South West mother fucker
Oh man, is that a song at the times and I really appreciate those guys for putting that song together
And the video because you know they'll get absolutely zero airplay on commercial radio
So well done well done well done
I think we should wrap the show up. It's kind of late and of course we don't have any
Any UK people on so we'll just have to you know get back into that when I'm back in the UK and back on a different different times
Own although I must say the little conversation we had earlier worked out pretty well
I think
Hey Adam this is perhaps from Houston
I've got a question for you. What's the how do I win?
Hope you win. What are we all competing for?
Given the lifestyle that you have it sounds like you've already won
Are we already winning competing and was the pop show as we are right now?
Great here
You already won Adam and
Love you man. No home. All right man. Love you too. No mama. Thank you so much
All right, uh looking at the time. I think we should wrap it up. I got one more song is relatively short
But I received this email and and in combination with the song it it really hit me pretty deep
So I'm gonna read this for you and then I'll play the song
This is from a brand and carpenter Adam
I know being away from home has got you down and often this will take your eyes off the many subjects
You are working on but here's something you need to put your eyes on
Body of war is a documentary about Thomas Young a disabled veteran of the legal war upon the people of Iraq
The documentaries produced and directed by Phil Donahue. That's interesting and the award winning director Ellen Spiro
Man Phil Donahue. He's doing some awesome stuff
The soundtrack is produced mainly by Michael Goldstone and Eddie Vetter
Eddie of course we know from
Shit Eddie Vetter was an intern at MTV believe it or not, but that's a story for a different day
The feature track is by Eddie Vetter. It's called no more, but this is track that's available on the pont safe music network by boy genius
Bright eyes
That's a Connor Oberst of saddle Creek records the track is when the president talks to God
It's simply poignant in the same vein as Bob Dylan or any of the 60s anti war folk songs
It's gotten lots of pod plays, so please give it a listen. All right here comes
It's short. It's simple and it's sweet into the points
When the president talks to God on the Charlie
729er
When the president
talks to God or the conversation's brief for long
Does he ask to rape our women's rights and send poor farm kids off to die? Does God suggest an oil hack when the president talks to God?
When the president talks to God or the
Consonance or harder soft is he resolute all down the line is every issue black or white does what God say
I have a change his mind when the president talks to God
When the president talks to God does he fake that draw or merely not
A sandwich convict should be killed where prison should be built and failed
Which voter fraud must be concealed when the president talks to God?
When the president talks to God, I wonder which one plays the better cop
We should find some jobs to get us broke
No, they're lazy George, I say we don't just give them more liquor stores and dirty coke
That's what God recommends
When the president talks to God, do they drink near beer and go play golf while they pick which countries to invade?
Which Muslims souls still can't be saved? I guess God just calls a spade a spade
When the president talks to God
When the president talks to God, does he ever think that maybe he's not?
The divorce is just inside his head when he kneels next to the presidential bed
Does he ever smell his own bullshit? When the president talks to God, I doubt him
I doubt him
Man, yeah, one really hits home doesn't it? It's on the pod save music now
Work with means you can get to it from the show notes a daily sourceco.com and better than you're in your blog
I'd say we've got a great great player you could use to embed it
All right everybody, I think that's pretty much it for the show
We've oh man, we've been at it for 51 about 51 minutes so
Time to wrap it up. I do want to remind you that we have this fantastic deal just to get into the commerce for a second
On the Nokia N8010 internet tablet and this is not for everyone but I know that there's a lot of people
Listening to the show who if you love Linux then this is the this is the device for you. I'm telling you
You're gonna love it. It has a Mozilla based browser that does all the web 2.0 stuff
And what I use it for is for all my my Google docs my Gmail, you know, it has the slide out keyboard
So you know again, I've been staying it throughout the show. I'm I'm definitely a keyboard guy and
You know, you can use all the keyboard shortcuts and of course the number one
Massively cool thing is that you can use Skype on it. You can't get that on your iPhone and by the way
I'm not looking for
You know, I want a device that is just an internet device. I'm you know the combination of the two
And of course if you drop it in the toilet you can take the battery out and still save it
If you want to if you want to pick one up at a 15% discount you can't get a cheaper anywhere else online or in stores for that matter
You go to dailysourceco.com
Check out the show notes you can also go to podshowoffers.com
We have a whole bunch of cool offers all with great discounts and I use my code, please dailysourceco.com
All right, that's also the web address where not it's daily source code is the code
DataSourceco.com is the web address we can find the show notes for today's program
My email address is adamatpodshow.com
Love to hear from you and
Tomorrow will be kind of difficult maybe tomorrow evening. I'll be able to crank out or show depends
How tired of him if we get to get back from Los Angeles because it's gonna be a day in a lot of land
Hey everybody, thank you very much for dialing in if you are in the conference call
Everybody everywhere live your life with passion will you? Don't be afraid of the man
And enjoy your freedom what it lasts another podshowpodcast stick it in your ear