Delta's here at Charlie's 7-9 or 1.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
In the next generation radio contenting my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
All testing, it's NATO Curry.
We want to leave, take a care
How we find a lot of nice things to wear
But then a lot of nice things done by our bed
Oh, baby baby, it's a wild boar
It's hard to get by our heart just to punish my heart
I always remember you like a child
You know I've seen a lot of what the world can do
And it's breaking my heart into
Cause I never want to see you sad girl
Don't be a bad girl
If you want to leave, take a care
Hope you make a lot of nice friends out there
But just remember there's a lot of bad
I wouldn't be well
Oh, baby baby, it's a wild boar
It's hard to get by our heart just to punish my heart
I always remember you like a child
Live it, laugh it, laugh it out, laugh it out
The light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the
of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the lighting of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light- the light of the light of the light of the eye of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the light of the
Oh, baby, baby, it's what I hold on
Oh, yeah, baby, it's a wild, wild world
And we're just actors on the stage playing our part
Hey, John, what is I doing?
The resource code episode number seven, nine or one
And it's September 18th, 2008, where is the time going?
I'll be sucked into the continuum I guess
For the first time now, I start my day off by going to the drop
Because that's where all the news is that's the real news
Drop.io slash daily source code, this show of course
He's comprised of that, that is the true source code to this program
You guys produce it, I just put it together and try to guide us along
Hey, it's been a pretty nice day today in the United Kingdom
And I've been home for, well, I haven't been home, I've been in and out of London doing meetings
There is also some stuff that's been happening like we released a whole new version of the site
That's pretty cool, mevio.com in the States and BT Pod Show
And in the UK, very proud of the work that we've done
And finally things coming together the way we envisioned them
So that's been nice, but also of course I've been pretty much glued to the television
Said whenever possible to CNBC, which we get over here in the United Kingdom as well
Just following the markets, it's been, I mean, it's been really fantastic
To watch all of this predicted, all of this foreseen, all of this of course
has been completely planned, we've talked about that here on the Charlie Shuckleheads
Are in the know
And today, I really only wanted to handle two topics
It was going to be a pretty short show, and I just wanted to whip through it
And as I started going through the drop, and yeah, there's only a couple of ways for me to do this
Either I do a show every single day, which is shorter and just get the news out
That's coming in or I try to aggregate it and make some kind of coherent story out of it
And give you some real valuable information, because I too have to process this is so much coming in, so much going on
And of course the financial markets is what everyone's talking about
And you know, I just, all these comments, because that of course is the new place to leave voicemail
Right there on the drop, drop.io slash daily source code and
Well, here's one right now, out wait a minute, this one isn't just a comment
It has its own jingle, of course
Hold on how much time will it be going in
I, I don't know what the number 10th is
me pretty Mack now my my I've never been a question I don't I don't I don't know
here the answer but what's the purpose of probably banging sector if all
what if all that happened my northern rock is taking over my coming in the
Bank of England right right is it I don't know yeah that's all in demand
so maybe your mind is advancing you know on this many thanks cheers well we
have lots of savants and and they've been sending me messages I've been
aggregating information I've been learning and I'm going to try and
distill the most important parts for you right now so first of all what's
happening now in the financial sector is the people who are used to making money
with money OPM is even better other people's money they're the ones that are
going down so they're going down but of course the people who are truly
putting the bill is us and that's why I'm highly interested in this because today
even though I haven't followed much of the news today I had another meeting and
really it's been two hours the last two hours just preparing for the show
hundred and eighty billion one eight zero billion dollars put into the
pumped into the economy as they say it by the federal reserve approved by the
Treasury Hank Paulson all criminals by the way I'll just say it outright I'm
not afraid to say it stealing our money this is and this of course is you know
if the pension funds haven't already been rated to the max then then this is
just printing money which means inflation on the way of course the coordinated
effort with the European Central Bank and with the Bank of England and this is
all to keep themselves afloat which isn't as futile it's not actually going
to work and the piece I wanted to explain to you is AIG this of course was the
news yesterday American international group AIG is an insurance firm it's a
holding firm of multiple types of insurance companies now you have the
traditional insurance companies that we know about car insurance how
insurance or home insurance I should say they in fact have a big aircraft
division for insurance who knows some of the insurance I have on the Delta Delta
Sheriff may even be through a subsidiary of AIG it's absolutely possible now we're
not supposed to or don't we're not supposed to be worried about these particular
companies because they are regulated by the government and the government you
know we're supposed to take a look and keep a watch fly and make sure they
have enough reserves that in case lots of claims come in that they can actually
pay for them and that regulation is done on something you keep hearing a lot
of these days the faith and credit of the United States of America the
faith part of course is the most interesting one because that means people
would have to believe in us believe our story well it's starting to get pretty
thin here my friends now the important part the part that's really
in measurable in size is the derivatives business the insurance of bonds now
already I can see your eyes maybe glazing over I really want to give this a
shot and try and explain how it works because as well worth it and then you
can understand the vastness of of the problem with the AIG and why it's all
interlinked and related so a derivative a simple plane derivative or swap a
credit default swap you'll hear people talking about this all the time the CDS
don't just pass over that let's pay attention to it let's find out what this
really means because it's it's interesting the the swap is put into place and
I learned a lot about this when when I worked at in-house actually with
our first company was thinking of ideas I'm wondering if it was still on ramp
of we've gone public by that point it was somewhere around that time and
bankers trust which is long since been sold and folded up into some other
bank traded mainly in derivatives and they hired us to build and market for
them internally a web-based trading desk and so I learned about these swaps and
a swap is very simply put if I have a bond okay so bond is basically it's
it's a collection of assets now this and these assets can be mortgages that
of course is the true problem we're looking at today but it could also be another
type of bond David Bowie issued a bond for fifty million dollars about ten
twelve years maybe longer than that maybe a maybe thirteen fourteen years ago
so he put fifty million bucks in his pocket and then the bond holders of
course have the right to go and use his his music mainly on commercials and
other stuff so this bond is going to throw off a certain type of yield which
means it'll make money just because of the value that it'll have an in-flow
of cash now let's just take it as a mortgage bond so I've put together I'm
making simple making million bucks doesn't matter that much worth of mortgages
and I've structured that into a bond and by the way I'm not a sovarant on this
topic I'm just telling you from a simplistic I'm a disc jockey okay so just
from reading and and and asking have been able to aggregate this information
it's not entirely right I'm sure and people can correct me but in essence
I'm pretty sure I'm spot on so you collect all these mortgages together there
worth a million which means they should be spinning out maybe a hundred thousand
dollars a year and you can sell this you can sell this to someone else let's
say I want to sell it to let me see John C. Devorac would be a good one now
John C. Devorac has to eventually pay me back for that right now if I'm not too
sure about his credit worthiness I might want to take out some insurance just in
case he defaults on that bond so I used to be able to go to a company like AIG
and say AIG I guess what I got this million dollar bond I've sold it to Devorac
but you know you guys please send me so many some insurance so that if he
defaults that I still get my million bucks back and maybe even plus some you
know yielders and interest or whatever and they'll write that you know just
like you can get health insurance or it's not not crazy you know people
write you insurance for a for a car crash thinking that you know you'll probably
pay it more than you'll ever have to claim and they have all those no claims
bonuses and all that you know so that you are incentivized not to claim anything
you know you have your your own risk portion and all that but it's exactly the
same thing only this is for someone defaulting on payments and AIG of course
will pay me will charge me money for that and that's typically measured in
basis points so in those days maybe it was 70 basis points which would be
$7,000 to ensure a million dollars worth of bond okay so that's a pretty
simple system now what's interesting is that AIG they can now say hey you know
we've sold this insurance to Adam based upon this money that door this bond that
he's lent to a devourack one and we so that's $7,000 that's coming in from that why
don't we packed together you know a 10,000 of those and go sell that and by the way
we're probably gonna go get insurance on the person that we sold that to so you see how
the domino start to stack up in fact this has gotten so broad and so massive that
AIG probably was ensuring money they had already ensured two or three times over
what's crazy about these derivatives particularly the credit default swaths and this is
what I learned working at bankers trust is that it's not was not really regulated as far
as I know it's all done on phone calls and the contracts are fact you know there's no real
trading system then there may be but now but when I was working with him in the 90s it was just
facts is going back and forth vanilla deals we call them very very simplistic stuff and
you know really the traders had the knowledge in their head and they had all their what they call
counter parties and this is you know and they just transform money based upon the contracts
but of course this inflates the actual original value that million dollars inflates it to
maybe a billion dollars worth of money that's floating around their system their system mind you
now when these people don't trust each other independently then everything starts to unravel
and of course the unraveling of that is you know how the you know geez how you how do you
find out where all this stuff is you know it's you've got to get all the facts is and you've got
to unwind these layers upon layers upon layers of lending to each other which is how banks make
money they lend money and whether it's in the form of insurance or whether it's in the form of
a bank loan which of course is not real money it's all just that it's you know it's it's a loan
it's a it's an entry in a spreadsheet it's not much more that is what created this this huge issue
and this is in the trillions of dollars it's a hundred and eighty billion dollars it's you know
unfathomable amount of money but it's a joke compared to what the issue really is and now that
and on these banks they just don't trust each other how do you know they don't trust each other
is because the spread or the rate of lending to each other or that's let's put it this way
AIG where they used to get you know 70 basis points will be kind of you know what you'd have to pay
if you were doing business with AIG that has now gone up to two thousand basis points
so to borrow ten you know to ensure against ten million dollars you'd have to pay two million
dollars and insurance well that obviously is not a real strategy because you're not going to get
that kind of money in from the original ten million that you loan that you want insurance upon
so AIG although we now own 79.9% of it as American taxpayers is useless it's you know yeah
maybe we'll make some of that money back by by selling off all the individual other pieces
and that's only taking into account that you know the regulators have actually paid attention
and haven't been you know having sex with the with the insurers and doing dope with them like
the mineral management agency has done with the oil companies let's just say that didn't happen
then we might be kind of safe for the what is it the 85 billion that they they gave to AIG in return
for 80% and by the way I don't want my government running the companies that I'm a co-owner of screw
that shit now I could go on and on about this but at least I hope you have a small idea of
well it's a pyramid scheme or a Ponzi scheme really what has just been built up and it's all
come toppling down which is exactly as we predicted to talk a little bit more about this issue I yield
my time to the distinguished gentleman from Texas congressman Ron Paul this is from his website
that he posted yesterday pre the 180 billion infusion into the markets which of course was printed
up and is also our money doctor run hello today we had a lot of financial fireworks in the
markets a lot of things are going on and I think we are in the middle of something going on it's
very big it doesn't look like it's going to end real soon today the Federal Reserve came in
and offered 85 billion dollars to buy on AIG and it looks like it's never going to end they're talking
about the next company whether it's more in Stanley or whatever already we've been able to
fannie me and Freddie Mac and the layman's went bankrupt and then of course of course Bear
Stearns had a bailout not too long ago and we're talking about big bucks we're not talking about
hundreds of millions or even hundreds of billions now we're talking about trillions of dollars the
obligation is immeasurable nobody can measure it and the derivatives markets very much involved nobody
knows how much you're involved but all I know is they're starting to unwind and that is why all these
banks and investment companies are in such big trouble and all the only thing they can resort to is
coming coming to the federal government coming to the Federal Reserve and asking for bailout the
interesting thing is like today coming up with this 85 billion dollars they don't come to the
Congress I mean the Federal Reserve buys them out they own it we we as taxpayers now own
me and Freddie Mac and nobody knows how much that will cost that could be that could be into the
trillions of dollars so they don't come to Congress we don't have appropriations it's done by secret
government private individuals behind the scenes moonoving them and they'd be lighting and trying to
patch things up but of course in the meantime I'm sure there's a few people making a couple bucks
out of this whole thing today and foreign affairs committee we had a bill come up was considered
insignificant it was only only a billion dollars and it was to send aid humanitarian aid to Georgia
and there was some debate on it which was fortunate but about 25 of the committee members
didn't show up for the vote he's going to be put on this suspension believing that they'll get
two thirds vote very easily and they say well it's humanitarian we need to help him and yet that is
such a controversial issue going on and to me it's just a disaster to pump more money in the
Georgia stirring up trouble can provoking Russia trying to reunite the Cold War all these many
many things but financially speaking we don't have a billion dollars I mean where are we going to
get it they try they're going to appropriate and authorize this money but they're not going to
raise taxes in the next few months to pay for this and they'll probably have to borrow it or you
know get it from the federal reserve some way you know just monetize them down and and get more money
but with all the problems that we have we have in this country the infrastructure in this country
we're still going around we're looking for more problems so in a way this casualness on how we
spend a billion dollars overseas and foreign aid for humanitarian purposes which in reality is a military
support for that government who's supposed to in return protect an oil pipeline in that country and
even this bill actually stated that it had something to do with the pipeline so this this to me is
is just you know a symbol of how serious the problem is that this is not even event and yet the whole
Cold War with the Russia with Russia now they restart stirred up again at the same time our
financial markets are collapsing today the market was down 450 points a couple of days ago down
500 points a gold I mean filing people made it got some sense and said hey this can't help the dollar
when they bailed out the money made pretty mac in the market this was in in collusion with the
Chinese because the Chinese were getting worried because they held so much of the security so we
had to bail them out as well to protect our dollar so the Chinese government and the American government
were in bed together and the immediate reaction there was it was a tremendous boost in the dollar
but that had to be temporary because you can't create money like we're doing and in order to support
the dollar because ultimately it hurts the dollar and everything we do in Washington today whether it's
on the appropriation size whether what the fit is doing buying up America is all put in pressure
on on the dollar and one of these days we're just going to have to wake up and say that we need
to liquidate debt this is a malinvestment our problems come from the fact first they start with
the Federal Reserve is a monopoly and it controls interest rates artificially low causes
people to make mistakes that's the basic source but they don't top of that in the housing market what
we had we had the community reinvestment act which told investors that they had to loan to risky
borrowers and that was a complication hard to contribute to this FDIC contributed it's called
moral hazard everything that we have done over here creates moral hazard that is we assure people
or assume that we'll take care of everybody just go out and take the risk it's the opposite
of the marketplace and then they have people come along and say see this is the failure of capitalism
this has nothing to do with capitalism this is something that started off as interventionism
and us being too involved in the economy for the benefit of special interest but now it's being
socialized out in the open I mean we the taxpayers now own mortgage companies insurance companies
and we're going on a lot more if our car companies need build up believe me it's going to happen they're
not going to let all our car companies go broke either but this will come to an end the end of this
comes when people reject the dollar and I think we're getting off we close to this we we you see the
movement we're seeing in the markets today we know that there are serious problems out there and
Congress basically are oblivious they had no idea what's going on better back I'm not even sure
the Federal Reserve has any idea what to do about this they've been manipulating maneuvering
for their benefit over the years but eventually the market wins out and right now I think the market
is is saying that this is so serious and so big that we better be prepared and the reason why
this is so important if we care about people and humanitarian sense what you want to do is protect
their value of the money just think of the third world nations when they have total runaway
inflation the middle class gets wiped out and today what we're seeing today is the middle class
being jeopardized by this type of system we have of unlimited spending unlimited debt
unlimited creation of new credit so it's time that we wake up I think a lot of people are waking
up and starting to realize this but also there's a lot of people starting to panic but the answers
are there the answers are in the free market and sound money in our constitution but we did that
we could solve it wrong it's so far we haven't seen very many people resorting to going back to the
basics the basic principles of the marketplace capitalism and our constitution
we're going back to the market and we're going back to the market and we're going back to the market
and we're going back to the market and we're going back to the market and we're going back to the market
and we're going back to the market and we're going back to the market
and we're going back to the market
he's guys we're so ahead of their time i'm actually i'm going to post a link to the lyrics in uh
in the show notes the dailysourceco.com and uh curry dot com hey listen this money get away get a good job with
good pay and you're okay money it's a gas grab that cash with both hands and make a stash new caviar new car
forced it star daydream think of buying me a football team money get back i'm all right jack keep your hands off
my stack money it's a hit don't give me that goody goody bull shit i mean the high fidelity first
class traveling set and i think i need a legit here comes money it's a crime shared fairly but don't
take a slice of my pie money so they say it's the root of all evil today but if you ask for a
raise it's no surprise that they're giving none away tell ya oh man it just gives me goosebumps
goosebumps by the way just coming back to a i.g. briefly there's a link in the show notes
that talks about uh greenburg not greenspam but greenburg he is uh the founder of a i.g. i think he's
so owned about eleven or owns eleven percent so he lost uh i don't know five or six maybe even seven
billion dollars in a week's time uh look at uh his associations really uh you know look at uh look at
what he's uh his associations with the bush family and look at some of the companies and what they
ensure okay and then think about uh why he need he and i think he's he's bullshitting us i think
you know i saw um letters on cnbc where he's really angry that they're doing this and all we need
it is a bridge loan and we shouldn't have sold out yeah i think it this is another crony getting bailed
out that's the way i read it that's just my personal opinion because then again the hell do i know
i'm just a dj uh dj former vj i linked to that story which is really worth reading in the
show notes daily source code dot com hey adam this is reaching home from Brooklyn, New York
uh just wanted to drop you a quick line say hi i just finished watching that uh zero nine eleven
investigation uh documentary which i thought was awesome um i just wanted to thank you very much for
turning me on to that and turn into world on to it uh i i uh seen other uh documentaries but this was
very extensive filled and a lot of the questions that i had and certainly uh brought to my
attention some some unanswered questions um i uh uh actually cut and pasted it to my uh blog page
and uh turned everybody i know on to it uh Facebook and all my friends and stuff like that so uh
people's a good work thank you so much for everything that you do Adam um a long time listener this
is my first call uh uh i don't know my sign off uh that's a name definitely uh uh work for us
and uh thanks for everything uh yeah and we got to keep reminding him Richard from Brooklyn my friend
that's all i asked for that is all i want there's an awakened citizen a true patriot that's
all you have to do first we need to we have uh a lot of movement right now and although it's uh seven
years old at this point nine eleven is a good starting point we'll talk about that later on in the
show but it's a good starting point to help people wake up just because there is so much evidence
empirical evidence that does not fit with the official conspiracy theory so uh that's all i'm
asking for it's just passed it on get people you know help people uh understand what's really going on
okay and uh that means you couldn't turn them on to this show or or a multitude of websites that
they're out are out there and there's this uh on there must be a hundred different uh quote
documentaries that of course is my favorite the zero and uh investigation to nine eleven which is an
Italian documentary which just makes me laugh because uh you know funny how we actually need the
Italians to show us how blind we are for what's been going on uh here's a topic i i didn't plan
on bringing up but after going through uh email and the show notes i i did want to just uh aggregate
all of these different reports and this is about the uh cervical cancer uh vaccination that i am so
against and i'm not just against the cervical cancer vaccination pretty much against most of
vaccinations um because i i don't trust our government and i don't trust our government and uh our
drug approval process to actually um allow them to inject something into my child now let me point
out that obviously when it comes to tetanus when it comes to polio uh when it comes to hepatitis
um these uh inoculations these vaccinations this uh yeah i've had them i'm still reasonably okay i
guess uh but it is my belief that the government lies to us uh for all kinds of reasons and i'm seeing
more and more proof that uh part of this uh particularly this hpv vaccination which is um called
Gardasil Gardasil Gulf Alpharomio Delta Alpha Sierra India Lima um that it's uh first and
foremost it's a scam to make money for the biggest drug companies on the earth the pharmaceutical
industry. Of course there are big trouble now because you know they have these patents and uh uh
the main one lipitor is uh running out which means then anyone can make it and uh and uh and there's
no huge profit so they need to you know there's nothing really left in the pipeline except for
of course the avian bird flu which uh as we know is a something that might have killed 150 people
uh in the 15 years that we know about it if that um but there's billions of dollars that they're
counting on for making uh up the vaccination which means they actually have the virus you can't
make of a vaccination for a virus without having it i'll get to that in a minute but um um the uh
the cost of uh polio tetanus hepatitis vaccinations which of course have been around for a long
long time uh four dollars this new um hpv one hundred and forty four dollars so that's a scam
it's a scam for them to make money and it's being rolled out globally we know about it in the United
Kingdom we know about it in the Netherlands uh coming in Canada, Switzerland and this is one of my
favorites uh left on the drop uh Renato uh Castillo from Brazil um I'll quote literally
Adam it's happening man Brazilian health department is doing a mass vaccination mainly men
between the ages of 20 and 39 their goal is to vaccinate 7070 million people the vaccine is for
German measles German measles even though we don't have any epidemics and and by the way you
can survive the measles okay you will not necessarily die from the measles and all of this is
to comply with the Pan American Health Organization determination to mass vaccinate people all over
Latin America and he sent me uh two links unfortunately they're in Portuguese and uh I don't speak it
but check those links out in the show notes a daily source code dot com along with that uh this one is
this one just blew me away uh this is all the drop uh this is from uh is MSNBC Austin Texas this
from 2007 uh turns out here is some conservative and parents rights groups are worrying that
requiring girls to get vaccinated against the sexually transmitted virus that causes cervical cancer
would condone pre-marital sex and interfere with the way they raise their children uh this is mandatory
uh shots for this HPV which again it is it's only something you get from having sex okay
and uh typically having sex with a lot of guys and a lot of guys with dirty dicks
and and that's a that's a poor man's assumption but that's pretty much what I understand from the
literature so it's not quite like polio okay and giving it to 12 your girls basically says okay so
go ahead but what else is in those shots that's what I want to know that's the part I don't trust
uh please someone here's what I'd like to know go get some of this guard to seal and let's have it
tested I'll bet you a hundred bucks right now it's got mercury in it I'll bet you it's got other
crap in there that they're not telling us let's have that shit tested show me that I don't trust the
government another link here all of these in the show notes a daily source code dot com
in July U.S. citizenship and immigration and immigration services quietly amended
it's list of required vaccinations for immigrants applying to become citizens one of the newest
requirements guardacil which vaccinate against HPV that's a money scheme but I truly believe
particularly when you hear about you know what's happened with they want to vaccinate Latin America
against German measles come on I don't trust that shit now the scariest one this is from the
BBC this really freaked me out the body of an aristocrat who died nearly 90 years ago has been
exhumed in the hope that it will help scientists combat a future flu pandemic this is the bird flu
this is the next one this is where all their money is going to come from so this goes back to
Yorkshire landowner sir Mark Sykes who died in France in 1919 from the Spanish flu remember now
that they vaccinated and he here he's a picture of him with his uniform on they vaccinated all
these soldiers and there's a lot of literature about this and it's quite well known that you know
50 60 million people died from the Spanish flu but that it developed from these soldiers
having all kinds of shit injected to them and you can live with viruses but stress and poor
nutrition brings out viruses and that's when they can become lethal the scientists believe
this guy's remains will help piece together the DNA of the Spanish flu which could have similar
genetics structure to modern bird flu so it sounds like science but to me it feels like they just
needed a nice little sample so they could make this vaccine and let me see I love this let me see
I can find this part in this story his body will have to be examined in a special airtight
laboratory to avoid any risk of contamination the guy was buried in a lead coffin okay a lead
90 years ago which scientists hope preserve the virus so we're digging up the virus we're digging it up
so we can make a vaccine and then shoot it in everybody and God knows what that means
and I've been feeling this may become mandatory as well so I'm just suspicious okay I really am
suspicious I don't just take it for granted I go ahead just shoot something in my in my kids arm
without me knowing exactly what's in there who's doing the testing on this HPV I'd like some
independent studies to show me exactly what this vaccine contains okay
read there okay running hi this is Blake Morgan hi this is Blake Morgan hi this is
this is Lee Colter from San Diego via the land down on Dave's Angie and this is Ryan
of love spiral this is Crystal Bell and this is Warren and we're from the band how it is
hi this is Randy Jackson from Zebra hey Brent this is Don Lafonte
hey everybody there's Ricky Hills from keep prick here let's have breakfast
hey everybody's smile here it's up everybody I'm from Plain White tea hi this is Jeff Smith
and David Olsen that was planned by my husband when I was just having a group of fire rioting
this is a pot of radio to enjoy these and have a great artist join me Brent Bradley over
a pot show radio dot com yeah awesome show you sent us to it on the weekends he tried
making it mevio radio but uh it just didn't sound right and he had all that invested in it so
I'm very happy to promote pot show radio hey Adam hi doing this is it's number 139 and we're
gonna start right away with intro okay it won oh I'm blank and I'm that one young it's about time
you stump me they've been kind of easy lately number two uh Billy Olsen when they're going
get stop the top get going eighty eighty three maybe eighty two eighty three eighty two
and the final one is number three
I know I'm gonna say shit I know that but I can't come over that unfortunately and it's time for
the answers and this week they're all from I got six test and this is answer number one in this
oh the fetch a boy
The Petra Boys has entered number one and this is Anthem number two. This is Billy O'Share
Billy O'Share when the going gets stuff is answered number two.
And this is number three. This is Don Johnson.
Oh man, it was said.
That's not clear.
Get it away.
You money don't be much to me.
Oh shit.
Oh honey.
Oh man.
A singing sunny rocket is answering number three.
With hard beats.
Just include Titus number one three.
Minor.
Yeah.
So Adam.
How did you do this week?
I kind of suck man.
Two out of six.
I'll give myself a third point for knowing that Billy O'Share's song is from the movie
Romancing the Stone.
Alrighty.
Test with me.
Use your place to find the answer to this and any other hitist.
And to also find the links to iTunes, you can buy the tricks featured on the hitist online.
Okay.
Let's look for this hitist recorded with a Mac, which still takes a bit of getting used to.
But this one's been created with soundbites by Black Cat systems.
And it seems I've got it set up just right since I use all my needs.
I use it all the time.
For recording the hitist.
One more thing after a month of 15 months or so,
the hitist podcast is back.
Right on.
Which is my own personal podcast filled with audio stuff and things to hit.
That I have to do with switching from PC to Mac.
And also personal stuff that's been happening in my life lately.
So check it out at, well, the same address.
Yompholette.com.
Alrighty Adam.
Thank you for playing everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I hope to be back with another hitist.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And remember, try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
Be back.
If test at gmail.com info.
Yompholette.com.
And be OLDT.com.
Yo.
Thank you.
You're on for providing a nice little break there in the atmosphere.
And we got to Ray on the Charlie coming up as well with more musical goodness and
just wacky stuff, just to balance out the show.
Now, there's a couple of links here that I don't have time to discuss.
And just, of course, they're going to be in the show notes.
These are mainly BBC stories, but just stuff I want to bring to your attention because
it's important.
So you can follow those links if you want to in the show notes.
DataSourceco.com, curry.com.
Iran sending weapons to the Taliban.
That is very, it's just data points.
That's an interesting data point.
That could be an impetus to send tanks, which are there being brought in from the Ukraine
from Afghanistan to roll them into Iran.
I don't actually believe there will be a nuclear strike, by the way.
That's pretty much off the table as far as I'm concerned.
Now, the link here from the BBC, the IMF, approves the loan to help Georgia.
This, of course, is a scam.
This is how we get these small countries under control.
We don't actually give them money, but we lend them money.
It's just a little thing there in the database.
They have to then pay interest.
And it's primarily used because they don't get money.
That money is actually paid out to the weapons manufacturers in the United States.
Some of those around the world, all who, of course, have ties into the IMF and the World Bank.
So they send the weapons over.
And they say, OK, so we just sold you a couple tanks.
That's a couple million there off of your billion dollars that we've promised you.
And remember, you still got to pay interest if you don't pay the interest.
Well, then we're just going to take over your country.
And that means we get to take over where the pipelines are.
And we get to use your airfields and please don't default on that money.
Because we're going to have to come in and take over.
Is Ukraine's government has fallen on a part.
Only two days after Vice President Dick Cheney visited the Ukraine.
And it's truly a, it's crazy because it's a fight between the president.
Now, these guys had what they called just like Georgia had the Rose Revolution.
Ukraine, when they separated from Russia,
the Ukraine had the Orange Revolution.
And they have a coalition, which is a very familiar type of government.
So they have multiple parties.
And the president, it's really the president versus the prime minister.
The president, he wants to join NATO.
Now, if that, of course, is why Dick Cheney was hanging out with him.
Because he was hanging out with the president, not necessarily the prime minister.
And most of the country, as well known, does not want to join NATO.
Unfortunately, on the other side, we've got the prime minister.
And she wants to become a member of the European Union, which I don't think is a good thing either.
But it's interesting to see how Dick Cheney was there.
Two days later, shit falls apart, what's next?
Will it be some form of violence or how is that going to, how is that going to end?
And they also have a breakaway province where the Russians are handing out passports.
They fact similarly of what happened in Georgia.
So I'm just waiting to see.
Something's going to go on there.
It's another data point to keep your eye on.
Something crazy that goes beyond me.
I just didn't have the bandwidth to go into it and to read into it.
This kind of like Opus Day type of religious outfit called Legatus.
And the title of this article is called How Legatus brought down Wall Street.
I think a gocker or maybe even Boeing Boeing posted on this.
But again, it was just too much.
My brain started to hurt when I was reading through it.
But I wanted to make sure you have it.
It's another important data point as we start to understand what is going around us.
As the veil is slowly lifted as the bars are widening of that invisible cage.
And we are starting to wake up.
Wake up people.
They work for us, but they don't know it.
And we're all being lied to.
We need to wake up and smell a coffee.
That I've been listening to to your show since about number 50.
So I've listened to a lot of your stuff.
Yeah.
And your rants and this and I got to say that lately I was beginning to wonder whether maybe you were kind of going crazy.
But I got to say that I want to congratulate you.
And I admire your courage and your willingness to stick your neck out.
So just a big thank you for my guy in Canada and keep up the great work.
No, no, man.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Everybody.
And I feel this so strongly now that people are waking up to multiple things.
They're waking up to 9.11.
They're waking up to the financial crisis.
They're waking up to vaccinations.
They're waking up to what's going on around them.
They're waking up to the cameras.
And they're making songs about it.
They're writing about it.
They're blogging about it.
They're making videos about it.
They're making poems about it.
Poetry.
Who thought I would ever give a shit about poetry?
And, uh, curry.
This is Brian Colin.
So I decided to start writing again.
And, um, you know, I wrote this poem.
Used to write a lot of poetry.
And, uh, I don't know, maybe you'll play it on your show.
Maybe not.
Or maybe you'll just read it and like it.
I don't know.
But it seems, you know, this is something maybe that I can do to help people.
But the aim of the poem is called, I'm awake.
All right.
A little nervous, but here it goes.
I'm awake to your master plan.
I see through your left right hypocrisy.
And my left are right.
I answer slowly.
I'm a human being on the small dot called earth.
First and foremost, I'm on to you.
I say, your fat tooth in.
This is in.
This is out.
By this.
Where this.
Your car is great.
Your floor.
I taste great.
I've cut your deceptive eyes.
Telling lies.
I'm on to your ways.
No more.
My numbing days.
I am free.
I say, god damn it.
I'm free.
You have my mind.
No more.
Checked in a paradigm of waste.
You can't stop me.
I can smile now and forever into the sun.
Stars, the moon and beyond.
I am alive now.
My ideas like prescription meds.
Take my reds and I will fill all your heads.
I'm your red pill dealer.
Your new age healer.
I've got your goodies galore.
It's truth.
And I've always got more and more.
I thought I was one, but I am many.
It's not me by far.
It's we the people.
Together strong.
Together I feel change.
We are all connected.
Every color, creed.
Man, woman, child.
We will create.
We will last.
Your plan has failed.
I'm sorry to say.
We have been awakened.
Yeah.
I don't know.
My palm.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Peace.
They work for us.
Are you kidding me?
Beautiful.
Absolutely stunning.
Thank you so much, my friend.
Chocolate heads.
This is what it's about.
It's just us.
And the more of us we bring in.
The better it gets.
We've got to wake people up.
We've got to let them know what's going on.
I want to slip in one little thing, which we have.
I don't talk about too much because, you know, there's already such a vast amount of
understanding to do just in the physical world.
Let alone the another dimension.
Yeah.
And this is a Ryan call for Massachusetts.
Hey, right.
I've been listening to your show for a while.
About a year or so.
And I just wanted to talk about the October 14 event that could possibly happen.
Yeah.
Now, is it October 14?
Is that where the Canadians are supposed to come first?
Yeah.
So this is the news and the word out that I've gotten through my channels is that.
And I'm so open for this.
The depletions.
We'll surface and make one of their enormous space crafts of visible.
It's supposed to be on October 14.
Now, could this be a total fabrication, just something I'd like to believe in?
Hell yeah.
Of course.
I'm not saying that I know anything.
I never say I know anything.
I know a little bit about music and flying, but that's about it.
All the rest is just self-taught.
So who the hell knows?
But I've spent a fair amount of time.
And I heard about the October 14th pretty early on.
I talked about it on no agenda.
And it's just another data point.
I think we should keep our eyes open.
And particularly if something shows up and there's a lot of debunking and a lot of government
saying it's not true or even worse if the government says they're here to kill us.
Or if it's all just a big promotion for Keanu Reeves' new movie.
I don't know.
I do not know.
But I'm very open to it.
Very open to it.
Perhaps.
But I know, or is it a separate audience?
Didn't have to do it possibly the whole Billy Myers thing.
It happened about, I think, 20 years ago, 25 years ago.
The thing with Billy Myers that he predicted two or a half wars, which is rather interesting
because George Bush won, and George Bush won, and then George Bush won.
And then Bill Myers also talks about debating Iran, which I think will call it pretty close to you.
So I'm just wondering, do you think, you know, I really would like something to happen on the 14th.
You know what I mean?
I think it would be great.
I mean, I think that would really wake up a lot of people.
I guess I'm a little skeptic, but good on it.
You know what I mean?
You know, you say, you know, keep keep a, you know, keep, keep peace and love in your heart,
which I, you know, I think that's a, that's just a good mod of the live by general.
But anyways, I'll let the show, and take care, and they work for us, peace out.
I do indeed my friend.
And I have nothing but love in my heart.
You know, this is a big topic here in the curry manner.
I can't hate anybody.
I really can't.
It's, it's, it's leading my body.
I have no, uh, remorse.
I have no guilt.
I have no greed.
I have no envy.
Uh, that's really all that's left is love and creativity.
That's, uh, that's what I want to utilize in my remaining days.
God, I hope I have a whole bunch more.
I really do.
That'll be nice.
Okay.
So we're about two thirds the way through the list.
We got some really good songs and an article that I'm going to read to you,
which is really, really something for thought, and it's really heavy stuff.
So I want you to prepare for that.
But first, uh, well, we obviously have to do a little bit of light entertainment.
Um, my buddy Ray has been documenting my life in his series of Ray on the Charlie,
which is the soundtrack to my life.
I love it.
That I do have a voice that, that is, of course, egotistical, but it's kind of nice because
the soundtrack to my life is a concept of everyone knowing exactly where they were,
what they were doing, and what feelings they have associated with the song.
And sometimes we share those soundtracks to our lives.
Sometimes in extremely different ways, but it's always fun to play the game.
All we want you tonight is Ray in good times.
My friends, good times.
Hope we've got to be a part of us against our name.
We'll talk to you.
I'm sorry.
The soundtrack to my life.
Well, let's take a look at the landscape on a road trip through your life.
This episode of Ed and Carys, the soundtrack to my life,
brings us back to 1988.
Ed was 24 years old, and lived with a lady Patricia and two house bats in New York City.
Most of it was wonderful time, living with a lot of your wife in the city of your ambition.
Ed was a VJ for MTV.
We also did radio work for the New York City Radio Station WHDC.
V100, New York, New York.
Oh, by the way, I almost forgot to tell you charcoal answered at 1988.
What's the year in which art, two little lot of words got married.
The fifth August, a road trip, driving drove around to block through just an hour.
To take a seat in the lady, P.S. and Mary, to couple, back to their apartment.
I'm talking to my baby on the telephone, all this done.
Okay, back to the job.
The soundtrack to my life.
During the years, Adam's image became more and more of that from the center of America.
Had metal dream, besides making some honor beards,
making music videos.
But MTV was also a host of the programs and English ball.
It's up to it to count down.
And most of all, modern, old, rock, and TV.
I just approved my two, my true leopard mania.
I brought in all of the 45s that I had.
My favorite one, of course, in cool for the V-sides is Armageddon,
which features stompers and maximists in the good old boys.
We released me on the V-sides.
Now, the deal is, we put all of these together.
Then you get the full album cover.
You know, maybe they should do this as a V-J test for audition in the future.
I don't know.
Phil Collins coming up with a leopard bite.
And so it was a stereo.
Soundtracks in my life.
Adam Cleared, you had a crush on the English Armageddon.
That old man broke Sheffield.
And formed in 1977 as a father.
We released me on the V-sides.
Adam Cleared, you had a crush.
Soundtracks in my life.
And it's a train that I won't be late to.
Night in 2018.
Adam coming up with a smile.
We made it up.
And no one can't.
You don't wanna make it up.
And now I'm holding with it.
When you made it up.
And you don't wanna make it up.
You got it.
Now you get me.
It's better than when we go.
Anything more to tell.
You know it's not fair.
Don't rock it.
You know you got it.
Now you get me.
We made it up.
And now you get me.
1 2 3 4 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5
5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5
5 5 5 5 5 4 6 5 9 5 5 5 5 9 1 5 5 5 7 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 10 5 10 5 5 5 6 7 5 6 10 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 4 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 1 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 8 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 9 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 10 10 5 15 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 4 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 6 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5 5
married what we did right after you know we just went down to City Hall in New York City
got married now we actually witnessed to another couple's marriage because their
witness didn't show up. Steve Lease from MTV at the time now it's serious
satellite radio was our witness we just pulled them into the car and said
come on we'll have the car circle and we got married and that night we had dinner
in a very small Italian restaurant totally our Italian restaurant which kind of
makes you think about Billy Joel's song it was right there 56 and 7th I believe
if it's still there could be right in here to our apartment back in the day. Andrew Gold
yeah I mean the both of us being from the music business we have so many songs that we
share together that really mean something to us when it comes to nuttools though I'll say
although not necessarily from that song per se from that from our wedding day but more from our
tenth anniversary when we really had a party because we didn't have any part we didn't
many money you know we couldn't fly people in we waited until our tenth anniversary
and then we flew everybody and had a big a big party at I wasn't able to have a place
the manner the manner in New Jersey right near where we lived among Clair Barona
and Patricia had a jealous violin player two violin players and a jealous I think
and as we retook our vows and this was a surprise for me they played you in my heart
you're in my soul by Rod Stewart and then later she sang for me the man I love so those are
some of our songs associated with the soundtrack to our collective lives thanks Ray really appreciate
a man it's great to have this record I love it this record of my life sorry I didn't have anything
to blow my nose with okay I'm you know I'm really big on history and I was just talking about
this at lunch with the reporter who's doing a profile on me for an entrepreneurial magazine
that history has taught so poorly I feel and there was this this essay on what really happened
dot com called the Rise of the Fourth Reich which was so good and it really hit home so hard
that I wanted to share it with you and I actually just want to read it it doesn't have an author's
name so I'm going to suppose that it was written by the person who does the site I don't know who
it is but let me just read this to you and of course a link in the show notes that it's
source code dot com create dot com so you can re-read it at your leisure maybe send it to somebody
so here goes the Rise of the Fourth Reich everybody likes to say Hitler did this and Hitler did
that but the truth is Hitler did very little he was a world-class tyrant but the evil actually
done by the third Reich from the slave labor camps to World War II was all done by German
citizens who were afraid to question if what they were told by their government was the truth or
not and who because they did not want to admit to themselves that they were afraid to question
the government refused to see the truth behind the Reich's dot fire refused to see the invasion
by fault by Poland as a staged fake which it was and followed Hitler into national disaster
the German people of the late 1930s imagined themselves to be brave they saw themselves as
the heroic Germans depicted by the Wagnerian operas the descendants of the fierce Germanic warriors
who had hunted wild boar with nothing but spears and who had defeated three of Rome's
mightiest legions in the Tutinburg forest but in truth by the 1930s the German people had
become civilized and tamed culturally obsessed with fine details in both science and society
their self image of bravery was both slave and slavery Germans were required to behave as if they
were brave even though they were not it's easy to look back and realize what a jerk Hitler was but
at the time Hitler looked pretty good to the German people with the help of the media he was
time magazines man of the year 1938 the German people assumed they were safe from a tyrant
they lived in republic after all with strict laws regarding what the government could and more
importantly could not do their leader was a devoutly religious man and it even sung with the
boys choir of a monastery in his youth the reality was that the German people as individuals had
lost their courage the German government preferred it that way as a fearful people are easier to
rule than a courageous one but the German people didn't wish to lose their self image of course
so when confronted with a situation demanding individual courage in the form of a government gone
wrong the German people simply pretended the situation did not exist and in that simple self
deception lay the ruin of an entire nation and the coming of the second world war
when the Reichstag burned down most Germans simply refused to believe suggestions that the fire had been
staged by Hitler himself they were afraid to but so trapped were the Germans by their belief in their own
bravery that they wield themselves to be blind to the evidence before their very eyes so that they could
not an agreement with their furer while still imagining themselves to have courage even as they
avoided the one situation most required real courage to stand up to Hitler's lies and deception
when Hitler requested temporary extraordinary powers power specifically banned under German law
but powers Hitler exclaimed he needed to have to deal with the terrorists the German people having
sold their souls to their self delusions agreed the temporary powers were conferred and once
conferred lasted until Germany itself was destroyed when Hitler staged a phony invasion from
Poland the vast majority of the German people their self their own self image depended on continuing
blindness to Hitler's deception did not question why Poland would have done something so stupid
and they found themselves in a war but Hitler knew he ruled the nation of cowards and he knew he had
to spend the money to make the new war something cowards could fight and win he decorated his troops
with regalia to make them proud of themselves further trapping them in their self image Hitler copied
the parade regalia of ancient Rome to remind Germans of the defeat of the legions at the Twittenberg
forest talismans were added from Orthodox religions and the occult to fill the soldiers with delusions
of mythical strengths and an afterlife of the fell in battle finally knowing what it takes
that it takes courage to kill the enemy face to face Hitler spent vast sums of money on his
wonder weapons airplanes submarines ultra long rage artillery the world's first cruise missile
and the world's first guided missile weapons that could be used to kill at a distance so that
those doing the killing need not have to face up to the reality of what they were doing
the German people were lured into world war two not because they were brave
but because they were coward to want it to be seen as brave and found that shooting long-range weapons
at people or they could you know they couldn't see them so it took less courage than standing up to Hitler
sent into battle by that false image of courage the Germans were dependent on their wonder weapons
when the wonder weapons stop working the Germans lost the war i remember as a child listening
to the stories of world war two from my grandfather and my uncles would served in Europe i wondered
how the German people could have been so stupid to his even elected Hitler the dog catcher
let alone leader of the nation such is the clarity of historical hindsight and with that clarity
i see the exact same mechanism that Hitler used at work here in this nation the american people
imagine themselves to be brave they see themselves as the heroic americans depicted by western
movies the descendants of the fierce patriot warriors who had tamed the frontier and defeated the
might of the British empire but in truth by the dawn of the third millennium the american
people have become civilized and tamed culturally obsessed with fine details in both science and
society their self image of bravery is both slave and slavery americans are required to behave as
if they are brave even when they are not the american people assume they are safe they live in a
republic after all with strict laws regarding what the government can and more importantly cannot do
their leader is a devoutly religious man the reality is that the american people as individuals
have lost their courage the government prefers that way as a fearful people are easier to rule than
a courageous one but americans don't wish to lose their self image of courage so when confronted
with a situation demanding courage in the form of a government gone wrong the american people simply
pretend the situation does not exist when the world trade towers collapsed most americans simply
refuse to believe suggestions that the attacks had been staged by parties working for the US government
itself americans were afraid to even as news reports surface proving that the US government had
announced plans for the image of a Afghanistan early in the year plans into which the attacks
on the world trade towers which angered the american people into support of the already planned war
fit entirely too conveniently but so trapped our americans by their belief in their own bravery
that they will themselves they will themselves to be blind to the evidence before their eyes
so that they can not an agreement with the government must illimaging themselves to have courage
even as they avoid the one situation which most requires real courage to stand up to the government's
lies and exceptions the vast majority of the american people to them their own self image
depended on continuing blindness to the government's exceptions never questions why Afghanistan
would have done something so stupid as to attack the united states and as a result
americans find themselves in the war now the US government has requested temporary extraordinary
powers power specifically banned under constitutional law but powers the government is claiming they
need to have to deal with the terrorists the american people having already sold their souls to their
self delusions are agreeing the temporary powers recently conferred will be no more temporary in
america than they were in germany the US government knows they rule a nation of cowards the
government has had to spend the money to make the new war something cowards confite the government
has decorated the troops with a galea to make them proud of themselves further trapping them in their
self image talismans are added from orthodox religions and the occult to fill the soldiers with
delusions of mythical strengths that an afterlife if they fall in battle and finally knowing
that it takes courage to kill the enemy face to face the united gut knights says government
has spent vast sums of money on wonder weapons airplane submarines ultra long range artillery
cruise missiles guided missiles weapons is a kill at a distance so that those doing the killing
need not have to face the reality of what they're doing as i mentioned above Hitler was time
magazines man of the year in 1938 stolen was time magazines man of the year for 1939 and 1942
both of these men and many others also celebrated by the media were unimaginable monsters
the lesson from these facts is that it isn't easy to spot a genocidal tyrant when you live with one
especially one from the press sports the press supports and promotes tyrants become obvious
only when looking back after they have done becomes known the German people did not stand
up to Hitler because their media betrayed them just as the american media is betraying the american
people by willingly voluntarily even proudly abandoning its traditional role as watchdog against
government abuse it is the very nature of power that it attracts the sort of people who should not
the united states is the world's last superpower is a prize that attracts men and women
willingly to do absolutely anything to win that power and hence are also willing to do absolutely
anything with that power once they have it if one thinks about it long enough one will realize that
all tyrants past and most especially present must use deception of their population to initiate a war
no citizen of a modern industrialized nation will send their children off to die in a war
to grab another nation's resources and assets yet resources and assets are what all wars are
fought over the nation that wishes to initiate a war of conquest must create the illusion of an attack
or a threat to start a war and must always give their population of powers and excuse never
to question that carefully crafted illusion it is naive not to mention racist to assume that tyrants
appear only in other nations and that somehow America is immune simply because well we're Americans
America has escaped the clutches of a dictatorship thus far only through the efforts of those citizens
who unlike the Germans of the 1930s have the moral Kurds to stand up and point out where the
government is lying to the people unless more Americans are willing to have that kind of individual
courage future generations may well look back on the American people with the same harshness of
judgment which we look back on the 1930s Germans I hack the Pentagon for self-incriminating evidence
of Republican manufactured white powder pestilence marine core flat vest with the guns and
ammo spitting bars like a demon stuck inside a piano turn a symbol into a soldier with just one
line so here's the truth about the system that a of your mind they gave out kind of six billion
dollars in 1989 and 1992 and now the last chapters of revelations are coming true and I know a lot of
people find it hard to follow this because the blame in no bigotry makes to hate my politics but
like America wasn't destroyed to buildings in a country that was sponsoring bombs dropped on our
children I was watching the towers and though I wasn't the closest I saw them crumble to the earth
like they were full of explosives and they thought nobody noticed the news report that they did
about the bombs planted on the George Washington Bridge for non-Arab's arrested during the emergency
and then it disappeared from the news permanently they dubbed the tape of Osama and they said it was
proof jealous of our freedom I can't believe you bought that excuse rocking a motherfucking flag
don't make you a hero the devil crept in the heaven go over slept on the seventh the new world
order was born on September 11 and just so conservatives don't take it the heart I don't think
bush did it why because he isn't that smart just a stupid puppet taking orders on a
the same people are sending a well stone the military industry got it popping and locking
looking for a way to justify the wolf with doctrine as a matter of fact rums fell now that I think
back without 9-11 you couldn't have a war in Iraq or a defense budget of world conquest
proportions kill freedom of speech and revoked the right to abortion acts kind of extortion
a blessing to the wealthy and wicked but you still have to enter to the arm again you scripted
and dick chain you fucking leech why don't you tell him your plans about putting your
pipelines through afghanistan how is Rayleigh troops train oh my god
Pakistan you might have some house niggas fooled but I understand colonialism
it's sponsored by corporations that's why haliburton gets paid to rebuild nations tell me
the truth I don't scare into paralysis I know the CIA so I've been Latin on dialysis
and 98 when he was top 10 for the FBI government ties is really what a government
life read it just felt instead of asking a government why because then the course of death
the course the propaganda that it died and all the way around the world is not playing the mighty
for mine and take up a deep breath my lungs still took a pass if you've got to be a good day
because it has to be stretched out my arms I say a lot my worries you've been aided
you'll end with the possibilities these are mine it feels a bloodline never so they come
hold as I swing from the bottom of the sun with time a finally feel fine days as it should be
of my own design there's no one on like me to when I'll rest sleep and dream mine to
continue with them so all that I need nine to the bad day and a hundred to be because you can't
have a good day unless you believe every day good and bad will be around for us focus on
the lessons of the politics sounds over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
all the fact that we are here yeah that day I'll come to you
you think the sun finds a little rising long shadows stretch out the brisk air flies in
I think we're in the pool cool the conversation concepts in the moment meditation though
old days playing back in my mind the whole of people and the faces in the moment at time so
well we're in smiles all the small in the misery so I find tomorrow all this become history
and we're to pop it in the mind before the war the artists know the stars oh the sunlight's a darkness
could be the dumbest ending in computer smartness and about respect between the ghost and the
fantasy I've been former in the season of the harborships on the soul of seats and they were the
hardest now and everything really bad will be a powerful answer for the song this will be the
song
Oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man
oh my man, oh my man, oh my, oh my man, oh, my man, oh my bro, oh my man, oh, my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh my man, oh...
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video,
comment from our buddy, Russ and Washington.
Hey, Curry, Russ and a lot of people.
I just have to say one thing boss of us are holding nine and seven
truth or stuff.
All right.
I'll admit, the government reports on the glass of the
world trade center and, you know,
and all that stuff, yeah, sounds like bunk.
Yeah, that would be the 9-11 commission report.
Really?
I don't know.
You know, have your right.
But one thing I have to say here, boss, is
you don't need to melt steel in order for steel to fail.
You'll lose a lot of it, Frank,
after being heated to some amount of degrees.
I wouldn't say I'm sitting in my work club right now.
So I can't just look it up online.
But you don't need to melt steel.
They want to do it in the term melt.
It is completely overlooking the fact that you can heat up
steel to a degree with both melt.
But it will fail.
And that's one of the things you see that.
These truthers need to get to their head,
that if you're still going to argue,
that'd be food and they'll come down this way.
And again, you know,
I've read the report that they've come out.
It sounds like a bunch of B.S.
But again, you don't need to melt steel.
So on that regard,
I want you to look into seeing what temperature
steel does fail with a given weight at a given heat
and temperature.
So that's, I think, in those you guys,
really need to look on,
if you guys are sorry,
if you guys are ever going to convince enough people
that there's something to this conspiracy.
Sure, there's a conspiracy.
It's a conspiracy.
It's probably too fucking incompetent to do anything about this.
And now they're trying to cover their ass
and, of course, like any bureaucracies doing a poor fucking job.
I'll believe that long before I believe these 9-11 truthers
because they're not arguing in the situation
and is sound and logical manner in my opinion.
So if you guys are really going to start
even with this subject,
I have to look there and say,
you don't need to, for example,
melt steel in order for steel to collapse.
And give me a situation where a burden
of building burned uncontrollably for seven hours
at any other point.
It could have been that this type of scenario never happened before.
So maybe we don't have a precedent to be set by
all building fires in a steel environment
have always had some type of retard in
or, you know, fire response that's so holy.
So again, you know,
you're saying there's talking about situations
really are unprecedented.
And it's certainly not helping the American people
in the government fucking up like they are
and saying, oh, look at this.
This is a possible explanation.
Really anyone who has any type of experience
knows it's a bunch of BS.
So that's my rant for today, Ciri.
I'm saying you're wrong.
Not saying you're right.
I'm just saying, if you're going to argue,
argue on something a little more consistent
and stop using these bullshit semantics like melt
and realize that certain things don't need to melt
in order to fail.
Anyway,
let's go back to you later.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
They should work for us,
but God knows they don't.
So until you give me a better reason
or you vote against my government,
I'm the least going to have to vote in the election
and it's a list of two evils,
which one that is?
Fuck if I know.
Let's have you later, Ciri.
Alright, Russ.
Russ and Washington, everybody.
Russ, I want to use that tremendous energy
that I just heard there.
And I want to direct it towards a theory
of being investigating and it sounds absolutely nuts,
but I do have some data points to back it up.
So what I want you to do,
this will be your homework.
I want you to take your attention away
from three buildings that collapse in free fall.
World Trade Center, one World Trade Center,
two and World Trade Center, seven,
which mind you had no aircraft flying to it
and still collapse in the exact same manner.
And I would like you to focus your attention
on World Trade Center building number six.
But the only way you're going to see the evidence
is if you search and I have links,
but I want this to be something you go looking for yourself.
Okay, I don't want to, you know,
in fact, I'd probably say just go to fema.org
and you can find these pictures,
but I want you to do some of the research yourself.
Take a look at building number six.
If you look at it from the street level,
you can see that there was,
there was some damage,
you can kind of see on the top as missing,
and there's definitely damage to number six.
And you would think that this is because of debris
falling from towers one and two.
Then I want you to find an aerial view,
and you will see a huge hole
in World Trade Center building number six.
But this is not just a hole of debris that fell onto it.
It's a hole all the way down to the ground,
and there is no debris.
Very much I'd like to add that there is no debris
that even shows a tenth
of either of any of the towers,
certainly of one and two.
Where is the debris?
This was a huge building,
and the only explanation of course
is that it got pulverized,
but even steel,
there should be all kinds of wreckage,
and that should be stories high,
considering these buildings were over 100 stories tall themselves.
Building six,
let's say a whole bunch of buildings
one and two fell on it and created this hole.
They would have to be debris.
But there is no debris.
There's a hole all the way down to the ground.
You can find shots from the inside of that hole
in World Trade Center six,
and you will see that there is,
yes, there's debris,
but no higher than a couple of feet.
That does not constitute this huge hole
that does not explain the hole,
or many other 24 feet in diameter holes
that you will start to notice and recognize
if you look at an aerial view of what we call ground zero,
being a big oh,
we're a hole.
One of the explanations,
one of the data points that I've found for this,
that you're gonna laugh at me
because I've brought this up before.
The correct term is directed energy weapon.
Oh, I can hear you all say,
oh man, here he goes again.
But this is not a new concept
to the United States government
and the Department of Defense.
In fact, most recently Bob Woodward
has written in his new book
that he's sworn to secrecy,
but we have amazing super weapons,
according to George Bush.
Remember, this is what Hitler also said in the final days,
you know, when he was going nuts
and about ready to blow himself up in the bunker,
oh, we have super weapons,
we're gonna kill everybody with him.
What is a directed energy weapon?
It's like a microwave.
And if you go ahead and you Google Project Blue Bean,
or you Google Directed Energy Weapons,
and you'll see plenty, plenty of stuff.
US government material.
And the proof is actually in the pudding
as witness from this YouTube clip.
I believe around 2003,
Donald Rumsfeld was still the secretary of defense
and he receives a very interesting question
for one of the reporters
during a Pentagon briefing.
Listen very closely to the question.
To the answer,
and then it'll pass it off to some military official.
And listen to what they're saying about the use
of directed energy weapons,
weapons that can pulverize material.
Pulverize it.
The question of some of the technology
that you're developing to fight the war on terrorists,
specifically directed energy
and high-powered microwave technology.
When do you envision that you can weaponize
that kind of technology?
Goodness.
It is in, for the most part,
the kinds of things you're talking about
are in very early stages.
Do you want to give anything you can?
I don't think I've ever had much,
I think they are in early stages
and probably not ready for employment at this point.
In the normal order of things,
when you invest in research and development
and begin the developmental project,
you don't have any intention or expectations
that one would use it.
On the other hand, the real world
intervenes from time to time
and you reach in there
and take something out
that is still in a developmental stage
and you might use it.
So if your question is not answerable,
it depends on what happens in the future
and how well things move along the track
and whether or not someone feels it's appropriate
to reach into a development stage
and see if something might be useful.
As was the case with the unmanned aerial vehicles.
What you know, you're going to experiment?
I think that's the point.
And I think we have, I think from the beginning
of this conflict, I think General Frank
has been very open to looking at new things
if there are new things available
and has been willing to put them into the fight
even before they didn't fully run out.
And I think that's not referring
to these specific cases of directed energy
or high-powered and microwave,
but it's sure that will continue to do that.
There you go.
Directed energy, weapons, microwave weapons.
We have them.
We're not afraid to use them.
When is the first time we use them?
Who have we used them on?
Time to do some research chuckleheads.
Here's a song for my mom
which is be smiling down on me
if you ever be play this.
It's from her air.
Come and sing a simple song freedom.
Sing it like you've never sung before.
Let it fill the air
tell people everywhere.
We the people here don't want war.
Hey there Mr. Blackman, can you hear me?
I don't want your diamonds or your game.
I just want to be someone known to you as me
and I will bet in my life if you want the same.
Come and sing a simple song freedom.
Sing it like you've never sung before.
Let it fill the air tell people everywhere.
We the people here don't want war.
700 million are listening.
Most of what you read is made of lies.
But speaking one to one, name it everybody's song.
We too in the morning when we rise.
Come and sing a simple song freedom.
Sing it like you've never sung before.
Let it fill the air tell people everywhere.
We the people here don't want war.
Brothers, souls and it's in our your busy.
If not won't you drop this friend alone.
Tell me if the man who is bound up your land
has got the warm machine on his mind.
Come and sing a simple song freedom.
Sing it like you've never sung before.
Let it fill the air tell people everywhere.
We the people here don't want war.
Now no doubt some folks enjoy doing battle.
Black presidents, prime ministers and kings.
So let's all build and show us where they can fight among themselves.
Leave the people be who love to sing.
Come and sing a simple song freedom.
Sing it like you've never sung before.
Let it fill the air tell people everywhere.
We the people here don't want war.
I say they believe that people are everywhere.
Come and sing a simple song freedom.
Go daddy I'm talking about e-m music talking about budget rent a car,
I'm talking about pet meds I'm talking about Drobo.
You can find all of these deals and links to those and the Coge needs to use in the show notes a daily source code calm.
Until we speak again my fellow chuckle heads enjoy your freedom.
And whatever you do live your life with love, with creativity and with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation stick it in your ear.