Alright, mevio, mevio, mevio, mevio, welcome to the Daily Source Code 753, brought to you by
the Daily Source Code 753, brought to you by the mevio.
Oh, well, here's the Daily Source Code 753, this is the Daily Source Code, the Daily Source Code.
Oh, well, here's the Daily Source Code, the Daily Source Code, the Daily Source Code.
Oh, well, here's the Daily Source Code, the Daily Source Code.
Oh, man, it could not be a better song to start this journey off with.
Oh, man, you know, it just goes from bad to worse.
I've talked with you guys about the 50 billion, that's $100 billion dollar.
The 50 billion, that's $100 billion dollar bailout of the banks here in the United Kingdom.
And the way that they're doing that is quite different from what's happening in the U.S. with the Federal Reserve, the Bank of England, just to summarize,
is basically going to make 50 billion pounds worth of bonds, government bonds available more than they've ever issued, by the way, as far as I can tell.
And they will swap those bonds with the bad debt that the banks have, and they'll let them hold onto those bonds for three years.
Okay, so that's the decision the current Gordon Brown government has made.
However, this article has been sent to me by at least 15 different people.
It's originally from the Mail on Sunday, written by Dan Atkinson and Simon Watkins.
Here's the deal. The Bank of England has apparently imposed a permanent news blackout on this 50 billion pound plan to ease the credit crunch.
So they're going to love this.
So they're not going to disclose the names of the banks that borrow money.
In fact, it will not be available under a Freedom of Information Act request.
Even after the 30-year period, which most all-sensor state documents are eventually revealed, employees who break the contract,
if they name any of the institutions at the Bank of England, I think they'll be drawn and quartered, and then perhaps even beheaded.
Now, I understand why they're keeping this secrecy, okay, because it's all about trust.
We're going through this before these banks are in so much trouble. And by the way, this really has nothing to do with the United States.
The UK did just fine on their own with their own little credit crunch and they're trading with everybody around the world.
So it's not like a US fever that's flowing over here. No, it's structurally wrong here as well.
Of course, the banks don't trust each other because they don't understand how much value they're securities actually have.
Or securities, the investment vehicles that are backed by mortgages. So no one wants to trade against them.
So of course, to keep trade going, that's where the government bonds come in because they're guaranteed and they have a value that'll be good.
Okay, that makes sense. Now, to not disclose those names, is a part of that trust factor because any bank that borrow or that does the swap,
and essentially says, please bank help me out, bank of England, please help me out, give me your bonds.
We'll look weak. So instead of all open kimonos, which I think would have been a much, much better idea. Still, I can understand it has to be done secrecy.
Okay, fine. What it really shows me though is how bad this problem has become. It has gotten so bad that the banks are going to the mother ship and saying, oh, well, let's keep it quiet because it's, we really don't want anyone else to know.
It's going so much trouble.
In Germany, they do it a whole different way. I think that they got the right idea over there.
Deutsche Bank, let me just bring up this article. This is hilarious.
What can I open this? Hello, here we go. You're going to like this.
Deutsche Bank, Germany's largest has been hit by the global credit crunch so badly. This is how bad it is in Germany.
It is issued a memorandum to senior executives telling them that brothel visits and adult channels in hotel rooms cannot be claimed on expenses.
Damn it. Damn that credit crunch. We can't go to the hookers anymore.
Anyway, this is all part of the government we deserve here in the United Kingdom speaking of which, you know, that is not my quote.
I didn't make it up and I've mentioned this before and Chris was kind enough to try and find the origin of this statement or quote, whatever you want to call it,
that every country gets the government it deserves because it is one of today's topics on the Charlie.
Hey, and this is Chris Thompson, so that's here. I look into some of the quotes you're using.
Demoxy people get the government to deserve.
That's often attributed to Alexis de Tocqueville, who is the French philosopher who visited America and wrote the book at Demoxy in America.
But I was searching through I can't actually find a source for that quote. It may just be one of those false quotes that history comes up with.
It's also an attributed to Jefferson.
And there's a little more another quote out there.
Demoxy is a system that ensures people are governed no better than they deserve or are governed the way they deserve.
That's by George Bernard Shaw, another unsourced quote.
So it's an interesting idea.
I just hate when you throw it on someone.
So I'm going to quote Adam Curry saying that the government didn't get the government to deserve because I heard you say it.
So I quote it.
And I agree with you.
You got to rise up, but man, that path, that's a troubled one.
You know, you know, Gandhi, you can ask dumb, I'm blanking.
But yeah, that's rough one.
So I appreciate the work.
You're blanking on some heroes, blanking on people who you can ask how hard it is.
How about Julian Aviles, Kyle Crowley, Estrella Soto, Jason Franco, Leslie D. Jackson, Bradley G.
Critzer, Michael G. Milakoulis, Anthony P. Roberts, Eric R. Seager, Nathan Z. Thacker, Steven J. Wallberg.
You know, with these are these kids, these are 18 year old kids.
The Washington Post has a site called The Faces of the Fallen.
And they give it to you right there.
You can even categorize our dead kids by age.
These are all 18 year olds.
I'd say they understand how hard it is.
Did they get the government they deserve?
Did the government they deserve to treat them well?
It's time to think about some uprising, my friends.
The shit is out of control and not right.
Not just here, overseas.
Probably everywhere.
Hey, Kerry.
Rust and Washington.
Check it out, chuckle heads.
You'll keep bitching about sign on how people don't have a voice or a ability to evote.
Oh, yeah, that may be true today.
I guess what?
When a communist revolution took hold, that was kind of the will of the people.
So yeah, right now they might have screwed themselves out of liberty.
But they got themselves there in the first place.
So let's not be so bleeding hard on the Chinese.
It may not be the generation today, but their previous generation led them to there.
And that's why we, the current generation, may not do that to our own future generations here in American Britain.
So there's a little factoid for all you chuckle heads.
So an official historian here set in the record straight piece.
Oh, we have an official historian, excellent.
Yeah, yeah.
It really is true.
You know, I got compassion, man.
I got compassion for all people of the world.
When a brother or a sister who is hurting in Africa or China or Tibet or South America or North America or Europe or the Middle East,
it all hurts.
We're all people.
This is the thing that we've come to understand.
This is the only thing that the internet has really really done well at.
It's connecting us and letting us share ideas and thoughts and forget everything else.
You know, I know lots of people in Iran now.
I know people in China that I never would have known before.
I don't understand.
I don't have any problem with them.
So we clearly got to fix our own houses.
That's what we got to do.
And man, we got a lot of work to do.
Some good responses, though yesterday to the conversation.
And I'm so happy to hear Jay Mack coming back.
Jay Mack, who was really laying into me about the government they deserve and the China had absolutely no chance
to change the ways of their government.
And by the way, we're not showing a very good example ourselves.
I might point out.
But Jay Mack's come back and just thought about it.
Mr. Curry, Jay Mack, I'm put aside.
I'm by the way, dude.
I mean, I know I'm 43 and all, but the Mr. Curry thing, that hurts.
I just wanted to call you and say thank you.
You were right.
I really, what I envisioned in my head when you had said the thing about China, the Chinese,
get the government, they deserve and you know,
they need to rise up and over throw the government and this and that.
You know, in my head I was envisioning, you know,
poverty-stricken, you know, peasants and people with sticks and stones trying to go up against tanks and Jackson.
You know, I guess I really never took into consideration exactly what you had said,
which was the, you know, like the kid in front of the tank and Tiananmen square with the, you know,
the symbolism of it all.
And you know, if people really did start to revolt against their government and there really was, you know,
math, math, death, you know, occurring.
You know, it's not too far fetched to think that someone like the United States would come in and assist and, you know,
stuff like that. I guess, I guess I was being a little bit shallow on the comment.
You kind of got to me right away and I jumped on it without thinking it through thoroughly.
So thank you very much. It's a very good point and I stand very, very, very, very corrected.
On the whole other,
uh, hold on a second before you get to the other thing.
Jay Mack, thanks, man.
Uh, it's not about standing corrected.
Uh, I'm not entirely 100% right.
And I'm just talking out of my ass too.
However, it's a cool that we were communicating, man.
And, uh, yeah.
I'm just saying.
End of the spectrum, man.
I got a quick question.
What the hell do you use for digital recorder?
Because, um, okay.
We use a computer to record everything and it's fucking sucks, man,
because everything keeps coming out, uh,
distorted and shit.
So, yeah, man.
Just to get you two fucking things from completely different ends of this spectrum,
have fun with it, man.
Take it easy.
Hi, Jay Mack.
Hoodhype.com.
Everybody go check out Jay Mack's work.
Um, so let me answer that second question.
Unequivocably unequivocalic.
Uh, without a doubt.
If you're on windows, check out castblaster, castblaster.com.
Uh, when I was on windows or whenever I find myself on windows,
that is the program of choice.
It's extra cool because it has an automatic upload to, uh,
to the media servers that features baked right in.
Uh, so I would recommend that above all.
And there's different ways to set it up, um,
and the way I've always used it is with an external mixer.
Now, um, I've been on a quest for about four and a half years now
to get everything.
All in one box on a Mac.
Uh, because it is my computer of choice.
I like it that much more.
Um, it's, uh, never quite been powerful enough to run all the shit
that I want to at the same time.
And there's been huge latency problems with getting audio in
and listening to the live signal.
And I've got all of that solve, J Mac.
Uh, CC Chapman was asking me about this the other day as well.
I put a picture up on curry dot com, uh, which you can find
the web blog there.
Uh, and you'll see it's a flicker picture of, uh, my setup,
which is I said I've moved it off of the, uh, kind of the production area,
which is still filled with mixers and all kinds of stuff.
I just wanted to clean environment, two screens, uh,
everything software and all I wanted external was just a little
MIDI controller, which I have, which is that fader fox box.
You'll see on the left, uh, the picture.
And what I still am planning is to do a screencast.
Now it's going to take a lot of work.
And I've already set some stuff up of done some trials,
because I have to do like picture and picture,
because I have to show you, um, how things work externally,
how they drive the software internally.
So it is coming and all the specs will be written up and, uh,
and then everyone can go and, uh, put these things together.
That's by the way, ordered a second fader fox device.
So I already have the six faders, which is the MIDI controller for the software
for Ableton Live.
I ordered, uh, I think it's the L, X, or LD2 or something.
And it's basically an identical, beautiful little box.
Only it has just rows and rows of buttons and lights.
We keep linking lights.
And I'll be using that to fire off, uh,
all of the carts and the voice mails, etc.
So, uh, maybe I'll wait until I have that in,
because it's like six or seven different pieces of software.
All running together and, uh, eventually we can bundle these all up
in one big tar ball or one big script, I think,
and, uh, be able to distribute it.
I hope it would be nice, because it does work and I'm very, very happy to share.
Hey, still, it's cool.
But yeah, if, uh, we'll try that again.
Hey, it's daily source code episode 753.
I had a bit of a map from Gang's Weasel.
Hope you're very well, sir.
On this week's show, we've got a review of Time Crisis 4 on the PS3.
Also on the DS, we've got the World Ends with you, a strange one there.
You can also win copies of Iron Man for the Nintendo DS,
and we've got an exclusive behind the scenes feature.
That's all at Gang'sWeasel.com.
There's what the third one of every set.
Now that's bullshit.
Now you go for a World End.
You can't check this number, not in length.
Now that's bullshit.
Then you paint, talk to what you spin.
Then you even got a paint, talk to your pen.
Now that's bullshit.
There's still one to take you in here.
English kids, wrapping them every night.
Now that's bullshit.
It's bullshit.
Extending the congestion genre.
Now that's bullshit.
Most of what you learn in class.
Especially recording the part.
Now that's bullshit.
Maybe in the funny spot.
You can choose but you ain't got a heart.
Now that's bullshit.
Every single single bullet can make a mouth.
The worst bullshit is bullshit.
It's bullshit.
Now that's bullshit.
All the tissues talk.
It's bullshit.
Holy shit.
It's all shit, the world's bullshit, it's all bullshit
It's all shit, all shit, the politicians told never do shit
It's bullshit, all the way they feed us in the news
It's all shit, plus what they teach us in the schools
It's all shit, the world's bullshit, it's all bullshit
AIDS come from Africa, it's fucking a month
It's all shit, fava come from the country
It's all shit, rapist come here when it's lost
It's all shit, what the fuck is wrong with our government?
It's all shit, read the false get last sentence
It's all shit, ask yourself why did defend it?
It's all shit, all the way they feed us in the schools
It's all shit, the world's bullshit, it's all bullshit
We invented the rockers, we were chatting, that's bullshit
It's the headweapons, we were the kids, they feed us in the schools
It's all shit, the world's bullshit, no question, no bullshit
Pretty much every rapper, that's bullshit
Like who is killing each other, that's bullshit
Especially because it's over nothing, that's bullshit
I bet my ends are not fucking that's bullshit
Look what we do to our mothers, that's bullshit
Hell yeah
All the tissues don't never do shit, it's bullshit
All the way, they feed us in the news, it's bullshit
Plus what they teach us in the schools, it's bullshit
The world's bullshit, it's all bullshit, bullshit
All the tissues don't never do shit, it's bullshit
All the way, they feed us in the news, it's bullshit
Plus what they teach us in the...
There you go, it's not spritz, it's bullshit, they're pissed off
It's all bullshit
Yes, bullshit, and I wish I knew who that was by
It was just dropped in the daily source code
Drop a drop.au slash daily source code
Which of course is completely anonymous
And if you drop something in, please add a little note
With at least tell me who's performing it, you know?
Oh, I got as a file name, not good enough
Because I want to give credit where creditors do
I really like the way that came off
Hey, let's continue on this trip
Adam Bigger, I'll ask you a second round
About anyway, my point is, everybody's wanting to talk and complain about things
Including people like you who have a ability to influence large volumes of people
But yet, nobody's willing to upset their state of affairs
They like to drive their nice cars, they like to have their nice electronics
And their nice quality of life
If we really, really believe we have problems
Then we have to be willing to make sacrifices
And that's part of the people in the best position
To influence others, and that's people like you
So, hey, put your money where your mouth is
I'd love you anyway, great hair, hope you'll win
44 married, two kids, teenagers
And three times a week, one I have to
I'll be later
Man, you'll be down too on the prostate prevention
Quotion, you need five, man, you need five, I'm at four for this week
So, I'm doing okay so far
If you don't know what that's about
You might want to go back to episodes and listen to
What that is, it could save your life
Yeah, man, you true, absolutely
By the way, I'm not quite sure what you mean by put my money where my mouth is
I think I'm doing that
I'm here to try and influence, I think I'm doing that
But you're right, you know, you're absolutely right
And you know what, we've got, we've got people who stand up in our country
And I just mentioned a whole bunch of those names, they're dead
All right, and if we're willing to send
We have to be willing to die for the same causes
I do agree with you there, if we're willing to send our kids 18-year-olds off into
Deserts and mountains to get shot at and possibly maimed or killed
Aren't we responsible? Don't we have
Responsibility to be just as ready to do that here at home?
I certainly, I certainly feel so
And of course, I'm a little torn because I have two homes
It makes me
Be kind of queasy to think
I should have to do
But right now I'm doing what I can do
But I'm old enough to say I think I am prepared to really stand up
But nothing has really been organized right just yet
And I'm hoping one day I'll stumble upon that and we'll get something going
It can't be far off because I can just feel that people are getting a little bit antsy
But stuff is not working exactly the way everybody wants
And a lot of that has to do of course with how we're being raped by the by the big oil companies
How they're taking all these wonderful profits and
literally
Literally
Screwing us sticking us with the bill. There are solutions though when we've got some months to help us out here on the daily source code
Adam
I think for God that you have an energy savant for the Charlie
Two days was a talking about energy crisis oil company profits biofuels and money
And not even a call out for atomic rod atoms. I am so hurt
Your gold bugs a lot of many about currency. But he has a little idea about what really makes the world work
If oil cost
120 dollars per barrel that daily value of oil transactions total more than 10
Building and dollars
That does not even include the amount this bent to transport refined and distributed to oil products
And it completely ignores the other fossil fuels like coal and natural gas
If we really want an energy alternative we have to stop thinking that the sun and wind are going to do the job
And look around to see what has proven that can replace gas and coal
Electrical power plants and oil on board ships and submarines like the ones I used to operate
Vision is the way of the future
But we have to work together to get the notion past the oil coal and gas companies
They are pretty darn happy with the way things are if you want to learn more visit atomic insights
Or the atomic fuel go blue go atomic folder blue feel great there hope we all went love you meet more than five
Possibly protect your freedom and seek the truth behind the news
Ha ha
Dominic Rod everybody
Hey, you know, I'm still waiting for my backyard nuked dude. I'm I'm way on board with that
I think that we've certainly improved the technology enough to use it and it is a stigma that is that lies on the whole nuclear or atomic
Just those two words in general
Obviously have really horrible connotations
I like you said so you said efficient in there earlier, which of course is probably the
The technical term for
For this process what if we could bastardize that a bit what if we called it fusion set of fish and it can we technically do that?
We just say fusion because fusion fusion energy you know that sounds kind of sexy
It sounds like you know like melding together and fusion
It's as a multicultural type vibe
We need to rebrand atomic and nuclear energy, okay, so let's work on that part first and then of course
There's no incentive for big oil companies to and and the governments that that subsidize them
Because they're all in the same boat together, so I did it may very well be that we have a fantastic solution right there at a fingertips
And and correctly if I'm wrong rod and I love that you're making it under a minute and a half these days, but
isn't fusion a lot cleaner wouldn't that help with the
Climate change and all those other issues that were so incredibly worried about I mean
Sounds like there may be a campaign to mount there and we'd have to draft some really smart people
Stuff to think about for sure that's wrap it up with this one. This is this is from a couple weeks
Actually, yeah a couple weeks ago and you know I keep all these voice comments and
And sometimes I just roll them out when I feel let's appropriate
Like because we use blackberries and not so much and we're
Accessible on email so listen my friend. I don't use that stuff
I like my email and my computer, but I don't need to take it with me and I don't ever feel the need to answer every email that comes my way
People send stuff and it can wait so small if there's even if there's stuff to work
I might look at it. I might not log in some time back the next day
Cares it's just our own business whether or not we answer emails all the time
We do not have to be a slave to people to say answer my email
Unless somehow your boss says you have to in which case
You know, I guess you don't have to work for them anymore. Do you just before my friend, but that's where I'm coming from
Make very much all the good
Like to hear to you. All right. Bye. Yeah. Absolutely
You know, I've started doing a lot of that. I've started doing a lot of just not answering email because the you know my rule is the less you send the
Let's you receive and that really does hold true. It is truly a law of physics somehow
And I've also stopped
We've talked about this before. You know, I go to the Google News site and lately it was I'll do it with you for it as an example
Just to show you how I save time and aggravation throughout my day because
Man, you just got to hear Google news. I'll show you what what do we have on Google news today is the headlines
Which of course is it's the only news?
US economy expanded in 0.6% pace. I might read that when GM post big loss as US sales hurt
Might not click on that here's the stuff all
I'll definitely miss
Miley Cyrus should apologize
Gary Durdand bust and loose from CSI
Prince Williams afghan flight a PR exercise
You know that kind of shit. Don't waste your time on that just if you read the headline you know what the story is gonna be
You know don't worry you won't look incredibly stupid in fact
I you know when you're at a cocktail party and you don't know the latest Amy wine house room roomer
I think you can you can chill out because
I'm finding more and more the people are very interested in very willing to speak about
some of the topics that we talk about right here on the daily source code
In fact I got some kind of exciting news. I told you earlier that earlier in the week that
British telecom was going to be installing some lines here at the house now these are digital
digital lines which would be hooked up to some high-tech
gear
Basically for anyone who technically wants know what it is. It's ISD headlines and I'll have a what is known as a codec
And that's that's actually a box that has the software. It's the software and the hardware all in one
So I can establish a high quality connection between here and the Netherlands because check this out
There's a guy who
My phone ring in there. No, there's a guy in the Netherlands who's and he's kind of an interesting guy
He's been around for a long time
He's about my age
There you go. Been around for a long time and he's he's purchased some FM frequencies and
These things are not cheap so I'm not going to share how he's doing it where he's getting the money from but he's he's got a real
Pirate radio vibe about him and he's been listening to the daily source code for a number of years
And he said you know Adam I believe you know podcasting in the Netherlands is not big
And the reason why is because they're oversaturated with radio stations
But you know, there's a huge gap in between the
Everybody good morning
I was bang on the drum all day morning shows
Where we're laughing about popular culture and then what they considered to be news radio and and this with 15 stations in a country with only
16 or 17 million people and the size of Rhode Island
That's a lot of media a lot of media to consume when I guess that people
Feel they have enough where there's this huge hole and I believe well actually so this guy approached me
I can tell you who he is right right at this moment and he said I believe this format that you have on a daily source code
Will translate into a local market in radio
You know the the idea of bringing up topics that
30 to 40 year olds care about and luckily some 20 or even younger
Your old like and he wants to try and experiment and I got to tell you my my crush is itchen to do this
So he wants me to contribute to
To a show it'll be a morning show
And of course, I'm not going to go live in the Netherlands so I said yeah
I can do it from here
We're wherever you know shouldn't be much for a problem. We've got connections. You know we can do it over the internet
We can do it through a high
High quality line that should be no problem. So we're spinning that up and we're going to test these lines out
And then we're going to you know work be work on the format, but literally the format that we've developed together
We're going to try out on terrestrial broadcast radio. I'm pretty excited about it because if it works there
Well, then I'm just my work in many other places
And as you know, it's not necessarily about the distributions about the ideas the thoughts the interaction and the community at least that's what it is for me
To anyway, so no one knows oh no one has heard about that yet. It's it's been kind of my secret project
But I want you guys to be the first to know that that's going on and of course it will not affect the daily source code or no agenda
Because I love that shit way too much
That's mellow and out of and holding on to this song for a couple of weeks it showed up on the drop the baked potato blues
Chill out enjoy
Plains
Lots of baked potato
Butter and me up and down to now, God
Oh, I've got a big but shadow blue
You can fall me back, me but don't mistake me
Life is falling down, it's been like a sun
You take me through the town
You wrap me up and fall
Take me home and put me in a bag then
So I don't fall down
You're like a potato that ain't no job
Lots of butter sell, I could even try
All right now baby
You're like a potato that ain't no job
I'm talking to my skin, stop me once, stop me twice, stop me three times
And through some day, my life will be gone
Ah, they never had particularly do they?
Take potato blues.
Yeah!
Yeah, not just don't hear enough of that on the radio, not do ya.
Absolutely not.
All right everybody, that's it for the Daily Source Code episode 753.
Thanks everybody, by the way, who congratulated me on 750, that kind of kicked in earlier this week,
even though we're now up to 7503.
Doesn't look like I'll be able to do a show tomorrow, probably not Friday.
Either some company my lovely wife to, to her first live show as I already mentioned before.
Definitely a no agenda this weekend.
You can look forward to that in next week.
Looks like I'll be here, but you never know where I could show up.
So please think about all the things we've talked about,
and if you're walking around healthy and free,
I live your life with passion and enjoy that freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation.
Share it with a friend.