Delta Shared Charlie 813
16 billion dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk
I'm guessing it's a matter of theory
Delta was there, divided with fall
Come on now people, let's get on to fall and work together
Come on, come on, let's work together
Now now people, because together we will stay and never fall
Never for a little man
People and people are home and they come home
We all end up through you travel and they stay
All over you, let's work together
Come on, come on, let's work together
Oh, you know who gather people stand
Never for a little man or man
Oh, we all end up through you, let's work together
Come on, come on, let's work together
Now now people, because together we will stay and never fall
Never for a little man or man or man
Oh, come on, let's work together
Come on, let's work together
Now make someone happy, make someone smile
Let's all work together
Let's work together, let's work together
Come on, come on, let's work together
Now now people, because together we will stay and never fall
Never for a little man or man
Oh, we all end up through you, let's work together
Come on, come on, let's work together
Now now people, because together we will stay and never fall
Never for a little man or man or man
Yeah, baby, hey, what's that?
Ah, damn microphone
Ah, it's going to be one of those shows, that's for sure
Come on, everybody, let's work together
Daily source code episode 813, coming to you from the affluent suburb of Suri known as Gilford in the United Kingdom
The very last episode from here, I presume
I think they shut the internet down tomorrow or Tuesday
All right, experimental show, very excited about doing this
I got inspiration early this morning
Actually last night when I saw a news article
Actually it's an editorial piece in the telegraph
And he invited Kingdom about global warming
And I figured, you know, here's an opportunity to roll out the stream live
Which we know that's working, we got hundreds of people who have already been testing this with us
Hundreds, let's see, not quite as many as yesterday during no agenda yet
But still quite a bit of people checking in on the stream
This of course is being recorded as episode 813 in a series of programs
And we've got the phone bridge up and working, I just want to check it for one second
Now the way this works is if you dial in and all the instructions are clearly posted at curry.com
We'll be talking a lot about the phone number in the system and how it works
And if it's actually functional at all, the remember my quest is to find a way to have an entire radio station in a box
The box being my MacBook Pro and everything pretty much being either in this
Maybe, you know, of course you have to have three external devices
One is headphones, the other is a microphone
And the third, in my case, is a MIDI controller which gives me physical faders to work with
And some services which are remotely located, so I'm using Skype and currently using Talksue as a switchboard
At least that's the way I'm using it, so if you hear that you are unmuted, that means you're about to go on air
And New York, I just want to test the quality with you
Hello?
All right, so that's an example of how we wouldn't want it to work
Louisiana, how are you doing?
Is Louisiana on?
I have a feeling this is going to be a rousing success, yeah Louisiana, who's this?
So the idea is when you hear you go, actually, the little voice will tell you, I'll give you an example
What it sounds like, hold on, here we go.
And we got to, as I played the song for a reason, we got to work together to actually make this flow
So when you're in the call conference room, and you have to call a telephone number, then use a pin code
And if you're not a member of Talksue.com, then I can see where you're calling from
And at least it results in United States geography, probably not anywhere else outside of the states
But you'll come in, you'll be on mute when you hear this.
You are unmuted.
That means I've just opened up your line, and I'm about to call on you, so you'll be ready to talk
So get your Skype headset on or whatever.
It's not a very effective way to listen to the show to just sit in the talk room, hold on.
This is what happens when I take you off air.
You are muted.
Okay, got it.
So it's not a very effective way to listen to the show.
If you're just going to sit in the Talksue room and listen.
Certainly, if you're not going to be ready, because I will call on you if you're dialed in.
So, lots of things to talk about.
Is this, is this actually efficient?
Is this the way you want to do it?
But I just got to make sure that we can actually get through one show with some questions coming in
or some comments or contributions, I guess, is what I'm really looking forward to from the source code listeners.
Play one more song.
I'm going to read this article, which will be the topic for today's program.
And then hopefully we'll get some feedback on the voice lines.
Dinen Spells.
You money just tell me what you want me to
God, money, now me, I guess or
God, money, don't want anything
Once it all, now we all can't say
No, you can't take it
No, you can't say
No, that's because of you
Because of you
And I see you
That you really pay me
Now I can play ...
And I see it
You in yourайт
It's got you
That you really pay me
I can write down
And I see it
You really pay me
I'll tell you
For the one
You Lorna You girl
Young
I ruin thee
Again
Watch
Teacher
I'll tell you for the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
I've got money's nothing for the country
God, money's like a surfer
By the second one of your
God, money's less
Dancing on the back
So the rules are God, money's nothing
One choose
Know you can't take it
You're right for me
Know you can't takes it
Know you can't take it
Know you can't catch all
Know you can't
If you get it, if you get it
Know you can't take it
Know you can't trade
If you get it, say it
Down before the world you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Down above the world you serve
Down below the world you serve
That's let's return again once
Make it welcome
Let it go
Let it shine
Get a show
Let it all
Let it go
Let it shine
Give it a show
let it all
Let it all
Let it shine
And I know, like in the sky, like in the sky
Give it time, give it time
I'll tell you for the one
You're going to get what you deserve
Nineteen skills
I'd like a whole daily source code episode eight one three
Source of course in this entirety from
The source code drop drop.au slash daily source code
I got a couple of people who've dialed in
I really don't know if the phone lines are going to work or not
It's entirely possible that my Skype connection has too much latency
Because I'm also sending this stream out simultaneously all from the same
Very pathetic internet connection
Which is going to change in just a couple of days
God willing
That is if British telecom sources the phone lines properly
And it gets everything ready for our arrival in the new house
Anyway, here's what I want to talk about
So if you want to call in
There are instructions you can find them at
TinyURl.com slash dsc live
There's also posted on curie.com on the homepage
But maybe it's just easier to go to tinyURl.com
Slash dsc live
There's informate while if you're hearing this now
You're listening to the recorded podcast
Which means you a phone lines are closed
You can call but you may be charged
And you won't win, you vote won't count
I would also like to say oh yeah so and then there's
Information on if you're listening to the stream right now
There's information on how you can call in
And I'll give you one song in a second to call in
If you have questions, comments, hopefully contributions
So we can have an actual dialogue
So here's the article that was published in
The telegraph in the United Kingdom
From Christopher Booker
Who's a columnist for the telegraph
The title which of course caught
Everyone's eye
2008 was the year man made global warming
Was disproved
And I want to read
About three quarters of this article
With you
Because I totally agree with with what he's saying
And it sparked a big debate in the comments
I can see this 439 comments already on the
On the article online
But it's important that we
At the very least discuss the crux of my objection
To the global warming hype
Because I think there are others out there who maybe just
Haven't quite figured out exactly why
It's bothering them or what is that little
Thing nagging it in the back of your mind
So hopefully we'll get to that today
Looking back over my column to the past 12 months
One of their major themes was neatly encapsulated by two
Recent items from the daily telegraph
The first on May 21st
Headlined climate change
Threat to alpine ski resorts
Reported that the entire alpine winter sports industry
Could soon grind to a halt for lack of snow
The second on December 19th
Headed the Alps have best snow conditions in a generation
Reported that this winter's alpine snow falls
Looks set to beat all records by New Year's day
Easily one of the most important stories of 2008 has been
All the evidence suggesting that this may be looked back on as the year
When there was a turning point in the great worldwide panic over man-made global warming
Just when politicians in Europe and America have been adopting the
Most costly and damaging measures
Politicians have ever proposed to combat the supposed menace
The tide has turned in three significant respects
First all over the world temperatures have been dropping in a way
Unproductive by all those computer models which have been used as the main drivers of the scare
Last winter as temperatures plummeted
Many parts of the world had snow falls on a scale not seen for decades
This winter with the whole of Canada and half of the US under snow looks likely to be even worse
After several years
Flatlining
Global temperatures have dropped sharply enough to cancel out much of their net rise in the 20th century
Even Schiller and more frantic has become the insistence of the warmest
Cheered on by their army of media groupies such as the BBC and the last 10 years have been the hottest in history
And that the North Pole would soon be ice-free as the poles remain defiantly
Ice-bound and those polar bears fail to drown
All those hysterical predictions that we are seeing more drops in hurricanes than ever before
Have infuriatingly failed to materialize
Even the more cautious scientific accolades of the official orthodoxy
Now admit that thanks to quote natural factors such as ocean currents, temperatures have failed to rise as predicted
Although they plaintively assure us that this cooling effect is merely
Masking the underlying warming trend
And that the temperature rise will resume worse than ever by the middle of the next decade
Secondly, 2008 was the year when any pretense of there was a scientific consensus in favor of man-made global warming collapsed
At long last as in the Manhattan Declaration last March
Hundreds of proper scientists including many of the world's most eminent climate experts
Have been rallying to poor scorn on that very consensus
Which was only a politically engineered artifact based on ever more blatantly manipulated data
and computer models programmed to produce no more than convenient fictions
Thirdly, as banks collapsed and the global economy plunged into its worst recession for decades
Harsh reality at last began to break in on those self-deluded dreams
Which have for so long possessed almost every politician in the western world
As we saw in this month's Poznan Conference when 10,000 politicians officials and
quote environmentalists gathered to plan next year's son of Kyoto Treaty in Copenhagen
Panicking politicians are waking up to the fact that the world can no longer afford all those quick
Quick sock that quicksodic schemes for combating climate chains
Which was they were so happy to indulge themselves in more comfortable times
Suddenly, it has become rather less appealing that we should divert trillions of dollars,
pounds, and euros into the fantasy that we could reduce emissions of carbon dioxide by 80%.
All those grandiose projects for emissions trading, carbon capture, building tens of thousands more useless
wind turbines switching vast areas of farmland from producing food to biofuels
are being exposed as no more than enormously damaging and futile gestures
costing astronomical sums we no longer possess.
As 2009 draws, it is time we in Britain faced up to the genuine crisis now fast approaching from the fact that
unless we get on very soon with building enough proper power stations to fill our looming energy gap
with in a few years our lights will go out and what remains of our economy will jutter to a halt
after years of infantile displacement activity. It is high time our politicians along with those of the
U.S. of the EU and President Obama's U.S. were brought back with a mighty jolt into contact
with the real world. And then he goes on with a couple more things about other
columns that he's written which don't relate to what he's saying here.
So I love this. Anyone who listens to the daily source code pretty much knows my
stance on the global warming hype. I'm just bringing up some notes here.
And what I like about this article is it almost almost connects all of the dots which is where my
true objection comes in which is hopefully what we can talk about today. You see you got to connect the
dots between the financial crisis which now I personally believe it was probably engineered but
that's neither here nor there. It is here. We know the severity of the financial crisis. We're
probably only halfway through all of the crap that's going to come out. This made off
rogue Pipponzi skiing pyramid based fund is just really I believe the top of an even bigger
pyramid because all of Wall Street appears to have been built on this basic principle of not really
creating any returns but just suckering in more money or printing it and then sucking it in
and handing it out to people as if it were profits. So you have to take that financial crisis where the
dollar which is basically a belief system. The dollar is a piece of paper. Now hold on.
That'll help. The dollar is basically a piece of paper and it stands for something. It stands for
a value which is a belief system. We all believe it. The numbers are published. We all buy into it.
That's okay. It's a belief system. You can do it with sticks, twigs, branches, gold, silver. Anything
you want as long as you we all agree that that dollar has some form of value. So that paper has
value across the world that is still the reserve currency. It's what oil is traded in for the majority
and other currencies are pegged against the dollar. I think we can pretty much agree on that.
Now this belief system is coming apart at the seams. The Chinese don't believe in the dollar anymore.
We've seen the dollar devalue although it was not done actually in a devaluation move but we've
seen what's happened. It is going to go down even further. And of course we have the European
Union now conspiring to introduce a new form of financial system which of course can't be based
on probably the dollar at all but certainly not on these derivatives. So they have to come up with
something else. Enter the global warming solution which is to reduce carbon dioxide emissions.
So by reducing these emissions we're going to save ourselves from peril and doom and death
and destruction. And let me just say as a side note, I totally want to have some alternative form of
energy. I've been looking for that for a long time and I think we should absolutely be treating our
earth in a much better way. But what I do not believe in is taking this carbon dioxide emissions
story that it is these the reason for our planet heading towards ultimate destruction and fixing it
by creating attacks because carbon credits, which is there's an article on the drop today about the
bovine flatulent tax. It's no joke. The environmental protection agency is actually considering
doing this because your cowfarts it has carbon dioxide in the farts. You got a bicarbon credit. So you
got to pay for that. It's going to be like 125 bucks per cow. So the question is how do the carbon
credits work? Well, the concept is you buy carbon credits which means you can produce an x amount
of carbon dioxide and apparently on the other side of the equation somewhere someone down the line
is going to produce less carbon dioxide because you basically bought that right from them.
That no one really talks about that side of it. All you hear about is what it's going to
cost. The interesting thing here is that it is my belief that you will be buying your carbon credits
from the bank. Maybe from the central bank, maybe from the federal reserve, but that system
will that those carbon credits will be used as a form of currency, something that we can peg
other currencies against and of course it's a beautiful instrument because the bankers can decide
how many carbon credits they want to print up as it were. It'll be exactly the same. They can
use the same spreadsheets they use for the dollars. Let's put carbon credits in there. The
big difference here is that they control the supply of credits and you won't necessarily affect
the economy of a country by creating more credits. You do create the economy of the bankers
and they're wealth and how much more money they can collect. So that basic premise is what where
my objection to this whole global warming, hype stems from, add on to that that I know a lot
about weather. It's very hard to predict. I deal with it all the time as an airman and I don't know
many people if any at all who can predict the weather more than 48 hours in advance. Unless there's
some extreme circumstances, maybe a couple more days, let alone years in advance and more over
all the predictions have been exactly the opposite. So I'd like to know what you think about all of
this. It's important that you contribute otherwise, uh, oh, what the heck am I doing or for? Just
listen to me, uh, pontificating. Curry.com has the information on how to dial in your phone calls next.
The rises as hard cries. That's the law we know now. We're occupiers. The world's
good up, scores down, and he's a higher. Prova's a low-ass soon as we go. As a rich,
white straw, I beat my shade of sol.
Take from the home, beauty, yes, take home
To reach the souls, narrow wide glass of goods
Still holding the walls to run before and more
And when we come close to the country
They kiss their ammo, they call it road rock
But it's a deep machine, it's so so
So close to the country, yes, take home
And when we come close to the country
They kiss their ammo, they call it road rock
But it's a deep machine, it's so so so so so so so so so so so so so so, so so so so, so, so, so so, so good
It's all done, we plan everything, we're the color of skin on the skin
We're in Lexland, ducks there at us, and soon as we begin
He went up the frame of thought there were it
I can't use it's got to do with the feeling
It's not where you're from, it's can they you live
The stuff we brought, and if we are given, a piece of the mud
Connect, we're ready
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's all done, we plan everything, we're the color of skin on the skin
It's all done, we plan everything, we plan everything
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, well, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Power water, rice soup,
I love it, proud, proud, proud
I'm just thinking about
how this phone system is going to work if it's going to work at all.
I just want it to be completely mobile.
I don't want to set up 10 phone lines, but why can't it all be virtual?
And why can't it all just run from my Mac?
It should be able to, but it's going to require some habitual changes I think in the way people
deal with calling in and participating in shows like this.
Urban Dan Squad, by the way, a deeper shade of soul on the episode 813 of the Daily Source Code.
The last one coming to you from the Curry Manor, although there will be one more show for the new year.
Our good friend Ray is put together a year and overview of all the shows from 2008.
It's fantastic. He'd put a lot of work into it.
It's going to go up on on the feed probably, probably the 31st, depending on if I do anything before that.
So we're talking about this article in the telegraph.
Of course, talking about carbon credits and looking forward to getting some form of feedback on the phone lines.
If you want to join in, go to tinyurl.com-dsclive.
All the information is also posted on the homepage at curry.com.
Let's see if we can get a check on here.
It's about 3350.
You know, we've got to have been following for quite some time here.
And the tie in with the financial community.
I mean, no expert in global warming or anything like that.
But I love your tie and I mean, you just think that I mean, the euros and the dollars.
I mean, they're actually going to start to possibly migrate over to the whole carbon credit thing.
Is that what this is probably all about?
That's what you can almost, I mean, look, I'm a conspiracy enthusiast without a doubt.
And I love putting those kind of dots together.
But when it actually starts to show up in the policy they're discussing, because you remember the European Union had a meeting in
Was it end of November there?
And they gave the United States a hundred days to join in with their plan.
And when you read the plan, it has carbon credits all over the place.
So if they're talking about the financial system and a new financial system they want to integrate.
Remember they did that like they were calling it Bretton Woods, too.
And everyone was getting together all the finance ministers, which of course is not really no more than a photo up.
Because it seems like it's pretty well laid out.
And yeah, the carbon credits, it's certainly a form of global taxation.
That's obvious from just from what it is.
But to start mentioning that in documents that deal with the financial system and whatever they're cooking up now.
And it can only mean that it's going to be integrated.
And it makes so much sense to me that this would be the way they would do it.
It could it could be anything.
But they just need a belief system.
You know, back in, I don't know, the thirteen high rates.
Yeah.
You say the one that's called the spreadsheet from from what we have now.
It doesn't make a difference.
It's all meaningless.
Yeah.
In history, if you go back to 12 or 1300s.
They used sticks with notches in it.
This is, and that was a form of money.
You just need a belief system.
One thing I know for sure is there is a lot of belief about global warming.
And I'm not denying that the earth changes, of course.
NASA just came out and said, hey, man, the solar winds are, that's kind of messed up.
Things have changed.
You know, it's got to be some influence there on the weather in general.
Well, like here in Chicago, just the other day.
I mean, it was kind of crazy.
I mean, we had a windshield of 20 below.
And then just yesterday, I mean, it was.
It was 55 degrees.
That was going outside of my t-shirt.
So, you know, that was just a couple of days spread.
I mean, there's definitely something crazy going on there.
But, you know, I've checked the John Coleman stuff.
You know, that you've pulled stuff there.
And I think it would be great.
I mean, he said, nobody wants to talk to a mainstream media.
It doesn't want to talk to him.
He was on this red eye show or whatever that I checked on YouTube.
You know, maybe get John Coleman or, you know, something on the,
Well, first I got to learn to start.
First I got to learn to start the show off without putting myself on mute.
And then when I graduate to the big leagues, then I can invite guests in.
So give me a couple shows to figure it out.
Hey, Chuck, you've been really nice, man.
If you don't mind hanging on, I'm just going to grab one or two colors.
Because people are stacking up.
I want to make sure everyone gets a shot here.
Luke Nova, you're on.
Luke Nova.
Okay.
We'll try the next line.
A line list that is non member.
I must be a foreign call.
Who's this?
Now, look.
This is Mark in the middle of the.
Hey, Lawrence, was that your name?
Mark, M-A-A, Mark.
Mark, how you doing?
Your, your comments on this, this fantastic article in the, the telegraph.
And, I think we should.
And, I think you have to be lying out to, but it's not like that.
Now, it's, that's probably just a Skype delay.
So what do your, what do your thoughts on this article?
And what's the article you're talking about because I missed the last part.
All right man, no problem.
Go to curie.com.
The article is on the home page.
That's what the discussion is about today.
And we're trying to get some feedback from source code listeners and droppers, a
like LG Latte, I think, you're on?
Hey, I don't understand.
I'm not serious.
Are you okay?
Who's this?
It's Liam.
Liam.
I am.
How are you doing?
Yeah.
We're the Skype calls.
We're just going to have to deal with the quality.
You're comments on the article.
I'm not going to come in on it because I've been away from the PFC.
I took a stream of, like, really, when you started getting into all the heavy
stuff.
But this is especially a factor, just like, ringing and happy testing, say, I.
Okay, man.
I appreciate it.
That's very cool.
Take a look at this article, though.
It is written by a fellow compatriot.
It's very interesting.
It's in the telegraph.
It'll be in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Crossposted at curie.com.
It's already up there.
You can take a look at it.
It's a pretty damning article about the, the hype around global warming, California, you're
on.
Ah, Adam, how's it going?
Good.
Who's this?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Randy, how you doing, man?
It's not on the show.
It's my job.
But yeah, definitely about this global warming thing.
There's only, you know, I agree with you.
It's definitely not me or me, but there's one good, good news to it.
And you're seeing countries like Brazil will get a credit back because they actually
grow trees.
So, you know, I guess there's some incentive to do some good too.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, that's, so you grow a tree.
What does that mean?
You can, they'll pay them if to grow trees, I mean, accredited someone pays real money
for it.
So, who's getting the money?
Where does that go?
Brazil just gets a little mark on their spreadsheet and tree or do they get some actual
cash?
I think it's probably more of a mark, but, you know, there's no actual cash in the system
anyway.
Right on, right on.
Right on.
You know, all about, you know, at least you can grow your own credits, right?
They're still good news to it.
Well, that would be, now, I have to say that would be very interesting.
I wouldn't mind having the opportunity to grow your own credits, you know, that would
be a system that I might even be able to get behind.
Because that would, that would certainly change the way the way people think about the earth
and what they do with it.
That would be fantastic.
All right, Randy.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to play another song here.
This is something that, let's see, that was left on the drop, which was, let me just
find the, here we go.
Under the heading, bagpipe punk rock, hey, Adam, love your shows.
Try to spread the truth, just as you do, just wanted to send some good punk rock with
bagpipes, drop kick Murphy's and the real Mackenzie's.
All right.
And now, if you dial into the phone bridge on TalkShoot.com, you'll be able to hear this
as well.
Yeah, nice.
The real Mackenzie's smoking bowl, bagpipe punk rock on the Charlie can get much crazy
of that.
I'm wondering, by the way, if my talkback system, if that actually was broadcasting live
on the stream, which is not the intended functionality, that could make total sense
of that was taking place.
I've got to look into some of the, some of the wiring here.
Let's see if we can get a couple more calls.
We're talking about this article in the telegraph of the United Kingdom, which you can find
at curry.com on the homepage, nor the New Jersey are you there.
Hey, Adam, how's it going?
I'm actually going from New York.
Okay.
Well, you show up as Northern New Jersey.
But I guess that's kind of the same thing.
It's a new Jersey cell phone.
Okay.
Who's this?
This is Ray.
All right, Ray, your feedback, input, comments, contribution.
Um, yeah, great news about the article.
I think, you know, we've got to spread the word and pile on top of it.
Otherwise, it's just going to get pushed to the side of this guy.
We've got to wrote it.
It's just going to be, it's credited in marginalized, you know, if we get more mainstream
support for this idea that global warming, you know, is a hoax, to further push along
the, you know, this sort of new world over agenda, then, you know, maybe we've got, you
know, maybe we can fight that a little bit better.
You know what I think, I think the, the main thing we have to do is, whenever something
like this shows up in the mainstream, this is the opportunity to show it to your friends,
you know, mail this link out and just let people read it for themselves, you know, the
whole problem is is that there's lots of good, you know, I say there are no secrets
only information you don't, don't yet have.
There's plenty of good articles being written.
There's great journalism being performed, if you perform journalism, not quite sure, but
this great journalism is taking place and, but it's just not enough and it doesn't show
up on the home page or on the front page or above the fold and this is the stuff we just
got to say, hey, man, you know, read this, take a look into the link, you know, it's
easy enough to send on, it's easy enough to, God, everyone could Twitter these days,
just have a read, you know, and there's, there's lots of comments below, which I like
that because there's pro and and against pro and con, the article, but I think that,
that's the main thing people can do is just to get this awareness out there because people
pick up on it, you know, then you're thinking about it, then you might see another article,
that's really what I recommend.
Well, I appreciate to keep up with the look at it.
All right, man, thank you very much for calling.
Thanks for participating in the test and I look forward to hearing from you in a future episode.
I want to go back to Chuck for a second.
Chuck, you said you were in Chicago.
Hey, Adam, Chuck again.
Yeah, you're in Chicago, right?
Yeah, your originator of love, you mean it great here.
Hope you wouldn't Chuck from the Northwest side of Shai Town.
I bow to you and homelessness, my friend.
I bow to you.
Hey, Chuck, so what's the scene like in Chicago right now?
Of course, the next president is coming from your, were you born there?
This is your hometown?
Yeah, hometown.
Yeah, it was a pretty big deal with, you know, the whole Obama thing.
Quite a great scene until our governor, Radlegoy Vitch,
came this year a couple of weeks ago.
I mean, he's denying the whole thing.
So what are, what are people on the streets?
And what are the jokes that are people making?
There's, I mean, are people just cynical about this?
And they shrug their shoulders and let it go?
Or is there any outrage to people understand what the implications are?
Yeah, I mean, basically that, you know, just, you know,
through throughout my circles and people I talk to and co-workers and things.
I mean, they're, they're saying it's surprising that it hasn't happened sooner.
His wife is, as a real estate broker and, you know, apparently she's had a lot of real estate
dealing through, you know, contributions and things from political figures.
Yeah, it's, you know, it's Chicago politics.
My father-in-law said this is like the sixth governor he's seen, you know, in his lifetime,
from the Illinois that's been indicted.
So it's, I guess, really isn't a situational.
Really? Well, I've read a lot about the so-called, you know, the Chicago mob.
And we're not just talking about gangsters.
We're talking about, you know, the real gangsters, I guess,
a mayor daily would be a part of that whole clan.
And, you know, that's been running for a long time.
And it, it, I don't know, is there any, so that's what your dad says.
Or there are other, you know, other, other people out there who are thinking that way,
talking that way, any more historical references to Chicago.
Because when you see these things happen, you've got to think.
You just, you just got to stop and think, uh, maybe this is not just one case,
maybe it's kind of the way things work.
You know, look at the Hillary Clinton's seat in, uh, in Senate, in New York,
looks like Carolyn Kennedy's going to get that, you know, you know, how did you know?
I mean, um, you know, uh, they read it a month for some reason.
I don't know if it was to draw attention elsewhere, or, you know, um,
Adam, what can I say, I mean, there's actually, um, there's a book up and you link,
my father was actually got some historical, uh, information with, with the way things ran back
in, oh, back in the 60s, or so, with Chicago politics.
And, uh, he's got all kinds of stories directly related to Mayor Daily's father and, uh,
okay, it's a good stuff like that.
No, excellent. I'd love to, uh, to get that link from me. I'd love to read up on it because, uh,
I think there's a lot of history there that needs paying attention to.
Adam, I wanted to say, too, um, we've got to connect here to, uh, Dr. Carl Hodges and, uh,
the Seawater Foundation. Okay. We had that, uh, I'll send you the link, but, uh, he's definitely
on the frontier of, you know, the climate change, and, uh, he works with, uh, Jakku Sto's daughter,
Alexandra Kusto, who's quite the babe. They had a presentation here, um,
back in November, um, that, that actually one of my co-workers went to and he said it was excellent.
So, I'll get the scoop on that, you know, it'll have to, and maybe we could get him, you know,
I'm one of these, uh, toxic things in the future. Once you get moved into the new pad.
Excellent, man. Excellent. Well, send me that information. Send me a picture of her,
most importantly, and, uh, I appreciate you calling in, Chuck. And, uh, we'll talk to you, sir.
Okay. All right. So, you mean, you can hear how it went.
Yeah, I love you. You mean, I love you. I love you. I love you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't stand a camera so I can
And I touch it in the face of place
I'll pay fire, I'll protect it
I'll never touch it, go to this place
I'm a church, it will come make a breeze
The thing that's wrong, they won't be far yet
Much, a glorious rainbow face
Fall that round, pick up the colors
And it wraps us while we're safe
I'll make fire, I'll protect it
Never see the glorious face
But I can't stand a camera so I can
And I touch it in the face of place
I'll pay fire, I'll protect it
Never see the glorious face
I'm a church, it will come make a breeze
Fall that round, pick up the colors
The end is over, wrap them up
ship in a source card episode number eight hundred thirteen
Those of you who are on the screen heard it works and all and those of you who heard the podcast version
You just don't forget stuff you cut out all the food cut out all of the mess in the Bible
I actually had the phone on you
Okay, good enough test. I think tomorrow I have something on it
Again, we've got a month tomorrow and Tuesday base for the moon
So look out for that ray on the trolley
That's the only thing I'm gonna put up on when the new pad with all the new band with I think I have to set up pretty much figured out
We'll be able to do maybe one issue a day
So I think starting around four or five o'clock in the day is probably a reasonable time
And it's a third or four in the pay time
It's a eight in the west post
So you pick up another couple of four you go to work
Maybe it's, no, maybe it's better if we do it at five o'clock
Five o'clock people are still kind of wrapping up their day
You know you really don't want to work in the UK that last hour you just kind of fuck off and listen to the Charlie live
Maybe a dial in west coast 9 a.m. you're not really ready to get to work yet
So you know you listen to an hour of the Charlie live just to get into your day
New York it would be noon. Hey man, you got an hour until lunch because no one eats at noon anymore
So you might as well mess about and listen to the Charlie live and of course
Well, Australia we don't have to worry about because the show will soon be banned there
Okay, talk to you soon if not talk to you in the new year again
Keep the feed keep your eye on the feed for that ray on the Charlie year and spectacular
Highlights from 2008 from this program daily source code
Have a look at our sponsors page that lists that on every single
Every single entry every single episode in the show notes a daily source code dot com crosspost that a curry dot com and of course
Keep everything flowing through the drop seven eight pages a day. I love it. I can't get enough of it. You should be enjoying it as well
Drop.io slash daily source code
So use that freedom wisely while you still have it and live your life with passion
Another fine media presentation stick it in your ear
You
It's just your fault, it's just for a sense of hope
It's just for a sense of hope
I saw the fire, it's all over
So let's do it again
It's all over, it's all over
It's all over
You