Delta Sierra Charlie 806
You're 16 billion dollars worth of airplane strap US
To the next generation radio caught any layers
I like to think I'm flying into the future
I'm dancing
It's a very beautiful sunset
It was routine
I love you back
Not be off my feet
Let it all go
And you know
I'm so wild
I need no coffee in my room
Let it all go
What's it?
I'll get there
Let it all go
Thanks so much
And want to smile
While it smile
How I know
All the real things
Are open
Yeah Feel that love
Only because
A night
Only when
The door
Look that way, let the child get made my day a little bit
What makes it a little bit, what makes it a little bit
What makes it a little bit, it makes it a little bit
Look that way, let the child get made my day a little bit
What makes it a little bit, what makes it a little bit
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, come to the toilet.
Hey everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the Charlie episode number 800 and sex coming to you from the affluent suburb of Suri known as gulford
Where the weather is not nice at all. It's a blustery
We would say lots of win, which is why I'm here and not on my way to the Netherlands
I was going to join my bride lady Patricia for
Her Friday night live show. I thought I'd go hang out there and look important kick tires
You know
With nothing to do except get my wife water and a protector dressing room door
Which I love doing carrying her bag
But yeah, it's just shit. It really is this like gusting 40 knots. So
You know
Certainly something I could fly through but why bother and it may not be much better tomorrow
Either anyway that gives us the perfect opportunity to roll out the second daily source code this week
Check it out. What's been happening since last we spoke which was Tuesday. Oh, Wednesday. Of course. This was the big
The first piece of monument monumental effort. I had to put into the ring here
As a part of the move to the new concept, which it is as of yet unnamed
I kind of like curry terrace
Because it is a terrace house or as they say an end of terrace house
It's on a square so I kind of like curry square
We got to think about that
But anyway, that's coming up. You know by I think December 29th we're moved into the new place. So
Besides start to clean up my crap upstairs here on the third floor of the manner
Which I've really been putting a lot of thought into it and I've pretty much
Decided that it's just going to be one 19 inch rack. I'm gonna finally break down and buy an actual rack probably one that's enclosed like a case
As long as I've good access to the rear panels
Put the stuff in there that I actually want which is really only
Maybe five pieces of gear stuff that is just great outboard gear that I know
I'm gonna need you know when Patricia wants to do something and then I won't have it
I have one two three five mixers currently up here in use
Which is ridiculous so I'm gonna break that down. I'm gonna bring it back to one
One mixing console which will be the Yamaha MG124 CX
Charlie X ray
Because that can pretty much do everything I want and then for the rest it's
It's all gonna be digital
I mean right now I'm 100% digital on
Creating the daily source code as well as no agenda
There's no external gear whatsoever except for a headphone and microphone and the microphone of course that I'm using is this love mic
Which just for some reason has fantastic dynamics and I until I get everything into the new place
I'm just gonna use this sit up and then I'll really start working on
unfixing all the all the sound and ground loops and God what else have you
So of course on wins that we had to go to storage and this is amazing because we've had stuff in this storage
Since we moved to the United Kingdom, so that's been
Working on four years now for almost five years
And I didn't miss a single thing. I knew there was stuff there that I wanted to keep and I had these long drawn out
Conversations with Patricia and I was like well, what do you keep and what don't you keep this?
You know, there are things and nicknaps and pictures and books and stuff that I hope someone would find of interest when I'm dead and gone and
She's quite clear. She says no, it gives a shit
It doesn't care about you. No care about me. There's a look. I'm now 59. She says
You know, it's like no one's ever asked for that shit. I never look at it
So I had a mission to find a number of things one is a VHS player
Desperately looking for one of those an NTSC VHS player or preferably a multi-standard
So I can digitize a couple of VHS tapes that I have
That are pretty funny and I want to put up online
That's actually the one thing I could not find and I wanted to find my stamp collection
My coin collection, which the coin collection passed down from my grandmother on my mom's side
I love that coin collection. It's not huge, but it's an American coin collection, which is nice
My watch collection, which we also dug up and then there were a number of pictures and a couple of things that I'd collected over the year
So really only one box of stuff that that I actually wanted and all the rest I mean there were boxes of wires
There were boxes of shit that
You know, wires and adapters that had no hardware
Connected to it anymore as far as I could tell you wind up with a lot of power adapters in your life
So all of that gone
Also there were just maybe 30 boxes of admin administration from previous companies and you're supposed to keep all that stuff for next
You know X amount of time. I think it's maybe seven years, but this has been about five years
and
As far as I'm concerned
All the lawsuits have come and gone everything's clean so everything's being shredded and
Disposed of and it felt good. It did take several hours. It was a lot of work a lot of Patricia stuff seem to stay stick around
Some furniture and we also do just you know giving furniture away give it to Oxfam
People don't buy a second hand furniture anymore
Even though there's some really good stuff that we essentially wind up giving away
And that's mainly because of places like well like Ikea where we went that afternoon
Incroyed in which is you know a good hours drive from Gilford
To pick up
What was it Patricia had me? Oh, I man. She's really good at this. She had this whole
Clositing system design. She knew exactly how she wanted it and so but that you know that of course took several hours
So that was Wednesday yesterday went into the city into the shortage studios
Pod show London
Recorded some more me VO today links which is pretty much the show that I'm now doing when you log on and be VO.com
It starts playing it's kind of a highlight of what it what's on the network that day and I sneak in a couple things there
From time to time see if you can catch him
Just just floating out some minor messages to to the yet to be converted charcoal heads
All right, so let's talk about some nut nutty shit that's going on
Across the globe a starting off in the United Kingdom
Which is there's some really funny stuff happening
Which is very clear how it works and what it's being done for the big thing that's a big news
Is now they're making the
Making speeding even more expensive and penalizing you more in the United Kingdom drivers cod breaking the speed limit by more than 20 miles an hour could face a six point penalty
Under new proposals
Which I think is pretty much after that you lose your license so you know for just speeding a little bit you could lose your license
And of course what the news won't tell you is that they're also going to be jacking out prices on
On these speed cameras and they're gonna be set tighter because really as far as I can tell
This is all about just bringing in more money into the coffers
And I wonder I guess in a way. It's it's kind of good if they if if they they being the government if they decide to
You know get more people off the road. What they say this is about is about
2,946 deaths they want to reduce that number
That's the annual death rate on British roads that that's the guys under which they're
implementing this where they haven't implemented yet, but I guess
I guess that's the consultation paper that's been doing the rounds
So if if you take people off the road then I guess in essence they still have to pay road taxes if they want to keep their car on the road
I don't know, I don't know, but it seems like this is one part of one big scheme to make more money and
The proof is in the pudding as we go down under to Australia
Red flex traffic systems
Has record profits amongst the economic woes G I wonder why it turns out that
Countries around the world the United States now getting into the game
Following these 6,000 cameras to monitor 60 million people in the United Kingdom
And it's on the rise these these things are money machines
That's it's it's literally right here in the numbers. Excuse me, well, I take a sip, yeah
Hmm
You know this does it actually slow you down on the road? Yeah, does it kill less people? Yeah, probably, but the main
The main driver behind this is money and so now everyone every government every council every
State all need money and this is one of the ways they're doing it
So
Just got to be more careful as you're out there driving don't exceed the speed limit. Yes, Lady Patricia
I'm looking at you. Hey, by the way down in down under in Australia. I love these guys, man
Here's a get another reason to go in north Queensland
An Australian holiday resort will hold a month long nude anything goes party
Aimed at combating the global credit crunch
I like this. Ah, you guys are crazy. Let's take in place in March nice
The white cockatoo resort in Mossman
And it's been inundated with inquiries. Yeah, no shit and anything goes resort for an entire month
Ah, March. I wonder if I could make it before in the march
That would be just fantastic. So that's what the Aussies are doing
Meanwhile here in in in the model land in the United Kingdom
Another governmental move. Okay, it's okay to to buy sex from prostitutes
But it's not okay if that prostitute is a woman who is trafficked or is being pimped
by a drug dealer or otherwise and
ignorance will be no defense
So I really got to think about this so essentially you have to get an affidavit from your sex provider
Because that's really what they are
Yes, are the women who are being trafficked and put into sex slave trade absolutely
Man and then just like any other industry
That needs to be rooted out and authorities need to take action
but penalizing good customers of
businesses and be they you know single owner operator businesses
Or in in a unionized form like a brothel
He's good
You know I grew up in Amsterdam. I grew up in the Netherlands. It's no big deal now
I must say that it's
The combination of prostitution and drugs
Has been and always will be a problem
But it you know, but there's a lot of really good legitimate businesses out there providing services to people that
Quite frankly, I think drives down a lot of bullshit in the rest of society
Domestic abuse
People abuse verbally abuse people at work because they're sexually frustrated
In a country where the divorce rate is one of the highest in
Europe
Team pregnancy at an all-time high. I mean come on. This is why 1314 fifth-year-old your old boys
They need to go to a hooker
That's good for them. That's what we've all did. That's how we all grew up to be healthy boys and girls
Notice that they never never ever talk about women soliciting sex
Which you know just to be fair it should be persons who are trafficked and persons who
Buy sex from persons who provided, but of course, it's never like that. It's always that's always men
So hey, man
I don't know I got to talk to Patricia again because you know the way it's looking
Australia's looking like a better place. They speak English there too and at least they got these month long nude anything go
Girl in casting with Adam Curry this this is the
Hey Adam, hey, do we yeah, I'm good. How are you man? This is hit this number 148
I'm going to start right away with intro number one
Oh
Man, it's I'm thinking kernel Abrams, but that's not it. It's a jackmaster phone jump
Farley who fun something like that
Frankie goes to Hollywood
Shit, what's the name of it Frankie goes to Hollywood at that and number three
Now I want to just go songs
Got to have a j-o-b if you want to be with me no idea who sings it. Oh, man. I'm sucking today and it's time for the answers and this week
They're all from
And this is answer number one
Yeah
Farley
Here comes
Look at her round.
Love can turn around.
Finally check my totally check my number one.
I'll take one star.
And this is answer number two.
Frankie Frankie goes through Hollywood.
I love it again.
Like the head of a humble young young strong
The wings of tomorrow.
Raise hard.
Here goes the.
To the right.
Raise hard.
Frankie goes through Hollywood.
Raise hard is answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
This is Gwen Guthrie.
Gwen Guthrie.
My.
Nothing in love the springy.
That's why I'm asking you.
What can you do for me?
I've been loving all and all and got the rims.
She's got to have a game.
Oh, me.
If you want to be with me.
Yeah.
Nothing going on.
But the rims.
All right.
I'll take three stars.
But I have a game.
If you want me with me.
Gwen Guthrie.
Ain't nothing going on.
But the rims.
And that concludes hit number one.
Four.
Eight.
Almost one.
So Adam.
How did you do this week?
I at least got one star out of every set of three.
Or the three sets.
So three out of possible six.
It does that.
Me the other.
It's the place to find the answer.
I try not to start.
And it also finds the links to iTunes.
So you can buy the threats featured on the hit list online.
Okay.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening.
Next week.
I hope to be back for another hit list.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And remember, try to think with your hearts.
Bye bye.
Be back.
Hit test.
She will.com.
info.
www.unpolet.com.
www.npolet.com.
Yes.
The organization for preservation.
For the soundtrack of our lives.
That's it.
That's what we do that under the auspices.
The hit test.
It's at least once a week.
Sometimes it's none a week.
And then twice a week.
Depending on how the show slipped.
I think you're much young.
Great.
I love it for Friday.
Good songs, by the way.
I was talking about Australia earlier.
And got an email from.
And he's actually been trying to help me out with an Australian trip and getting in touch
with some folks who are into the alternative energy stuff down there.
And actually, for me, this email chain from John Christie at Lute Tech.
Those are the guys that made these.
He's one of the inventors of the free electricity generator.
You know, the one where you hook it up to a small week powered battery.
You get that thing spinning.
And then all of a sudden it spits out, you know, killer watts or mega watts of power.
And these guys, they really must be onto something.
They really must be because he, he sends back after this beautiful,
the email that Phil sent him.
His John Christie emails back.
Sorry, mate.
We're just too busy now to handle our current rate of interest without trying to get more.
Thanks all the same.
They don't even want to talk.
I can understand a bit the whole world is falling over.
But all right.
Well, how about an update, guys?
You know, free publicity, free promotion here.
Once you can sell something or whatever.
And there's some other interesting news.
A lot of this, by the way, of course, comes from the drop, the source code drop.io slash daily source code.
That's where you can, you can pretty much go there three times a day and get fresh news and enjoy it.
Stuff that you, that isn't the mainstream and a lot of the articles that we point to.
And when I say we, it's the community of chuckleheads, you know who you are.
Stuff that we point to and a lot of it is mainstream news.
It's just it doesn't really catch those big headlines.
So it never gets into the into the public mindset, if you will.
This is, this was actually kind of cool.
And of course, all these links can be found the daily source code.com.
Just check under the episode for today 806 or crosspost that at curry.com.
A title of this article from new scientists.com.
Plumbing the oceans could bring limitless clean energy.
Very good read.
I'm not going to explain exactly how this works.
But essentially, by using different temperatures at different depths, you can create a renewable energy source.
As it says here, that has the potential to free many economies from their dependence on oil.
There's one thing I do know, we got a lot of ocean.
And a lot of water in the ocean, a lot of stuff we can do with that.
And I encourage you to take a look at this because the results are astounding.
It actually around, I think around 19, when was it here?
In the first flush of success, because this stuff does work.
Just not, you know, completely experimental.
The US Department of Energy began planning a 40 megawatt test plant off of Hawaii.
In 1981, the funding for ocean thermal technologies began to dwindle and dried up all together.
And 95 when the price of oil began to drop eventually falling below $20 a barrel.
And this, of course, is part of the danger that we must be on the lookout for.
That we don't forget that we don't take the price of oil to be of any importance to our energy future.
It's finding cheap energy that anyone can essentially make.
Did anyone can harness?
That's how we free ourselves from the shackles from the true owners of the globe.
Forget about if we're going to save the earth with CO2 emissions dropping, et cetera.
Forget about that.
What's really important is we need to be unshackled, unshackled from the energy elite.
Well, that kind of sucked.
That was supposed to be.
Hold on a second.
Let me try that again.
Unshackless.
I can't get the same emotion back.
Unshackless from the energy elite.
A comic strip.
Sorry about that.
So yes, be commanding.
Hello.
If you know not all people are slender like myself, some people are fifth peaks.
I guess he's calling himself a fat pig.
So they are afraid of getting naked, particularly in public and the good news.
But that's okay because now everyone's going to be naked.
Just come on down to the 54.
Come on down to the white cockatoo.
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
That's where y'all can be naked, whether you're fat or not.
Hey, by the way, whenever you get a whole bunch of people together, I'm just a whole
lot of second comic strip blogger.
That's actually beautiful because you know that naked people, we've been trained
what naked people are supposed to look like.
First of all, naked guys, if you think women have been stigmatized and if you think
women have been portrayed a certain way in the media, try men.
Guys naked generally, not a good look unless you're, you know, look just women.
Most guys are not like Brad Pitt.
We're not like George Clooney.
We're not like Will Smith.
Okay.
When we're naked, we're just not.
And conversely, guys, women aren't like Angelina Jolie or Aaron Burnett.
Oh, man.
Oh, Aaron.
Damn.
I love it when the market is crashing like yesterday.
Oh, man.
That's when Aaron's at her sexiest.
Anyway, just enjoy each other for each other.
This external stuff.
That's got to stop.
I mean, that's destructive.
Just in destroying our kids too.
Anyway, I'm sorry, CSB.
Fat thin, tall, skinny, whatever.
Love y'all.
Love you too, CSB.
You, for this Fat Fat Fat is that new airport scanners that would show people naked,
immigration officers are not coming after all at all.
Oh.
Hold on a second.
So those, yeah, that's the new scanner they're implementing.
Where you can actually, it's like an x-ray.
And then you can see right through the person's clothes, see if they're concealing anything
underneath.
And the pictures I've seen, I don't know if they're real or not.
But it pretty much, you're looking at naked people.
And my case in point.
And with the pictures I saw, no George Clooney's.
No Brad Pitt's, no Angelina Jolie's.
And certainly, no Aaron Burnett's.
In other story, Poland has set to French proposal
about CO2 emissions trading scheme.
I quote,
What the hell does that mean?
In it.
Pan Nintendo.
Yo.
What the hell does that mean CSB?
Vatére, Futra, La Cache.
Ah, I wish I could understand French.
Tére, Futra, La Cache.
Frégan, Schim.
I quote,
Vatére, Futra, La Cache.
Ah, sounds like.
In it.
Pan Nintendo.
Yo.
Yeah.
Let's talk a little bit about that.
I definitely want to talk about digital money.
Before I forget, a little promotion for a new drop site that popped up.
If you want to find out more about, I guess, hydrogen alternative energies.
Drop.io slash.
Hydrovolution.
Lots of YouTube videos.
Lots of interesting inventions.
Link in the show knows the daily source code, of course.
And this thing that I found off of, like, oh, someone put this in.
No, I think I found this on a Boeing Boeing.
This kind of freaked me out.
Apparently Apple, the Apple video card and monitors are speaking some kind of digital rights management
protocol when they're talking in HD.
I'm reading the article here now.
And I think it was at the HDCP control.
What is that?
High definition copyright protection or some bullshit acronym like that.
But if you don't have an officially approved monitor or a non-compliant monitor, then the HD video just may not play.
And it's happened to a couple of people where this is actually some of their monitors.
And, you know, it's, I guess it's kind of like, remember when Microsoft came out with plug-in play and everything was supposed to work together.
And it was all about the drivers.
I guess that's kind of the problems we're going to run into now.
You can't just hook up any old display to your to your Mac.
But I just thought it was kind of kind of weird, you know, that it's come to this.
Because now they're in, basically, would you call that a subsystem?
They're in the hardware bits of our computers now.
I mean, the Hollywood establishment.
And I bet you're going to make money off of the sale off of each of these HDCP controlled units, something like that.
In fact, the title of this is Apple to Mac owners throw away your monitor if Hollywood says so.
Yeah, that's pretty nasty.
Okay.
Some finance and economics.
Oh, man, I used to hate it when my teacher said that in school, and now I'm just loving it.
And the Fed.
This is kicking off tomorrow, Saturday.
It's in 39 cities.
You can find information about them at endofed.us.
The Federal Reserve, along with every other central bank, is truly at the root of all of our problems today.
In the United States, we have a constitution, which clearly lays out.
It is allowed to control the money.
And what money is, is even defined.
Gold and silver coins, not paper, not fiat currency.
And our money is consistently being controlled by central bankers, the reserve banking system.
That's how they got themselves into this shit hole, which we are merrily just handing out the money.
Just handing it over to them.
They're gobbling it up and giving themselves bonuses and businesses usual.
So if we really want to get to the root of this problem, we've got to end the Fed.
At very least, we should audit them.
That would be a good start.
That's what Dr. Ron Paul is going for.
He's a little bit more moderate.
But I do see him on this website and the Fed.us.
If you can go to one of these rallies, I suggest you do.
It's a very strong statement.
And, you know, what momentum is building?
And this is a good step.
Because politicians are representatives who you also need to bring into this game.
They're not really very smart.
You know, not like they're dumb, but, you know, they're no more educated than you and I.
They don't really understand this banking system.
You know, there's, I heard Ron Paul talking about someone who's on the banking or the finance committee.
The other day, or, you know, a couple weeks ago, said to him,
Well, it's not our money backed by gold.
You know, it doesn't even know that in 1971 or whatever it is.
In the 70s, the American moved off the gold standard, Bretton Woods busted.
There's nothing backing this money, which is why we just keep on printing it.
And it is a problem that's existed since 1913 when the Federal Reserve Act went into play.
And if you go back in history, it is one of the reasons we actually separated from the United States.
We separated from the United Kingdom in the first place.
Those of you around the world, please look at your own central banking system and come up with your own cool slogan and website.
And the ECB, as an example.
END, the ECB.EU.
All right, talk about that bailout.
Oh, man, this is a beautiful YouTube video, which I'm just going to play a little bit of.
This is James in in hope, I think you pronounce his name.
He is a senator.
And just I'm just going to play a little bit.
This is from C span.
It's a mainstream channel.
You can listen to this all day long if you want to.
And listen to how he wants to stop now, stop the bailout spending.
And he's actually introduced a bill to do that just that.
So if you support this, then you need to go and call your representative.
This is really what it takes because these people, they just need input.
Eventually, if it's a thousand to one, like it was with the bailout in the first place.
And they brought down the phone systems and they jacked up the websites.
So you couldn't email anymore.
They would be the people who wanted the bill to go through at all cost.
Threatening, using threatening tones to senators when they were mulling over weather to vote for this package or not.
Hey here, let the senator speak from self here.
Hold on a second.
You're not hearing that, are you?
I'm sorry.
I mean, you know what I did?
I forgot to start up in a central part.
Oh man, well, I have to re hijack this whole thing off.
Okay, hold on a second.
I'm going to go through the motions here.
Whenever I want to bring something in from the web browser, then essentially, I won't keep trying.
Essentially, the way I do it is I use audio hijack pro, but if you don't have the instant hijacking in place or whatever that's called,
then your browser has to quit and restart to get, why am I telling you this?
I'm just trying to delay.
I'm just trying to delay until it starts up again.
Okay, here comes the senator about the bailout.
Mr. President, given the recent news about Secretary Paulson's execution of the tarp program,
I'm firmly believe action is required by Congress.
This morning, I introduced S3683 as legislation that would do two things.
Mr. President, it would freeze any of the amount of money of the first $350 billion that has not already been expended.
And secondly, it would change the process by which we would access or Secretary Paulson would access the second $300 and in $50 billion.
Well, so that's the basic.
First came to this.
That's basically what he's what he's up there for.
A conference call.
Listen to this.
On that conference call, it was September the 19th.
President, he's going to talk about how Paulson freaked our representatives out into signing this bill.
Listen to it.
That time he was talking about the crisis that is upon us now.
We have to do something.
We have to do something big.
It's got to be $700 billion.
It has to be done right now.
The only way to do it is to buy troubled assets.
At that time, I asked some questions.
One question was, well, if there are assets, they're going to be bought.
What is the criteria that will be used to determine which assets should be bought?
And there was not an answer to that question.
First not.
Second question was, which institutions that are holding these assets would be the ones who would be eligible for this for this buyout?
Well, I'm not going to tell you.
There were no answers to that either.
Of course not.
Well, that's not a priority.
They don't actually have to tell you.
That's in the Federal Reserve Act.
The Bolsheet from 1930, how much longer do we have to live with this?
We're almost at 100 years.
Stop the insanity.
And as the next few days went by, we had several conversations.
I didn't have any personal conversations with them except in one conference lunch.
And that is, is this the only way to do it?
Yes, it's going to have to be buying out troubled assets.
And they still, the answers were not there to those questions.
Now, in my statement opposing, I voted against the policy plan last month.
In my station opposing it.
I laid out three primary reasons why I voted.
All right.
So that's more homework.
You'll find the link in the show notes at dailysourceco.com.
And if you live in Oklahoma, call up Senator James in hope and tell him he did a good job.
Congratulations.
You got to give some good too.
And anyone else who gives a shit?
Yeah, you can contact your Senator, your representative.
Send him this YouTube clip because they don't know what's going on in the Senate.
All the time, not everyone's there.
For sure.
Because we can make this change.
I guarantee you.
Meanwhile, in the mainstream media,
a CNBC Peter Schiff, who we've talked about and played stuff from on the show before.
And he is really killing over there on CNBC.
And they just, they can't stand what he's saying.
He's essentially saying the same things that we're discussing here on the Charlie that you read and
Oh, the stuff you read on the source code drop.
And stuff that Dr. Ron Paul says.
And these guys, they really get offended by it.
In fact, I'm not quite sure this is some one of these panels.
Panel shows is probably on the evening.
One guy says, and what did you think of the play, Mr. Lincoln?
You know, like you doomsday say, well, the guy has been right.
His name is Peter Schiff.
He predicted this.
This collapse in 2007.
Markets collapsed right back in 2006.
I've been making the rounds out there in cyberspace.
Turned out he was right on the money.
Here he was on CNBC.
Way back in February of 2007.
Aren't you looking at the glut of houses on the market for sale with no buyers in the
collapse into subprime market for on the verge of a major major recession.
It's probably going to start by the end of this year.
Maybe early next year.
The housing market is just beginning to unravel.
We're seeing the tip of the iceberg here.
And that clip was from before the initial signs of the subprime crisis in the summer
of 07 and the record highs above October of 07 leadership.
It's a present of Euro Pacific Capitol.
He is the author of the way.
I'm not quite sure who this presenter is.
This Asian woman.
Stop shouting, bitch.
You're irritating.
Little book of bull moves in bear markets.
He is here tonight in a fast money day view.
Peter, great to have you with us.
Thanks for having here.
What do you make of what we saw today is this sort of the capitulation that we've been waiting
for in this market.
The capitulation is probably the most over-realized word on CNBC.
I've heard every day for months.
I think capitulation if we get it is years away.
So don't be looking for it.
What is the worst case scenario for our markets?
Our markets are going lower.
This is not just a financial crisis.
This is an economic collapse.
Our entire phony economy is collapsing around us.
This guy is going home.
He's just stopped, but they should get away.
And we let it happen.
So other than that, I'm still like it.
I just feel like the play.
Look, you have to understand.
That look for the past.
It's amazing.
These guys that like, they do not want to believe it.
I guess they just don't understand how anything works.
If you watch this entire clip, it's about six minutes.
I'm not going to play the whole thing here for you here.
It's just funny.
And Peter Schiff is just boom, boom, boom, boom.
He's throwing them out one after another.
And the guys that acting like he's like he's some genius.
He's just saying, look, it's simple, simple economics.
This is yesterday when the Dow dropped 444 points to 7552.
I have a bet riding that it'll hit 7286 before Valentine's Day.
I'm going to have Ron as my partner, Ron Bloom.
He's like, no, this is great.
I was going to rebound.
I'm like, no, man, this thing's going down.
The dollar's going down.
Of course, right now, the dollar's looking fantastic against the euro.
And the, and the, and the euro to pound ratios.
Like, one 18 now, I mean, this is unprecedented.
So I think that Peter Schiff, you know, and he's just, he's not a magician.
He's just looking at the evidence.
And he's saying it's going to drop even further.
And I have to say, unfortunately, I think he's right.
Of course, there are many of us who believe that this is all pretty much orchestrated
and said into motion.
Well, you hear there is the nice little, little blips from MasterCard.com.
This link dropped on the site on the source code drop as well.
Our new money, which, of course, will not be at all paper or
course, certainly far from coin.
It'll be digital.
And MasterCard is coming out with a pay pass.
You can go.
I guess it's already implemented now in, uh,
select locations around the United Kingdom.
You just tap, tap and go trademark.
To pay with MasterCard pay pass, you simply tap and go.
MasterCard pay pass will change the way you pay for items under 10 pounds forever.
No waiting, no queueing and no fumbling for change.
Just tap and go.
I got the little tapping goes on.
Where is it?
I want to hear that again.
Yeah, playing tap and go.
Let's hear the sound.
You've been assimilated.
One more time, please.
Yes.
We have you on record.
Thank you.
You have used four credits.
You know, you know, my take on that, right?
About carbon credits becoming money.
Now, this is not a news article.
This is from Atos Origin.
And they're huge IT consultancy firm.
And this is a press release from then.
Ground breaking trial proves carbon emissions can be managed like money.
Gee, really.
Atos Origin, an international IT services company today,
deals that feedback from the first ever trial to enable real-time calculation of personal carbon emissions.
Demonstrates a willingness and readiness to measure such emissions.
Ah, the pilot initiated by the RSA and using, who's the RSA?
Say, no, this is stuff you got to go on and check RSA.
Doesn't even say with the RSA, the Royal Something Association?
A built using Atos Origin technology, bullshit, Microsoft,
focused on measuring the carbon emissions from individual use of road fuel.
The trial highlighted key conclusions.
Let me just see.
So they're saying that, here we go.
The pilot, they're already in the pilot stages here.
The pilot tested five options for capturing personal carbon emissions.
And this is, we're going to get down to carbon credits.
That's the money we're going to be using.
All you need to do is just phase out the money part.
Carbon Carter proposed national card to be issued to all citizens to provide consistent capture and reporting across the UK.
This would be likely to require significant new infrastructure of money across all parts of the fuel purchase of transaction process.
Now, this gets better.
And debit cards and pre-pay financial cards provides large-scale current coverage.
It looks like I got to find out who RSA is.
I need to do some more research myself.
Find out who these guys are and why they wanted this pilot initiated.
I'll bet she has royal something.
Anyway, what we're talking about carbon credits being used as money,
we have something much better.
We have credits in the form of reduction on all kinds of awesome products from...
Oh, man, what do we have?
Budget rent a car.
We've got eHarmony now.
What you need to do is go to www.meviooffers.com.
That's where you can find all the best prices on some excellent services.
Can't get a better price online at any time just use my code,
or, you know, which you can find in the show notes at datasourcecode.com,
or use any other person's code.
Because I don't get the money anyway.
If I was getting paid for the shit, then I would actually be begging you.
And of course, our old favorite, we currently do about 50,000 transactions a month for these guys.
What a great partner.
They are fantastic as a sponsorship and advertising.
And really helping support or doing a building up a new alternative media industry, GoDaddy.
Hi Adam, it's Brennick, this reality podcast.
Just drop in your quick line to say, thanks very much for your GoDaddy discount codes.
I've just dropped a huge amount of money on GoDaddy for services and used your discount code.
And it's brought things down very nicely.
So, you know, supporting you, supporting them, loving you.
And, uh, trying to keep it real.
Take care.
Alright, Brennick.
Thank you very much, my friend.
It's highly appreciated.
I've been talking in my hands lately when I'm waking up.
Well, my tongue is tight.
I've been thinking I should leave instead of waiting for the time is right.
I've backed the bags under my eyes.
Well, I've seen enough to know what it's like.
Just turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's written, me down.
Looking at the inside out.
Well, my rules got changed somehow.
Maybe it's suicide.
To stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
Till now.
I've been walking in my hands lately when I'm waking up.
Well, my legs are tight.
I've been thinking I should leave for the window of it's a marathon.
I've been dreaming I could fly it.
Well, I'm free enough, but I'm still waiting.
Turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's written, me down.
Looking at the inside out.
Well, my rules got changed somehow.
Maybe it's suicide.
To stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
Till now.
I've been afraid to just walk out.
And I know where to stop me now.
It's turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's written, me down.
Looking at the inside out.
Well, my man, I'm making a lot of emails from the blatantly.
So I've been doing the careers doing well.
But gentry and old friend of the church.
Just stick around the church.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
Charlie hands.
Oh, till now.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
When everything's written, me down.
I've been afraid to just walk out.
That's the guy who should be on American idols.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
You would kick so much ice.
Oh, till now.
Bob Gentry upside down.
Daily source code episode 806.
Taking you into the weekend with a footballer Friday festivities.
Yeah.
Oh, the beautiful song that is.
The bailouts are just laughable at this point.
I hope you've been following along with some of the C.
Span coverage more of these hearings, which is just funny.
And now, of course, I love the way.
This is this is now taking place in all industries all over the world,
except the one that really counts, which is banking,
in particular central banking and financial policy.
So as a citizenry, it doesn't matter if you're in the United Kingdom,
or if you're in the United States and the UK here.
You know, it's like, hey, we're going to get these bastards who are making way too much money.
Who the fuck do they think they are?
And so they grab a TV host, Jonathan Ross.
Well, by the way, it doesn't make too much money for his talent.
But, uh, or for the marketplace, let me put it that way.
But that's what's happening.
Now in the US, so the automakers, they say,
oh, and we're going to die if we don't get to any cash,
because our cash burn is about to five billion a month.
And so that means even though they've got money coming in,
they're still burning five billion a month.
So that seems like there's some deficit there in there in their business plan.
So they want to be bailed out.
And what do they do?
Schmuck's.
They all take their private corporate jets down to Washington.
And these, I looked at some of the pictures.
These are serious.
This is a serious hardware.
And these are $40,50 million jets.
You know, at a cost of, I don't know, maybe eight grand an hour.
Got to spark one of these babies up.
I mean, I know venture capitalists have their own airplanes,
and they've gone over to China to get investment for their funds.
And they're talking to the sovereign wealth fund.
So, you know, like the Chinese state,
and they fly commercial, they're not stupid.
You know, guys, you know, oh, man, how dumb can you be?
But of course, that's being attacked immediately.
I think there is, there is some kind of in-between way that, you know,
these guys would scale down, so they at least could afford the pension plans for their workers.
And then let new industry come in.
Let new companies hire workers who are already pre-skilled at, you know,
sure there's some things you won't, some positions that won't be needed as we move to
electric or other forms of non-combustion base transportation.
But it's what has to happen.
You know, someone is going to get hurt somewhere.
And people will go in and out of jobs.
But as long as we're building towards something new,
there's going to be jobs.
That's just my humble opinion.
And of course, the auto industry isn't really about cars.
It's really about the finance.
These, these, these auto makers.
So you have GMC of GMAC, which is the, the finance arm of General Motors Corporation.
It's a separate company, but essentially GMAC LLC is the largest lender to GM.
And so they've now done what American expressed it, you know,
another credit-based company said, oh, we'll just turn into a bank.
So that we can take some of that bank money.
So they're already looking at getting a 38 billion.
In loans or however else that works with, with Paulson and, and Koshkari is
little butt boy there who does all this dirty work.
Adam, Eric from Portland.
Yo, I was trying to think of a reason why Henry Paulson would put
Neil Koshkari in charge of the bailout.
Okay.
And then I thought about Uncle Hank and his group as gangsters involved in organized crime.
Yeah, you think?
Then it hit me.
Koshkari is being put forward as an economic hitman and a fall guy.
There you go.
He is young.
And he can go to prison for a few years and come out as a made man.
When the prosecution start, Koshkari will take the fall protecting the real criminals,
and Bernaki, Cox, and others.
Koshkari will do a few years in a minimum security prison and he'll come back
a made man for the rest of his life.
Yeah, he'll be king now.
I would like to end this thought by saying, this is completely conjecture
and injuendo.
But if you put the processes known to be evolved involved in organized crime
and overlay them on the current bailout system, you have a clear
match.
Big hair.
Hope you win.
Riddle.
And fighting for your freedom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, man.
Thank you very much.
Well, those guys are given our money away in our economy collapses.
They're all having fun.
Giving themselves millions of dollars.
And you.
You might have to put your house up for sale.
The sun went up, we're reading more than just a couple of hours of the dawn.
Mrs. Hadley picked out through a curtains,
only what was going on.
When they were sad, over coffee cups,
the night she got full of sleep in her.
In the living room, the living memories,
still they're said to go.
And they're all the same, once more.
We're in spring to see my roses grow.
And all the things you try to fix,
the luxellies, the gossip sticks,
as for sale.
You're getting on the side, as for sale.
It was yours and it was mine,
and tomorrow, some strangers,
would apply me now, the stairs,
to the bedroom, fill the memories of the wall.
We used to share.
I know you always love the band.
From the time it shall be sped.
Remember how we found it,
where we died soon,
from that southern summer day.
But the things I keep to celebrate,
my money gave her,
I know as in day,
as for sale.
You're getting on the side, as for sale.
It was yours and it was mine,
and tomorrow, some strangers,
would apply me now, the stairs,
to the bedroom, fill the memories of the wall.
We used to share.
I know as for sale.
You're getting on the side, as for sale.
It was yours and it was mine,
and tomorrow, some strangers,
would apply me now, the stairs,
to the bedroom, fill the memories of the wall.
We used to share.
I know as for sale.
You're getting on the side, as for sale.
This was big in the 70s.
It was just a wee lad in 71, 72,
or 73, or 74.
Lucifer, and house for sale, Dutch band.
You might have been able to tell by the pronunciation of the accent.
We used to share.
Funny thing is, I know most of the band members
by now been known for a long time.
The drummer, Henny Heismund,
who went on to the presenter,
a host of many television shows.
This was what I hit this was, man,
back in Holland, in the day.
Oh, man.
That would just be blasting out of speakers,
because you gotta play that one loud, you know what I'm saying?
So, while all this crap is going down,
and we're not holding our politicians to the task,
there are some definite, I hate to say it,
but points of light.
You'll love this story.
Apparently having learned nothing from Nevada,
I guess it happened in Nevada as well.
I'm a little behind.
Arizona's fourth legislative district,
GOP meeting,
was abruptly halted Monday night.
When Chairman Bob Burgess realized he did not have the votes
to elect his delegates to the county convention,
or reelect his friends to leadership positions.
The reason a large group of constitutional Republican reformers,
including many, of course, Ron Paul supporters,
showed up and established a clear majority.
So then what does the guy do?
Or the chair, I guess, I don't know if he was the chair or not.
It was flustered upon realizing his predicament,
gavled the meeting to a close without electing delegates at all,
ordered the sheriff's department to clear the hall,
and had the light shut off.
And here comes the true patriotic part of the story.
The reformers quickly gathered in the parking lot,
determined to finish the meeting.
When Chairman Burgess had the exterior lights cut as well,
the group found a janitor and had them turn back on.
And here it comes, they established a quorum,
which means there were enough people to hold a vote,
and they elected a slate of delegates and new leadership.
I love this. This is the type of revolution we can actually make happen.
And I'd love to hear from someone who was a part of that,
and how they went down if there's some kind of blueprint.
I'm sure it sounds like it was planned.
They knew what was going to happen.
I love it.
Some more homework for y'all.
There's a video.
I've put the link in the show notes of Ram Immanuel.
This is the chief of staff of our present electobama.
Just so you can kind of get to know the guy a little bit better.
It's very interesting to hear him talk,
because we have not really heard him speak publicly,
at least I haven't seen it anywhere.
And this is kind of in a free forum with the press,
who he's very chummy with, I might add.
Now he's a politician. He's run for multiple offices.
And he will be running a lot of the big show come January.
So just something you might want to take a look at, just to,
you know, just to kind of get a little preview of what your government
is going to be like.
That's not even getting to you.
This is something that was dropped on Danny source code.
Drop.
Thought I always find Danny source code.
I like it though. My team, oh man, nothing for nothing.
Chuck 806.
All the decisions from our...
daily lives.
Ten to a new system.
May everything seems so black or white.
I wish that you mad nature.
Soldiers fighting in our holy land.
It's not pretty big shit.
You'll go fight these days.
And he's right.
That's life.
A little mirror.
Send out the mountain.
As I'm the way it's supposed to be.
None of the mountain.
You'll just give me a little hold of me.
And I'll be.
All the layers seem to be.
I guess we need a little extra sunscreen.
All day never ever.
It's me.
Thanks God for the gift.
And man.
Send out the mountain.
So not the way it's supposed to be.
None of the mountain.
You'll just give me a little hold of me.
And I'll be.
Don't you be away.
I'll do.
There's a change in the weather.
And you see my whole world of you.
Without love, all the emotion.
You might as well kiss your life right off the floor.
While the steward tries to ease our pain
I lose people a little reassure me
Late night hosts just seem to say the same
It's just a matter of TV rades
Look at the mountain
There's not the way through the steward
Just give me a lift
All that means
Oh, give me a lift
Yeah, give me a lift
All that means
Yeah, I might see you all bad, nothing for nothing
Nice
Oh, yeah, that makes me feel ready for the weekend
Do some more work tomorrow
Setting up a green screen in the office here
Got this new license.new
I've seen it before this program called VideoQ
Got some concepts I want to mess around with
Maybe I'll use this prototyping
Who knows it might even turn out to be something
I can use online and full on production
And I'm going to go look for a VHS player
Because I really got some tapes that I want to digitize and put up
Because you're going to laugh your ass off when you see it
Two more articles that didn't really fit anywhere else
That I did just want to mention today
One from the United Kingdom
From the mail
Here's the headline fury over 100 million pound plan
For hundreds of gypsy sites across the country
And I was reading this
And essentially there's a little map
And the map is titled where the camps will go
And the showing all these different parts
North East, Yorkshire, East Midlands, the East London, Southwest
And how many people will be able to stay there
Essentially these are nomadic people
Who have trailers
Mobile trailers, mobile homes, caravans, I guess you could say
And I was looking at this and I'm like, wow man
Knowing that the Lisbon Treaty said, look, if you're homeless
And mental ill or you're addicted to alcohol or drugs
We can incarcerate, yeah, I'm looking at these
And I'm thinking, yeah, you can think it's like a camping ground camp
But it could also just be a camp
I don't know, something going on there
To say the least
And this one just really drove home
How stupid we are to let our
Governmental representatives set this shit up
Where this is actually coming from
Devorac.org slash blogs where I found it
Blackwater gunboats and private navy will now protect ships from pirates
So, you know, I've talked about this so many times
The forces in Iraq
Yes, there's a large number are enlisted men, women
But there's a lot of these commercial companies who are going to be commercial
Police forces and other types of enforcement units
And let's see what they have
They've got their own ship, it's called the MacArthur
It will carry up to 40 armed guards and has a landing pad
For an attack helicopter, which I presume they also have
Should we be paying for this?
And I'm definitely going to bring up the in the conversation
I think we're doing no agenda tomorrow
John is in Portugal, so we're doing tomorrow morning early
For some reason the old man is to get up early
I guess like eight o'clock or eight thirty crap
It's my free Saturday
I'm definitely going to bring this up and say
What is the deal with these pirates?
What are they after?
And what exactly is the point, I guess
You know, I guess you can't bomb them to high hell
Because that would cause an ecological disaster
But do they really expect to get away with this
Or is this a political statement?
It certainly warns more investigation
That's for sure
So those are things that you probably won't see on the fox
Or CNN or CNBC and certainly not on your mainstream nightly news
But at least you're in tune
And you can always follow the latest headlines at drop.io slash daily source code
But it ain't all bad, my friends, chuckle heads
Because no matter what you think, no matter what it reads
It can't brain every day
This little one tries as hard as she can
Do anything just so she can fit in
She wants a friend so bad she'll do whatever they tell her
To make this small she would miss behind
But all the while they would laugh for the face
She begins to cry because she thought that they liked her
Even though you feel all alone
It can't rain every day
It don't rain forever
Your sunshine may be gone
I know it can't rain every day
It don't rain forever
Your sunshine may be gone
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I
know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know to see it.
The young ladies been lost for a while
But that's okay now she's having a child
She found a guy who she wants, she's got someone who loves her
But this morning she woke up in pain
Nobody had to tell her because she knew right away
So she started to cry because she won't be a mother
Even though you feel alone
The car rain every day
The rain forever
The sunshine may be gone
But I know the car rain every day
The car rain forever
Has a little bit of a chilly pepper's vibe
Do it, I'm not quite sure what that is
Like a KOD best name for a band
Playable on death
I like that
Thank you
Definitely words to live by
You can't rain forever
You're willing
I don't care we can say about climate change
And that wraps up episode 806
Coming to you from the Curry Matter
One of the last few shows that will be emanating from this location
As we get into the weekend and already another month over
We're getting close to December, holy moly
Time is going very very fast
It's like it's speeding up just a little bit
You know what I mean?
So you've got your freedom
Please enjoy it this weekend
Do something with it, do something with your wife
Your girlfriend, your boyfriend, your kids, your parents
Do something with each other, do something stupid
Like something old fashioned
Yeah, take a walk or cook a meal together
Enjoy it
Because the tough times they're still ahead
They really are
But we're going to get through it
We're not the first ones and certainly won't be the last
Whatever you do live your life with passion
Another fine, medium presentation
Stick it in your ear