As we always say it the first the month bunny bunny, Delta Sheriff Charlie 786, headloor
60 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
The next generation video content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm guessing it's an angry.
Let's start in the dark place.
The story of a car chase.
I've become a criminal.
I'm flying from the sea.
I've been caught in a bad dream.
The truth becomes ain't like the Lord.
I'm on the break of disaster.
Steering down the galaxy on the stairs.
The break heart will be better.
It's not up to you.
What it takes to fail will never stop.
You're the kind of selfishness.
You're the fact of the matter.
I can't control the same about the way.
But we never do it.
But I can't control the same about the way.
I'm on the break of disaster.
Steering down the galaxy on the stairs.
The break heart will be better.
It's not up to you.
What it takes to fail will never stop.
You're the kind of selfishness.
You're the fact of the matter.
I can't control the same about the way.
But we never do it.
Steering down the galaxy on the stairs.
I'm on the break of this escape
Steering down the clouds and I'm in flames
The break heart will be better
Night off you, what it takes to fail
You'll narrowly rest there
You'll be tired of solving everything
You'll hear what the fact of the matter
The end is coming
I'm on the break of this escape
Steering down the clouds and I'm in flames
The break heart will be better
Night off you, what it takes to fail
Obviously taking from the source code drip
Which means I know absolutely nothing about the band
I like it, M-A-E, bring a disaster
On episode 786
Up the Charlie, everybody how you doing
A steady source code for Monday
The first of September, 2008
Two more days until I turn 44
Hey boy
Man, I remember when my dad turned 40
40, four years ago for me
I thought, oh man, that's ancient
And here I am, now I understand
The world, the universe is so much more open to me
That I still feel like that 19 year old kid sitting up
In his attic pretending to make radio
Exactly what I'm still doing
Except on a podcast
Yes
Well, a lot of things that discussed
First of all, the Dutch gig I was doing
On the Aeroclasic Rock in the mornings
And it'd rather abruptly
Actually it ended last week on Friday
But we really just decided not to continue as of today
Which I learned a lot from this
First of all, although it was a real contract
It gig and it was a serious business
Having a national radio signal
And quite a strong one as well, I might say
And to be able to use that completely openly
As long as I played my 9 or 10 songs
Now I could pretty much do anything I wanted
Or wanted to
And so for me it was a huge experiment
To see if a lot of the topics that we discussed here
On the Charlie, if they would translate over to live
Radio, if they translate into a new marketplace
Into a different country, great ecosystem
Because it has its own language
So I could really see the containment of what was working
Or what wasn't working, built up a pretty large online presence
With the show
And really talked about everything that we're talking about
Here on the source code
And it was actually what's called your wake-up call
Quite pleased I came up with that
And boy did it work
And of course I also learned that
Well mainstream media, even though this was the last independent media company
In the Netherlands, at least when it comes to radio
Maybe even when it comes to any type of media
But certainly radio
That even the government still controls
Who has the licenses, who's on air
The licenses are for limited times
Is all kinds of connections between
What's a small country, basically
And I got word that was essentially
Hey, either you start doing a full music-driven radio program
Or you got to stop
So I said, well that's easy
I can do it
I want to do a music-driven radio show
I got lots of choices there
But not really interested
I like to roll out a good food bar from time to time
But every single morning I want to be talking about
Stuff that affects our world
Look at how press manipulates
Are thinking brain washes us into remaining
Well really a form of slaves
But that's okay because we take the shackles off
Every single time we roll out a daily source code
And really important news for you today
By the way, so of course I do want to welcome any of the arrowheads
Who have come on over
Yeah, the Dutch they all speak perfectly
Perfectly good English
And I've invited them called the arrowheads
Obviously, for obvious reasons
Being a part of the listenership of arrowclastic rock
To come over here and join the chucklehead
So you're all welcome
And of course the place where we get together here
Is at the source code drop.io slash daily source code
And actually I don't even know if I got this
No, I did get this off of the drop
This is the big news
This is something that hits me right you know right right where it counts
Australia is suffering a man drought
Yes indeed
To BBC news article
And of course I've gotten pretty good at listing all the links in the show notes
So you know it'll be there
An analysis of new census figures has shown that Australia is suffering from
An unprecedented man drought
The statistics have revealed that there are almost 100,000 more females than males in Australia
And the problem is worse in the coastal cities like the beaches
We're when have moved
Seeking better jobs and lifestyles while many men have gone overseas
Fast and 18
And very opportunistic
Now I know for sure I'm heading down under
Certainly now that a little bit of my time has been freed up
I wouldn't mind a little trip
I've been talking about it for what three, four years now
Of course I've been to Australia and loved it
Just absolutely I did a little mini documentary
You can probably still find that on YouTube
I did it for Veronica was called Veronica goes down under
And I started in
Well we started in
I guess I did land in Sydney
But I basically went all the way over to Perth
And went in the outback
Unfortunately didn't get up north
That was a different part of the documentary
But just witnessed the people
And it's a really nice mix of Australia
It's got kind of that English properness
Still to it of course
The prison colony of the Brits
Originally
It's got the commercialism of the US
They got their malls
And it's got something Dutch as well
It's got that kind of coziness or
Facilified as we'd call it in Dutch
Which really doesn't translate perfectly to coziness
But it's the closest I can get
And it's work hard play hard
Love it
And now that I know that
There are hundreds of thousands of women
Who will never find a mate
Ha ha ha ha ha
Yeah I can dream candy
So that was that was top of the most important news
And I'm taking invites from all you Aussie women
Let me know I need to set out a tour
So I can travel around your beautiful
No wonder one of Christina's boyfriend
Arthur went on a
Use going for like six months after school
Kind of his backpacking trek
Will you still go to Europe since he's from Europe
He decided to go down on demand
He's going to have a fricking blast
I better not let Christina see this
Better not let her see this report
This was the top of the news
And the Netherlands this past week
Of course last week I should actually say
It was front and center
And it was fascinating
It did get picked up here and there
On some mainstream reports
But of course not enough to actually have it
Make any difference we all know how that works
Headline from the head
The US intense to carry out an aerial bombing campaign
Against Iran within weeks
Credible sources say
The campaign will be directed against crucial sections of Iran's nuclear facilities
As well as against the country's military command and control structure
Analysts expect Iran to attempt to block the
Strait of Hormuz in retaliation
Although a very substantial US-led western naval forces
On its way to the Persian Gulf to prevent that
I think it's about ten ships
And this was revealed because
A highly successful operation inside Iran's arms
Industry by Dutch intelligence service
The AIVD aimed at disruption and sabotage
Are they learned that from the CIA?
Has been halted
And Dutch intelligence personnel have been withdrawn
Because of the planned attack by the US on Iran within weeks
Which also would be directed against facilities
That played a role in the Dutch operation
This is according to the Dutch newspaper
The Taylor Traff
Which typically I wouldn't believe
Because they're so shitty
But it's more fun to believe this one
And it was just amazing to have that on the front page
Of the Dutch newspaper
And it did travel around the globe just briefly
So make sure you read that entire article
Read the translation of it
We got so much cool stuff
And on the way on the Charlie coming up
Including, well, that of course is the soundtrack to my life
We've got a hit test for you for today
Some more cool music and a blatant
Just blatant freaking article about the new world order
In the Guardian that you just might want to read
First of all, the picture in this article
There's two youngsters as it says
And the Georgian capital
Quote grappling for power
It says so much
It's a little boy, little girl
They're probably about
Not say six or seven years old
And they're looking at each other
They're laughing kind of hysterical fit
Of laughter, they're playing outside
Except the girl has, which I presume is a toy AK-47
Which he's holding onto
Playing it at the boy
And they laugh and they're having a good time
And he's got to see this
Actually, I might even even make that the album art for this show
In fact, I'm going to do that right now
Let me just save that over there
Perfect
Oh, what a horror
I mean, it's a funny picture
But it also just says so much
And this of course is because Gordon Brown
is in Brussels with the 26 other European Union
Prime Ministers and Presidents
And they're trying to figure out what to do
It's like, you know, well, you know,
Of course, they're all ignoring the true fact
The Georgia
With funding and advice from the security consultants
Read Blackwater
From the US and Israel
And of course, the UK is in that as well
They actually started this attack
On South Isetia
On the August 7th
The Eve of the Olympic Games
And then Russia retaliated very, very quickly
So this is all about how bad Russia is
And that's what, you know,
This barely another word
Anywhere about who actually started this and why
And the true intentions behind
Sakashvili's movement there
And who's been funding him
And we've talked about all of that here on the
On the source code
But the EU, of course, is shit and bricks
And they clearly were not involved in this
In this move
By Georgia
Because the EU gets their gas and oil
From Russia a lot of it
Not all of it, but a lot of it
So, you know, well, we're going to the
Basically they're going to wag their finger
At Russia saying, now you shouldn't have done that
But they've got no backbone
They're not going to stand up to Russia
Not going to say anything
Because they don't want to get cut off
And it just seems like
A new enemy needed to be created
Maybe the war on terror
Maybe that isn't cutting it anymore
Maybe the
Maybe the new world order
Polsters have figured out that
And too many people are on to the bullshit
Of terrorism
And we needed to get something
Yeah, I know, let's get the Russians
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's always easy to make the Russians scary
Let's make them the bad guys
It's got to be something like that
It's just too
Too
Ridiculous
So I've got a Gordon Brown article here from the BBC here
It is backboneless
Prime Minister Gordon Brown has said NATO and the
European Union must reassess the relations with the Kremlin
To prevent further Russian aggression
His comments came and it fears Russia could cut oil
And gas flows in the row
In the row
It's just a little row honey
It's not too much
The row over Georgia
Mr. Brown and the observer
Erge the EU conduct a root and branch review of
Relations with the Kremlin
Blotty, Blotty, Blotty, Blotty, Blot
Meanwhile, if you didn't have a chance to listen to
No agenda over the weekend
The BBC is reported that
At the time being
Britain, the United Kingdom
Is in the worst recession
The worst economic shape
They've been in in 60 years
Which would be just post World War Two
And that now
I thought it was going to be a million
But they're saying that over 2 million people
Could be without a job
2 million people
Granted there's 60 million here
But the actual workforce
2 million, this is going to be bad
People are really hunker and down
Embracing for some serious shit to hit the United Kingdom
And of course this is all falling on
From the crisis in the United States
A great article here
Banking on Big Changes is the title of it
It's from Reason.com
And it's you know
I could go through everything
That we've gone through over and over again
Just keep your eye on Freddie Mac, Fanny May
Once those so-called government-sponsored enterprises
Are officially
Effectively nationalized
By the Treasury
And the whole Bush administration
That's when everything is just going to fall to shit
There's nothing left to borrow
Nothing let the FDIC
The Federal Deposit
Insurance Corporation keeps adding banks
To its watch list over 100 now
Warning that they probably won't
Have enough money
To ensure all the depositors
Now this stuff is purposely kept
Very much out of the picture
Even though the reporting's done
Again, it's up to us to aggregate
This reporting and help people to
Connect their own dots
Because they're sure going to put this on the front
Page of every newspaper
Because there would be a bank run
And that would surely tip over the entire system
So that's really just some homework reading
That I suggest that you do
But if you really want to
Hold on, I got to play this for you
This is fantastic
This is actually a little English YouTube documentary
One can imagine having a holiday
In a motorhome
However, having to live in a motorhome
It's much harder
It's perhaps the only thing that still remains
As part of the American Dream
So this is a it's called living in our vans USA
And I think as Thone left this on
Drop.au slash daily source code
If you really want to see what's going on
America with over a million and a half
People who have lost their homes and now
Resorted to living in their cars, their vans
Their mobile homes
This is like a 10 minute YouTube thing
It's kind of a documentary
But you literally see all the places
The piano, of course, where do you go
You let's get some some seaside view right here
I don't have to pay taxes on it
I don't have to pay rent for it
To look at it
I just pull up and there it is
This is I love this
You know, you can't be good Americans down
You can take away their home
You can try and bankrupt them
But you can't you can't beat Americans down
These guys that get, you know, they're in the
Winpower solar power, they're
Figuring out how to live in
In a new world
It's it's it's all been reset
A complete reset of of where we're going
And this is just the beginning
I'm telling it it's just the beginning
Of what is going to happen
As unfortunately
The the shit really is hitting the fan
Don't take my word for go ahead and
Turn on CNBC or MSNBC
And and and you know
There's no excitement on Wall Street
There's it's all like, well, we really don't know
We're all kind of waiting for the other shoe to drop
What's going to happen to Fannie Mae for the Mac
The game is over
It's falling apart as we speak
We're watching it melt down before our very eyes
And now of course
Enter Gustav
Ah, which is
Hampering oil
Really gas I guess
Oil and gas coming from the from the Gulf of Mexico into the states
It was just amazing watching Fox News
Showing the radar images
And having the scroll underneath saying
Stand by brace for five
Dollar a gallon oil
Or gasoline I should say
Ah
But you know what we're going to come out of this
One way the other and that's why I want you to take a look at this living in our bands thing
It's a done from a British perspective
Which kind of makes it maybe that more honest
But you'll see this is what Americans are made up
We're used to living in the wilderness
That's how we grew it's only been a couple hundred years
And we can go back to it
Not a problem
We understand how to do it
And now that we are understanding more about the technology that's been withheld from us
How to come up with efficient clean power and fuels
I'm talking about biodiesel
Which just takes waste oil products
I'm talking about running on pure vegetable oil
These legends will do that
I'm talking about
The hydrogen
That's some amazing things that are being done with with salt water
And radio waves creating fire
Which can create heat which can create power through steam generation and other methods
Wind power solar power
You're not going to know when you can get the American people down
We're very resourceful that way
Just had to be kind
Yeah, this is of course
Labor day today in the United States
Interesting how we celebrate work by not working
We celebrate the fact that we have some work by not going to work
And I just love it
Have a look at that documentary
You won't be disappointed
Hey, Kerry
Don't try this thing out
Saying how things work
Use the pause feature of my cell phone
So this works well
Yes
Oh, the pause feature
That's what Candyman Lucas talking about
You go to drop.au slash daily source code
You'll find a number you can call in
Use that. I had not had time to go through the old system
It's tedious
It's just not a simple way. I have to go somewhere else
And now I've got everything all aggregated
And one spot, please use that
You have to use a pin code
And so the suggestion there is
You can enter the number and then a pause function
Which unknock your phones as a star
And then the
Then the pin code and so you can basically have it
Stored into your cell phone ready to go
At a moment now
Hopefully I'll be able to use this a lot more
Easily than the old device mail
So
Comment can't wait for the food bar
Just later
Alright, so of course i missed the food bar
But we do have some elements of it for you today
Just so we all feel like we're up to speed
I'm crawling casting
I'm going to be this
You think it is just
Get it just
Young pole
Hey Adam, this is your first number
I'm going to start right away with intro
Number one
It's a rock scene music or Brian Ferry
I can hear it but I don't know the name of the song
Number two
That's your day
I don't remember
Number three
Toto Rosanna
Wow
Maybe i'll get four out of six today
Let's see how we did yon and it's time for the answer
And this is answer number one
Yeah, she's Brian Ferry
Don't stop the dance
Answer number one
Brian Ferry and don't stop the dance
And this is answer number two
This is your day
Hey, let's go!
3, 2, 1.
1, 2, 1.
What's the call?
2, 1, 2, 1.
Hang on to our love.
Hang on.
2, 1, 2, 1.
2, 1.
And 3, 2, 1.
Hang on to your love.
And this is answer number 3.
Toto.
I think I need it too.
Oh, we can win the more we can see right.
Roseanna, Roseanna.
Come in to all the way.
Don't take out all the way.
2, 2, 1.
And so number 3, Toto, Roseanna.
And that concludes this 80's music hit test.
So number 136.
Yep.
So how did you do Adam?
I did not do good.
Yeah, I did.
4 out of 6.
Better than last week, I think.
Sorry.
I stuck.
That's it.
Well, I had fun creating this one.
Hi.
I heard music from the audience.
You know that.
Alrighty.
The answers to this hit test.
And also the links to my tune.
So you can buy the tricks online.
Or to be found at hittest.mevio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening again.
Hope to be back next week for another hit test.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And remember to try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
We back to test as she will.com.
info.