This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
The show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Walk it with your fruit-whip log from GoDaddy.
Delta Chericharly has 7-1-2.
You are listening to a man identified by the Transportation Security Administration as the Supreme Commander of the dual-ford humorist movement Adam Curry.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing here's Adam Curry.
Had enough, all the bad times, won't be nobody's fool free.
Curry night, all the good times.
This is half things I've supposed to be.
I try new hard to please everyone else.
Always morning, myself passed.
I try to hard to feel what they're feeling.
I try to hard to make it less.
This is perfect, that's what they call it.
Only for me, I feel so free now.
Only for me, no one can hold me down again.
Only for fame.
Well, you're back and what I've done.
If I made anything worth learning there, only know.
It's time to have fun.
It's time to live without having a care.
I do believe there's a happy end there.
Do this little fairy tale plan.
Now I know I will break it for abandoned.
I'm going to give it all I care if I've made.
This is what they call it.
Only for me, I feel so free now.
Only for me, no one can hold me down again.
Only for fame.
Well, you're back and what I've done.
Wow!
You go!
Knock down the doors and throw out the roofboards.
Nobody's coming for me now.
I hope my head higher and higher.
I'm going to take what's done now.
Only for fame.
That's what they call it.
Love feels so free now.
Only for me, no one can hold me down again.
Only for me, that's what they call it.
All right, I'll give you...
Only for fame.
I'll give you two guesses worth.
Yes, thank you.
The shrimp has just been delivered.
It's shrimp tempura, no less.
Thank you, darling.
Yeah, that's a new jersey.
But you guess that already, right?
Actually, he's from New Jersey.
John Tagliari.
Leap of Faith.
I'm sorry.
But he's still there, huh?
Yeah.
Just as that song was ending,
just as I cracked the mic Patricia came up with the tempura shrimp.
Oh, what a life I have.
Yeah, the John Tagliari.
He sounds like Bon Jovi when they sell out the spark, you know what I mean?
Remember those days when they actually still had like spark?
I can hear Jersey boy fans.
Hearts break all over the globe at this moment.
I don't know.
Second, there's a little too much.
A little too much echo there.
Yeah, you know what?
I created a new show, which if you follow along my weblog at curie.com,
you've probably seen it.
It's called soundtrack of our lives.
You can find it at opsol.podshow.com.
Of course, that's for the organization for the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
There's opsol.podshow.com.
And I really wanted to create a different kind of show where, you know, you basically,
someone would send in their story about a record.
And then I'll play that record.
And then that way we create a community soundtrack to our life.
And so I really wanted to set up kind of formatted wise.
It'll be easy for me to just sit down, read someone's story,
and then edit the song and just release it as a show.
And hold on.
Oh crap.
Oh, come on yet.
Let me just check.
I'm sorry.
This is really gotten bad.
So anyway, so I set it all up.
And it blew out all the settings in my mixer.
That's what you hear me messing around with.
I'm trying to find the settings that I use.
I did get a good education in in logic studio, pro, whatever, because I wound up actually
producing the whole thing on my MacBook, which was kind of fun.
I had really never spent any time just sitting down and you know, and learning the program
as I normally use something on the studio PC, which is Adobe Audition.
Not about programming.
Actually, I think I may like it better when it comes to editing this type of stuff,
but Jerry still out.
So with the hell, it's Monday.
It's January 21st, 2008.
This is the daily source code.
Location is the curry manner up in the attic,
in the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford.
We're on the west side of G-town for those of you that don't know by now.
What should we start with?
It's up to you.
Shall we start with some red pill stuff, some polyticking or hot chicks?
Okay.
I heard that unanimous vote.
I got to tell you.
That whole thing with the Kirstie Hawkshire.
I don't know if you listened on Friday.
You'll have a chance to listen again, because it's coming up in this clip that I've got for you.
Was this really, really chuck from Shai Town, from Chicago, Turn Me On Door?
And, you know, she's really talented.
She's actually, she's quite well known.
She's done a lot of stuff with the famous DJs, like DJ Chiesto.
She's the voice of a lot of dance dance, and I'm not particularly my favorite kind of music.
And I played meteors, a real slow chilled out song by her.
But man, it hit a chord with the listeners, of course, with the guys,
which I'm still convinced is the only people actually listening to me.
Let's see, Chris Lacharel sent me a video to, I guess this is her.
He says she's killed her in the dress.
Let's see another one here.
Yeah, this is the Cursey Hawkshow Live with T.S. dough walking on clouds.
A lot of people just really nuts about her, and calling up with the same message as well.
Hey Adam, this is a, hey, look at I'm not trying to get out of your show.
There's a mark from us about the Angela's really in all seriousness.
Oh, he's dead.
This, this, this, this chick, dude.
I'm telling you, it's a, she has, the Obama girl cannot touch your voice.
I'm sure.
Man, what a, okay, I've had a couple of beers, but yeah.
And my wife's not home.
Damn.
Same problem I had.
Holy crap.
What a great show, dude.
All of that.
Enjoy the weekend.
This was great.
Hmm.
Thanks, man.
Really appreciate how much and on a shrimp tempura as we speak.
My God, what a life I have.
I get to make shows that I like to make.
I get served.
I get sexy phone calls.
Sexie feedback.
Don't believe it.
Yeah.
Chuck's going to set it up for you.
I'm Chuck from the Northwest side of Shite Town.
Oh, Friday.
Fubar was amazing.
Totally rock.
I just wanted to call it.
Thank you.
Thanks, man.
That's beautiful.
Chris, we got to be kick out of that.
And she said.
Let me just imagine for those of you just joining the show, which I can, I can imagine.
The setup is that Chuck turned me on to her and got her to create really sexy
show ID's for me.
And I just sexy sexy stuff.
And I guess Chuck is helping her out with Chuck's trying to get into her pants, honestly.
Listen to the rest of the message.
Ident response.
So I'm going to email it to you as well just so you get it.
And she also was taking her response too.
So we threw it up.
There's a podcast six at the Kirstie Haksha podcast.com, which is also on pod show.
So anyway, I hope you had enough some weekend.
Best of Lady Patricia.
Hope she's recovering well.
And rock on, man.
Rock on.
Thank you for that.
So Chuck signing off.
And.
Love you.
I mean it.
Great hair.
Hope you.
Thank you.
Love you.
Meena.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Back at you, my friend.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm telling you everything's all fucked up with my system.
I hate that.
Um.
So what's going to cool?
I'm sorry.
I'm being very rude eating in front of you.
So I go over and check out the Kirstie Haksha podcast, which is, indeed, is on poncho.com.
And of course, you'll find a link to this in the show.
No, it's a daily source code dot com or the cross posting at curie dot com.
I'm going to play this whole thing.
It's about four minutes.
So you'll actually hear me talking about Kirstie about Chuck.
But the camera is on Kirstie.
And she's got this like really sexy, low cut t-shirt.
Oh man.
She looked even better than the videos.
And so you can see all of her facial expressions and her response as well.
So he's listening to this for the first time.
So there's, uh, I'll just run you through it.
Okay.
The audio's pretty pretty decent.
Mine.
You're going to the email from her another up there.
She has to play some more.
Okay.
So she's looking right in the camera right now.
She's got maybe it's, uh, it actually it's not a t-shirt.
It almost looks like a, um, what do you call one of those things that, uh,
uh, one of those, um, not quite jacket.
Like, uh, the keeps really warm and winter.
Oh, god.
My brain is for doesn't matter because I'm not actually looking at the garment.
I'm looking at the little cut part of it.
Oh, that ain't.
And it's her, it's her in her studio.
That's really cool.
She's got a, you know, he looks like a 24 track mixing board in the back.
I almost looks like she's kind of in a basement vibe.
So it's all, it's very grungy and it's black and white and sexy beyond belief.
Bitch.
And it makes me feel good.
And then, of course, there's guys like Chuck.
Hey, Adam.
So she's, she's got him out there for now.
She's surprised.
She's happy.
She's screaming.
Hey, um, I just emailed you to Adamacrid.com to audio bumpers.
And of course, that wasn't mistake.
It took Chuck, uh, another try.
Don't send it to Adamacrid.com.
Send it to Adamacpodshow.com.
Her work, uh, from crispy hoxia.
The, uh, the chance to leave us from open three back in the day.
Remember 92.
Yeah.
She's not out.
She's like shaking her head going like, oh, no.
She's embarrassed.
You know, it's, it's a good, um, healthy dose of, uh, um,
of embarrassment having people talk about her.
But as an artista, of course, I know she's really happy.
Deep inside.
Um, anyway, I just, uh, you know the most to Adamacrid.com.
I want her to make sure you got him.
And, uh, and then I can do a little preview.
Just listen to Chuck.
Oh, cool.
So that's the ideas that she made.
I just shot him off to you.
So, um, yeah.
Let me know if you think.
Check out our new tunes and, uh,
public music network.
She uploaded seven of them.
And, uh, we're talking up some stuff for NGB too.
So, uh, oh, she's looking really into camera.
Yeah.
You think of both of us.
I sent you.
What have you done, Chuck?
All right, man.
Lovely.
Meet it.
Great hair.
Hope you win.
Okay.
I love you.
I mean, it's going to help you win.
Thank you.
And maybe it's something she says that love you mean a great hair.
Hope you win.
It's sure her response was like, oh, this is so great.
And she, and, and, uh, man, she leaned back and she went,
and then she immediately closed up the, uh, the garment again.
A fleece.
That's what it's called.
Fleece.
That's almost as good as, uh, get Cape where Cape fly.
Let me hear that again.
That was pretty cool.
I got to remember this one.
All right, man.
Love you, meet it.
Great hair.
I love you, meet it.
Hope you win.
Absolutely.
Hi.
This is Kirsty Hope Show.
I'm listening to Adam.
She's laughing at her own voice.
She's soft coat.
See, he sends me the artwork with her and a little DSC logo on it.
She is beautiful.
Of course.
Oh, she's, she's, she's waving on air in her face.
Oh, he gets me, uh, an ID.
Of course, I'm going to play this song.
And now she's looking at the camera.
I can't hear that now.
To the end of the song.
Yeah.
I could play that.
I could accompany her.
Percy.
She's beautiful.
Yeah, we'd make a nice, uh, I wonder what tall she is.
Yeah.
Oh, how long for the good old days?
Yeah, she had when I say I wonder how tall she is.
She does this like, huh?
Why is he asking that?
That's because I'm rather tall, Percy.
I just want to make sure we kind of fit together that the picture will look right.
When the talent would just blow the DJ to get their song played.
Now, these days, kind of just got to do it with a picture.
Okay.
Percy Hawkshaw.
And meteors.
And, of course, you'll find links to that song and all the songs played
on today's football Friday in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
I've got an idea for an idea.
Okay.
So, so in response to what Adam just said, I just knocked up a quick cheeky
idea.
Here it is.
Okay.
You know, oh, actually, yeah, this might sound good from the video.
It's a whole she did a whole second angle on this and she actually edited that.
And so she's now she's replying to my question.
What happened to the good old days when talent would just blow the DJ
to get their song played on the radio?
In the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
I've got an idea for an idea.
Okay.
So in response to what Adam just said, I just knocked up a quick cheeky
idea.
Here it is.
Yeah, those were the days.
I'm actually getting to blow the DJ to get your radio plays.
How am I going to get Adam Curie's attention again?
Oh, he's a phone number.
I'll give it a ring.
Well, the video says, Adam, thank you.
Ah, isn't that cute?
Wait, let me play the, let me play the high-res version.
Because I like it so much.
It's really cool.
So nice of you, Curci.
Yeah, those were the days.
When you actually get to blow the DJ to get your radio plays.
How am I going to get Adam Curie's attention again?
Oh, he's a phone number.
I'll give it a ring.
Plus, 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 6, 8, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
Ah, Curci.
Every time you call that number and you say something sexy,
I'm going to play one of your songs.
So all you have to do is tell me which one you want me to play.
I'm like a million up there.
And I can't wait until we speak again, my dear.
Hey, Adam.
This is Maurice Osondar here from the Sunnis and Adam.
The dude with a free CD of the best of the Sunnis and Adam,
which you can order at www.Sunnisandand.com.
Thanks for playing the promo, man.
That was pretty cool.
The orders are keep coming in as we speak.
You asked for more info about this idea.
So I thought let's give you a comment on that.
And of course, I had contact with these artists on the CD.
You know, I got this CD because I wanted their music off the three players
and computers and get it into the living rooms and the CD racks over there.
So, yeah, these artists deserve that.
So to do something in return, I worked out this idea.
I'm first I talked to Carmen Tyler about this idea.
What she, you know, as an artist, thought of this concept and this thing.
And she was enthusiastic right away.
So I contacted the other artists and asked if they wanted to join.
And well, except for one, everyone was thrilled with the idea.
So yes, right away.
So I guess the one who didn't say yes and I was banging her head to the wall.
You know, this is a very interesting project that Maurice Osondar set up for the Sunnis.
The Sunnis Sundown podcast.
And what he's done essentially is he's created a CD of pod, pod save music that he's played on his show.
And he got permission from all the artists.
That was my question essentially.
And he's not selling it.
He's giving it away, which is I think just awesome.
I don't know if he's producing them in bulk or if he's just burning him at home.
But, you know, in certain, which of course is a very valid way to do it.
But still, you know, that's got to be a couple of times a CD.
And I got to say that's awesome idea.
And he's letting his listeners have it, which I agree.
I think is a great way to get you get stuff out of the digital realm, make it tangible.
It's a great way to introduce people to pod save music.
And it's given me a couple ideas.
I mean, why wouldn't we do the best of the daily source code?
I mean, shit.
If the artists are into it and, you know,
I can just basically give it away.
Oh, man.
I got some strategies where we could actually make some money doing that.
If we could build the brand, you know, powerful enough,
why wouldn't newspapers want to distribute free music with their papers?
They do it here in the UK all the time, granted with established artists.
But if you turn it, you know, if you brand it properly and say these are the,
you know, this is like the up and coming UK talent as an example.
I think we could probably sell it to them.
We could probably all make a couple under box.
Maybe even more.
It's a great, great concept.
But yeah, this, this gives a good opportunity for these artists as well.
They get, we'll get some CD stew so they can spread it around in their network.
Yep.
And they're at a gig or something or want to get to fans or something like that.
Or for like using it as demo kind of stuff like that.
Now, we don't make any direct money from the CD, of course.
It's just a promotion, promotion value that creates.
I handled the distribution myself and so these discussed ceremony.
And so the name sponsor interlocks and the immediate network.
I mentioned in the promo is the name of my website.
www to interlock the mill.
It's main page where all my podcast products are coming together and syndicated, syndicated there.
So this is how we can promote these artists and my show, of course.
Yeah, I love it, Maurice.
It's a great idea, man.
FedTAS.
If you go check out a show, go request order, a copy of a CD, which as far as I can tell, it's completely free.
And it's a great collection.
It really is some good songs on there by a well-established pod safe artist.
You know, we've got the finally have the codes for the Nokia N8010, which you can now buy
to 15% discount.
I've not seen it at cheaper anywhere without all kinds of tricks like ordering, actually credit cards and stuff like that.
And you can do it by going to the Nokia Store, NokiaUSA.com slash N8010.
We have a special link for UK residents, which is BT Podshow.com slash N8010.
And if you enter in the promo code daily source code, you'll get your 15% discount.
Now, more countries coming online have already seen Italy store, which is coming online soon.
I think France was coming online.
They're doing their best.
It's quite interesting for Nokia as a company, because I don't think they have a lot of experience
with this type of a setup where you basically have people selling their stuff.
Now, they just expanded their sales force across all these podshow programming and fantastic response.
I have no idea about sales numbers yet, but I know certainly several people have already ordered one.
If not through using my code, one of the other podshow podcast network programs.
And pretty soon we'll be opening this up much wider, so any show can participate.
This is a new customer.
It's a new, we're really trying something new both for us and for them.
So we want to keep the first group a little bit controlled, a little small, so we can actually oversee what's going on.
But I think it's going quite well, so with a bit of luck we'll be able to open that up to more more shows across the network.
More information on that in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com, of course also at curie.com.
And talking, okay, so we get into some red pill stuff here for a second.
Well, before we get into the red pill, atomic rod, who is, of course, my nuclear energy savant called in with answers to my questions about nuclear facilities being put up by 2020 in the United Kingdom.
The atomic rod items here are your energy savant.
Sorry about the rather useless common galasio.
Everybody has a bad day.
The UK government has announced after a lengthy public comment period that nuclear power plants should be encouraged.
But they will not provide any subsidies.
Even with that statement, there are a lot of companies that are interested in the market.
Several of the largest utility companies in Europe are lining up.
Partner power plants suppliers, according to a recent article in the Guardian Unlimited, the plants make financial sense because of high oil and gas prices, along with the costs that are being imposed for carbon emissions to meet key elements.
The most likely sites for the new plants are the places that already have nuclear power plants.
All those sites are owned by British energy.
So there's a lot of talk about needing until 2020 for new plants.
The most recent experience in Asia is a construction period of about five years.
A new nuclear plant replaces the need to burn about 1.7 billion cubic meters of gas each year.
That removes about 500 million in sales from the gas supply.
It looks like the interest in nuclear in the UK is encouraging a new discussion in the rest of Europe.
Okay, so that's interesting.
So the gas guys are running interference.
Is that where you're saying their atomic rod?
That is quite interesting.
And I had no idea that plants could come online in five years.
That means seven years earlier than they're predicting the plants could come online at the current pace.
Interesting.
And I have to say, of course, I peruse to the Guardian once in a while.
Very left-wing paper.
But I'm pretty selective.
The message is definitely differently in the mainstream media here, so that's always interesting rod.
It's a necessary tool in the fight against greenhouse gas emissions.
And it is a heck of a lot better than depending solely on the good graces of Iran and Russia to keep increasing their sales of natural gas to cover those days and the wind is not blowing.
Far better for countries like the UK and the USA to build up their nuclear power plant industry and provide good jobs for tens of thousands of local engineers.
Technicians, security guards and operators.
And to keep sending pounds or dollars to place like Iran.
Russia, Venezuela, Nigeria or France.
That's right.
If the Brits fight nuclear plants too hard, the French will be more than happy to build them in France.
And sell the Brits to power they need to keep their gadgets coming.
Yep.
You'll write on when it comes to safety.
The record of the industry is pretty spectacular.
And comparing Chernobyl to a modern reactor is a bit like comparing your jag to a Hugo.
As an aside, the back yard nuclear power plant business may also be looking up soon.
But I cannot share any damned announcements.
Folder, red pill.
Love you.
Yeah.
Love you too, man.
Awesome.
Thank you, atomic rod.
Really appreciate that.
And keep us up to speed on what's going on with these nuclear plants.
And in general, you should learn a little bit more about nuclear energy.
Because the safety record is fantastic.
The waste is not like green group that oozes around.
You know, how to learn some of this when had rod on in one of the savants series.
So it's definitely alternative that needs to be looked at.
You just do your own research.
Not with the help we have Google for.
Oops.
I come that didn't work.
There we go.
Hey, Adam.
This is Dean.
Beautiful Morgan LA.
I was just listening to DSC 709.
And I got to tell you.
I heard you talking about how you're jealous about being alive.
And my opinion.
Podcasting is the way to go.
I think you have a larger audience because hey, we can listen to you whenever we want.
And that's the way I feel.
Anyway, just want to pass that along.
Make a comment here.
Hey.
Folder.
No.
I'm a hybrid.
Now, I used to be a sprinter and now I'm a hybrid.
Anyway.
Love you.
No homo.
I don't know.
No homo man.
I don't know how that works.
How you can be a hybrid.
But you know, there is, I'm still going to try some live shows.
And it doesn't really matter because it's not like, well, only people who are participating
in the show at that very moment will actually be able to hear anything.
So in the first brush of the test that I'm still planning.
What is it not two, three weeks?
It's more just to get people to talk to than it being live.
I obviously want you to be able to get the file, the minute it's ready and listen to it.
And the only real timing issue is participation.
If you want to participate, then we have to somehow come up with a schedule or an agreement or a
time so that you can plan your life.
And my life is already complicated.
So I don't want to change any plans.
And I did get a nice email and voice mail from Alan Levy.
He's the founder of blog talk radio.
And I'd kind of dismiss blog talk radio because they don't have the functions I was looking
for like a mute and an unmute function.
And he sent me a login to test some stuff and they've got some new features coming out,
which might just be perfect to satisfy my needs.
Because really what I'm thinking here is I want a mix mine.
And next mine is basically the signal from my mixer.
I want to go into the phone line, which in this case will be Skype, I guess.
Because that is much more reliable just to listen to people on the phone.
Unfortunately, we just can't rely on the, on the VoIP technologies yet.
Unless you're using VoIP to call into their phone bank.
So I'll still get phone quality back.
But the people on the call will be able to hear the show and hear the other callers.
But not themselves.
I guess I'm saying that right?
There won't be any feedback the way I potentially have it set up in my head, at least.
So I do want to try it.
I really do because I enjoy speaking to other people about topics.
And you know, that's kind of what I was trying to do with the sabons.
But again, you get into this whole, you know, if you got to basically produce the show.
And guess what?
I got no time for that.
A couple of reports here.
Good article at the times.
The London Times.
On flight thirty eight.
Some good data points in there.
They finally talked to some pilots.
And they, you know, and they have some good information on, you know,
basically what happens in the plane the last two thousand feet.
How the autopilot and auto throttle are engaged and disengaged.
Then some other data about previous triple sevens that have had problems similar to this.
But a different situations.
August 1st, 2005 Malaysian Airlines triple seven from Perth to
Kuala Lumpur was climbing past 38,000 feet.
And the crew was confronted with what the official report of the incident described as a situation that had previously been considered not possible.
They got a low speed warning suggesting the plan was approaching stalling speed.
Almost simultaneously the primary flight display screen warned exactly the opposite.
The aircraft was approaching the over speed limit.
And then what happened is all of a sudden.
This craft, the pitch that's nose up, the autopilot did that climb.
And then they really started to saw a stall as they got, you know,
what happens then is the the yolk or the stick starts to shake.
And so you know, they've got to put pitch that nose down immediately.
So it seems like the triple seven may have had certainly some electrical problems.
And electrical problems in a fly by wire aircraft can, of course, lead to, well,
bad shit.
That's for sure.
So I'll put a link in the show notes so you can take a look at that at your leisure.
And let me see some more things I've collected here.
Bush pardons himself retroactively.
This is a very interesting piece of data that see who sent this to me.
It's opening up the the Gmail as we speak and I can tell you.
Ah, there we go.
Ian Kath.
Okay.
I can think he's from Australia.
Let's follow this link.
You should listen to this.
This is pretty interesting.
This is from the situation.
I'll be getting to think with the wolf blitzer.
I've done these interviews yesterday.
An iteration.
This is actually quite disturbing when you listen to this.
When was this video posted?
Three days ago.
Listen to this on your door asking for transcripts.
Ordinarily, we don't do a question two days in a row.
But this is important enough to be an exception.
The house just passed President Bush's bill to redefine the treatment of the
Tainees and the Senate's expected to do the same thing tomorrow.
Very deep inside this legislation is a provision that will pardon President Bush and all
the members of his administration of any possible crimes connected with the torture
and mistreatment of detainees dated all the way back to September 11, 2001.
At least President Nixon had Gerald Ford to do his dirty work.
President Bush is trying to pardon himself.
Here's the deal.
Under the War crimes Act, violations of the Geneva conventions are felonies, in some cases punishable by death.
When the Supreme Court ruled that Geneva conventions applied to al Qaeda and Taliban detainees,
President Bush and his boys were suddenly in big trouble.
They've been working these prisoners over pretty good.
In an effort to avoid possible prosecution, they're trying to cram this bill through Congress before the end of the week when
Congress adjourns.
The reason there's such a rush to do this, if the Democrats get control of the house in November,
well, this kind of legislation probably wouldn't pass.
You want to know the real disgrace of what these people are about to do or in the process of doing
Senator Bill Frist and Congressman Dennis Hasterd and their Republican studios.
Apparently, don't see anything wrong with this.
I really do wonder sometimes what we're becoming in this country.
The question is this, should Congress pass a bill giving retroactive immunity to President Bush
a possible war crimes?
You may have your thoughts to carefully file.
So that was the check-offer.
How come that guy doesn't get more airtime?
He should be doing.
He should be doing a show like Anderson Cooper.
Man, that guy is always right on the money.
He's always down deep, but he's always showing up in other people's shows.
But you never really tune into watch his show.
He needs some like star vehicle, because the guy has got it going on.
He's got the research.
He's got the stories.
He's not afraid to report on him.
No fear, no favor, which is the,
the financial times is slogan.
I like it.
No fear, no favor.
I just may have to borrow that one.
So if you have any information on that bill, of course,
it being mainstream media, there was no detailed information that really helped me out with anything.
I'd like to know about it because we've got to start bitching about it,
because that is just disgusting.
Absolutely disgusting.
And I'll bet you there's a lot more going to be uncovered when we get to the bottom of this one.
Adam Curry.
Yeah.
Um, I'm curious.
So, let's go.
What is red pill?
I've missed a little bit of the DSC way behind, like, a year behind.
But so I'd like to know what you're referring to as red pill.
Thank you very much.
Tell me what I say.
Yeah, I catch you, Mike.
Yeah.
My name is Mark Finkel.
Uh, go watch the movie The Matrix, Mark.
And then see the choices that are given.
You take the blue pill.
You wake up.
Everything stays the same.
You take the red pill.
You go down the rabbit hole, my friend.
And join the revolution.
That's what the red pill is all about.
Hey there, Adam.
This is Andrew from Ottawa, Canada.
I thought I'd send in an audio comment about what's going on in Afghanistan.
Like you.
I try and understand these things as well.
And I had a once on a lifetime opportunity earlier 2007.
Did you see things up close for our Canadian Army?
It's me to go on a one week trip across to Afghanistan to bring.
Let me just stop them for a second.
I did get a lot of comments from people who heard the Noah Jen to show.
And I think I mentioned on the Daily Source Code as well, where I said, you know,
so basically we've got the Dutch, the English, and the Canadians in Afghanistan.
And I said, you know, the typical asslickers.
But just so we're very, very clear on one thing.
I'm not talking about the military, not talking about the troops, not talking about the
guys and gals who are actually doing this fucked up work.
I'm talking about the politicians.
I'm talking about the people running the country.
I can see the prime minister of the Netherlands, young pay to bulk in Andy.
He's a total asslicker.
We know about Tony Blair.
And God, do I have something to say about Gordon Brown in a moment?
So it kind of makes sense that Canada would, you know, based on his proximity.
It's relationship with the US.
I know that it's a United Nations call out.
But how come it's only these three countries?
One is the smaller than the state of Rhode Island.
Come on.
And then I guess I said, well, what do we do in Afghanistan anyway?
Let's move away from Iraq just for one second.
Let's just focus our attention on Afghanistan.
Please explain to me, what are we doing there?
Besides getting blown up.
Hopefully Andrew couldn't fill this in on the Canadian involvement.
Our Stanley Cup, our hockey trophy and hockey players and the music from Newfoundland
to cheer up the troops over on Canada.
It was an incredible trip.
They're amazing people doing an amazing job.
It was quite something.
By the way, that trip and the visa stamp in my passport has screwed up all my border crossings.
So the last guard actually said, ship, what's this Afghanistan stuff?
So I can feel for you with your Iraq stamps and your passport.
Yeah, that's what happened.
Canada, in the south of Afghanistan, is one of the oldest cities in the entire world founded by Alexander the Great
and sacked by Ganges Khan.
A lot of people know it as the country invaded by Russia.
In Canada, there is a cave with the cape of the Prophet Muhammad.
This is a very holy city.
This cape was worn by Bin Laden and Sheikh Omar before they were chased out of the country by US Special Forces in Korea.
Really? How does that work?
So they go into the sacred cave and they just said, I'm a size four.
That's perfect.
I'll just wear this cape.
Or is it something that's passed on from leader to leader?
I'd love to know more about that.
This desolate isolated country so close to Pakistan and Iran plays a key part in the entire Middle East
process.
And allowing the Taliban to continue to operate in that country is unacceptable.
So there have been two main thrusts in that country since 2001.
And the biggest one is Operation Enduring Freedom, which is the US's anti-911 forces kicking people out of the country.
There's a parallel force being run by NATO forces.
They're invited in by the Karzai government to restore power, police, basic infrastructure
and start training the country back up again.
It's really been decimated by 40 years of war.
So I got it.
I got it.
That makes sense because I follow the Dutch news.
And clearly the Dutch troops went in as, you know, as people who are going to rebuild the country.
Yeah, it's the same old story, right?
Train the police force, stabilize, etc.
And the reason why has got to be pretty evident at this point.
But it's certainly not to go looking for bin Laden walking around with a cave.
So, so of all the United Nations countries, we still have the Netherlands, the United Kingdom, Canada.
And Denmark, I think, I've done some homework now.
The US forces are separate from the NATO forces.
And the NATO forces are mainly composed of the British, Canadian, and the Dutch.
Okay, it's NATO, I'm sorry.
NATO, not UN NATO.
I think about US defense secretary Gates comments about NATO.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
NATO doesn't stand for North American trade organization.
How come they get to call up wars and stuff?
Do they have that right?
Is that what they're in business for?
Oh boy, let me see.
Surely there's a, let's see, is there a NATO website?
There must be, they must have some kind of mission statement.
Let's see, we find home on NATO.
North Atlantic Treaty Organization, there you go.
NATO.int makes sense.
What is NATO?
Okay, let's click on what is NATO?
Go, we got a pop up here.
Nice, nice pop up guys.
What is NATO?
Okay.
The North Atlantic Treaty Organization, NATO, is an alliance of 26 countries.
26?
No less.
From North America and Europe committed to fulfilling the goals of the North Atlantic Treaty signed on 4th April 1949.
Okay, there's a link to the North Atlantic Treaty, that's nice.
Now here we go, the parties to this treaty reaffirm their faith in purposes and principle to the charter of the United Nations and their desire to live in peace with all peoples and all governments.
Okay, they are determined to safeguard the freedom, common heritage and civilization of their peoples, founded on the principles of democracy, individual liberty and the rule of law.
They seek to promote stability and well-being in the North Atlantic area.
Ah, the law of base.
It's not quite the North Atlantic.
They are resolved to unite their efforts for collective defense and for the preservation of peace and security.
They therefore agree to this North Atlantic Treaty, and then you've got all kinds of articles and that's pretty interesting.
Doesn't seem like it's exactly their charter, but I'd have to delve into it a little deeper to know for sure.
But it doesn't seem like their jobs should be sending people to war.
And of course, Afghanistan, I don't think their member of NATO, are they?
Need to check that.
No, tactics in Afghanistan.
I think it comes at a particularly sensitive time right now when after Budo's assassination, there's a big upsurge and violence coming out of the tribal areas in Pakistan.
The elements of the Taliban are surging and I think it's a little frustrating for all the military commanders at all the restrictions that they have in all the different kinds of rules for each country fighting in these large alliances.
But I think relatively speaking, NATO forces aren't really as well trained at fighting these complicated long-term surgencies, as say, a more conventional military attack with clear battle lines.
But I have to say that my experience over in Afghanistan, in Canada, our Canadian soldiers are adapting and changing every day to meet their incredible things they face of the IEDs on the side of the road and everything.
It's quite amazing to see and I was blown away by their professionalism and determination in the face of such a
odds.
It's quite something.
I think the UK, Canada, the Netherlands, Australia, New Zealand, Denmark all have a lot to be proud of for what they're doing over there.
The opium is part of the story.
Foreign insurgents are part of the story.
It's a huge story.
It takes a while to get around.
But I applaud you for bringing up on the show and bringing people more information.
I think everyone needs to know more.
So anyway, folder and I'm not going to say I love you.
So fuck you, Adam Curry.
I love you anyway, man.
No, homo.
Okay, I'd like to know more about NATO and how that actually works.
I guess that's the next step to understanding this because it just makes no sense.
And every single day I wake up and I have conversations with my wife and she listens to the BBC, which is still heavily biased towards all kinds of creepy things.
And we have conversations about this.
I say look, Ron Paul has the right idea.
Take everyone out.
Just take this leave.
I've pocketed on.
Use that $10 billion we spent.
You know, why are we over there?
I think we all know kind of the answer, but I still want to hear someone say it and I want NATO to cop to it.
I would make things so much easier.
As long as we understand why, of course, we give big props to our soldiers as I do to our policemen, our firemen, our teachers.
But not to Gordon Brown.
I just want to say one thing briefly to the UK listeners.
Okay, I'm going to change my opinion on Gordon Brown.
I thought this would be a great patriarchal figure.
He would be good for the country.
And now that I've really scrutinized him and he's had a chance to be in office for a couple of months.
This guy's a fucking tool.
And I don't know who he's working for.
But, you know, he's a fiscalist because he was the, the chancellor of the, extracur.
Basically, the dude who takes care of all the finances.
So he's a fiscalist.
He understands very well what's going on.
And of course, he indirectly or directly approved this 24 billion pound loan of UK taxpayers money,
which includes mine as well.
You know, we do employ 15 people over here.
You know, we do pay corporate taxes.
You know, it's our money, too.
To bail out a bank, a commercial institution to bail out Northern Rock.
And I just want to say a few things for the US listeners.
You have to understand Northern Rock is really almost like a building society.
It's more that's hence the Northern Rock.
It was really built.
I would have to say on the back of the wages of, of hard working Northerners in the UK.
A lot of minors.
I'm sure I contributed to the assets of the bank.
And really, it's a lending bank.
And, and as well as a, I think a retail commercial bank,
but lending bank above all for mortgages.
And they fucked up.
They were a part of the big game, which is now probably in the fourth inning.
Of what could it could turn out to be a much longer than it could be a 12 inning.
Easily.
But what kind of it's, you know, a third of the quarterway through this credit crunch
and banks are doing all kinds of crazy stuff because they've got to save their own asses.
Now remember, banks are commercial.
You know, it's not like it's not like we're shareholders.
Well, that just actually might happen because
So Gordon Brown signed this check.
It bailed out Northern Rock.
And now they've been waiting.
It's now coming up on two months.
Is someone going to come in and buy it?
Or are they going to nationalize it?
Now remember banks have shareholders.
So these shareholders, they're pretty much fucked either way.
But if someone comes in with private money,
at least there's some chance of working out a deal,
so they can get a couple pennies on the dollar.
If, if it's a nationalized, which means the government,
the country, the state basically owns it,
then all the shareholders get screwed over.
And they'll probably get zero.
Which is what the bank is worth,
except for the fact that there's a 24 billion pound loan
sitting right there.
That's 50 billion dollars.
Now, here's what's happening.
Uh, those are you in the UK.
You've seen Gordon Brown in China.
You've seen him on the news continuously.
And lo and behold,
who's along for the ride?
But Sir Richard Branson.
Now, you can tell me a lot about Richard Branson.
Uh, but there are very few people in the world.
And I don't, in fact, I don't think there's any,
any man alive who actually can be successful
at all these different, huge, diverse disciplines,
such as aviation, such as finance,
such as music, such as trains.
I mean, it, it really takes a lot of knowledge
to run any one of those.
I can run a company in any one of those industries.
And Richard Branson probably knows a lot about the music industry.
And he knows a lot about customers.
And he certainly knows a lot about the virgin brand.
But he's not the brain child.
And he's not operating virgin Atlantic or virgin USA.
To even example virgin Atlantic is actually run by Singapore Airlines.
And it's funded by the huge hedge funds, which sit underneath the virgin brand
and contribute money basically by, you know,
these are people who know what they're doing.
So when it comes to bids that virgin does for the national lottery
or for the trains, you know, it's Richard Branson.
Have you ever heard the guy say anything that he actually sounds like he knows what he's talking about?
Well, I haven't.
And he was interviewed by the BBC ITV channel for everyone's been interviewing him
all his over in China.
And the only thing he can say is, well, I think we have a good bid for Northern Rock.
Because he doesn't actually know.
He doesn't actually know the numbers.
He's not going to run it.
It's not his money.
Of course, he'll make money on it.
It's his brand.
And the feeling is that brand will save all.
Okay, that's well and good.
And of course, it makes a lot of sense because when Richard Branson comes to,
you know, here's a proper Englishman.
He's a sur.
And he's going to save the bank.
But what actually is going to happen, my friends, my fellows, citizens,
my fellow countrymen, my fellow residents of the United Kingdom,
is that an I believe Virgin will win the bid.
And they will immediately write out bonds,
which will go to China.
Because China is the savior of all at this moment.
They are going to save Northern Rock.
They're going to put billions of dollars,
pounds, euros, and yen into Britain in exchange for free trade,
essentially.
Everything's going to be made in China that you find here.
And you're going to see a lot of Chinese run around.
Now, nothing against the Chinese as far as I know.
Because I don't actually know any Chinese people.
But there's a lot of them.
You know, and when you give them the ownership,
then they'll come in and act like owners.
So we've got to be very, very careful about this bond business.
This is actually quite a fallacy because a bond is written,
and a bond is secured.
So it's my belief that Virgin will come in with maybe 10 billion pounds.
And we'll work out all kinds of financial ways
to basically start a new business with a 10 billion pound investment.
And another 10 to 15 billion will be secured by the state.
And we'll be owners or co-owners or not actually owners of Northern Rock,
but we will be guaranteeing these bonds for many, many years
to come five to 10 years at minimum.
So it's a total scam.
Total scam.
And Gordon Brown is just sitting there and coasting through it in plain sight.
And he's opening up the floodgates to China.
Which I think I'm not even saying is a bad idea,
but I think people need to understand what it could mean.
You know, any foreign ownership by any country.
I once read, I'll have to look up the quote and say,
see who said it, but when it comes to global issues,
will be us all when we awaken the sleeping giant that is China.
It's going to be an interesting couple of years, my friends.
I wish I was 15 years younger,
and I could be running around, protesting this shit.
I'll do a whole-dent-do-for-add-gile.
All I can do is, all I can do is inspire you with a song.
How about this one?
Come on and join the band.
Well, you need us loving and understanding.
Bring the family life, people will know.
This life beyond the share, break, tear.
Come on and feel it, you know.
It's coming to all.
What is all?
That's why I'm talking about Roger Glover and guests love his all and the butterfly ball apologies for the
for the crappy sound and I had the kind of record that one off the internet with audio hijacked
crow and it turned out kind of booming and crap but you get the idea it's a thought that counts right
and that's it for this daily source code episode number seven hundred and twelve of course
feedback is appreciated at amazonpodshow.com check out the new show the soundtrack of our lives
up saw dot pod show dot com op s o l uh and uh information on that on how you can send in your
stories as well so uh to appreciate if you give it a listen see if you like the idea and give me some
feedback daily source code dot com for the show notes and of course my weblog at curie dot com tomorrow
yes i think i will be able to do a show even though i have to go into the city for a couple meetings it's
not until later so hopefully in about twenty four hours from now we'll be back together again
another pod show podcast stick it in your ear