Make a statement with Sony stereo ear buds, sleek metal housings that reduce vibration
delivering killer sound from a tiny package, by yours at Sony.com-slashheadphones, Sony
ear buds with style meets sound.
Delta Shira Charley, 708.
Dynamic programming is what's all been missing.
That's the reason that you had swalli to do this click and listen.
You all came to the place where you can make a statement.
Reclaim it, regain control of entertainment.
Real people with ideas that stretch to go to is only one spot you can do that.
This pot show, the game is shut down of the company's lay down.
We're changing the rules and things stay sane now.
We're pot showers doing others want to copy us.
These catches like old hamburgers, they need to catch up.
The whack shows, whack shows with no spine any atty.
They're drowning in the sea in thirst for originality.
Pot show, both tsunami and earthquake.
To wave with the future and y'all are just in our wake.
Pot show the endless gorilla stint in that supervillain making the cannon still.
We're ripping it before the cellar.
Pot show up in the supervillain making the cannon still.
We're $16K employers worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content, in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into thisæ³.
Autistic, here's a new curry!
You are listening to the number one threat to our national security, Adam Curry.
I let off the airways, here is my request.
You don't have to play it, but I'll kill you best.
I've been listening to you show on the radio.
And you seem like a friend to me.
I'm your coach, I don't mind.
I'd be happy just to hear good boys say,
and this is for the girl who didn't sign her name.
Yes, she needs a dedication just to say.
Let us learn our stories,
swimming from place to place, my client Jason Slider.
People say I'm weary, but that's just a company I keep.
You make the night and race.
Ooh, I don't need to see your face.
You're sounding new.
You sounding good.
You sounding good to me.
I love the airways, here is my request.
You don't have to play it, but I'll kill you best.
I've been listening to you show on the radio.
And you seem like a friend to me.
I love the airways, here is my request.
You're sounding new.
Leave us, night and race,
swimming from place to place, my client Jason Slider.
People say I'm weary, but that's just a company I keep.
You make the night and race.
Ooh, I don't need to see your face.
You're sounding good.
You sounding new.
You sounding good to me.
You're sounding new.
You don't have to play it, but I'll kill you best.
I've been listening to you show on the radio.
And you seem like a friend to me.
Ooh, I've been listening to you show on the radio.
I love the airways, here is my request.
You don't have to play it, but I'll kill you best.
I've been listening to you show on the radio.
And you seem like a friend to me.
courtesy of the organization to the preservation of the soundtrack of our lives.
Charlie Doer, pilot of the airways.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code episode number seven hundred and eight.
The title that song showed up in one of my filters somewhere.
I can't remember it showed up yesterday.
I started to hunt around the net for it.
I looked on iTunes, couldn't find it.
I looked at my favorite MP3 search engine, seekpod.com.
It did show up one result, but it was a broken link.
And then finally, I found like a dog pile or whatever.
A really, really crappy version.
Very low, fidelatye.
And I remember the song a little bit hyper.
Then the what it sounded like just now.
But I don't know.
Just felt right today.
It's really crappy outside here in the United Kingdom.
Of course, coming to you from the curry manner.
We're in the attic in the manner here on the west side of G-town.
The affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gilford.
And Gailforce wins.
No flying from me.
Not today.
Although I have to tell you, I did dream about flying last night.
It's getting time to get.
It's been a couple of weeks.
In fact, I was it's a crazy dream.
I dreamt that I was flying a king air.
B-90.
Oh, maybe it was a C-90.
It was a big twin engine.
And I was flying all by myself.
And I was doing a lot of take-offs and landings.
Not quite what that means.
And this morning when I woke up, Patricia said that she had a dress.
She had, she told me.
She had a sexual dream about Tony Blair, which is quite concerning.
And I think there's reasons why she's having weird dreams.
And finally, today, I'll be able to tell you a little bit about what's going on
with the lady Patricia.
It's kind of a personal thing.
And I didn't feel like I could talk about it just yet.
Nor did I actually have permission from her to discuss it.
So, all you'll just have to wait.
I'll be talking about that a little bit later on in this show.
For those of you who are looking to curry.com thinking, is he going to do a live show today?
Obviously not because I said if it was going to happen, it would be around 7 a.m.
Eastern Standard Time.
It's probably 8 a.m. now.
Yeah, about 1 p.m.
Here in the UK.
Plenty of reasons over the number one reason.
I'm just not ready yet.
I tried testing some stuff out.
Yes, they actually.
I got several really good suggestions of software and systems to try.
One of these is this.
Check this out.
I don't have them.
This is for confirmed German.
Well, it's just listening to your show.
You're talking about the tool to interact with your listeners.
And I think I've just got there.
I think it's called Adobe Connect Professional.
Formerly called Mechan Media Breeze and they bought it.
It's a flash based online tool.
You can log on.
You can talk to your listeners.
They can talk back.
You could even connect the webcam.
So they can see you.
They can connect the webcam.
Let them.
I'm using it in my university with fellow students.
So if you want, check it out.
Yeah.
Love you, John.
John.
Yeah, I don't know if that's, you know, the webcam stuff is completely irrelevant.
In fact, I don't want people being able to look in and see me here in the studio.
It's something young, pull that loves doing.
And we do have a hit test coming up later.
In this program, since I will not be able to produce a footballer Friday show tomorrow.
Because I, I'm going into the city.
So it's just no way I'm going to be able to handle it.
So I'm not, I'm not really big on the webcam thing.
But I have to say hands down the most pimples.
Hey, you pimples out there.
The most pimples out there sent in this as a suggestion.
Yeah, I'm just listening to a DSC must have been 707.
And you were talking about doing a live interaction.
You know, there's a website called Talk to you that kind of does that.
And it's kind of cool because it allows you to, um,
for the, the colors to wait on hold and then you have a, um,
interface until allow you to unmute people and stuff like that.
Um, there's, uh, people that are using it.
Um, then at night or, um, I figure what they call it.
It was Adam, or Amber McCarthy and Leo Leport.
They do that and then you stalked you.
So check it out. Talk to you dot com.
Talk to you later Adam.
Thank you. Yeah, you know, I did check it out.
I set up an account and I tried to, uh,
to get a feel for how it was going to work in a real-life situation.
Um, and obviously I had no one else to call in.
So it was a little, uh, just,
I just didn't really have the time to focus on it entirely.
Although looking at the screenshots, it seems like it does have a lot of the,
a lot of the pieces that I'd want to use.
So that would be, uh, certainly it's high on the list as a contender.
Um, thinking about maybe doing some experiments over the weekend.
Just keep your eye on curry dot com.
Um, because that's where I'll announce.
Uh, and I also couldn't figure out how to make the announcement link work.
And yeah, it just, I'm sorry.
It was just too much going on.
Um, and also, um, what is it, uh,
uh, net meeting?
No, is it net meeting?
That's not what it is.
It's, uh, maybe it is.
Go to meeting?
No, what is it?
WebEx.
That's it.
I know WebEx has a pretty good system because we use that for our, um,
our, our pod show football Friday.
So when we connect all the offices up and we do presentations,
what's nice about that.
Obviously, it's stuff that I don't need for the show.
You know, you can show, um, your screen, essentially.
Uh, you can share that.
Um, I do know that the conference bridge is reasonably good.
So it'll be one of those two.
I'm pretty sure.
Uh, just stay tuned as I said to curry dot com.
We're going to, we're going to give it a whirl.
We'll get to it.
Let's see.
Um, lady Patricia, I want to tell you about her first this.
Allow me to introduce myself.
Macedonia, the name.
Beatsots, the acronym for the website and the show you need to have within your pod catcher been.
Both sides of the surface.
Independent and pod safe and worth the time it takes to zone out to the tones that you're
up in your headphones.
Hip hop, soul, funk and electronic harmonics that are sonically rich in nutrients,
guaranteed to give your mind body and soul what it needs.
Got it.
Let's start fulfilling broadband dreams through dial-up means an August of 2005 and continues to keep true vibes a lot.
Immentators with whack music gets stomped out like a roach.
All this from the poor man's podcast as low fine approach.
But high fine results.
Seriously.
You need to check this radio.
Beatsots.
www.beatsots.com.
www.beats.com.
Hey, I made another run.
Yeah.
Interesting show.
I love it when people do street poetry.
What the hell is that?
That's my Nokia Connect box.
At least that's what I call it.
Since I use a US cell phone, a US number that is on the Nokia E61 eye.
It's very expensive for data.
So I have my old E61, not the eye, just the regular E61, which Christina was using for a while.
We call it the brick.
It's literally indestructible.
I think a T-Mobile local T-Mobile account in there.
I use that for data.
I just throw it in my bag essentially.
When I'm using the N80010 web tablet on the road, it connects to it automatically through
Bluetooth, which is a perfect combination I might add.
But of course, it's T-Mobile.
So I can see from the number.
It's an 800 number.
It's probably T-Mobile calling to offer me something.
I really hate it when they do that.
So ignore.
Anyway, the Lady Patricia.
It's been so difficult not to tell you about what's been going on with her.
And it really just wasn't my place to talk about it.
But yesterday she said it was okay for me to discuss it on the show.
Now, you remember Monday, I said that I didn't do a show because there was some, I was in the hospital.
And I said everything was okay, but there was a lot of stuff going on.
And I kind of left it at that left some cryptic messages.
It was Patricia was in the hospital.
And let me explain why.
For those of you who've been listening to this show, you know that for the past year Patricia
has had often on some really serious abdominal pains.
This actually started in December of 2006 when she did the celebrity version of Dancing
with the stars or strictly come dancing as we say here in the UK.
She did that in the Netherlands.
And her dancing partner, your professional dancing partner, had done a lift on her.
And he kind of squeezed in her on her right side.
And she woke up in the middle of the night, you know, literally puking from pain.
And you know, she rushed to the hospital.
They tried to figure it out.
You know, they said, well, maybe it was something to do with her kidneys.
It could have been some kind of, you know, like kidney, not stones, but dust that would
had dislodged or something while she was doing all this extraneous exercise.
And this has basically been going on for a year now.
And we're varying degrees.
You know, sometimes it wouldn't bother her at all for weeks on end.
And then she would just have these incredibly painful attacks literally in her, in her side.
And I got to tell you, we've been through the mill here.
We have been through to every single doctor, every single specialist.
She's in the past, oh, in the past a couple months alone.
She's had the scans, you know, like a cat scan, you know, for cancer.
She had something that she definitely didn't want to talk about on the show.
Call an Oscar P.
It's not a very lady like thing.
You know, I've been with her throughout all of this.
And I have to tell you, it's really been a little bit concerning, worrying because, you know,
if you go off on her own and travel to the Netherlands, she can get an attack at any moment.
And you know, what if it happens on the airplane or just when there's no one there to help or so,
you know, it's been very worrisome.
And when I've been away for weeks on end in the States, you know, I keep the phone next to my bed.
And just hoping that it doesn't ring in the middle of the night with, oh, my God, you know,
I don't know how to attack.
And I don't know what to do.
That would be Christina, probably.
So we found another specialist, Professor Bailey, who is, and it guts, I guess, is his specialty.
He speaks all over the world.
And of course, this is not part of the National Health Care System here in the UK.
If you actually wanted to do all the things that we've done through the NHS, she would probably be,
it's still being a lot of pain and a lot of trouble because it takes so long to get, you know, anyone to sign off on anything.
And honestly, I questioned some of the, some of the quality of the health care because we found out.
So essentially, she had another attack.
This was just around the holidays.
And a really severe one.
And you know, and so my wife is lying here on the couch, you know, in tears saying,
you know, this is worse than contractions when I was pregnant.
Now, that's saying a lot to me, even though I, of course, have, you know, have no comparison.
I do understand what she's talking about.
So we called the Professor Bailey and said, look, we got to do something.
He said, all right, let's immediately.
And this was last week.
He said, let's, let's do a laparoscopy laparoscopy is where they make several small,
keyhole incisions and going with the camera.
Essentially, go take a look at what's going on with the, with her bowels.
And oh, by the way, you know, I've had the barefoot doctor over here.
I've had him do hand laying.
I've had, you know, I've had fucking mojo voodoo guys.
I've tried everything because you get so desperate, you know, and, and all the doctors say,
well, it's irritable bowel syndrome.
If fuck that, it's not irritable.
That's excruciating bowel syndrome.
And of course, what does irritable bowel syndrome really mean?
It's just a description for, you know, the area of where shit is messed up.
It's not really a diagnosis.
So, and she went on Monday.
And that's, of course, why I couldn't do the show.
And, you know, obviously, you know, when you're going into full general anesthetic,
you know, there's a, it's never really a fun ride.
And with her heart condition, there's all kinds of little nuances and little, you know,
little things that you have to be very careful of, particularly because her blood doesn't
clot as fast as others because of all the data blockers that she's taking.
So, you know, there's all kinds of parameters.
You know, it's, you know, it's, although it's a, it's a very common procedure.
It's concerning to say the least.
So, who went in around 11 a.m.
They came to take her away.
What is it about 130?
You know, it always lasts hours.
Takes hours for them to get that shit together.
And so I sat there for a couple hours, you know, pacing the room, waiting,
and then Professor Bailey came back in and he said, you are not going to believe this.
By the way, not necessarily what you want to hear from the doctor.
When he comes back after, you know that your wife's been operated on,
says you're not going to believe this.
So, let's take a look at the pictures.
Of course, I always ask for four video and pictures.
When is a camera involved?
And like, dude, would you please take some pictures or give me an MP4 files?
At least I have some record.
I've lots of interesting video of the insides of my wife.
He said, it was her appendix.
And he showed me this picture.
And this, my poor, my poor wife, poor girl.
She's been walking around with an infected appendix.
Probably for the better part of a year.
It's undetected.
I mean, it makes no sense.
She's had scans and tests and blood tests specifically to see if it had anything to do with her appendix.
And, you know, and no one called it, no one, no one pegged it.
Let's, let's put it that.
And Professor Bailey said, this is really, this is, he was angry.
He was really, and he's going to delve into this.
So he says, and talk to the people who did the scans and the other tests.
It was just an inflamed ball of crap sitting in there.
And it was the entire problem.
So appendix to me.
He, he ripped it right out.
And, and that was it.
Of course, you know, it's, it's still a major operation.
So Patricia, it's home.
She had to stay overnight.
I see.
I didn't tell you any of this.
You see how hard this must have been for me.
I was just bursting at the seams trying to explain.
But of course, I couldn't because, you know,
A, we didn't know it was going on B.
I didn't know if she even wanted me to talk about it.
But she is so happy that this alien infected life form has been removed from her body.
Even though she has a lot of pain still from the actual incisions,
because they make three of them for this keyhole operation.
And, and also, you know, they pump you full with air and gas.
And so she has, you know, pain in her shoulders.
Anyone who's who's been opened up kind of knows what that's like.
So the good news is we found it.
It's taken care of.
She can normal life can resume.
It can resume.
And once again, just goes to show how important health is.
And I wish great health for all of you for 2008.
And I'm sure I'll get the lady pee on maybe next week,
because I was planning on going to the States,
but I have to stay home because of the anesthesia and everything.
She's not even allowed to drive until the end of next week.
So Christina and I are, you know,
basically trying to keep the household running.
Doing a reasonable job, not the best of all jobs,
but a reasonable job.
So anyway, now you're up to speed on what's going on here.
And finally, getting some answers on the primaries,
how they work, and how these caucuses put together,
I'll put together.
Let me just give you a couple of pieces of feedback here,
because I think for those of you who are interested in what this actually is that's going on.
You know, which, of course, the mainstream media makes it look like we're already
electing a president, and there's already winners and losers.
Nothing could be further from the truth.
Particularly if you see what happened in New Hampshire,
boy, what an upset there.
Gee, the polls were wrong.
Go figure, why were they wrong?
Adam Denny says, hi, listening to your last show in a caucus.
People gather in groups, and they declare who they are for,
and people try to get the most votes for their favorite person.
And Iowa, the Democratic caucuses,
there you had to have 15% or better.
If the caucus, if the candidate in that caucus doesn't get the 15%
then the votes go to someone else.
So essentially, in this caucus, the parties sit together,
and they decide who their candidate is going to be,
and who's going to get the votes.
So primaries, as Adam Denny says,
is just like a regular election.
One thing to remember is that primaries is about winning delegates
to the convention.
I'm sure you've heard of the Democratic convention,
and the Republican convention.
So you want the delegates to go to this convention.
Those are the ones that are going to put forward the candidate.
So delegates is actually trying to read this here.
It's a little discombobula.
Delegates is who actually votes for the nominee.
There you go.
A perfect example is Mitt Romney, who came in twice,
who came in twice, who came in second,
and first in another election.
But as more delegates than the rest of the candidates.
So winning the state doesn't really mean that much.
It's all about the delegates.
So when you look at these results,
look at how many delegates each of the candidates has,
because the delegates are the ones that go to the convention,
and from there they choose their candidate,
and then we go into a general election for the presidency.
Here's another way to look at it.
Say Adam, it's Jesse and you answered your essay column.
Listen to the B.F.C. 7.6 in your explanation
of how the U.S. presidential election process works.
I think you did a good job, man.
I know.
I'll thank you for even more of the things and clear
in the three minutes you asked for.
The only point I would clarify,
or add to having voted in New Hampshire
in the primary yesterday myself.
You do not necessarily have to be registered as a Democrat.
All of the Republicans to vote in.
That's the corresponding primary.
Many voters, particularly in New Hampshire,
are registered as independent or on declared.
And they won't give them the choice of which primary to vote.
And then they can only vote in one or the other.
But I can choose these kind of going to vote
which primary I will vote in.
And I did my duty yesterday.
And I made choose to vote in a different party next time.
That's all.
Thanks.
All right, man.
Thank you.
Love you.
No, homo.
This is a great story.
I don't know if you picked this one up.
I saw it on techcrunch.com.
This just goes to show you how stupid the mainstream media is.
Now, in this case, it's the French mainstream media,
but you're just going to love this.
So apparently someone came up with an application on Facebook,
which made it look like this application was to elect
the president of Facebook.
And, you know, so you install it.
And then you can put yourself up as a candidate.
And then you could get votes.
And so this guy who I have to admit this guy looks very
presidential, which is named Arash Derem Barsh.
I'll put a link in the show.
And it's a daily source code.com.
So you can look at the read through the whole story.
It's just hilarious.
So he won this application's version of an election.
I don't like 9,000 votes or something.
It doesn't really matter.
But all of the French media jumped on the story.
And they're like, oh my god, it is fantastic.
The president of Facebook is Frenchman.
And every single big news outlet,
TF1, Le Plan, Express, France, International,
The Parisian, every single one of them reported on the story
without even checking with Facebook.
How hard can that be to check the source of the story?
And it's just, it's just,
for my mind, just another nail in the coffin of mainstream media.
You guys are so fucking lame.
And, you know, because other people reported on it,
we figured it's all copy and paste.
That's what I need to do.
I need to find that link.
Let me just write this down on my notebook here.
I wrote many years ago the copy paste culture.
And essay, I wonder if it's, it's probably
have to go to the way back machine to get a copy of it.
But I'll put a link in the show.
No time to look at that.
The copy paste culture, because this is exactly what mainstream media is all about.
It's all about copy paste.
There's absolutely no fact checking done whatsoever.
And what a great scam from these guys,
who put this together, really fantastic.
Okay.
As said, tomorrow, no football Friday,
because I'm going into the city.
We got all kinds of meetings and stuff.
I'm really, because of all this appendix crap.
I'm way behind on meetings.
So, I just got to catch up on stuff.
Luckily, Mr. Yon Poled is on the ball.
And he has put in his hit test submission early.
So, let's enjoy hit test one.
Oh, four.
One crowd casting.
With Adam curve.
The video version once again.
You ready to be stumped.
Because he is the good texture.
With Yon Poled.
Hey, Adam, this is hit test number 104.
And we're going to start right away with intro number one.
The next.
That's it.
Hit it.
Um, uh, Fleetwood Mac, go your own way.
Yeah.
Number two.
Uh.
Good.
Everyone's champagne king.
Shame.
Keep the fire burning.
Something like that.
And the final one is number three.
Out.
Wait.
Yon.
Do you really want to hit me?
Good songs, Yon.
I think I got them all this time.
Not sure about everyone's champagne king though.
And times up in these ID answers.
Answer number one is from 1977.
Love and hear.
It's the right thing to do.
You can go your own way.
Go your own way.
You can go this under the right day.
Don't leave it.
You can go your own way.
This is not you before.
Good.
But Fleetwood Mac can go your own way.
But thanks for suggesting the song.
This is answer number two.
I love this song.
From 1978.
Evelyn King.
This is Shane.
Shane.
Good.
Keep the fire burning.
Yeah.
There you go.
I got it right.
Shane.
Keep the fire burning.
Yeah.
Your home.
That's my home.
Shane.
Oh man.
That takes me back.
And what happened?
That feeling champagne king.
As answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
Wow.
Do you really want to hurt me?
Do you really want to make me cry?
Bit by by without reason.
I'm prepared to let you go.
Do you really want to hurt me?
Do you really want to make me cry?
Boy, George.
Yo.
Do you really want to hurt me?
And do you really want to hurt me from 1982?
As answer number three.
And that's it for hit this number one out four.
Yeah.
So Adam, how did you do?
Three out of three on.
As always.
And I keep repeating myself at the end of the hit test.
The iTunes link so you can buy these tracks online together with the answers to this hit test.
Or to be found at hittest.barsho.com.
Thank you for playing again Adam.
Thank you for listening everybody else.
And watch it.
And next we got to be back for hit this number 105.
So until then, take care.
Bye bye.
For feedback, test at gmail.com.
info, young bullet.com.
And POLVT.com.
So, if you look at hittest.barsho.com.
You can see the video version of this.
I got to tell you.
First of all, the production value is amazing.
And Yon, what exactly is this guy has a studio?
I'm jealous of it.
Yon, would you please write down what,
I mean, I'm looking at these at some awesome looking software that you're using.
For the audio, you've got a beautiful mixer and please.
I want a YonPolette studio, man.
You know, it's all fine and dandy, but that shit looks good.
I'm jealous.
All right.
I'm turning green here.
Another great hit test.
Thank you very much, Mr. YonPolette.
See what else do I have here?
Of course, you probably heard about the video of these Iranian fast boats
that apparently were circling around US warships in international waters,
so they claim.
But the Iranians, this is another one of those mainstream media things.
The Iranians are saying, you know, the video that the US showed was fake.
And they have their own version of the video, where these guys are basically just
rolling out to the ships and saying, hey, are you doing?
We're over here.
You're over there.
And I don't know who to believe in this.
But I certainly would be very dismayed if this was being used as a catalyst to go to war with Iran.
Let's be very, very careful people.
And let's not just believe any kind of video that's being put out there with the
connotations of they're being an attack on US property.
Really, really concerning.
I'll put a link to that story.
I'm sure you've heard about or read about it by now.
Oh, and this one, this is this really pissed me off.
You know, I'm a big fan of GoDaddy.
And of course, you can use my codes to get great deals on domain names at godaddy.com.
If you want to domain name for $6.95, which is nothing,
you can use checkout code DSC3.
And I have two other codes.
You can find them in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
You can use those for, you know,
that's like, I think there's a 30% offer,
offers an offer or 10%.
It's a good deal.
It's all written down there, so use those.
But I've always wondered about this.
Apparently, network solutions.
And this was a story uncovered by the Enquirer,
which is kind of like a tech news site here.
That's produced here in the UK.
Apparently, what these guys have been doing
and I have wondered about this.
If you search for a domain name, so let's say,
love you know homo.com, which is, would be,
by the way, it's a great domain name.
If you search for that,
it'll show up as taken,
because what these guys, what these cock suckers,
we're doing, and I don't know if they're still doing it.
What they were doing is they'd take the search,
you know, it's called a who is search.
And if you search through their domain name,
they'd take the results of that search,
and immediately reserve that domain name,
so that you could only buy it through them.
I think there's like a five day grace period
where they can do that kind of stuff.
And I've always wondered about that.
I've always thought, you know,
me with conspiracies, right?
I always thought, it doesn't make a lot of sense
for a company who has evil intentions.
To look at the search that someone's doing
on a domain name.
And then immediately claim and say, oh, no, sorry,
you can back order it and charge them twice as much.
This is exactly what these guys were doing.
I don't know about the charging twice as much bit,
but they were definitely reserving it
so that if you then went to, if you search for it on godaddy.com,
it would show up as already taken.
So you could only register it in that five day period
through network solutions.
I think these guys should be fucking crucified for this.
That's really, really nodding.
And frankly, I'm annoyed that this isn't getting
a lot more play.
So again, link in the show notes,
dailysourcecode.com.
You should check that out for sure.
All right.
Let's talk about some music here for a second.
Hi, Adam.
This is Justin from San Francisco,
calling again.
I just finished listening to the black crow.
I'm going to do you see it now.
Amazing.
Awesome.
Except for one thing.
I noticed you encode your show at 96.
Oh my God.
I mean, it's okay if it's just talking
about when you play music and when you play good music,
like the black crow, it sounds like crabs.
Can't you bump that up just a little bit?
I think my heart drives mine.
I part can handle a couple more megabytes of your show.
Can you think, consider doing that for me?
All right.
Thanks, Adam.
Very interesting.
Yeah.
Love you, too.
No, homo.
Very interesting.
You know, the bit rates.
This is what he's talking about.
Basically, the quality that this show is recorded with
is something that we experimented with many years ago
and really tried to find the perfect balance between
file size and quality.
So the next obvious step up would be, I guess,
128 kilobit per second encoding rate instead of
what I'm doing now, which is 96.
And, you know, we really thought that this was
more or less the sweet spot.
And I think a lot of people recorded this bit rate
because, you know, now it's basically about a megabyte
per minute of audio that is created.
Which I think is just about right.
And I understand what you're saying where you know,
you wish you could hear a better quality copy of it.
But I guess in that case, you should go buy the track, right?
That's, or actually, there's another question about it.
A good one that relates to this.
You know, for those of you who just want to consume music,
if you're not a producer, if you're not making shows,
what do you do with pod save music?
I don't know, it's been able from running area again.
Just go to, to say, just with me in 707,
and you talked about pod save, what have you.
But it was mostly from the artist's point of view,
and the producer's point of view.
And I've been a bit mystified kind of from the listener point of view
and a music consumer point of view.
What the kind of correct way of proceeding is,
if you like a song that you hear on a pod show,
am I supposed to go to the pod save music network
and download it, or am I supposed to go and buy it from somewhere?
Or do I have to go and see where the band published it?
Just wondering, how about the side of the business works?
And who I should give my money to, because it was,
and I don't like, I don't like you, but I do like you.
I'm just, well, you know, make some emotions.
It's hard. Mixed, I know.
It's hard.
Oh, you do love me if it's hard.
Yeah, okay, so that's a very good question, actually.
Now, whenever I play a song from the pod save music network,
you'll see in the show notes that I link to a page at podshow.com.
Now, this link will not take you to the pod save music network,
but it takes you to the artist's page at podshow.com.
And right there, you'll be able to play all of the songs
in the quality that the artist uploaded it to the network in,
which is usually pretty high quality.
You know, all things considered about MP3s, which, of course,
in general are just really not that great when it comes to quality.
We are really depriving our ears of quality music,
but that's a whole another conversation for another day.
Right there, you can take the player, the artist's player,
and you can export that, you can insert into your webpage,
you can put it on your Facebook, or your MySpace,
or your Weblog, or whatever.
And you can play one song, you can play all of them through.
Now, some of the artists have made these tracks available for purchase,
and there's a little green buy mark next to it.
And essentially, you can then buy that track,
which will be a free and clear MP3 to download.
Or you can go look at the artist's website.
They often have free downloads available,
or they'll have links to iTunes.
I mean, that's kind of the whole idea here.
You know, when you listen to a song on the regular terrestrial radio,
it's all compressed, and the quality is all fucked up,
just because of the way radio stations make their signal sound.
Very much like I do.
I mean, I compress the shit out of my show, because the way I want it to sound.
If you really want the song, the whole point is you've heard the song,
you like the song, go buy it, go buy it, search for it on iTunes,
go to emusic.com, go to Amazon,
that is essentially the point.
If you really want the quality from the, by the way,
go to CDBaby.com, get the CD, so you get a really high quality version.
That's kind of the way it's supposed to work.
So the freebie part is that you hear it on your favorite show,
that you're able to listen to it online,
just like, you know, you can listen to lots of artists tracks
on, you know, with a my space player or whatever.
You can, you can kind of get the, you know, get the emotion,
get the vibe of the song.
And if you want it, that's the point we were counting on you
to fulfill your end of the bargain.
Go buy the song, support the artist.
That's the way it's supposed to work.
And I have to say, so far, I'm pretty pleased.
Adam Curry, with 16 million dollars with their planes,
grab my ass.
This is Mark, Mark's the,
I have something, might be interested,
a guy named Chip Tatum.
If you do search on Google,
YouTube or something about search,
it's not really really interesting stuff about,
you know, whole free CIA thing,
and very interesting stuff.
Stuff you haven't talked about yet.
So yeah, check it out.
Take care.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Good suggestion.
Chip Tatum.
I did Google the guy and looks like he was in the CIA.
Around the time my uncle was,
maybe a couple years later,
but also in some of the regions.
So I only heard this comment just before I started doing the show.
So I haven't dealt into it.
Just when I thought that I was done with all the conspiracy shit.
Now you give me another name to go and investigate.
Thanks.
But a good one.
It looks like the guy has some interesting stories about him.
So I'll definitely be on the lookout for that.
Here's something that's showed up.
This showed up yesterday.
For those of you who don't know,
I do a weekly show with John C. Devore,
I called no agenda,
which is exactly that.
The show has no agenda.
We just fire up the Skype,
fire up cast blasted record about
anywhere between 30 minutes in an hour of us just talking about stuff.
And it's caught on.
It really has.
People really are digging this show.
The numbers are just growing astronomically.
And yesterday,
I kind of equated to one of those 1960s answer records.
Where you know, you had Neil Sadaka did.
Oh, Carol.
And then I forget who it was who did a song called.
Oh, Neil.
You know, answer records.
Kind of like what Eminem did at one point.
And two savants who are definitely
members of the stable of savants here on the Charlie.
Namely, the candy man Luke from Nokia,
and our very own comic strip blogger have created a show
in response to no agenda called Yo Agenda.
And their first episode is episode number 11,
which I really didn't get it at first,
but then I understood,
essentially, Yo Agenda is a number 11 is in response
to no agenda number 11.
We've done 11 episodes so far.
And I just wanted you to hear a little bit of this show.
If it would be somebody else involved,
I was going to have some kind of...
There was this, I should have queued this up.
I'm sorry.
There was this, this is one piece where the,
you know, John and I were talking about the,
the no-row virus.
And the fact that I refused to puke,
I just haven't peaked in 30 years.
Let me just find this bit for you,
where they're talking about vomiting.
It's so funny.
There's nothing like a guy from Finland
and a Polish guy in Germany
talking about puking, hold on a sec.
Let me see.
I think that's around here.
I know exactly what to...
So you had a moustache nutty.
Yes, my old family was out with all my rods.
So here, here Lucas talking about his family
having the no-row virus as well.
It's just funny.
But I don't know for us,
it took only 24 hours.
And usually it takes only three to five days.
So I don't know what,
if Adam is really weak or what's happening to him,
but it sounds quite long.
Let's say more than seven days to be down with the no-row virus.
So probably has something to do with the fact that he doesn't puke.
So if you puke them,
you can read over it immediately.
And if you don't puke,
it kind of stays in your system.
So I think that generally puking and vomiting is a healthy,
because you throw away all the stuff in it,
because you can both sides.
You should try to puke and vomit through everything.
Some fine advice there.
Please check out this show.
You will not be disappointed.
I put it in the Daily Source Code channel as well.
So you can pick up the latest episode.
You'll agenda.podshell.com.
Adam, it's Paul Durham from Black Lab.
You know, as the New Year begins,
I've been looking back at all this stuff we've done recently.
And it's hard to believe that it's been almost two years
since we first put see the sun up on the PMN.
Along with releasing two albums this year,
the highlight of 2007 was of course the roller coaster ride
that was bummerous to charts.
And the tremendous support we received from the New Media community.
We don't play live months these days,
but back in the summer of 2006,
we did play a special acoustic set in San Francisco live at Podshow HQ.
Until now, only a handful of crazy Podshow folks over there have heard it.
But as a token of our gratitude to all the podcasters
who've shown us their support over the last two years,
we here at Black Lab Central are releasing the show as an acoustic EP.
Available as a free MP3 download at blacklabworld.com slash podshow.
So come over and grab the exclusive live at Podshow EP
and check out our two new albums technology
and passion news a trace.
So thanks again, everyone.
And you know, I love you about a company.
Dance, you can feel fine.
You can dance a little twist.
You turn your pretty red head back.
You've got the eye access.
Can you see yourself in my better night?
Would you leave me at the side of the road?
Won't you walk right up to me?
Would you talk to me?
All right, yes.
Don't mind me.
More at it back.
Baby, back in your leaves.
You teach me how to fly.
You see, I'm scared to die.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
Keep me up at night.
You'll be there all the world if I should.
For you.
I feel like the spot is staying like a memory in my mind.
I feel like the morning fell like the bottom's falling out.
I can see what's up there all the way down in the valley below.
I can walk right up to you.
I can talk to you.
More at it back.
Baby, back in your leaves.
Can you teach me how to fly?
You see, I'm scared to die.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
Keep me up at night.
You'll be there all the world if I should.
You see, I'm scared to die.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
You see, I'm scared to die.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
You see, I'm scared to die.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
Keep me up at night.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
You see, I'm scared to die.
Won't you just be gone too long?
Teach me how to fly.
Keep me up at night.
You'll be there all the world if I should.
Mostly you.
There you go, that's how it's supposed to work.
Black, hand it out the freebies.
Learn the crawl.
You can find it.
I'll put the link in the show notes.
Of course, there's lots of black, lavender, pod tape music.
Now work as well.
Before I go, I'll remind you of the voice.
You become it.
I'm thinking maybe I should, uh, while I'm at it, maybe I should, uh, give you the UK number
as well because, uh, well, let's face it.
I like hearing from my British friends.
Here's your number.
Let's 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 16, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3, plus 4, 4, 2, 0, 7, 16, 1, 3, 7, 5, 3.
And with that, I'll sign off again, no show tomorrow, but look for experiments happening
over the weekend.
Keep your eye on curry.com, uh, probably going to do one of these talk shoot type things.
See if we can, uh, see if we can make it work.
So I'll announce it in plenty of time, uh, for the experiment to actually, uh, make some
sense.
Adam at podshow.com is my email address dailysourcecode.com as we can find all the show notes,
links to everything discussed in this program.
And for sure, we'll be back next week.
Have yourselves a great weekend, live your life with passion, and enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow pod guest, stick it in your ear.
Dramatically reduce ambient noise by up to 85% with Sony's noise canceling headphones
at work, home or travel, shut out the noise and really enjoy your tracks.
Get yours at Sony.com slash headphones, Sony headphones, your music never sounded so good.