Delta share a Charlie's 7-8-4.
Delta share a Charlie's 7-8-8-4.
Baby, baby, baby, baby
But then come meet
Why don't you sleep
Ask me to forgive
Fuckin' and fuckin'
To live with you, baby
But you must live with you
All this one little thing
Don't want to stay near it
Baby, baby
Don't want to live
To live with you, baby
Yeah
Baby, baby
Baby
You stretch to the living room
Mad hair of that too
I was a girl of a man
I met you
I met you, sorry
Oh, but I'm not a star yet
You'll be when I show my hand
Baby, you've come to tell me
Don't want to stay near it
Baby, baby
If you live with you, baby
With you must live
All this one little thing
Don't want to stay near it
Baby, baby
Don't want to live with you
Baby
It's two little three, which was who was all this one little chain.
Yes, you little three, which was who was all this one little chain.
It's two little four, two little three, from the pod save music network,
to be found at music.neveo.com.
As well as pod save music network.com, of course.
Nice.
Come on boys, they come.
Oh, fade out. Oh, man, what a bummer.
I don't like fade out. That's so, eh.
80's. Hey, how you doing? Everybody's dating source code episode number 784.
Adam Curry here in the curry manner.
Hey, we only spoke to each other a day or so ago, and I'm even going to try and do a show tomorrow.
Friday might even have a three show week. Imagine that.
Lots to talk about. That's the main reason.
You guys are just hammering me with information these days.
There's so much coming in, so much to process.
And I'm starting to kind of figure out how citizen journalism should work because, you know,
it's not, it's not the journalism part per se. I mean, let's face it.
Something isn't really truth until it's been in the newspaper, right?
I mean, that's the for the 99.9% of the rest of us out there who get our information from mainstream media.
It's not proof until it's been in the newspaper.
You know what? A lot of the stuff that we're seeing, a lot of the questions that are asked about
how our world is run, about our government, about us as people or slaves is written about.
And it's written about by really good journalists. And I think our job, this is what I'm seeing,
our job is to aggregate that.
Adapinian as you wish, but aggregated, aggregate their own words, aggregate their own media.
The truth is really out there. Or as I'd like to say, there aren't no secrets only information you don't yet have.
And the minute you start to aggregate something, you've got, you know, five, ten,
fifteen or fifty sources, that becomes pretty compelling evidence to point to someone and say,
look, you know, here's the New York Times writing about it.
Here's the Washington Post writing about it. Here's the Wall Street Journal writing about it.
Here's a, here's a Fox news affiliate writing about it.
That's very powerful stuff because it truly is, it's really the editors. A lot of stuff sneaks by.
And they learn a lot of stuff we'll buy, but the editors aren't just such tremendous pressure to tow the company line.
And that's really, that is really our bottom line. So aggregate and promote, I would say,
that's how we work together with our brothers and sisters in mainstream media who again are under tremendous pressure.
It's almost like a media virus, you know, everyone knows exactly what to do.
It knows exactly how to treat the audience.
Condescendingly, I might add most of the time, but it's not their fault. It's the system.
They're all our brothers and sisters. Some of them, you know, one hundred is a psychopath.
Those are the ones that usually wind up becoming president or prime minister.
And I'm not joking about that.
And that, of course, pulls in more psychopaths into government, the justice system.
Not all of them are bad, but the rest of them have to tow the line.
Got it, got to do, got to survive. That's all what we're all doing.
We're all just surviving.
On, yeah, you'd almost call it a prison plan.
I know it's not original, but it's kind of funny how a, a proposal it is.
Anyway, I didn't really want to start off with that.
I, well, it does have a little bit to do with my first topic for today.
And that is about a blog post that I read written by Tim Borkin.
Tim is the founder.
I believe with his brother, but I think he's really, he's really the guy that's run it all.
Tim Borkin is the founder and CEO of the new media expo, which took place last weekend in Las Vegas.
I did not attend this year.
I certainly could have, I considered it more than more than once.
In fact, I had an idea to take a buddy of mine out to LA from LA out to Vegas.
We could hook up in Vegas and have some fun and hang out.
Because that's really what it's always been about for me.
I haven't attended every single year, but certainly the first one.
And I never saw a business benefit to the new media expo, not for the business that we're in.
Anyway, so Tim, I have a tremendous amount of respect for him for what he's been doing and what he's been building.
He's an entrepreneur.
And I have massive respect for that.
Anyone who tries and follows the dream and trying to do something and build something.
And literally with his bare hands is great.
So kind of disheartening to read his five reasons why he's thinking about quitting the trade show business.
And he goes on to list a whole bunch of things.
I can just give you the top line.
Of course, links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
One, high speed internet costs.
Of course, you get ripped off when you use a convention center type of scenario.
Something called drag, which I don't think if that's the way you pronounce it.
I'm very familiar with it.
It's all this convention stuff is all unionized.
And you can't touch your box.
And I've been through that.
It sucks ass.
Pay to play mentality.
Very interesting.
This is probably one of the hardest parts.
I mean, this is a business.
It's, you know, this trade show stuff is a real business.
And it works in a certain way.
And typically, you know,
you'll have, you'll have vendors who will say, you know what?
We'll buy a booth and we'll sponsor.
But it's, you know, buy booth if our VP or CEO, whatever can speak.
So, you know, it's kind of a deal.
And in fact, that was, we had a little chat about that before the very first podcast
and new media expo when the word podcast was still attached to the property.
Where we were asked to sponsor.
I think it's like $25,000.
And we were offered a keynote slot.
And I said, well, not really interested in speaking.
Because I don't really see the benefit.
And I think it would be, you know,
more like a whole year than that type thing.
You know, I want to come and hang out.
But, you know, also, I really don't see the benefit of it.
You know, honestly, I just don't see the business benefit.
You see the benefit of hooking up with people who work with our network,
now, mevio, then pod show.
And, you know, so we threw a party.
And, but we've always made sure that we've always gotten a return on our money
in the form of programming.
So, everyone that we sponsored or paid for to go out and hang out,
basically, was always associated with the programming that had to be delivered.
And everyone made shows and delivered on that.
And otherwise, it was pretty much about how do I make money.
And that's really the crux of the issue.
Because there really is no money in the so-called pod casting industry.
Michael Gohagan says, he says appropriately on his blog.
Michael Gohagan, one of the early pioneers,
he was a great radio, I think.
And I tried to hire him, by the way.
He didn't want to, he didn't want to do something on his own.
So, that's a cool lot of respect for him.
He says, pod casting is not an industry.
It's a community.
And that's absolutely true.
And that's the way we've treated it.
And so there's a problem right there.
It's not an industry because, you know,
really, when it comes to vendors, you know,
what's a vendor for a podcaster, you know, Apple?
I think he had like Microsoft and a couple other big companies come in
and have some booths, but I don't know if they really have the goods.
I mean, it's kind of freaky, you know,
it's like the NAB, the National Association of Broadcasters.
They have a convention.
Yeah, the vendors, you know,
there's tons of expensive and really cool automation
shit and, you know, it's very different.
We really don't need much more on a laptop and a bit of software.
You know, how many vendors are you going to get?
So, but also,
it's really about one thing.
You know, how do we make money at this?
And as I was reading around, you know,
obviously I looked at a couple of views,
Paul Colligan, how to review.
And it sounded like a lot of the sessions were good and very helpful.
But, you know, that can almost be like a pod camp or,
you know, you don't necessarily have to put together.
I mean, it's really the whole vendor thing,
I think, is where it sucks because you have to play
by stupid rules, old fashioned way of doing stuff.
So, I want to say something about making money,
but first I want to wrap it up and say to Tim,
you know, dude, you've totally got it in your fingers.
You know how to build stuff.
And I think, yeah, you probably should quit the trade show business
and I hope you didn't get too burned on the new media expo.
I know that the numbers weren't, you know,
I know the number of attendees wasn't quite what you wanted.
At least I've read that.
And, you know, a lot of people bailed on speaking with sucks.
But I think you should quit it.
You know, why don't you change that to reinvent it?
I really think you can.
I really do think you can.
And I think that, you know, you'll find ways to make money,
but it's just not in the traditional way.
It's just not how it's going to work with hotel rooms and all that crap.
And maybe Vegas was just, you know,
I understand why I understand that it makes so much sense
and business plan to make that jump.
And then it's very disappointing.
But if anyone's going to change the trade show business,
it's going to be you.
Now about making money.
Michael Gohagan wrote extensively about this.
Now I'm not going to preach one way or the other.
But I do want to say one thing about something he wrote on his blog.
I think it was in reference to the expo.
Says that, you know, the only sponsor of podcasting is GoDaddy.
So let me just say a couple things about that.
First of all, I met Chris from GoDaddy.
I met Chris from GoDaddy at Nomedex,
which was many years ago.
And which just goes to prove the point, you know,
I wouldn't have known her if she hadn't come up to me and was talking
and we were chatting for a while.
It wasn't until about 45 minutes that she handed me a card
and said, you know, we should hook up.
And the time now is like, I'll goDaddy.
I don't know my name, guys. Okay.
Interesting.
But she was very, very smart.
And Nomedex, not the conference itself,
but the hanging out part, which is why I like getting together
hanging out, hey, I'll buy the beer anytime for that,
which we've done.
We've bought the beer many times,
particularly at hookups like the expo.
Because that's where good shit comes out.
And goDaddy is not a sponsor.
Okay. This has to be really understood.
Because now here we are four years into the lifetime of my company
and we're still going.
And even though times are a little bit challenging,
certainly for advertising,
the part of our business that we consider to be transactional
is extremely successful for us and the people working with us on our network.
And because I know a lot of these people really don't,
for whatever reason they rarely speak up.
Actually, that's not true. They do,
but the most vocal voices are the ones that are loud and complaining
and many of them.
And it kind of drowns out the success stories.
And we have certainly 200 programs
and produces associated with those programs.
Audio and video who are doing very well on our network.
And it's for two reasons.
So let me talk about the transactional business.
What we've discovered and not we as in me,
me, via or whatever.
But what we have collectively discovered is that
our audiences who are really our customer, who are our client,
are so loyal that they will buy things through you.
With full disclosure, knowing that if you use checkout code
and DSC3, you get your domain name from GoDaddy for 695
for a year.
And then I get a piece of that.
That's fully disclosed, everyone understands it.
It's not really advertising.
It's actually super advertising.
Because you're only going to do this if it's relevant to your audience.
You can package it any way you want to.
In fact, I just didn't add right there,
without even really making it not about the content.
It just fits right in, right?
And with the proper support,
we have five people working on our transactional business
who support the campaigns continuously.
That means supporting the producers,
but also, and we don't just have GoDaddy.
Let me give you a couple other examples.
We have pet meds.
We have e-music.
We have budget rent to car.
We have Drobo.
And all of these are transactional deals.
And really, it's almost like QVC needs a weird version of MTV, if you will.
The way QVC works, which is the piece that is a part of our maintaining of the campaigns,
is we have now developed a system where we can vet the right company,
which includes something that the audience will probably already want to buy
or we'll be in the market for.
So there's a lot of research that goes into that.
Then we need to go and acquire the best deal,
not just for our customers, for our audience, because it has to be anything else anywhere online.
It has to be the price.
And boy, give you a difference.
It's a Nokia with the Nokia N10 promotion man.
We were fighting Amazon all the way down.
It was amazing.
And Nokia worked with us.
If it's got to be the best price anywhere.
It's got to be cheaper than Amazon.
Otherwise, it won't work.
That's the system.
So with GoDaddy, you can't get a cheaper anywhere else.
Except perhaps from some other podcasters.
But then again, here's where it comes into play.
We can deliver in volume, because we have a system.
We have a support.
Yeah, a support and management team for these campaigns.
Yeah, it's a lot of work goes into it.
And then, of course, we ensure that our producers get the highest bounty of all of these deals.
So it's really, we're doing a lot of business to make this work.
We, of course, profit.
And it's really what you might call a rev share.
And we also spend money on marketing our shows that are part of these campaigns.
And this is about to become a million dollar a month business.
And this is big.
This is really, really big.
And particularly, if you get the formula right.
And the cool thing is, you can do this on your own.
Or anyone can join mevio and join in campaigns.
When we're not quite ready to accept them, just saying that.
Because, you know, we want to be careful, because it is a lot of work.
And the teams are already pretty strapped on what we got going now.
So they're not just sponsors.
It is a new version of being an intermediary between the producer of a product,
whether it's a physical, real product or virtual, like GoDaddy.
Yeah, it's, I said, just lost my train of thought there for a second.
But it's working.
It's really, it's really what we proved early early on with the sense sale.
I sold a lot of sense sale machines.
And it was clear that it was working.
So this is something new.
And I don't want it to just be poo pooed as, well, you know,
if GoDaddy wasn't around, then no one would be making any money.
No doubt about it.
If GoDaddy fell over tomorrow, it would suck massively.
But there are more companies getting into this and more brand names,
as highly, highly, highly interesting.
Now, just in the other side, the only other way we're able to monetize at the moment on video.
And by the way, the transactional business works best in audio,
but particularly works well if someone does video and audio together.
It's also much easier for us to promote video and send people who are interested in the topic of the show over there
to watch some things.
So it's just for a number of reasons, including technical and industry standards.
It's just much easier.
Has to do with flash players, not it's very frustrating.
But also it's just two different media forms.
So some is appropriate, some isn't.
And just so you know, the only other way that we're making money,
which is now really starting to crank up and we're seeing some advantages of the economy crunching,
is we're selling it just like television.
And then honestly, that's what the media buyers want.
They want it just like television.
And it's pretty roll in its 15 seconds,
and it's totally not related to the content,
and it's old fashioned, and it's dominant interruptive.
But that's what's going on.
And honestly, I got very tired of trying to tell people holding the check that they were going about it the wrong way.
That's not a good way to build a business.
Doesn't mean that we don't have ideals in the when advertisers start to experiment,
and maybe change their ideas and minds that we won't be there for them and ready because we will.
And we've had lots of adventurous advertisers who have already jumped on board and tried stuff.
But at the end of the day, it's about massive reach.
It's about repetition.
And it's about that being pre-rolled and on video.
I just want you to know that that's what it is.
And for that, you really need to be part of a network one way or the other.
But for transactions, anyone, I mean, look, I know, I know guys who are making hundreds of thousands of dollars.
And they're working very hard because, you know, you've got to be communicating with the audience offline as well as online.
In other words, not just through your show, but you've got to follow up.
It's a shitload of work.
I'm lazy.
I'm happy I don't have to do it.
Still, I mean, there's thousands of dollars that are being accredited to the daily source code on a monthly basis.
I don't get it.
Of course, it goes into the pot.
And I'm not doing anything.
You know, when's the last time I talked about budget rent at car?
I mean, I always say go to the show notes and you can see all the deals there and their fantastic deals.
And the system works.
And you can do it with relatively small audience.
Really, you can.
And that's what makes it beautiful.
But even better, you don't have to.
You can find any place to upload your stuff and build your audience.
You don't need to be making money.
You can just do it for whatever reason you want.
Okay, crap.
How long have I been talking?
Let me just see.
What is that?
Shit 20 minutes.
I got so much to go through today.
I'm never going to make it.
All right.
Let me play this from from the candy man.
Here we go.
Hello, Adam.
It's candy man speaking here.
It's time with the kids for the audience.
How to make better use of this trophy.
Voice mail.
Yeah, that's something that I'm glad you bring that up.
Candy man.
The drop.au slash daily source code, which is such a valuable resource.
I wish those drop guys would put a search in.
Because so many times like, oh, I know there's something here.
I want to find that file that posting.
It'd be great if we could have that search.
So I'm sure that they're thinking about that.
And I've already tried to have Google.
Google search didn't work.
I guess it doesn't crawl it or whatever.
But yeah, it's it'd be very awesome.
If you can send your voice mail through to drop.au slash daily source code.
And so the bummer about it is you got a first dial the number.
Then you have to dial an extension.
And so Luke has a little solution to that candy man.
Hey, line.
Because this this five digits code that you are.
We're sharing.
Yeah.
And two zeros in code.
So it's an extension code.
So that's also why you see in the.
X between the number and the and the five digits code.
So that's.
Expansion code.
And the actually it's quite easy to use that.
If you program.
The drop.au phone number into your phone.
Then you add a P for pause.
And pressing.
Nokia phone.
You can find the P under the.
Under the star button.
When you are a programming.
Okay.
I'm listening to your memory.
And then you add this five five digits extension code.
So your phone will then just dial the drop.au.
Okay.
So it dials the number.
And then it'll actually pause before it hits the.
The DMTF tones or whatever.
Well, it's not number.
It's with a weight for a while because of the P.
DTMF.
I'm sure.
So the post for the.
Let's a collection to be established.
And then it will start dialing the extension number.
And your.
Or two other medical.
To do.
Or smell books.
So not the real.
Problem in mild being.
If you just program the whole thing.
Into your phone.
All right.
It's one number.
Then it goes quite smooth.
I get it.
I know.
That was a.
Use.
Can you man.
Can you.
Thank you so much.
Love.
Love my Nokia phone.
By the way, the E71.
Which I bought.
Instead of the iPhone.
God.
I love this phone.
Several times a day.
I say, I'd love this fucking phone.
I really do.
A couple of things.
I don't like about it.
But that's not for today.
I got a move on.
Okay.
All stuff from drop.au today.
Drop.au slash daily source code.
This is.
This is from truth out.org.
Tiedless Georgia war, a neocon election.
Play.
This is.
Here's the interesting.
Part in this.
I actually read the lead in paragraph.
Is it possible that this time the October surprise was tried in August.
And at the garbage that the garbage issue of brave little Georgia struggling for survival from the grasp of the Russian bear was stoked to influence the US presidential election.
Woohoo.
Before you dismiss that possibility, consider the role of one Randy.
Shonen man.
I think it's hype enough.
It's shown in mom.
Sierra Charlie Hotel Echo uniform November echo.
Mike Alpha November November.
Shonen mom.
For four years, he was a paid lobbyist for the Georgian government who ended his official lobbying connection only in March.
Just months after he became.
Wait for it.
Republican presidential candidate John McCain's senior foreign policy advisor.
He could better.
Previously, Shonen mom was best known as one of the neoconservatives who engineered the war in Iraq.
That's a big statement there truth out of the org.
But they say they engineered the war in Iraq when he was a director of wait for it again.
The project for a new American century.
It's unbelievable.
He was Shonen mom who after working on the McCain 2000 presidential campaign headed the committee for the liberation of Iraq which championed the US invasion.
And you got to read this article.
It's just amazing.
I mean, all these ties are not coincidental.
It's just impossible.
It's.
It almost makes you laugh.
And this, I got to play this for you.
This is from Fox News.
This is a YouTube video.
And these days, I'm just hooking and straight into my.
Into my Ableton live set up, so I can play this for you live.
This is fantastic.
I don't know if this is even true.
But you got it.
All right.
Here's that cell phone story.
And by the way, Shep Smith, I love this guy.
What a cheap robot head.
All right.
Let's go waiting for cell phone users.
Beware big brother.
Maybe listening.
The federal bureau of investigation can now hear everything you say.
Even when the cell phone is turned off.
I know it sounds kind of out there.
When using your phones tracking device authorities can now activate the microphone inside the dreaded thing.
Allowing them to eavesdrop on you and your conversations.
So we've decided to start saying all kinds of weird stuff all the time.
But hero.
Not really.
Seriously.
Yes.
I use this form of surveillance to keep.
Let me guess.
Terrorism.
Tabs on critical conversations by people.
They call no members of the mafia.
Oh, that doesn't sound like people talking to foreigners.
That doesn't.
That sounds like a violation of the Pfizer act.
Experts say the only way around it is to take the battery out of the thing.
Okay.
I've heard this story before.
I've heard similar stories.
But now there's actually reporting on it.
You know what?
I have a hard time believing this one.
First of all, I mean, is it for all cell phones?
I mean, that means these guys have back doors into every single operating system and every cell phone.
Can that actually be true?
Candy man?
What is Nokia's position on this?
Are you selling me phones that even when I turn it off?
The government can tap into.
But can only be.
Well, actually, can also be in the chips.
It could be embedded directly into the chip.
But someone's got to know about that.
So there's the same on Windows as it is on Symbian or on the Apple iPhone operating system.
You know, I'd like to know.
Is that really true?
You know, this is a big claim.
The FBI is saying it according to Fox News.
So I wouldn't mind hearing hearing about that one.
And again, I'd heard about this and I know you can buy programs.
You can even buy cell phones online that will answer phone calls.
This is like the, you give this to your husband or wife if you think they're cheating on you.
And it'll answer a call without actually ringing or out giving a notification.
And it'll just turn on the microphone.
You can listen in.
So you can always call and listen at any time.
One vibrate, nothing.
And if someone wants to use the phone, it'll automatically disconnect to like stealth mode.
So with that's an application that you actually have to put in.
So there must be something at the OS level or even at the chip level.
The hardware.
So if you have any info, let's hear about it.
And also I presume that this thing would then be radiating.
And it would be talking to the tower.
Now we should we should not just pass that by.
I'm so happy with this next story.
And I'm going to believe this one immediately.
You've probably read this or heard about it.
I just want to make sure I told you and gave you the link on daily source code.com.
This is the story about Michael Phelps.
Not actually winning the seventh gold medal at the at the Olympics.
And you could find this at 100th of a second.com, 10000 TH of a second.com, 100th of a second.com.
And so you know, Michael Phelps beat his opponent.
Kavik Chavik, I think it is, by 100th of a second.
Except the photo finish shows something else.
The photo finish shows, is he serving?
I think he's serving.
Millerard.
This show Millerard clearly, Millerard Chavik, Kavik clearly touching first.
Unfortunately Phelps is sponsored by Omega for a couple years now.
And Omega also does the timing, a clear conflict of interest, but also does all of the timing for the Olympics, at least for the swimming.
And I'll just point out that Kavik beat Phelps in qualifying in the semi-finals.
And when you read that this page is great, this is a great aggregation of all kinds of mainstream media stories.
That really show that this thing stinks.
And by the way, I can clearly you can see that according to the FINA rules, Phelps has to have both hands touching the pad simultaneously.
That certainly didn't happen.
And as sure it looks like he just hits second.
But obviously you can see the importance of this guy winning, not just a time mark spits his record, but he wanted to beat it.
You know, there's a lot of money involved.
He has to be a winner.
Look at the poor Chinese guy, the athlete who he pulled a hamstring.
I mean, the country is destroyed, his contracts are shit.
You know, this poor poor child.
There was something funny about Omega.
Let me just see if I can find it.
Shit, where was it?
They used an interesting, oh, here it is.
This is where this is from.
This is from fitness, own brochure.
In 1995, Omega, a fitness.
Omega.
One more thing.
Omega combined timekeeping with information technology.
Introducing A-R-S-A-R-E-S.
The automatic recording evaluation system, combining a black box, chronograph unit that captures
and prints time from sensors in the pool with a computer that can process the data and make it available
to the outside world without compromising the security of the black box.
What marketing genius wrote that?
Oh, that's crazy.
Also on the Olympics.
And this is from the New York Times.
If you hadn't heard about this.
China names of Olympic women's giant gymnastics team on Friday.
This is, uh, what was this post at July 27th?
And had the inclusion of at least two athletes has further raised questions.
Why spread in the sport?
Apparently they were 14 and not 16.
So I just want to say that what I've always thought.
And it's a shame, really, because the athletes are really in it.
And we sit at home really, you know, rooting for our favorite athletes.
I love the Dutch field hockey women's team.
God, I don't give a shit if they win or lose.
I just like watching them play.
It's it's beautiful.
Um, it's a scam.
It's a big fucking scam.
It's a big commercial bullshit money grubbing scam.
And it's bad for the athlete to participate.
It's bad.
They're just evil.
And they're lying to us and they're showing a shit.
Absolute horseshit.
Now, if you can't even do the score.
I mean, uh, just makes me sick.
It's exactly what I thought exactly why I said a boycotting stupid Olympics.
I don't want to talk about them because they're crooked.
And the people in the IOC are suspicious.
It's a lot of politics going on with this stuff.
A lot of money involved.
Okay.
All right.
Let's move out of that hole.
Part of a program or come on in, buddy.
I did.
It's a political program I hear from San Francisco California as usual.
Yeah.
I was in DSC 701 where you said that the bad was sheriff.
Uh, per business sheriff.
The.
Now, former president of Pakistan.
It turns out that he has a home in because he'll make Maryland outside.
Washington DC.
It's not also in DC area.
I know this because my cousin similar lives in the water area.
I knows the guy.
Anyway, that's all.
Cheers.
I'm very out.
All right, P.P.
Thanks, man.
I thought the guy.
Well, the guy is certainly a said.
You know, I got no money.
I got nowhere to go.
I don't have a big fancy house.
So I guess I was bullshit.
Looks like, I mean, you got a house in Maryland in the DC area.
That's nice.
Oh, I'm so worried about all that shit going on over there.
I really, really, really bugs me.
New report that came out.
I've not verified everything.
But I just did want to read this to you.
This proof of global warming hype published.
Okay.
So I'm still looking for the published bit, which, of course, is.
I just haven't had the time to look everywhere to find it.
I will.
Mathematical proof now that there's no climate crisis has been, has been published.
In a debate on global warming in physics and society, a scientific publication of the
36,000 strong American physical society.
So that's the part I need to verify.
So this is basically debunking the IPCC report, which has resulted in us being taxed on carbon emissions,
which, by the way, when I open my fat trap, that what comes out is carbon.
Okay.
CO2, the trees and the plants breathe that shit.
It's being taxed.
You watch one day, you got to talk less.
You got to pay more CO2 tax.
The article entitled Climate sensitivity reconsider demonstrates that later this century,
a doubling of the concentration of CO2 compared with the pre-industrial levels,
will increase global mean surface temperature, not by the six Fahrenheit,
six degrees Fahrenheit predicted by the IPCC, but harmlessly,
little more than one degree of Fahrenheit.
And they go through this hole.
Let me just read you the revelations in the paper.
Right.
So this is against the report, though, the IPCC 2007 climate summary,
which brought us into all of these extra taxes.
So this is science, right?
This is science against science.
Highly interesting.
So let's just run down.
The IPCC's 2007 climate summary overstated CO2's impact on temperature by 500 to 2,000%.
After our models and every model is built on a certain number of assumptions,
the same in business, by the way.
The CO2 enrichment will add little more than one degree Fahrenheit, 0.6 degrees Celsius,
to global mean surface temperatures by 2,100.
Got that?
That's 90 years from now.
Not one of the three key variables whose product this climate sensitivity can be measured directly.
Interesting.
The IPCC's values for these key variables are taken from only four published papers,
not from two and a half thousand, I guess, as previously stated somewhere.
The IPCC's values for each of these three variables and hence for climate sensitivity are overstated.
Global warming halted 10 years ago, and surface temperature has been falling for seven years.
Not one of the computer models relied upon by the IPCC predicted so long and rapid accooling,
which I guess is saying that their models are off and don't make sense.
Like this one, the IPCC inserted a table into the scientist's draft,
overstating the effect of ice melt by 1,000 percent quite an error.
It was proved 50 years ago that predicting climate more than two weeks ahead is impossible.
I don't know what kind of proof they have, but interesting they're saying it.
Mars Jupiter Neptune's largest moon and Pluto warmed at the same time as Earth warmed.
Oh, that's a good one.
How do you measure that shit?
In the past 70 years, the sun was more active than at almost any other time in the past 11,400 years.
There you go, go figure.
Something's warming up a little bit because of the sun.
I like mathematical proof.
I'm not sure what's going to come next, but obviously keep in my eye on this one because you know I don't buy that.
I really don't buy it.
I would not buy much from Al Gore.
Alright, hey, UK folks, how you doing?
I got some news for you guys.
This blew me away in the times.
Okay, this is is the times online, but the times highly respected newspaper in the United Kingdom.
Headline fat children should be taken from parents to curb obesity epidemic.
Yes, grossly overweight children may be taken from their families and put into care.
If Britain's obesity epidemic continues to escalate according to council chiefs yesterday.
Council chiefs are, and this was, this is August 16th.
So this is earlier in the week.
These are people that run the councils like Gilford Council.
So I guess they're a part of it.
The local government association are you that parents who allowed their children to eat too much could be as guilty of neglect as those who did not feed their children at all.
You know, this is exactly what the Lisbon treaty prescribed as part of the new human rights, which once they ram it down our throats and totally disrespect Ireland and the Netherlands and France.
It says that if the government feels it's necessary to do to have children exposed to better education, they can take your children away from you.
Here you go, the news articles just a little bit too soon because well the Lisbon treaty ratification is a little bit delayed.
So they didn't quite time it perfectly, but here it is.
Now, of course, thank God there's some people who are fighting against this pretty balanced article.
You should take a look at that.
But obviously, you know, that's not the way to fix the problem.
And the problem is is to get people eating healthy.
I talked about this with Patricia. She's like, well, how it makes sense. She says, you know, this is exactly what happens. You know, good food is too expensive.
People got no money. It's getting hard.
So they buy crap. And by the way, the healthy food isn't advertised on television. The crap is I'm loving it.
Right down into the programs, right into East Enders, highly watched program in this country, not by intellectuals. I must say I'm a fan myself.
Let's get some nuggets. Finish your nuggets, love.
That's some other frightening statistics in this.
In fact, councils are spending tens of thousands of pounds widening crematorium furnaces to deal with fatter corpses.
God.
Shit. Standard coffins are between 16 and 20 inches wide. That's 40 to 50 centimeters.
But coffins twice that size are being ordered to fit larger bodies.
Oh, my God. New ambulances have been introduced across whales with special equipment for fat patients, including a winch and an extra wide strength and stretcher.
We're killing ourselves people. We're eating ourselves to death.
Oh, my God.
Ah, I got to play a song. This was not exactly the spot I had to play. I just got to play some.
Oh, my God. I got to chill for a minute.
Process.
This was left on the drop.
Giles on the letter to Bush on your daily source gun.
Oh, my God.
You sit there in your home.
You're making decisions forever and forever.
When you get so confused, you can turn the time went down.
The light's on the line.
Oh, my God. Trust you.
I don't know you just don't look like you know it.
If all you say, oh, you just keep your heart straight.
Just look at the place that's way to play.
Oh, my God.
Don't help us all.
If I were you I'd leave the thinking to those of us who are higher I can.
They're struggling.
The power of the faith was simply too much.
Or I'd deal with like you.
Think it's up you go home.
All I did out catch me a fish and it'll all know it.
Daddy please tell me what you got to do.
I keep on fishing if I were you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my Lord.
But you know where it goes
You say you're looking at you, keep your arms straight
Just look at the mess that's made of clay
You're going to be on the floor
Ah, Jail's led up to Bush
That's a badass axe work there
I'd be like the sound of the guitar
It's why I played it I guess from the source code drop
The drop.io slash daily source code
Okay, let's see what we have here
It's just going to fade out
Yeah, another fade out
Ah, that's weak
I don't like fade out
Okay, a couple more things here
One more for the UK folks from the register
I just love this man
Just one more about your government
And mine I guess here in the UK
UK government to spend hundreds of millions on snooping silo
The government is pressing ahead
With plans to spend hundreds of millions of pounds
That's the twice as many hundreds of millions of dollars
On a massive central silo for all UK communications data
It's called IMP
The interception modernization program
That's right, go get the IMP
The team has recently been expanded
And a director level official appointed to run the project
Which is not yet official policy in public
Read that on daily source code.com
I just push in ahead my friends
I just push in ahead and we're standing by
And you know what I don't know if it's floor right in the water
Or what's going on?
We're just letting it happen
And the more of us that wake up
And start talking about it the better
That's all you really have to do
It's just talking about it
Tell you friend, tell you neighbor
And it's everywhere
It's everywhere
Here, Italy
Also from today
I'm sorry, July 16th
Just showed up on the drop
Italy may demand all its citizens to be fingerprinted
A move aimed at diffusing widespread criticism
Of government plans to force Roma people
And their children to provide fingerprints
As a way of tracking criminality
So the people in Rome don't like it
Then if I get everyone will do it
And we're going to get everyone to it
That policy has been condemned by the European Parliament
By Romania where many Roma come from
This is all about immigration
And of course the religious groups who have compared it to the tagging of Jews
By Nazis and fascists in the 19th
Of course it's fascist
It's fucking crazy
It's no worse than identity cards
It's all the same
It's all you know who gave these guys the right
They work for us
Really kind of take this back
Let's pop over to my old hometown
And Jersey actually not exactly my hometown
But it would have affected my hometown
Ah
New Jersey now requires flu vaccines for preschoolers
And children attending licensed child care centers
The flu vaccine requirement along with three additional immunizations
Doesn't say what they are was approved in December
According to the New Jersey Department of Health and Senior Services
Studies suggest that young children are particularly effective
In transmitting influenza to their close contacts
Yeah it's sometimes it's good
You know you build up resistance
I do not like the idea of the government
Shooting shit into children
Not our children
I do not like this idea at all
And we should not stand for it
Excuse me
This should be reversed
This is really really bad
And what are these other additional immunizations
There's three more
I'm going to play a little bit of a YouTube video that
That was sent to me just because
I've seen to required if you're headed to war
But target five discovered that a frightening number of US service men and women
Are having severe reactions
Including a young marine from Claremont County
So this is from
It's a news five
It's an NBC affiliate
And where are they?
I probably can't
See where they're from without
Shit
WLWT TV
My question where they're from
I just want to I won't play this whole thing
I just want to get the you have to get the gist of it
Because it's an official news outlet
And these are these are like real reporters
They know fluff piece
Listen to it
It's difficult for real
At a time when young men and women
Are dying on the battlefield
We live in a very volatile time in the military
There is an enemy here at home
And no one wants to move back
It's not as shot from a gun
This is the worst cover of
In the history of the military
But a shot from a syringe
That's leaving some US service men and women
On the brink of death
I mean it's very, very dramatic stuff
Of course the way it's positioned
But the story is indeed quite dramatic
So just let me tell you what it is
They the government is
Vaccinating our soldiers
Our boys and girls going over to Iraq
And by now some have been around
So long have been this fucking worst
So long they're men and women
Boys and girls men and women
Children of the sun
Literally 18, 19 year olds
Sun children
Goddesses all of them is horrible
These are highly intelligent beings
They're the next generation
They've grown up with Facebook
Imprinted on their mind
They understand networks
Technology, socializing and whole new ways
And we're sending them off to throw hot
Let it each other
Poisoned by depleted uranium
And we're testing them
We're using them as guinea pigs
They're being inoculated
And they're dying
Thousands of them
And the shit is being kept secret
It's not being recorded
And it's being covered up
And that's what that video is about
And now we're going to do it to our preschoolers
And kids entering school for the first time
Sucks
Really, really fucking sucks
So the highly aware of your government
Trying to shoot shit into your veins
Okay, they've already got the lock on heroin
And that's for another show for another day
How do you get it from Portland?
Well, there's another dead super delegate
Stephanie Tubbs, Jones, State Representative
From Ohio
Supports Hillary Clinton in the spring
In Dorses, Barack Obama
In June
And his dead August 20th
Why to wake in Germany?
Yeah, I got a lot of email about this
One after we looked at
The previous Democratic official
It was also super delegate
It was murdered in Arkansas
Now I haven't had the time to look into Stephanie Tubbs
Stephanie Tubbs Jones, I guess, is our full name
Haven't been able to look into it
But even what I've just the couple of things I've seen
Is that this woman was a great representative
And I think she was a congresswoman
She was a congresswoman
And a super delegate
Very African-American I just want to make sure you understand that
She was very important for her community
Respected and loved
And I do not like the way this went down in the reporting
There's lots of reports on this
Here's what I've collected
Again, just aggregating from the mainstream news reports
She was driving her car
High speed, I don't know
It didn't come across like a high-high speed but speeding
And erratically
They were able to maneuver her off to the side of the road
I did see the pictures and video
It wasn't no crash
Apparently the car stopped
Not by force, I didn't see any dense or anything
And the word is that what happened
She was driving got an aneurysm
And I'm not quite sure how that works
Usually we get an aneurysm
You're not going to be driving
If you're either driving her stop and if you're incapacitated
It's not both
And I didn't see any forceful stopage signs
She was then taken to the hospital
Where and that's when reports came out that she was dead
But then the new reports came out saying
No, no, no, no, she's okay, she stabilized
She's in serious condition but stabilized
And then the report that they unplugged her life support system
At 12, 10 AM
That night they unplugged her life support system
From an aneurysm
Dude, Terry Shivos that hooked up to a fucking machine for years
They couldn't unplug
They unplug this woman's machine in a couple hours
A DSC or in Cleveland rights
This is public on the drop
I live about two miles from the intersection
Where the report where the representatives car came to rest
After an officer noticed the car's erratic driving
Some sort of helicopter came extremely close to the rooftops
It was flying fast and low to the hospital
Headed towards the crash she
It shook the house, my wife grabbed my hand
Because it sounded and felt like it was landing on the house
This happened before we heard the news
Was it military?
It didn't seem to leave
I don't think it was life flight
Did it land at the hospital?
Interesting
I think she was taken to the hospital by ambulance
Of course I don't know what kind of helicopter it was
But I've seen lots of lifeline
It might have been a news
If anything was probably a news helicopter
That's probably what it was
I'm not associating anything there
Anyway, the local TV newsroom reported
Local news in Cleveland, mainstream media
The hospital was under lockdown after they brought the representative in
Why?
She was an avid Clinton supporter
Who switched to support Obama
This is going to be so fascinating next week
With this convention, what's going to happen with the vote
Although I cannot believe
I see now that Lady Duroth child is now using her lid
I think is her first name and her maiden name is Forster
She's now using her maiden name everywhere
She's fighting the good fight for Hillary Clinton
Now it's just billionaire Lynn Forster
She's dropping the Roth child
Which of course is good because Baron Roth child
Donated funds to John McCain
There's husband and wife
Crossing both sides there
They're right of course
I don't think the Baron is an American so we can't vote
But he could certainly support it whoever he wants
Although there's question about the legality of his donation
Maybe they want to make them fry them both
I don't know
Maybe Lynn Forster is really out to use Sir Clinton
I really don't know
I would think that the illuminati is what's called
The energy elite
The true owners of the earth
It makes sense for them to support both
It doesn't matter when they're both under their control at this point
Well, maybe they want to get them both out of the way
And have Obama win
No, I don't know
I don't know
This has, however, been
Here we go
I'll read this to you
Tubbs Jones becomes the third African American woman in Congress to die
In the deadliest term of Congress in over 20 years
Eight members of Congress have died during this term
Tubbs Jones began a term in 1998
Was one of Senator Hillary Rotten Clinton's biggest supporters during the primaries
Was a co-chair on Clinton's campaign
She announced her support for Barack Obama in June
And was a super delegated next week's Democratic National Convention in Denver
Ooh, chilling
I, we should look into that
Eight members of Congress died in this
And the deadliest term ever in over 20 years
I love that we should look into that one
For sure
I'll put a couple more links on the drops you can read them
And let me see
Okay, I'm just going to do two more. I'm going to skip over one thing here
Now, I'm not going to do that
I was going to do a whole government and drugs thing
I'll leave that until the next time
I will promote because I was planning on doing that
Downsized.org
A true you work for us website
One press of the button
A can fire off
All kinds of documents, faxes, emails
To your representative
Excuse me, it's a total automated system
Really good helps you get your complaints in
Because you know, that's what it's for
You're supposed to call your congressman
Now you can do it
They can't ignore this stuff forever
Nor will they
They just can't
If they look, look at the FBI
They have to now go back and show more evidence about Bruce Ivins
Which they can't because they destroyed the evidence
Everyone knows the score now
Another notch in the belt
Final one, I just want to
And this is great and awesome news
I got an email from Brian Cox
Shit, sorry about that
I don't at least I blew my ear drums out as well
I got an email from Brian Cox's wife
Brian Cox is a, he's a physicist
He's a rock star
He's working on the large hatred collider
It's certainly Switzerland
And his wife, who is a fox by the way
Damn
She pointed out to me that he did this awesome speech at Ted
And it is, it's fantastic
And you know what?
If anyone is going to discover a new energy source or something
Spectacular, it's going to be this guy
And I really hope he does because man
I would buy a second hand card from him any day
And it sounds extremely exciting
And you know, this, wow, man, he's living his dream
He's very, very excited about what he's going to discover
About the creation of the universe
But also I believe in alternative energy form
Someone's going to come up with that
It could be this guy
If you really want to hear a good explanation
You won't understand all of it
But you'll feel much better
When you listen to this Ted speech that Brian Cox did
I'm just trying to, you know what?
I just want to search something, almost
I can Brian, I'm just looking at the Gmail
Damn
I want to get her name
Because I'm blanking on it
How's been Brian?
Come on, Gmail, don't film me now
I should be able to, here we go
That's her name, Gia
And she lives in the UK
Go look at Gia.co.uk
She's stunning
Brian, don't get your head too wrapped up
And that collider thing dude
You got an awesome woman at home
And who is promoting you with a lot of love
Alright
You know what?
I'm going to leave it with one more song for today's show
This is also on the pod save music
Fantastic to have Dave Stewart on
With his rock fabulous orchestra
With an awesome version of Lily was here
Which will recognize instantly
Check out Dave Stewart
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's a great sex player, it's a sexy girl too.
It was also played with Prince of a new power generation for a while, until she, I guess,
a tired of it.
This was on a soundtrack for a Dutch movie called The Cushierra, The Cushierra, and I have,
I know this was a hit in the States, I haven't feeling was used on a couple other movie
soundtracks, but I couldn't find anything really particular on IMDB.
Great to have Dave Stewart in his rockfab, his orchestra on the pod save music network.
Thanks for sharing Dave.
And that's it, I'll be back tomorrow, and we'll continue, oh, he's footballer Friday,
so we should get your music in man, drop it into the source code drop drop.au slash
Danny source code, and until we speak, which I hope we'll be tomorrow, live your life
with passion and as long as it lasts, enjoy your freedom.
Another fine, medium presentation, stick it in your ear.
Thanks for watching, and I'll see you in the next video, and I'll see you in the next video.