Hey there Adam, this is Roscoe from Lockjaw, Kentucky.
Hey, I took your advice on a win-on line and looked up that hydroxy blaster.
I tell you what, Adam, I think I made a good one.
To kick off the DSC 775, I got my hydroxy converter with a five gallon steel bucket.
Yeah, I didn't want to miss around that little jar of the head on there.
And then I went ahead and, uh, so it wouldn't evaporate and so it wouldn't spill.
So I went ahead and, and soldered a lead on it.
And now I got some extra power running to it.
This thing is going to purr like a little pussycat.
All right, Arlene, go ahead and fire it up.
It's going to be great.
Yeah, I just turned it over fire it up.
You're less than an hour.
Aircraft from here will join others from around the world.
And you will be launching the largest aerial battle in the history of mankind.
mankind, that word should have new meaning for all of us today.
We can't be consumed by our petty differences anymore.
We will be united in our common interest.
Perhaps, it's fate that today is the 4th of July.
And you will once again be fighting for our freedom.
Not from tyranny, oppression, or persecution.
But from annihilation.
We're fighting for our right to live.
To exist.
And should we win the day?
The 4th of July will no longer be known as an American holiday.
But as the day might go quietly into the night,
we will not vanish without a fight.
We're going to live on.
We're going to survive.
Today, we celebrate our independence day.
We're 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped by us.
In the next generation radio contenting my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
For testing, he is very hurry.
A famous middle-aged rock and roller call me last week.
The sank me for speaking out against the war.
Only to go on to tell me that he could not speak himself.
Because he fears repercussions.
If you oppose this administration,
their can and will be re-emphasizing.
Re-emphasizing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ya, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, um, right now, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, OK, if you're going to take a news, yeah, here you're going up there. Yeah, you're a good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, your
It's the only way, when it's the only way
Ministry kicking off, daily source code
Episode 775, watch yourself
We're gonna hold on, you're home
And that track, just about along with almost every other track
to end on today's program, source from the source code drop
at drop.io slash daily source code, everybody how you doing
It is hump day, addition of the source code, but of course
It's really the first one of the week, it's July 9th, 2008
The weather's been just absolutely horrendous for the past couple of days
In fact, today I was slated to travel to the Netherlands
to Amsterdam on some family business, not gonna happen
Looking at the cloud layer, it's about 700 feet at the bottom
And about 10,000 feet at the top, in between it's just all crap
You know, like thunderstorms and hail and you name it
And the rain has just been almost torrential
It's really been just completely wet
So the good news, of course, is I'm here
And we can have a nice show together
I don't know if it's gonna be the only one this week
We'll talk about that in a second
But first of all, you've probably heard the news by now
If you read curry.com or if you follow along on anything
It's happening in Silicon Valley, we received a C
Around a financing
15 million dollars, very, very proud of bringing
Yet again, a fantastic investment firm
Particularly Kudos going out to Jim Feuer
who really helped us work this deal
And now I want you to understand that a C round, which is the third
And really the final stage of funding for any company
If you look at the trajectory
Is really, it's not, you know, like investment money
Well, maybe these guys have got some kind of idea
This is really based upon a business model that we've developed
And we really refined since our craft November
Which probably explains a lot of my absence
During the week for the daily part of the DSC
Because we've really been doing that
Workin' hard day and night, getting it together
Working with our board of directors, working with lots of people
Who understand what we want to do
To understand a lot of these traditional models
And we really cracked it a few months ago
And so this money is really meant to put fuel onto the fire
So we can light this rocket and blow it off into the atmosphere
Time, of course, with the trends we're seeing in the advertising world
Where brand advertisers are ready, just pretty much to advertise
Online video, real brand advertising
And they're just sick and tired of what the audiences are of television
Which are diminishing
And be the content
So they're looking for relevance they're looking for reach
And we're seeing success with it
And I gotta tell you, it's been a very challenging and interesting time
To raise money for anything, I think
So, and of course I want to thank my partner
Ron Bloom, who really put a lot of personal sacrifice
Into this, you know, really raising the funds
Doing a lot of the meetings by himself
Or leading the teams
While also working with everyone to run the company
And make it work
And of course, major, major thanks
To all of our producers
Independent, part of the media network
And without doubt, last and of course not least
The audience who really makes it all happen
And who keep showing up, time and time again
To watch and listen to our programming
So, you know, I should be really, really happy
And I just should be bouncing off the walls
Of course, I am, but I'm extremely troubled
My fellow chuckleheads
I'm really concerned about what's going on
And, you know, the first thing we really need to do
We need to change the title of this program
From daily source code to something else
Because the amount of time and research it takes
From me to really look at the conversations that we're talking about
And the things that are going on in the world
It's just, it's a lot of preparatory work
And sometimes it takes multiple days
In fact, I've been working on this show
Except, of course, for the funding announcement
I've been working on it for almost four days
You know, parts of the weekend, deviated there
And, sorry, help me out
Come up with something for the D
I mean, I do like the DSC
I like the Delta Sierra Charlie Aquarium
You know, I like the chuckleheads
But I think we need something different from the D
Since clearly, daily is just, it's just not a possibility
Not just from my own schedule and agenda
And other activities
But really, for the preparatory work
And there's a lot of reading, a lot of watching videos
And boy, I have learned so much, I feel
In many ways, enlightened in other ways
somewhat awakened by what's been going on
And what I've been able to follow and what I've learned
And hopefully you'll be able to help me
Figure out some of the loose ends as we work on those together
So for the D, what would it be?
Dirty source code, deadly source code, disaster source code
I want to hear from you
Call in to the voice mail lines
Which you're listed in the show
No, it's a daily source code.com
And of course, it's a curry.com
So what is happening in the world, man?
Think things are crazy
Here in the UK, we've had
Multiple suicide packs of kids
Throwing themselves in front of trains
And killing themselves
We've got increased activity of UFOs
The police helicopter chased one the other day
Here in the UK, reported widely in mainstream media
We continue to have distractions on television
Of Brittany, Lindsey, Paris, you name it
It seems like in a way we're awakening
We're becoming aware of things
Things are happening around us
And the worldly powers that be are fighting it
I'm really not quite sure what it is
But I'd really like to work on it with you guys
To figure it out
And I've done some preparation on it
In today's Charlie, which is
Wow, episode number 175
So first of all, I've been tracking oil prices
You know, this is almost a hobby of mine
In fact, today being Wednesday, 253 p.m.
In the United Kingdom, so British Standard Time
I saw oil go down yesterday drastically
Down to like 135 dollars a barrel
Which to me, man, something's up
You know, either there's
I mean, I just could not believe that this would be
You know, a gradual sloping off
It was down like four or five bucks all of a sudden
Down into 135, 136 dollars a barrel
And low and behold, just as I thought this morning
Word comes that Iran is testing missiles
And there's a rumbling in the Gulf
And of course, oil starts to pop up
It is now at 8.53 a.m. in New York
Oil is almost up to two dollars a barrel
So there's clearly clearly things going on
Clearly things that need to be brought to the forefront
And in particular, what is going on between the US and Iran
And we've been through this in previous shows
That Iran just never wanted to play game with the
With the dollar currency for oil
And they've threatened to flood the world markets with cheap oil
And based that trading upon the euro
And it seems like there's only a couple of ways to go
For our current United States administration
And you know what?
Heck, I'll just bring in the UK administration as well
It's all the same thing
It seems like the only answer
The only solution is to come up with a reason to go to war
And then actually go and do it
Do you feel the repeat?
Is there deja vu happening in your mind
At all with the Iraq
One and two
Well luckily we do have one solitary man in the US Senate
Who is trying time and time again to point out the exact obvious
Had you not heard this, Ron Paul on the Senate floor
I'd like you to take a listen
He talks about oil prices
And the disastrous, disastrous decisions
That are being made towards fellow men, women
All the majority of them under 30 years old in Iran
We must not go to war with this country
Dow Jones average was down 350 some points
Gold was up 32 dollars
Oil was up another five dollars
And there's a lot of chaos out there
Everybody's worried about four dollars a gallon gasoline
I don't think there's a clear understanding
It's actually why that has occurred
We do know that there's a supply in demand
There's a lot of demand for oil
The supplies may be dwindling
But there are other reasons for high cost of energy
One is inflation
For instance, to pay for the war that has been going on
And the domestic spending
We have been spending a lot more money than we have
So what do we do?
We send the bills over to the Federal Reserve
They create new money
In the last three years
Our government through the Federal Reserve and our banking system
Created four trillion dollars of new money
That is one of the main reasons why we have this high cost of energy
And four dollars a gallon gasoline
But there is another factor that I want to talk about tonight
And that is not only the fear of inflation and future inflation
But the fear factor dealing with our foreign policy
And in the last several weeks
If not for months now we have heard a lot of talk
About the potentiality of Israel
And or United States bombing Iran
And it's in the marketplace
It's being fed up
The energy prices are being fed up because of this fear
It has been predicted if bombs start dropping
You're going to see energy prices double or triple
It's just the thought of it right now
That helps to push these prices
The price of energy out
And that is a very real thing going on right now
But to me it's almost like Dejavu
All over again as it has been said
We listened to the rhetoric for years and years before we went into Iraq
We did not go in the correct manner
We did not declare war where there it's an endless struggle
Where in Iran we're endlessly struggling there
And I cannot believe it
That we may well be on the verge of initiating bombing of Iran
Leaders on both sides of the aisle
Any administration that have all said so often
No options can be taken off the table
Including a nuclear first strike on Iran
The fear is they say maybe someday
They're going to get a nuclear weapon
Even though our own CIA and our NEI
Says a national intelligence estimate has said they had not been working
The Iranians have not been working on a nuclear weapon since 2003
They say they're enriching uranium
But they have no evidence whatsoever that they're enriching uranium for weapons purposes
That they may well be enriching uranium for peaceful purposes
And that is perfectly legal
They have been a member of the non-proliferation treaties
And they are under the investigation of the IAA
And alberadai has verified that in the last year
There have been nine unannounced investigations
And examinations of Iranian nuclear structure
And they have never been found to be found in violation
And yet this country and Israel are talking about a preventive war
Starting bombing for this reason without negotiation without talks
Now the one issue that I do want to mention tonight is a resolution
That is about to come to this floor if our suspicions are correct
After the July 4th holiday
And this bill will probably be brought up under suspension
It'll be expected to be passed easily
Probably will be and it's just more war propaganda
More preparation to go to war against Iran
And this resolution H.J. Res 62 is a virtual war resolution
It is the declaration of tremendous sanctions
And boycotts and embargoes on Iran is very, very severe
Let me just read what is involved in this
If this bill passed and what we're telling the president he must do
This demands that the president impose stringent inspection requirements
And all persons, vehicles, ships, planes, trains and cargo
Andring or departing Iran and prohibiting the international movement of all Iranian officials
I mean this is unbelievable
This is closing down Iran
Where do we have this authority?
Where do we get the moral authority?
Where do we get the international legal authority for this?
Where do we get the constitutional authority for this?
This is what we did for 10 years before we went into Iraq
We starved children 50,000 individuals
It was admitted probably died because of the sanctions on the Iraqis
They were incapable of the time of attacking us
And all the propaganda was given for our need to go into Iraq wasn't true
And it's not true today about the severity
They say yeah, but all my data job he's a bad guy
He's threatened violence, but you know what?
Us threatening violence is very, very similar
We are must
We must look at this carefully
We just can't go to war at the end of the time
These violence, frivolous conditions
Oh, I believe
Let me tell you
Man, it's been seven to one
Time to tell me it's time
This administration is failed to do it
And now we have an urgent duty
We should do it now
Do it well
It feels good, do it
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it
do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, rotate your body, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do
and our duty is fulfilled and service to one another
duty
that that also showed up on the source code drop do a do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do oh yeah there you go it's almost like the good
forces versus the evil forces to old guys man oh man oh man I'm just so
concerned about this but you know as I search around more and as people more and
more people start tuning into to the show and start sending me links and
really turning me on to all different yeah all different types of
information just there is you know it's it's like this really haunting
feeling you know just like at the back of my neck where I'm thinking you know
could there actually be something to this whole illuminati story if you look
at you know the bloodlines if you look at the secret societies of
skull and bones you're there's so much information out there you know the
information that I've learned from the confessions of an economic hitman or the
the true inside stories behind the the CIA and legacy of ashes I mean
these are these are all books that we've discussed and hopefully you've
read them or you know if not find it you can even get audio book versions you
know don't even have to use use your eyes I'm thinking there's this huge
mountain that is just in right in front of us that that we we haven't even
seen you know we're looking at little a little other obstacles like towers
and stuff we want to dart around and don't want to fly into but the huge
mountain has been there and it's been growing and it's becoming ever
increasing in size and it's really starting to well piss me off first of all
but man you know this like these the talks of well here's here's something
that showed up on the daily source code drop okay you have to read this
PDF I don't really know if it's you know what the authenticity is but it
really does make a lot of sense having read through it although I'm no
mathematician which is of course part of the plan is not to have smart kids but
just from an economic standpoint this document which was found many many
years ago by accident and it's basically a manual if you will for controlling
an automating a population or if you will the world it's called silent weapons
for quiet wars and you'll find at drop dot IOS slash daily source code
give this thing read because even if it's not authentic man the whole theories
behind it are scary enough and the basic principle is it's equating the way
to control people and the money in an economy to one or a few people's
benefit they've equated it down to a science that is on on par with
electricity using conductors resistors switches volts and amps and and
equating each of those pieces to very basic things like inflationary rates
or the price of oil all things which as we know are under control of definitely
a few people I mean certainly interest rates is is completely under control of
the central banks and inflation is under control of institutions like the
Federal Reserve by printing more money you can create and create inflation and
when you read this document it is literally a blueprint on if not a blueprint on
how to control maybe on the way that we've been controlled expanding and
contracting the economy and making a profit on each expansion and each
contraction and doing that on lower levels with poor countries I mean this
comes right back to the confessions of an economic hitman it's really it's
really crazy but when you just sit back and chill out and think about it because
you know the first immediate thought is I know a man that can't be true
you always think people can't be as evil as as they're made out to be
certainly on the just plethora of sites that you can find on the internet and I'm
not talking 9-1 one stuff that's just a small little piece of the entire plan
if there is one and let's just say for argument sake that there is man if
there is there's a lot of coincidence going on and coincidence of facts and in
many cases basic laws of nature and laws of free markets it's in a way it's
disturbing but in another way it's really exciting because starting to be
able to figure all this stuff out means to me that well if it's just basic
physics and it's putting circuits together and increasing things here and
there you can inject an antidote you absolutely can make something different
and it's going to happen through all of us in fact I've read many cases that
the theory is should the people awake and should we become aware just aware
of what's going on but even that little bit of motion and commotion which
doesn't have to be a huge amount will basically shed off all of the evil powers
very akin to a dog who's wet and just kind of ruffles himself and throws off
all the water droplets to one by one we've got to start waking up thinking about it
we don't want no one no more bring our boys home to our shows we don't want big
government for the build the book proof that place all with you you don't have
your
we haven't followed the constitution and that's what we are to be doing
the system we have they are ripping off the middle class
and you imagine how the nation would have if we didn't have the federal reserve system
printing on this money
if you haven't seen the video have a look you'll find that on youtube run
Paul the revolution song and there's a couple of cool things coming up centered
around the republican convention which will be in there was a Minneapolis in
there but they're also going to do some big stuff and I've been asked to get involved
and I am trying to change around a couple of things to actually accommodate them
so that should be pretty cool anyway back to the topic at hand there's just crazy
shit going on particularly here in the UK this is I got a couple of really nutty
new stories here check this out this is from the telegraph and this is from actually
from a couple weeks back I hadn't heard anything about it as is often the case of course
in the mainstream media there might be a little bit of news popping up and then
usually drops off the radar when there's another
written speakers episode
a quarter of the adult population in the UK faces an anti-pedophile test
in an escalation of child protection policies according to a report check this
the launch of a new government agency
which goes unnamed in this will see eleven point three million people in the UK
vetted for any criminal past before they are proved to have contact with children
aged under sixteen
vetted for any criminal past any criminal past
the increase in child protection measures is so great it is poisoning relationships
between the generations according to respected sociologists professor Frank for
the yeah hell yeah professor Frank hell yeah
in a report for think tank civitas which I don't know anything about
he said the use of criminal records breaks checks of the criminal records bureau checks to ensure
the safety of children and vulnerable adults has created an atmosphere of suspicion
yet no shit
so let me see the checks were introduced to tighten procedures to protect children
after school caretaker e-in-huntly murdered ten-year-old Jessica Chapman and
holly wells and so on and two thousand two
well of course that's horrible and of course we want to
you know make sure that this doesn't happen but come on I mean
parents apparently will even be checked
to be in contact with their own kids
this is this is just taking things a little bit too far
I'll put a link in the show notes to this one and
podcast Paul park is actually sent me something as well which I can't
seem to find at the moment you know the you've probably seen the videos on youtube
I think voing or wired even pointed to one not too long ago
where someone's filming something in London and then a couple come up and say
you know it's illegal you're not allowed to film this building and of course
it's perfectly legal and if you're on public property you can film
whatever you want and well that's changing now and this is what I'm trying to find
but I guess I shouldn't and I must have thrown it away or done something
with it let me see
now
anyway the just of the article was that a change in the law is being proposed
where the constable in question that would be the police officer on duty
at his or her discretion can stop filming based upon the situation at hand
so all of a sudden now you know even though there's millions of cameras in the UK
and by the way this isn't just a UK thing in the US have a look around
millions of cameras watching our every move we're not allowed to film anything
not even in public spaces anymore or we're allowed to but at the discretion of the
constable on duty in the situation at hand they'll be able they will have the authority
to say no you cannot film I mean this is uh this is not good
no no in fact this sucks
it sucks
hey Kerry
hey Ross
thank you with the legary church colon said about fathers not having the ability to bitch and moan
about what goes on and I think he's absolutely right for the following reasons
and the primary one is that we do have ways of enacting our will
I mean voting is just one small aspect of the whole thing
I mean we actually have to tell our representatives what the fuck we actually want
you know and I think the term settlement majority really sums it up
that the majority of the people don't say anything
and I mean what are there representatives for some think of this
that I mean there's only two conclusions that either people are supportive of it
or that people don't give a deal
and if these minority groups special interest groups these lobbyists you know can affect
them then I think that we the majority can certainly have a bigger effect on them
you know take this and run loophole for example there are lobbyists right now saying that
this is going to affect the free market economy and I'm like well this is true
but oil is infrastructure dude and infrastructure as far as I'm concerned should be regulated
and considering you guys these lobbyists are basically representing people already
natively influencing the system and manipulating the free market so it's no longer free
then you know I think we have very right to backlash that
you know especially with these high bloody oil prices
so yeah I think that's what we need to do a chucklehead you know we need to get off
our assets opting silent and actually start the voicing our opinion
who knows maybe we actually might just get something done then
but that's my two cents let's get the ball rolling on this conversation
there we go great air hope you win
love you a minute we got one on the week
I'm going to go for more as we progress and they work for us
but only when we tell them what to do that's the head let's start telling
peace head on over to the source code drop man take a look at that PDF silent weapons
for quiet wars and just read it I mean forget the diagrams and all the circuitry and all that
you don't actually need to know that the calculations although I'm hopeful that there's a chucklehead
out there or perhaps someone of the savants status who can actually help us
decode some of these some of these equations that see if it literally is that simple
and if we can understand how the blueprint works how all the details are put together
then of course we can jam the machine right so it's not going to take it's not going to take a
typical type of revolution I don't think I think that as long as we all start off
with an awakening and start seeing what's happening and and start coming out of the numbness
that we've been just beat over the head with for decades now particularly was coming out
that box in the corner of your living room or these days you've got your tuna right in your
built into your computer I mean that's that's the thing we've got to look out for
I would say got to be very careful so for all the UK chuckleheads I've got a nice little
UK protest song for you I thought you'd appreciate
investment in that so far because he takes us all he's a Texas man to the hungry
drives the Lexus fans you don't need them big the shins for the show but all the
people are not so safe and we are going to bring the wreck
do I think too much can we hear you all night still give a fuck tell you I don't
wave the flag because we're arrogant enough don't need to black go on
pace in the forks facing away facing career because we're friends with the states
little we are going to face be a face how we from corporations is a big disgrace
don't forget walk up on the walls where we all go report it reflects on us
best in on the beach say in the club loud up great say in the English pop man
I'm amazed that we still get a lot more punch in the world with American clubs
come tell to rant animal waves and we've come back up is a low play those are real men
don't forget locked up no charge for using count I'm a pressure ain't really
man because you're idiot what's on a kid your jokes and you're idiot what's on a kid
your jokes and the good DJs get night times lost it's a load of crap like
planes made them too tough to like that straight down your back when we're old
who great kids will be like mom that trolley push cold enemy
take away no police these days those will kill Kennedy
call us the remedy this was about energy supply
the word about terror has to go down high and it's even been proved
that lead is right in the world terrors racism in disguise and we still don't
vote when for it is time and we have to
stay to this point because the new deal is the double
to avoid them this war is based on the past
from these to Z from the first to the law this was based on the past
the law the law the law the law the law the law the law the law
the law the court the frsta that
well men how I wish i knew who are done this track I just showed up on the
Drop it's showed up as Seriana and Stiles.
So I guess it's the performer as Seriana and I, or maybe it's Seriana style.
I don't know.
May you guys, you got to put more data into those things when you drop it.
Drop.io slash daily source code.
That's we can always find all that's really become such an intricate part of the show.
I'm so, it's so cool.
I almost want to figure out how to flow some of that over into curry.com or even
daily source code.com or whatever the D will stand for in the future.
Don't forget to help me out, give us a call, send me an email, give me some ideas
where what can we do with the D?
Let me see, we could do, you want to do one more, one more heavy thing here.
I've got some about fluoride, which is really pretty cool, although.
Let's just do something completely stupid for them.
Well, let's not call it stupid.
Let's call it a little bit of entertainment distraction because we do need to have a balance
in our diet today.
Don't you agree?
I'm ready for your test.
Get it, test.
Young boldness!
Hey Adam, how are you doing?
I am doing good, man.
This is hit test number one, two, nine are.
It's not right away with a drone.
Number one.
It sounds like maybe it's a depression mode or an ABC.
Maybe it's older than that.
Maybe it's early, eighties.
Number two.
That actually sounds like ABC.
Oh, man, I'm stuck in today.
It's all right.
As long as we're all entertained.
And the final one is number three.
I'm literally sitting here with my eyes closed and I'm realizing, once again, I'm failing on all three.
I can't do it.
I'm stopping all of these weekend answers are from 85.
85, huh?
As soon.
Answer number one.
What is this?
This is tremendous.
All down.
I never would have known.
I was into Duran Duran at the time.
I never can even sing along with a song.
Hey.
Oh, man.
It's for me, in his answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
Renee and Angela.
Man.
You're not.
I don't know any of these tracks.
Oh, man.
Okay.
I kind of recognize it now.
Again.
I must have been listening to ultra-box or something.
1985.
What the hell was I doing?
I wasn't paying attention.
Were these like, even in the top 20?
Answer number two.
Renee and Angela and I'll be good.
And this is answer number three.
Long time no see.
I don't know this one either.
You haven't little time.
Just spend it with me.
Okay.
I got it.
Yeah.
What was this again?
I mean.
Is that a loop?
Time to say.
Baby.
Oh, man.
Oh, time.
Answer number three.
Freddie Jackson.
Freddie.
Yeah.
I mean tonight the net concludes.
Hit the number 100.
Oh, yeah.
Well.
So I didn't have to do this week.
I stuck John.
So let that be a birthday present for you.
Happy birthday, by the way.
I got none right.
You stumped me completely.
As always, the answers to this hit this are to be found.
Hit this.
That's not me.
That's all sort of place to find.
The iTunes links.
So you can buy the tracks featured on the hit this online.
And I'm thinking for playing again.
Yeah, sure.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening.
Next week, I'll be back for hit this number 130.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And remember.
Think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
Be back.
Hit us at gmail.com.
info.
Gunpoint.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-D-T.
Gunpoint.
J-A-N-P-O-L-D.
Hi, Adam.
It's Matt from Gamesweasel.
On this week's show, we reviewed Battlefield Bad Company on the Xbox 360.
We play Okumi on the Wii.
We've also got some info about the new NASCAR-09 game from the drivers themselves.
And you can win copies of Unreal Tournament 3 for the Xbox 360.
That's all at Gamesweasel.com.
Hey, I'm big man's back.
WWE that the kit from Brooklyn.com.
I was watching the Larry King show the other night yet on one of these big oil executives.
His name was O'Reilly.
He's telling Larry King that the oil companies are making that much profit.
But Larry King, he don't dig into the game.
What about the $40, $50 million a year salary of getting Mr. O'Reilly?
Who pays for that?
The fucking American people.
I mean, who?
Who deserves that fucking kind of money?
$40, $50 million a year.
To all these big oil executives out there.
And they're claiming they ain't making those fucking money.
What does he grow taller than a fat fucking cop on a quality of fucking red batches?
Who loves fucking kids?
You're making fucking videos of dollars and a working man in his fucking country.
Got a fucking shop.
You, bad batches are making a work in land today.
He can't even go out and buy food and pay for shelters for his fucking family.
But it's all right.
It's all right.
But then big oil executives can get $40, $50 million a year salary.
That's okay.
But the average Joe King can't even afford the biggest fucking family.
I'm telling you, it's gonna be a rebel bullshit in his fucking country.
He might've got to take this shit no more.
I mean, how many times are he going to get kicked in a fucking face
before you kick fucking back?
I mean, come on, give us a fucking rate.
What a fucking salary.
What's the matter?
Who the $1,0, for fucking oil executives in today?
They got to be $40,000,000.
Go fucking a showship breed.
Breakfast, fucking batches.
Anyway.
They come party.
This is something man.
The rice.
Shut up.
People.
You're a pile of fake clothes.
I hope you're screwed up.
Fuck you.
Nothing.
You ran.
Passen.
Ha.
But this.
This.
You think it will be so screw.
I'm going.
Yeah.
Shit.
Out.
It's.
Hey.
I'm.
Repeat.
Hold on.
I'm.
I'm sure.
30 pack a straw 30 pack a no rogue ain't in the pro pay for
He's in charge in one half the living proof with a gift from the city of truth
I challenge that and not critics back and I did not start it when I said that
I'm going back no selling rhymes I went back no seven times
He's still the ill they want to see us ride I guess because the only god knows why
Why why why why why
They call me powerful I have a single reply from someone bigger with the air
Let me see where you're at, say hey hey hey hey hey
Let me hear where you're at, say hey hey hey
I'm giving it back to say hey hey hey hey hey hey
So be so bad to say hey hey hey hey hey
Let me hear where you're at, say hey hey hey
I like ACC, the ACC time will see this piece
These are the kings of rock Scanner, see your lip on the storm
Pay me an alley go with no show, show
Yeah, that's that bottle of rock got the rock for Detroit
So for both out the art and the crowd of soul
Need a deal with tracks that make us that back the rock
Never, never, never, never, never
But watch me rock, we live a rock, keep, blast
For rock, the class boys, man's a track
Like Johnny Cass and Grant Master
Blast, blast, blast, blast, blast, blast
Big one, call, call, call, call
They have a single reply from someone bigger with the air
Let me see where you're at, say hey hey hey hey
Let me hear where you're at, say hey hey hey
I'm giving it back to say hey hey hey hey
So be so bad to say hey hey hey hey
Yeah, I saw your band
Shot the band on stage, I can watch you give it a docks
You're my sucker, just give it
This band, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip, rip
I'm an American man, watch me kid
You can roll with rock, you're a comedian
I'm a porno, blast, I'm like amazing crazy
I'm gonna, some, let go of rock, this place
I'm super blind, it's a double white sight
Call my eyes, it's so deep
Big five, ball, fat, you share, bring it flat, you play
Got the longest, wing it middle, wing it, no, wing it
Big six, big six, big five, you're fair, see me by, see
In a rebel, get her, ball, lift it down
So we're new, do, get the next generation of things
Who knew, I'd throw a black, I'd walk, walk, walk
Check on that school, fall, the mind, the blow, fall
Spell the old, blow, walk, check my head
So I don't wanna stay in here, rush out there
Call my eyes, it's so deep
I'm gonna, make a witty edge, see me by your back
Say, hey, hey, hey, hey, say me, hey, say me
It's so deep, it's so deep, it's so deep
Say, hey, hey, hey, hey
I'm not a god, hold me, I'll let that escalate
I'm singing baby, baby, baby
Don't fight inside the box, don't fight the back
Say baby, baby, baby
I want you to try singing back, don't fight the back
I'm singing baby, baby, baby
I'm singing back, don't fight the back
Don't fight the back, don't fight the back
Hell yeah, American badass
Kid Rock shows it can be done
Turn some of that energy towards
You know who?
All right, so in my continuing search and research
You know, and again, I'm just, I kind of tend to stay away from a lot of the real, you know, like the occultish
And believe me, I've read it all, you feel free to send me links
But I've read all about the stuff about eating babies
And et cetera, et cetera
I think I've read just about every single conspiracy theory that is out there
Until I come across something that has been poking at the back of my mind for a number of years now
People have sent me messages and I don't really quite tuned into it
Because it's like, this is some kind of spiritual conspiracy theory
By the way, the conspiracy theory is just a theory
It's a theory about a conspiracy
It's nothing bad, you're not in a conspiracy when you're looking at a theory
So this is research is what I could consider it
And, you know, people often laugh at people who say, you know, things that seem extraordinarily out of the ordinary
Or just extraordinary, I should say
I bumped into one of those debates
I think was the CNN slash YouTube
Where was it?
Can't remember who asked the question
But it was said to Dennis Cassinage, who was a democratic
No, not not many, but he was running for the democratic ticket
And, you know, this is the guy who's got the really hot wife
So Dennis Cassinage, you know, is it true?
It's like his mother-in-law or his aunt or something
It's surely McLean, and the question was, it was Tim Russell
Actually, that's what it was
You know, you claimed to have seen a UFO, and of course everyone's chuckling
And man Obama really slaughtered him when Obama had to answer the question about UFOs
But, you know, people laugh at people like that
And it's, you know, as I said, there's lots of activity going on
And, you know, so I run into things like the, how was the name of it?
Not the, not the demo, there's something project
Anyway, it's from 2000 and 2001, I think, may of 2001 for the National Press Club
All of these airmen, excuse me
Air traffic controllers, pilots, people will throw work in, you know, top, top secret high security clearance
Positions within the government, all sane, hey man, you know, we've had contact with, you know, not just contact
We've flown their aircraft and the government hasn't been telling this
And there's all kinds of reasons for it
And one of them, of course, you eventually get around to the story about Niburu
Or planet X as it's also known
And this partially has to do with, you know, the, the Mayan calendar apparently
And I'm just going to try and relate the stories I've understood it so far
The Mayan calendar, the Mayans were very, very smart, ends in 2012
Which is when in the, in astrology
We move into the age of Aquarius
And I do believe that actually the planets are all lined up in a particular order
And this is also the time, in fact, it is going to be the 21st of December 2012
Which is, you can just Google 2012 and you'll find out about this instantly
All the, all the links on the pages are about this
So here's the theory, there was a planet Niburu
Which actually I believe by itself, by colliding into Saturn or something like that
Actually created the earth
Was in deep trouble and that we're talking 500, you know, 1,000 years ago
Maybe 500 million years ago, no, 500, I don't even know
A long time ago
And by the way, this is all documented in the Sumerian tablets
In the translation there of that is the Sumeria, which is now known as Iraq
There, and this is known fact in the, in the Museum in Baghdad before it got bombed
As I think I've heard somewhere, I remember reading a quote or hearing a quote of saying
Someone in the armed forces, or maybe it was probably some of the idiot general who said
Man, they got a lot of pottery over there
Well, of course the pottery was like, you know, artifacts from 5,000 years ago
It's well known that civilization more or less started in that region
And so the theory goes that there's these intelligent beings on the planet Niburu
Which only crosses the earth's path, every 3,000 or 3600 years or maybe it's 30,000 years
It's kind of irrelevant, but it's in some form of weird orbit
And it's supposed to be coming by again in 2012
So with these guys they initially, when they had some problems with their own planet Niburu
Mainly their atmosphere was all screwed up
And they needed gold in order to sprinkle that into their atmosphere to protect them from whatever rays
Or, you know, because they were acts as a reflectant or protective shield
And so they decided to
Mind this on this planet, which was planet earth
And of course we were kind of crawling around
So we kind of existed, but not really
This is where the missing link theory kind of comes from
So what they decided to do was to create a whole world of minors of workers
Slaze essentially who would mind this gold and then they would be able to save their own planet
So they created a hybrid and the hybrid that created was 80% of us, you know, web feed
Walking around like idiots
And 20% of their DNA and there's all kinds of theories about that's how you get the double helix
The twisted DNA representation
And that 20% is actually of highly intelligent beings
Who are based on light and love
So you're going to start to see a lot of similarities with
Almost every religion, every story
The numbers come back like 12 disciples, you know, the Jesus being number 13
And number 13 actually being a very good and lucky number instead of unlucky
And you kind of see that things are all turned upside down on their head
Because what happened is, and again, I'm really sketchy on the details here
So boom, they created us a self-reproducing
I believe actually the fact that I've read this theory that the fact that women have pain
And labor was actually a mistake in the construction of how they put us together
These intelligent beings
And through the years, you know, we started to morph and this is where all the stories of, you know, giants
And goal of our travels come from
Again, I'm just paraphrasing don't take my word for, do your own research, read the story
So as this continues through thousands and tens or maybe hundreds of thousands of years
We also start to develop that 20% and we start to become enlightened
And we start to develop technology and we start to become a lot smarter
However, the guards, the fallen angels, I believe they call it
Who essentially want to keep or are supposed to keep, I guess, this minors, union of slaves, a global planet of slaves
Mining for gold, which by the way, we do see defined gold is pretty important, not quite sure why
But, you know, there could be an explanation
And they want to, and you know, they've also evolved
And, you know, they're all about not evolving into an enlightened being where it's all about spirituality
They want to keep it in the carbon being and the way they do that is through suppression
And by enslaving the entire population because with them, it's all about the possessions and the money
It's at tre, and they want to keep that gig going because hey, it's kind of a good gig, I guess
If you look at it from there, it's perspective, where if, which, of course, anyone who, you know, can send off, can create wars for profit
Which is what wars are all about is obviously has a very distorted reality field view
So anyway, so in 2012, the Nibru is supposed to come back and they're going to check up on us
And I guess this is why, you know, the evil forces on earth
Who are all connected to royalty, so legend goes
In fact, I've read that 34 of the 42 US presidents all have bloodline connections back to royalty up to, well, even the Queen of England
And don't forget those oranges, the Queen of the Netherlands, who's husband Prince Bernard started the Builderberg group
So you see how all these things start to kind of fit together and
And they, you know, they're building, and this is well documented, they're building all kinds of electronic shields, which, you know, how about star wars, you know, what could that be for?
And this is where the conspiracies, the plot really thickens in the conspiracy and the theory of it
They want to keep the Nibru out, they don't want to come and help us through the age of Aquarius
They want to help us into that dawning
And at the same time, they're going to control us through mind control, which, of course, is already working very successfully
By essentially tweaking the economy around us, so making oil very expensive
Or then, you know, giving and helping us, being flush with cast or we can build up all kinds of debt
And then taking it away, that's the expansion and contraction as I talked about
What's really interesting though, is talking to Patricia about this
And she said, oh yeah, well, this is what, you know, this is what the hippies were talking about all the time
In fact, I picked up the song
Well, maybe I will play the whole thing because
When you listen to it, the dawning of the age of Aquarius from the musical hair
This is about what is supposed to happen in 2012
And they were singing about this in the 60s and 70s
And now watch it listen to the lyrics, okay?
Because it's really all about what is supposed to come
Harmony and understanding
Timothy and trust of all
The mind is true liberations
So it kind of supports the whole theory, you know, and back in the day Patricia was a part of that
It's, you know, she has the age for it
It's just they were maybe a little bit too early
And didn't have the internet and couldn't communicate that well amongst themselves
I think they had some good dope dope
Let's listen to it again
So it seems like that's, you know, after you peel away all the layers of the onion
Such as 9-11, which I'm pretty convinced we certainly need to get a whole bunch more answers on what happened there
I mean, if you've seen any of the most recent videos
And if you think you've seen them, if you watch them in 2003 or 2004, go back and go look again
And go look at YouTube or Google video because there's a lot more evidence out there
I'd also like you to take a look at pilots for 9-11 Truth.com
I think it's.com.org
Man, if you're into flying and you actually see the details as provided by the NTSB and the FAA and the NSA
I think even of the black box contents and of the data that's coming out of the flight recorder
You will be amazed at how many complete loose ends there are
And just, you know, the multitude of questions
You know, it's too technical to go into here, but man, just check it out
But this whole idea of the kind of the space thing, I gotta tell you, I'm kind of into it
And a lot of things start to click in the place, you know, is the suppression
But then again, the enlightenment, something, you know, just being around the corner
And everywhere you see on the internet, people were tuning into this idea
You know, about waking up and coming out of your sleep and that it's built into our DNA
And we've evolved and we're kind of in this race for the next four years, you know, four or five years
Are we going to enlighten into beings that find intellectual, being intellectual and love and find power from light
Is that, is that actually, you know, what's going to happen or the dark evil forces take over
And every, you know, my question is, well, what should we do? What can we do?
And every single answer I get is just start to wake up and help others to wake up
And then it will happen all by itself. I don't even think there's going to be any kind of huge physical
Revolution that's going to be needed because of the power and that's part of it
I think that's part of our mission. Do I sound spacey to you because I certainly feel it that way
But I've never seen a UFO in my life. I've never seen aliens pickled in a jar or anything like that
But I know I saw an engine that wasn't from our terrestrial technology
If the government has really been in contact with superior alien
Wouldn't we see some evidence of it
There has been a monumental cover up
Your government knew we were dealing with extraterrestrial intelligence
And as you probably know we have indeed retrieved crash-tardware
And we have reverse engineered it and we have indeed been flying some of that hardware
And this base is not too good to any miles outside of Nellus
The town's a ground control
I'm standing through the door
And I'm floating in the most peculiar way
And the stars look very different today
For here my sitting in the temple
Far, far, far
When it's on this blue and there's nothing I can do
The first and most famous alleged contact was the Roswell flying saucer crash of 1947
A fascinating government official is warning we may be on the verge of intergalactic war
Saying quote, the Bush administration has finally agreed to let the military build a forward base on the moon
To put them in a better position to keep track of the comings and goings of visitors from space
And to shoot at them if they so decide
One bus one hundred thousand miles of really very soon
And I think my space just knows which way to go
Till my white line of hope very much now
Clouds control to reach a time when your sun gets lit
The sun glink on and you'll be on my reach a time
Can you feel my reach a time?
Can you?
I'm my project manager again
The US government is playing host to extraterrestrial biological entities for EBEs
I'm identifying flying objects in fact real is real is the airplanes flying over your head
And that there has been a monumental cover up for more than half a century
It's very significant that someone of the staffer of a governor would come out and say that they
It's not what they experienced a UFO
Because it brings a lot of credibility and strength to the case
NASA knew very little about the object reported by the Apollo 11 crew
It was obviously an unidentified flying object
The time has come for the government to tell the people what it knows
The truth has got to come out for over 30 years to late
The people not only have a right to know they have a need to know
Well it's not impossible if this spacecraft came to Earth from an alien civilization
Boy talk about making history on the radio
The disclosure project that's what I couldn't think of
That's the name of it Google that or take a look at it on YouTube
The disclosure project it will open up your eyes
So now of course I'm feeling I'm feeling pretty good
I'm feeling like there's a lot of stuff happening
And I hope I've been able to take you through this show
Hopefully not too much of a downer and not too much of a freak out
Because you know you can of course go nuts if you really start to think about this stuff
But bit by bit let's just keep our eyes open
Let's watch each other's back and let's be in a lookout for things that are really big moving pieces
Like with this new Polywell energy device that has been developed
Hold on a second this was a fantastic story that I saw
I'm like and it looks so alien in nature
It is
Bussard iEC fusion reactor
Which could produce a hundred megawatts and you see pictures of this thing
It almost looks like what's the Jody Foster movie
My brain is not with me today or at least not the memory part
Anywell and anywell anyway
This polywell thing is something that some guy developed
And then I guess Dr. Nibola is his name
He's picked this up and they're starting to see results
And there's all kinds of exciting things going on
So let's be careful of what's happening
Let's as I said watch watch our backs
Let's definitely live our lives with passion
And while at last
Enjoy our freedom
Another fine medial presentation
Stick it in your ear
Thank you