Delta Shara Charley's 7-6-4.
This is the deadly source code.
Oh, I'm going to be!
$16 billion worth of airplane scrapped by us.
Do the next generation radio contenting my ears.
We don't need not to dig into it.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I guess it is that I'm going to die now.
$15 billion worth of airplane scrapped by us.
I can't expect that I'm a world like that
I can't expect that I'm like that
I can't expect that I'm a damn thing
Go wild, wild, wild, wild, wild
Go wild, wild, wild, wild, wild, wild, wild
I can't expect that I'm a damn thing
Go wild, wild, wild, wild, wild, wild, wild, wild, wild
Here big blue, old, that will fit face
The Japanese lot the fabstar don't waste time
On the mic to gerade stop, jump, jump, flip a jump
And I'm here too thus.
Being delivered to make your shake the panic of the chance
I'm coming in to hand-guys perfect girl
Don't wait, make the world.
It's show rolling, AM 10!
It's world it's world trying to get mad
It's never unsure but it's true
The dance floor for your heart
Can't sense the air
More day yeah everybody over here
Everybody over there
The crowd is livin' up in this
Body people in the house
That's a lie
Who's that lie?
Everybody over there
BENNING
All the people around
Yea they live
All the men一起 come up
We're tribal people
Lower units, ramps in all security
Balance feelings, peace in all burden
Coachella!
Rock city, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man,
man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man eaten me crazy, he's my son, he's my son, he's my son, he's the man. and he's the man,
from the curry manner, we're on the west side of G-town,
the affluent suburb of Surrey, known as Gilford.
All boy, I gotta, I gotta topic for you today.
We're not gonna be talking about oil,
we're not gonna be talking about nuclear,
we're gonna be talking about Europe,
in particular about the European Union,
and specifically the Irish,
because we've got a huge event coming up here
in just a couple days about what is today,
the third, so in nine days from now,
an historic event will take place,
which could literally change the course
of the European Union.
As you know, Europe is turning into United States of Europe.
There's a number of steps that have been taken to get there.
This actually started back in 1945,
right after the Second World War,
there's ties to the United Nations,
which of course was funded initially
by the Rockefeller family,
which makes it all that more interesting, doesn't it?
But that's perhaps for a bit later,
I would like to say that I'm gonna make the show relatively short.
It'll be probably about a regular Charlie Length,
but there won't be a whole lot of topics in here,
because it's really gonna focus on one main topic
after we get through a couple of important notices.
Now, if you're Irish, meaning you live in Ireland
or have family or friends who live in Ireland,
you definitely want to take note of this show,
and you're gonna want to send them links to it,
and you're gonna want to back up some of your knowledge
of what I'm gonna talk to you about today
with a documentary, which has been released on the internet.
You can find it at curry.com.
Of course, I'll put a link to that in the show notes.
Frick, maybe I'll even embed it into the show notes today,
because it's well worth it if you haven't seen it.
And it's about the European Union and the Lisbon Treaty,
and it's pretty shocking when you find out what's going on.
So you can look forward to that.
You could fast forward if you want to,
because right now I have some other very important business
to take care of.
As you know, I'm pretty convinced that I'm one of those people
who people want to really give me any props
for anything until I'm dead and gone,
and maybe I'll get a little pod father on the tombstone there,
although hopefully if you have something else,
but that's a total possibility.
But we lost one.
We lost a real good one just yesterday,
Bo didly passed away, who, of course,
was just a monster when it comes to rock and roll, really.
And the number of people that he influenced with his songs,
with his guitar, the way he played, his riffs,
is just so many artists have been influenced by him.
And he passed away at 79, which I think is,
oh, man, that's still, that's not old enough.
I sure as hell, hope I make more than 79.
And I was thinking, so how can we best pay tribute to him?
And well, lo and behold, upshowed a comment
from Gary Alexander, who, of course, is a member
of the Muvio pod, pod cast network, excuse me.
And he had a pretty good suggestion,
and I just want to share that with you
and the song that he attributes to Bo didly.
Hey, Adam is Gary Alexander from the ultimate pod cast.
In the wake of the Bo didly passing,
I wanted to bring to your attention
a song that you have played of mine on the DSC4s called,
once upon a time in America, and it basically
takes a trip through all the, in my opinion,
all the styles of American music that have made it so great
that I love.
And in the middle of that song, you can hear a bit
of a tribute to Bo didly on the drums.
You'll hear a bit of that traditional, you know,
for Tom kind of a group, a bit of a 60's feel
in the chorus, and a bit of John Melanchamp,
and just a bit of the boss.
You're going to hear it all in that song.
Obviously, I'm a big fan of Bo didly.
I'm a big fan of all American music,
a big fan of music in general, from every country,
especially American music being that I'm
pouring bread and one option of proud to be an American
proud of the accelerators, a matter of fact.
You'll hear a little bit of Ronnie Van Zance
from Learn Skinner, Dean Flint, and there as well.
So even if you don't play it on the show, my friend,
I hope you take another listen to that song,
and think of the wonderful songs that Bo didly gave us.
Even though you all had that same group,
they're all great.
I could go bright on a Friday night,
down on the thunder road.
I was only not standing in line,
as brings things show.
I had a plan for rockin' roll band,
having made it in the shade.
I was gonna be a star with a bunch of young kids up.
All that song, what I say.
Nice, nice, nice.
I made me want to hold on my sleeve,
I was so cold, I'm in America.
I'm gonna be a star with so much time,
and I'm feeling fine, in my neighborhood.
It seems she told she's far as hate,
I mean she's looking good.
But she's so pale girl with the times
I'm being injuries and I'm feeling better.
I'm Mr. Romeo, this one's name is Blue Jeans
There's girls like this
They made me want to roll on my sleeves
It was upon time to make love
Oh yeah, it was upon time to make love
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We're gonna round the end of the break
It's gonna be us
Well they go 20 years
I don't know, I hear that song
And I roll down the window
I think back to those days
Oh, I remember
You're so close, I am the miracle
Hey, completely fitting and fun-safe tribute today to board deadly, dead at 79.
He influenced the greats, all the well-known ones, and some of the lesser-known Gary Alexander
were once upon a time in America, thank you very much, Gary, perfect, perfect for today.
Okay.
I've been making a study and talking to a lot of the chuckleheads in the UN, EU, in the European
Union, and I'm actually I'm quite amazed that this hasn't popped up in something
common-extra blogger sent me, but it's one of those things that it's so huge, it's so big
that it just gets completely overlooked.
Let me see if I can break it down for you.
Two years ago, approximately, you remember, that there was a referendum for a European Union
constitution.
Of course, when we think of constitution, then we think of the United States constitution and
some very basic rights that are put in there, the pursuit of life-librity and the pursuit
of happiness is, of course, one of the main ones, that's really the credo that we live
by in the United States.
So something very similar was created by the European Union.
Let me just try and explain, part of the issues that I personally have and a lot of people
have with the European Union.
The idea here is, after we now have one single currency, which is, of course, the euro,
all, we had gilders, we had Deutschmarks, we had Franks, we had Zlotys, we had all kinds
of currencies, these all got folded into one.
Technically, in 2000 officially, as currency I believe, in 2002, along with that goes a central
governing body, and this, of course, is what sits in two places, interestingly enough,
in Luxembourg and in Brussels, they alternate back and forth, that's a very, very complicated
structure.
I have no idea exactly how it works, because you've got the European Commission, you've
got the European Parliament, where we have ministers of the European Parliament.
So what I do know is that, as far as I understand, not a single one of these people was
actually voted into office by the people of the member states, of which there now was a 27,
which means that a lot of laws are being created and passed centrally in Europe by people
who do not represent the people of Europe.
Now this, of course, is a contentious.
It's an issue.
A lot of people are really pissed off about it, and I think more, some countries are more aware
of it than others.
And in fact, when the European Constitution was presented, countries had a referendum.
Now, if you don't know the referendum is, is basically a vote.
So they put it out to the people, the people go out, they vote, they say yes or no, for whatever
it is.
And the deal was, if one member states says no, we don't like this Constitution, then it
was back to the drawing board.
You may recall the two countries said no to the European Union Constitution, namely the
Netherlands and France or France, as we say in the states, I'm practicing my UK accent,
which meant it got sent back to the drawing board.
And this was a huge disappointment because there was a lot of powers that were created
inside of this document.
The most blatant one, the one that really stuck out is that the Constitution could be
amended by the people given the power in the Constitution, mainly all these guys and
gals who sit in Europe who make up laws, I believe they'll probably be responsible for
making up 80% of all the laws that pertain across that will be enforced across Europe.
About 20% of the laws, I'm not quite sure which ones, I'm not a lawyer, look, I'm just
like an XDJX VJ guy trying to figure stuff out because I happened to live in the European
Union and I have a finnity with it.
So the people don't generally like that idea and furthermore, I am one of those crazy guys,
we'll go and download the document, we have a website in all, I don't know how many different
languages but it's been about a billion euros a year to translate the European Union
website, which you can find at Europa.eu into all languages that are spoken.
And I downloaded it, I took a look at it, let me tell you, it was so complicated to
read.
It wasn't as it, like the American Constitution is pretty easy, you know, you read through
it.
It's just a document and you can understand what they're saying and yes, it's open to interpretation
which of course is what we've gone horribly wrong in the United States where lawyers are
re-interpreting the actual meaning of the Constitution.
And boy, when you look at it, it was still a pretty damn good document.
Now, of course, we've had all kinds of things in the States like the Patriot Act, which
took away a lot of liberties and I think we're finally waking up to that and we're going
to have someone new in the White House regardless, I don't know if it's going to change
anything but we know the Bush will get kicked out.
So when this thing went back to the drawing board, that pissed off all these, well, I basically
called it, you know, it's the political class who had wanted to run Europe since the end
of the Second World War.
You know, they basically said, look, we're never going to let that happen to us again.
We've gone to form a strong front part of that initiative was the United Nations.
We're never ever going to let this happen again.
If we can really bond together as one, Europe, I'd like half a billion people and will
really mean something in the world fair enough.
But I think the incestant need and perhaps somewhat greed from bankers and the political
class, I did themselves a bit in really what they've been trying to accomplish, which is
basically run the shit.
All right.
Now, I'd like things being run on a local level, whether it's a state level or a member
state as countries are now called, that are members of the European Union.
And I don't like the idea that these rights will be taken away from local governance.
So they had to figure out a new way to pass all of these, you know, basically pass the
constitution and they didn't want to have to go through the process of a referendum again.
So they came up with the idea, very, very slick.
And this is what's pissing me off because I cannot believe that this slip by again.
I think it's one of those things.
It's just so huge that no one noticed it.
They came up with something called the Lisbon Treaty.
Now notice that the word constitution is not in the title.
In fact, if you look at the document, which I have also done, and I'll provide some links
in the show notes, it's boring stuff and excuse me, quite honestly, you won't be able
to figure it out.
Because the Lisbon Treaty is really, it's an amendment, it's almost like, well, in fact,
it is a legal document.
If you look at it, it refers to the original constitutional document.
But nowhere does it mention the word constitution, because the minute you mention the
word constitution, then the member states almost, in many cases, I think, have to are
obliged to write out a referendum and let the people vote on whether they think it's
a cool idea or not.
So they called it the Lisbon Treaty, which, of course, for many people Lisbon is Portugal,
golf, son, sand, the beach.
It sounds kind of friendly.
But really, all that it is, it's just some amendments, some changes.
You know, basically, like, if you read through, it'll say, well, in all these different
articles in the constitutional document, take the word constitution out and call it a
treaty.
That's one of them.
It's a little nitpicky things.
But honestly, the only way you could read it and understand that is if you put both
documents next to each other, it's almost like a red line, only it's not integrated.
It's not like they give you a word document with the original constitution and then the
Lisbon Treaty merged into it so you can see the actual differences.
You have to go back and forth.
It's a long-ass document, too.
It's not simple.
And this thing is now coming to a head, because all that the member states have to do is
ratify the treaty.
And if all of the member states ratify the treaty, then it goes into effect as per January
1, 2009.
At that point, the European Union will literally be able to create a single tax code for
all of Europe.
They'll have the high court.
Will be a European high court already, law in different member states is decided by
European law.
But I've been reading up on the subject and looking at it for one reason.
And this is where you Irish guys come in.
And I know we got some chuckleheads there in Ireland.
Luckily, and you'll see why in a moment, luckily, Ireland.
And I'm not quite sure why, but they've done a fantastic job.
Someone was definitely awake while at the wheel.
Ireland is the only member state that is going to hold a referendum about the Lisbon
treaty.
So here's what I've learned.
Lisbon treaty is basically the old constitutional document, but it's gotten a facelift,
a little makeover, mainly taking out the word constitution to be able to kind of push
it through.
You know, just all the governments, you could just ratify it and then it all be cool
and we'll be good to go.
And this is actually happening this week, many of the member states are going and many
of them have already ratified the documented fact.
And now they're going through the courtesy of explaining it to their individual peoples
in the member states what it means.
Well, I found a couple of excerpts that I think we need to discuss here because it's
really, really a frightening document.
Again, we're looking at the merging between this original constitution.
And I didn't even read this in the original constitution because it's kind of purposely
meant to be confusing.
I'm quite sure of that.
It has all the nice, important words and the short sentences up at the front of the deck.
And then in the back, you've got these things like the charter of fundamental rights and
the protocols and all these additional amendments or addendums, I should say, that you
kind of have to read to understand how the laws will be applied.
So I want to read and I put links to this right in the show notes.
It's all from the European Union website.
You can download it, have a look at that for yourself.
And any language you want, by the way, article two is about the right to life.
Now this is obviously a pretty big one.
So here's the, here's the front of the page article two.
Number one, so this two dot one, everyone has the right to life.
I'm thinking right on, I'm not a, I'm against the death penalty.
In fact, here's number two, that's article two dot two.
No one shall be condemned to the death penalty or executed fantastic.
So I'm like, okay, this is all for me.
Now if you dig in a little bit deeper into the, into the charter and into the protocols,
article two dot two A deprivation of life, she'll not be regarded as inflicted in
contravention of this article when it results from the use of force,
which is no more than absolutely necessary, and they give three examples.
So deprivation of life, which basically means killing someone will not be
in violation of article two, everyone has the right to life known to be condemned to
the death penalty or executed unless it happens in defense of any person from
lawful violence.
So if you attack a police officer and they kill you, it will be deemed legal.
Number two, in order to affect a lawful arrest or to prevent the escape of a person
lawfully detained.
So if you resist arrest and you try to run away in the European Union, if this
passes, if this treaty is ratified unanimously, and if Ireland approves it and
ratifies it in their referendum, if you try to get away from someone trying to make
a lawful arrest, which could be for anything, if they kill you, it will be legal.
And here's my favorite one.
It will not pertain in action, lawfully taken for the purpose of quilling a riot or
insurrection.
So basically, if you're protesting and it turns into a riot, and you get shot and
killed, it will be legal for that to happen in the European Union.
I think it's pretty clear what that means.
Hey, it goes on article two, B in the protocols here, referring to protocol number six,
a state, which, of course, means any country in Europe, they make provision in its law
for the death penalty, in respect of acts committed in time of war or of imminent threat
to war.
Does that sound familiar?
Does that sound a bit like the wording of the Patriot Act?
So if it's a time of war, if we're actually in war or at war, or if there's an
imminent threat of war, I.e. the threat of terror, the war against terror, then you
may be put to death.
Any European state may put you to death, basically invoking the death penalty.
You liken it so far, it gets a lot better.
Okay.
So the selling point that the politicians are using right now, right now, telling the
people of Europe, and this is about right to liberty and security.
This is actually article six.
Everyone has the right to liberty and security of person.
No one shall be deprived of this liberty, save in the following cases and in accordance
with a procedure prescribed by law, you, I bet you can't wait for this.
Can you now, okay.
So here's some exceptions.
The detention of a minor by lawful order for the purpose of educational supervision,
or his lawful detention for the purpose of bringing him before the competent legal authority
is authorized.
So that means that in Europe, a minor may be detained, lawfully, for educational supervision.
How fricking scary does that sound?
We don't think that your child has been educated properly, Mr. Curry.
We think your child needs some educational supervision.
We're going to take your child away from you.
Here's the big kicker.
The lawful detention of persons for the prevention of spreading of infectious diseases,
persons of unsound mind, alcoholics, drug addicts, or vagrants, is permissible by European law.
If this is ratified, let's just go through that again, because who are we talking about here?
So you're free, you're completely free to do what you want.
You have liberty, unless, unless,
you are spreading infectious diseases.
Let me think, what group could that pertain to?
Let me think, what's an infectious disease that is spread?
Could it be HIV?
Well, yes, of course.
So there's an actual possibility that people with AIDS may be lawfully locked up in the European Union.
If this has been treaty, is ratified and put into effect.
But not just that.
It's persons of unsound mind.
Can be locked up at will of any of the member states of unsound mind.
I think we all pretty much qualify.
We walk around, call on ourselves, chuckle heads.
We're sitting on public transportation with earbuds jam to our ears, laughing and laughing
out loud, having fun.
We might actually drink a little bit or smoke some weed.
Oh, I'm sorry, that's alcoholics and drug addicts.
Of course, real easy to quantify what a drug addict is or an alcoholic is.
And, of course, alcoholism is proven to be an illness.
So if you're ill that way, you can be locked up.
Or if you're just a vagrant, let's get the frickin' vagrants off the streets of Europe, shall we?
You can see where I'm getting a little bit worried about what's going on here.
Okay, and here it is, freedom of expression and information.
This is article number 11.
So if you look at point one, of course, it makes a lot of sense.
Everyone has the right to freedom of expressions.
This is what the politicians in Europe will tell you.
This right shall include freedom to hold opinions and to receive an impart information
and ideas without interference by public authority and regardless of frontiers.
This article shall not prevent states from requiring the licensing of broadcasting television
or cinema enterprises.
It sounds pretty reasonable.
Let's read on into the fine print of this document.
The exercise of these freedoms, since it carries with it duties and responsibilities,
I'm still with that, by the way, I think freedom of expression comes with responsibility.
Maybe subject to such formalities, conditions, restrictions, or penalties, as prescribed
by law and unnecessary in a democratic society.
So in the interest of national security, who will boy where we heard that before, territorial
integrity or public safety for the prevention of disorder or crime, for the protection
of health or morals, for the protection of the reputation or rights of others, for preventing
the disclosure of information received in confidence or for maintaining the authority,
the authority and impartiality of the judiciary, you shall have no freedom of expression.
Do I really, I think I should walk through that again.
So if it's for the prevention of disorder, well, I'm sorry, you have no freedom of expression.
Well, essentially, I'm doing that right now.
In the interest of national security, well, the man, how big is that one?
That's the whole, that's the Patriot Act of Europe right there.
And I love this, the protection of health or morals.
Wow, the morals of the European Union isn't that just amazing.
It's, you could have freedom of expression, say what you want, except if don't touch our
morals now, please, we've got morals.
We can't exactly describe them in the document anywhere.
We have morals.
And for the preventing of the prevention of the disclosure of information received in confidence,
that's the whole whistleblower thing.
That's what it's all about.
If you get confidential information, which could be about your government, your local
government or the European government, you're not free to express that.
This is the shit that drives me crazy.
And it has to stop, luckily, it can stop.
And this is what I love so much about this.
On June 12th, Ireland will hold a referendum.
And if they pass the Lisbon Treaty, it goes into full effect, including everything you just
heard me talk about here.
Can you believe that shit?
January 1st, 2009, we will effectively be prisoners of the European state, a police
state as far as I'm concerned.
Oh, by the way, they do totally intend on creating the European army, which will also fight
outside of the borders of Europe.
Please pay attention to that.
So my chuckleheads and friends in Ireland.
This is a responsibility that rests upon your shoulders that is just about the largest
I can imagine.
It is, oh, please, people, don't bug me while I'm in a rant.
It is such an incredible responsibility that rests on your shoulders and not just you,
but anyone in the European Union who cares about your freedom, your rights, your right
to life and liberty.
Indeed, the pursuit of happiness, although, you know, apparently there's nothing about
happiness in the, in the, in the semi quasi constitution for Europe.
If you care about it, you must tell Ireland to vote no, vote no to the Lisbon Treaty because
it will lock us up for good, vote no to the treaty, where green, call your friends, put
us up on your weblog, talk about it in your podcast.
I'll have links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com so that we can all try and stop this
lunacy.
It absolutely has to stop.
Let me play a little bit for you here.
This is not really a speech, but Nigel Farage Faraj, I think, who I don't think is actually
well liked in the UK because he's a member of the UK independent party, which is often
seen as a very kind of weird out there party.
He said some amazing things recently about the European Union and about the whole process
of ratifying the Lisbon Treaty, which really is just a wolf's in sheep clothing.
It is the constitution that we voted down before.
You can tell there's evil wrong things in this constitution.
It has nothing to do with the way that Europeans feel in general.
I know enough of them, it has to stop.
Listen to what Nigel says in the European Parliament, as you stand up and let's
everyone have a piece of his mind.
Hold on, it's coming.
What the European Parliament is engaged in here today with this debate and subsequent vote
is nothing less than a massive exercise in the state.
A pack of lies are being told and they're being told because you do not want the peoples
of Europe to have the referendum that you promise them.
It is the imposition of the will of the political class upon the citizens.
We all know the truth that this been treaty is the same as the EU constitution.
Exactly, the same number of new competencies.
Exactly, the same number of surrenders of visa.
It is virtually identical in every regard and it is constitutional because it gives
this European Union a full legal personality but was still a gives it the ability to amend
itself in the future without having to refer to more intergovernmental conferences.
It gives the EU the ability to legislate over literally every single aspect of our lives.
I'm told though I shouldn't worry because the flag on the anthem have been dropped.
Well, pull the other one, there's a great big flag at the front there.
It's nonsense, it's all part of the lie.
The truth is that you are too chicken to have a referendum.
You don't want to hear the voice of the people and now you resort to totalitarian means
to get this treaty through.
We heard Danny Komendit say that those that oppose this treaty are mentally ill.
We heard Mr Schultz say that those of us that objected to the sheer dishonesty of this project
were behaving like Nazis back in the 1930s.
Well, I think the ordinary decent citizens of Europe will make up, will work out for themselves
who the extremists are and I must say I wish the people of Ireland, I wish those
the believe and democracy every success in a couple of months time and I hope they send a large
resounding no and I hope the voice of the peoples of Europe will be heard, not that of just you,
the political class and you may be complacent today, but you are increasingly being held
in contempt.
Well, that's what I call fightin' wars and he is exactly right, Ireland, please help us out.
Vote down this craziness, get rid of it for once and for all, say no in your referendum.
We're counting on you.
Political poetry, words with tears.
We're have you been my brother, tell me I be siege, so far gone but not forgotten yet completely out of reach.
Your world invaded with vengeance, you left so many to die, you must have been taken by surprise,
is that a tear in your eye?
Let me into what has happened, tell me I am poor, your eyes are red and puffy, your hands bleeding with
gore, their telephone taps, hidden cameras and units used to spy, these are not utensils of safety.
Is that a tear in your eye?
Please talk to me and tell me your silence is frightening, are you fit to make me bed?
You are so different, torn and shattered, lost within your head.
The orders come, now thousands are no more, because of a political lie.
No explanations given, just money and freedom is that a tear in your eye.
Again, I ask where have you been my brother, tell me of your plight, your eyes show the depths of hell
from a ghastly fight, send away to kill the boys and girls alike, not even wanting to try,
using their bullets, their guns and more, is that a tear in your eye?
If I could write the world's perfect poem, would that even bring your home?
Would they hear the words spoken from my tongue?
I fear upon deaf ears and the changes would be none.
If I could change the world with my words, bellowed from my heart,
would they notice just enough to make the cleanup start?
If I could tell everyone how to be fair, just and true, would that be enough for me to get through to you?
If I yell it from the rooftops, can humanity open its ears and eyes to see?
Would my work reach the weak, the self-centered, and the powers that be?
Will you tell me my dear brother, what have these choices done to you?
Have we lost our freedoms through the actions of a few?
Tell me please, I search so hard for answers trying to break through.
Relax, dear sister, I will tell you, fill you in on what you need to know.
I have been marching and fighting for freedom in a show.
It was not invaded with vengeance leaving so many to die. The world was taken by surprise
and that is a tear in my eye.
I will share with you the devastation from the eyes of a child, ready to believe in all that they are told.
Living life so mild, the story I'd complacent just waiting to give in.
These choices have been made for us and by rights, it is a sin.
They lied and said it was for freedom, for others rights but yet.
Where are the changes now moving in, moving out, how easily they forget?
The earth is burnt and barren with nothing left to see.
Who has the right to choose this fate for them, for you, or for me?
Through my plight, I closed my eyes and did as I was told. Nothing lives there now.
Just the ground that grows stiff and cold.
It is hard to believe in a land. I was so proud to see the evil sore turned to dictators where trusted
fathers for money and power to clear war.
You write that world perfect poem. It may be enough to bring the rest home.
Do not fret if they hear the words spoken from your tongue, lose your fear of death
and the changes may just come. You can change the world with words,
bellowed from your heart. They could notice just enough to make the cleanup start.
You can show everyone how to be fair, just and true.
That is enough for the important ones to notice you.
If you yell it from the rooftops, humanity may open its ears and eyes to see,
reaching the weak, the self-centered, and the powers that be.
Use your words to fight. Make them know this is wrong.
If you never try, then too, your freedoms will be gone.
Finally, I tell you, the effort is up to you, my sister, my friend,
take the chance, band together, and bring these wars to an end.
Ireland, only nine days left, June 12th,
vote no in the referendum. Vote against the Lisbon Treaty. Vote against this crazy
constitution. Do not make the same mistakes America Day.
In above us, only sky, sky, sky, sky, sky, sky, earth, and magic. All people, all people,
living, living, for today. Magic, there's no country's country's country's country's.
It is not hard to do, hard to do, hard to do. Nothing to kill or die for.
And no religion, too, too. It's a good idea. Imagine all the people, all the people,
living side by side. In peace, peace, peace, peace. You could say, I'm a dreamer.
But I'm not the only one. I hope someday you'll join me.
In the world, we'll live as one, two, three, four, the magic of those decisions.
I wonder what you're wondering, what you're wondering, if you can.
No need for great or hungry.
Brother, there's a man.
Magic, all the way.
Sure. All the world.
Imagine, if you want to choose, please.
A wise man once said, you can't change the world all in one go. You need to affect change,
bit by bit. I've done my bit. Ireland, the rest is up to you.
So while you can, enjoy your freedom and live your life with passion.
Another fine, medial presentation. Stick it in your ear.