And now it's time for a long-distance dedication.
Todd from Jersey writes, dear Casey, back in the 80s my friend Yann and I used to have
the greatest times.
We would run wild on Fridays, getting all food barred and watching MTV's Headbangers
Ball with Adam Curry.
Yann would create great games around the names of tunes, and I would try to introduce him
to the latest bands.
It was truly a unique and special time.
Then Yann returned to the Netherlands.
We tried to keep in touch, but nothing was like those Fubar Fridays.
Casey, could you play Adam Curry's Daily Source Code 796 for Yann?
The Fubar Friday edition.
I know he is out there somewhere remembering those Fridays too, and the DSC 796 will
really make his day.
Honestly, Todd, well Todd, he is your long-distance dedication.
You need to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to be gay.
You need to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it
run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run and if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run and if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to create it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, if you want to make it run, music, you
Oh, let it set you on the road
You can buy another
You can now
You've got a sound, you're willing to hear
But you live in all the different
You get it, you fall in the wind
You get it, baby, you get it
Oh, let it set you on the road
That's right
A big wild street shuffle we all witnessed it
This past week
In the United States of America
Hey everybody, you're doing a steady source code
Episode number seven, nine or six coming to you from the Curry condo
It's, um, well, it's Friday somewhere
It's Sunday, elsewhere
It's Saturday night here
It's currently nine, 20
Probably the past four or five hours
I've been just scouring through the archives
I'm feeling a bit bit melancholy
On the other hand, uh, reasonably chilled out
And, uh, and relaxed
But I just didn't want to get into an entire, you know, long-winded show
About how messed up everything is
Make no mistake, my friends
It is not a Wall Street crisis, it is a global banking crisis
And I say specifically banking because it's their system
And we're just attached to that system
And, uh, it's come crashing down
And there are many, many ways you could learn about this system
Uh, if you've been listening to this program
You've probably already learned quite quite a lot
Uh, if not, there's a significant information out there on the internet
I'm going to touch on a lot of different things
Uh, in the show
Which I think is kind of a show you might want to consider
Um, playing on the speakers at home
Uh, preferably, uh, you know, just, I mean, a Sunday afternoon
I think would probably be perfect
And really, if you're 30
Hmm, I'd have to say 35 years or older
You're going to enjoy this show
Uh, because I spent four or five hours pulling together
I must have, I don't know, 20 songs
Something like that
And they're all relevant, all relevant to my mood
I relevant to what's going on in the world
And we'll probably speak louder than any words
That, uh, that I could, uh, could come up with
Now, just, briefly on this bailout bill
Um, this is a bill about power
And it went from three pages to 106 pages
To 451 pages in the time of what, what was it?
Not even two weeks?
No, no, not even one, not even one full week
And it was, uh, past, under extreme pressure
Um, I believe even, uh, threatening pressure
Uh, going on inside, uh, the House of Representatives
Um, probably the Senate as well
And this is really a bill that is good for the bankers
They are bailing themselves out
Before everything comes crashing down
Um, the, what they're doing is they're creating, uh,
Inflation which could lead to hyperinflation
Which means prices go up way way up
And you buy less for your money
And, uh, I mean, there's all kinds of things that could happen
And, uh, one just interesting thing
You know, I'm pretty much, um, uh, pretty much
Reliant upon ATM machines while I'm here
Um, ones that are in the neighborhood
None of them have cash, it's Saturday
None of them have any cash at the moment
And in fact, one of them was giving, we weird transaction errors
Not got to walk like four blocks to get some cash
And I'm hoping it's not related
But anything could happen at this point
It's a very, very connected world
Just as the physical world is connected
The world of finance connects to everything
And the bankers got themselves out
And it was, you know, with the knowledge that I have
Which is not that hard to gain
Understanding how the, how the, how the, fractional, uh, lending, fractional banking works
And I'm going to give you some pointers by the way
We can learn about this over the weekend
It's not hard at all
And, you know, I'm just, uh, I'm just a kid
From America
You know, hey, Europeans, we're all the stupid people live
Yeah, I want an M
And I could figure it out
It's really not that hard
And when you, and when you understand what's going on
You're watching C-SPAN, a lot of C-SPAN actually, boys, that fantastic
Uh, um, watching Pelosi holding the bill out in front of, uh,
Reporters in a nice little blue box
Before she sent it off to Bush
We had, uh, Bush and Paulson, the secretary of the treasury standing on the
Capital steps
Looking like two thugs, smug little thugs
Ha ha, we did it
And of course, we couldn't even communicate with our representatives
Because they, uh, for all intents and purposes just took down the website that
To enable you to email your, uh, your congressman or congresswoman
Uh, uh, because there was too much, uh, use of the website
Yeah, I wonder why
Let's see what else has happened with your money, AIG
Which, uh, we already own 80% of
Used another 61 billion dollars in federal reserve loans
Links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
Uh, the, uh, the entire bailout, now I just haven't had the energy to go through all the pages
I know what's in there, I know what they're doing
Um, they're going to be paying back foreign banks, foreign investors
It's all in the bill
Um,
There's, uh, there's all kinds of weird stuff in there
Hidden taxes, tax relief
But, uh, a carbon tax provision
Um, and of course, you know, in order to spend
$700 billion of our money
They had to add it over another 100 billion
Almost at the 150 billion of bullshit stuff
There'd no normally never would have passed
The people just pile an arm
They weren't, they weren't talking about the actual bill
No, they weren't talking about getting their shit in there
I mean, even if even if all the chalk hides all together
Said, hey, let's go and spend 150 billion
Dollars, we would probably have a hard time coming up with a way to spend it
In a month, let alone a couple days
Amazing how quickly they could write all that, huh?
All those pages
You don't think any of that was pre-written to you
Or is it really possible to get hundreds of lawyers together
One moment and within days, right, hundreds of pages of legislation
I guess so
Ralph Nader, who I will talk to
I will talk about later
Gave a species
I'm actually, I'm turning on to Ralph Nader
There's a couple of independence that I want to mention later on today
But before I get to Ralph Nader, let me play something for these frequency eos
These guys who basically cause the problem
By creating debt upon debt upon debt upon debt
And splitting up risk
Stupidly
Because I found this on the pod tape music network
I thought you'd get a kick out of it
Literally a shit kicker out of it
Hey, you bastard CEOs
Keto Peters has a song for you
I must see a CEO
Ralph Nader, who I will talk about
The show
I'll be king till the numbers fall
A little dip goodbye
That's all
I must see a CEO
But trickle feeds them down below
We ring every nook and vain
Oh my dead before the rain
Oh we shot the dirt well by doing glue
I think it's no last too long
In my neighborhood
I'm a CEO
I must see a CEO
Ralph Nader, who I will talk about
I'm a CEO
But I'm so proud I scaled a link
Virtues mostly fall the way
I must see a CEO
Where did all our futures go
Looks like I look straight ahead
Got to be the eighth turns ring
I wish I could turn well by doing glue
It saves no last too long
In my neighborhood
I must see a CEO
But trickle feeds them down below
I've heard too much doomsday stick
I don't questions make me sick
I know I'm doing well by doing glue
Down there's no last law
In my neighborhood
They took our money
And more importantly
They took the power into their own hands
Finally they have all the pieces that they want
Keyto Peters from the pod save music network
And CEO
Before I get to Ralph Nader
I want to play a little bit from Dr. Ron Paul
Congressman who of course voted against this bill
Along with 170 other true patriots
who see that this is absolutely wrong
Make sure that you know if you're
Not just your congressmen or congresswoman
But if your senator approved this bill
And I would like to remind everyone
Immediately that both Barack Obama and John McCain
voted for this bailout bill
Barack Obama according to the record has about
20 has received about 25 million
Dollars and donations from Wall Street firms
Including a half million donation from Goldman Sachs
These are all names you should recognize by now
These aren't these are the top of the news
John McCain I think only $3 million less
$22 million from Wall Street firms
So don't you think that these guys should give that
Give that money back
Well Ralph Nader has a pretty good rap on that
The first here's Congressman Paul
who his immediate response right after the bill
And he just he it rolls off his tongue so quickly
He just slams it right out
And immediately you understand what's going
Ron Paul joining us now to let us know what he thinks of this
Bill as we look at it
That is just from the CNN actually
Is a heck of a lot of pork isn't it
Sure is it's pretty amazing you take a bad bill
And make it a lot worse and you get 57 members of the Congress switching from
No to yeah so that's actually something about Washington
There's really not hope much hope for us here in DC to solve the problems
Because it's just more the same more the spending
You know they're dealing with this
There is a financial crisis and a credit crunch
But they're not dealing with the fact that this country is bankrupt
And and and we're on the verge of some really major events
But we're adding far to the fuel there
We're just dumping carocene on it and making this problem that much worse
If death is a problem just think of what we've just done today
We have ballooned a debt like never before
Putting more pressure on the Federal Reserve to monetize this debt
And print more money so expect a lot more inflation inflation in the future
Do you think there was a reasonable alternative for this?
Oh absolutely do nothing would have been a reasonable alternative
But a reasonable alternative would have been to give some tax breaks
And also regulate the Federal Reserve
The exchange stabilization front
The President's working group on financial markets
They need regulate because they're working behind the scenes all the time
To satisfy and take care of their friends and buddies
So those are the kind of regulations we do need
But we should be enforcing contracts not canceling
Contracts like they are doing you know in the mortgage market
But the most important thing that we should not be doing
And that is to prop up bad death and malinvestment
Because that only prolongs the agony and makes our problems that much worse
Do you think that a lot of the politicians and I hate to use that word
But it's one of many of the markets where I look at you guys there and Washington
Really got this thing really understood it because I got to tell you
This is a really complicated deal perhaps as complicated as anything
It's ever been passed right?
I don't think I think it's the idea what's in the bill and what it does
And the unintended consequences
But you know Warren Buffett said he had no really good understanding of the derivatives market
That's why he stayed away from it
So he has trouble understanding them
Can you imagine the average member of Congress
Understanding the correction of the problems that have developed
Because the derivatives market is becoming unravel
So now there's very little understanding of the nature
Because they're limiting their thoughts to a credit crunch
Which means some people have lost their credit rating
And that's good because why keep learning the people that don't have a good credit rating
People who have good ratings can still borrow money and buy a car
People who have overspent and overbarred like the US government
They're going to have trouble and we are having trouble
But we have to deal with the nature of government and why we spend so much money
Run pull
Oh man
He comes out of him so easily doesn't it?
He just says it like it is
You know the Ralph Nader thing I would like to play it for you
But I'm worried that the sound is kind of shitty because it's indirect
So I'm not going to play that but you have to watch it because
Well this is really the problem with Ralph Nader
He was running for president by the way
And you can vote on him there are a couple other independence
And yes, thank you for all the notes
Bob bar
Not Ron bar
Chuck Baldwin, Cynthia McKinney
These are the main independence that I'm aware of at least
And even if you know the Cynthia McKinney is quite interesting to me as well
I think what's her website?
It's like vote o8.com
I'll get to her later
But the Ralph Nader thing
You got to listen to it
The whole problem with Ralph Nader is he has absolutely zero like fire
And enthusiasm he talks you know just like it almost like he's dead
And people just tune out within seconds I'm sure
But you put all of this together man
Yeah, man
I knew we were heading for something bad
But now with this bill passed and all the crap that's in it
And look at how happy these cock suckers look
Ah
They know they've got us by the balls now
So when we start hurting that's what we're going to take action
I'm sure
Adam
Yeah
We're in Portland
Every morning
I wake up I have a coffee
I walked across my backyard
And I go to my office
And I don't plot the drugs report
I don't pull up puffin' post
And I don't pull up the BBC
I pull up the drop dot IO
Yes
Daily source code
It is the best place for news
because I'm a contributor
I am Ed dashboard
Really egg
And
Other people are contributing
contributing also, we are outside of the mainstream, we're pulling it together under our own
perspective. We are an aggregator, the alligator of truth. I am wide awake. I have taken the
red pill and I've pulled because that's crunches stuff is nasty. Right, oh, man. You know, I do the
same thing when I wake up in the morning. It's drop.au slash daily source code because that's where
the true news is coming through and it's outrageous, some of the stuff that is an disappearing
in mainstream publications and we're just aggregating it, make sure you check that regularly
drop.au slash daily source code. This is also why I found out that the follow-up to the most
excellent movie zeitgeist is now out and available, link in the show notes of daily source
code.com. It's called zeitgeist Adendum and it completely explains how the money system works
where there's always a man out. It's like musical chairs because there's not enough money
in circulation for all the loans plus interest to be paid back. That's the long in the short of it.
And then it, you know, it kind of takes you through what can happen, what what we could do,
where we could take it. And actually there's a call to action, which I like about this.
About two hours long, well worth the watch. A lot of it, you'll probably already know or understand,
but that means you're learning. We're learning. That's good. The call to action at the end is
is pretty simple. Expose the banking fraud by, uh, well, exposing it first and foremost, but then
also, um, boycotting the banks and they talk about, uh, bank of America, city banks specifically,
uh, boycott the military, meaning no longer let your children, your friends, your co-workers,
join it because they're not fighting for your freedom, they're not fighting for your country. They don't
know it. Unfortunately, they don't know. They're fighting for corporations. There's a call to reject
the political system. Um, a lot to say about that, particularly now that I've learned that,
well, this is just one of those funny things. And it's something that I, I'm really
saddened and pick up on, uh, on earlier, but, uh, you know, there's a reason why only the Republican
and Democratic candidates get to debate on television. That's because there's some bogus-fucking
organization that, uh, that is the, uh, the representative or the organization that determines who
can be on the debates. And they, of course, uh, are founded by a Republican and a Democrat,
and they're run by these two parties. So there's no way an independent can even get into the debate.
And so there's not like law or anything that says they can't, it's just, you know, mainstream media,
regulating what we can see, determining the war you could call it censoring.
And of course, there's a call to join the movement. And as, and I was going through this, and I'm
prepping the show and I've been prepping the show kind of since Friday. You know, we did, um,
I was really busy, but also John and I did, uh, did a Thursday night, no agenda. So I, I,
just didn't have the band with the creator of Friday show. As I'm going through this, I'm like,
you know, we used to have all these cool fucking songs that would talk about the world around us and,
and what we felt. And, you know, and I'm talking like not even that long ago, you know, in the
80s and the 70s and there were shit out there. And when we were angry, you could really hear it. And I'm
really not hear it. And this, in this corporate bubblegum pop crap that passes from music these days.
Even these guys used to be cool. Remember this. I'm getting goosebumps just listening to that
intro. You too, on the Charlie.
Oh
I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I
I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not a human, I'm not an human, I'm not an human, I'm not a human, I'm not an human, I'm just an ordinary, I'm not a human, I'm just an ordinary, I'm just a human, I'm not a human, I'm just an ordinary, I'm just an ordinary
You're the sister's daughter-in-law
Somebody, but it's not me
How long have you seen this song?
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Somebody, but it's not me
You're the sister's daughter-in-law
Oh, there's tears away
Oh, there's tears
And it's true we are you
We're like the picture to feel the tears
And today the million is quiet
We need a great one tomorrow night
Oh, there's tears away
Where's that bottle, huh? Bring him back
Oh, there's tears
That's corporate shadow
Although I think honestly he really believed that he could change the world with corporate money
No way, man
We got to take the money out of the equation
It truly is the root of all evil
As constructed
By the true owners of the earth
You too, Sunday, funny Sunday
On Daddy's source code 79 or six
There was so much inspiration, so many cool things
That happened over the past like 36 hours
That I was watching or thinking about
So that's where I got all the inspiration from
For all the songs that I'm gonna play for you
Last night actually
Well, there's no today shows
So I wanted to get
Some current feedback from the mainstream
On the debate
And so Letterman, of course, is always a good choice and he's done exactly what I expected him to do as he's laying really hard into Sarah Pailin
Of course for those of you who don't know and if you haven't please listen to Noah Jenda Noah jended up
Meavio.com
Because you know this whole thing is it's just a show
It's just one big television show and these two parties
They pretty much agree on all the same things as no real difference
Both McCain and Obama voted to to pass this bill to help their buddies on on Wall Street
They're contributors millions of dollars
Go to the show notes and check out the video of Ralph Nader he'll he'll tell you more about it
DailySourceco.com
But anyway, so Craig Ferguson comes on
at what is that like 1235 and for the the whole opening the first
Oh, I should preface this by saying that
After 10 days here
I have connected with with one of the organic farmers
Who grow some of the most awesome is only herb in in this part of the country and they do it with love
I mean this this is a no, it'll make a lot, but it's a it's a real agricultural operation not not a money making scheme
And well some money. I'm sure but there you go
So I'm it's Friday night right so I'm it had a long week
I'm chill and I'm watching Craig Ferguson and
Kind of baked so
And he has this like sock puppet like muppet doing the whole opening and it's like all about this research they've been doing
And you know, so it's a whole long lineup is a fantastic joke
That they've they've researched and found out that a lot of people who watch
Late night was it to the late show or yeah, I think it's a late show
That they that they smoke herbal cigarettes and so of course I'm like
Laughing because they were right and then one of his first viewer males is is about some get from some guy who's name is Adam
And he's like oh man play that
Play that viewer male jingle because if you played while I'm baked it would like totally trip me out
And so you know here's Craig Ferguson, you know
Using my name talking about a situation and then it got me thinking
Hello, anybody there man
Yeah, like a make really happy you man
I sure also
Face okay, if I fool around of him it do beware room
All right
Yeah
Two eight out on order a hash brownies man
Oh, man, you always get it you wait this place, man. Yeah, hey, they guys
Grab a bite for the tops
Oh, wow
Just once I bring the cops
All right, there's those steps in the seeds
Never run if you be and you guys make a bacon double wide burger
These are my splits two days
They're quantal and they're known away and the do me
And the do me ah two American heroes there
Cheat and Sean
All right
All right, so here's a these are feedback that comes from
One of our chuckle heads who calls them very often. I always appreciate is appreciate his feedback
If you want to leave a voice male you can do that you can just drop an MP3 into the source code drop
Or that you can actually go to drop.au slash daily source code on the right hand side
You'll tell you how you can call in using phone number and a pin code and it'll show up as a as a voice male
In the drop, which is where I get you know everything is basically source now
From there for this show and and there's also a record over it. You know, so if I don't use it then
It still gets out to the community for those who are interested in listening to a lot of voice male
So Ross from Washington
Send it in the following which I'm very happy he did
Hey, Curry
Trust in Washington
Down here South of Seattle next to see that care port. Oh, yo, and all right bus
Uh, I want to use some bad references here, but
Got the five tell you what's on my mind. I keep here. What you're saying about this whole
The world basically the world's constructed around us there's a great awakening and
All this stuff and you know, I know that could think of it. He's like a cross between the expiles
And the matrix yeah good apologies speak of this
Mobile conspiracy that seems to be so vast
You know what and I've said this many times before
But it's often the biggest mountain that you don't see in front of you when you're looking for little trees. This is this way you learn as a pilot
When you start out you're instructor will lay down a map in front of you and say you're going from here and you're to there
Now find all the obstructions you have to look at look out for and so you're going to be looking for trees and towers and
Telephone poles and all kinds of stuff and you'll be pointing them out on the map and he'll say
Dude, how about that freaking mountain right in the path
How come you're not going to look to avoid that
So it's not like a conspiracy
This has been going on for a long long time and history is a lot longer than
The history channel can show you
This has been going on for
centuries
millennia
Okay
People's suppressing people and it all revolves around pretty much around money and a lot of
Ancillary crap that pops up to make it tougher like religion
So it's not a global you know conspiracy it's how the world works
But not how the world necessarily has to be
That no one's can in theory do anything about it at every time something happens. There's always a contingency plan for it
And yes, there's this awakening you know like this right neocard is going to come up
And the human population is going to rise up against the autonomous now unfortunately Russ
I don't believe that's going to happen the only way you know this great awakening is as you put it
Is truly an awakening people are now you know seeing things and it's because we can now communicate amongst ourselves
All please like we have to protect the internet
That's why we're waking up our our consciousness and this has been predicted actually in religion
You know our consciousness is now melding together through Google and Facebook and my space and and web logs and and podcasts and
whatever else
An instant messages and chat and
On and on and on you know flicker
Exchanging images
Seeing the world I mean we don't think twice, but but it you know
I communicate with people from Iran how come my government wants to kill them
And how come we think that they want to kill us they don't their government maybe and it makes no sense
So that isn't awakening and we can't be fooled anymore
Unless of course we're still stuck to the television and and sucked in and
And hypnotized which is what that box is all about so yeah of course
There's an awakening, but no no quick fix is taking a long time to get us to where we are
To get us to be in complete submission and enslaved because you know we have to the way the system works
So yeah, it's that doesn't mean like oh, oh now we have to you know run around and save the world
Well, you can't we can't do that overnight, but
Part of solving the problem is
Waking up to the problem and talking about it amongst ourselves. So you know
That's just a starting point Russ
The great conspiracy just like in the expile series and move
Always be one five 20 steps ahead and
People like you just gonna be a brief value. You know just like
Meal was just like or fierce was that you're gonna
Disoppose it. I'm not saying that you will but you know you are this embodiment of this great awakening
Then you guys want to try something or
Once you do get to a certain level the
Powers that be you're gonna come to you all
For a few add in these
Circular cyclical cycle will begin again
ah
I don't think I'm that important
uh
No, we're not gonna go do anything and
This is about an awakening of consciousness and it'll all happen automatically if enough
You know, one not if but one enough people have figured it out
Then there'll be no stopping us. I mean that's that's just the bottom line
It's not gonna be a handful of people. I it's not gonna be like a Gideon's army
We have uh, you know, 300 of 10,000 go and and topple the powers now
That's not gonna be like that. It's gonna be massive and
It's you know there will be there will just be no and doesn't you have to be violence? There will be no stopping it
Once we figure out how to vote and how we you know reject
Rigged voting machines and and lack of choice
Really, you know, we have no choice well of course we do
But the percentage of people who can actually name three other independent candidates running for president
Identified would wager is fairly low
Because they're excluded from the mainstream, you know that so that's that's the game right there
We got to start changing that game first
And that could take another 20 years
But yeah, I feel it is my responsibility to
the past this information on and and to help people get there and so when else is gonna have to pick it up eventually
And I'm not the only one man. This is all over the place
So there must be millions of people who who who are switched on to this and who are communicating it and are in their own way
Re routing and broadcasting the information
That's step one. That's what we're all doing here
You know, so unfortunately unlike the rest of you'd like your life to be
There's you know, we don't solve it in 22 minutes plus eight minutes of commercials like they do on TV
You know, it's not gonna be a sitcom that winds up and
All happily ever after
You know, we've actually got to do some work
Not doesn't mean you have to go out and start you know yelling and screaming and beating up and
Politicians no no no
We've first got to get every we first got to get scale
Actual scale
I've seen all these small you know small groups doesn't work
So that's just and that's just information of the of the mind you know passing that information on and it's clear
Rust you know what's going on you you're awake for sure
Again, you know, yeah, sounds like I really fed
You know analysis that really seems to be what you keep presenting to me and
You know you you say that we the people to make it's different and you
You present this huge
Unscalable and feasible force that we have to overcome and you're right is probably have true
Not as big as we view it to be but really what where are you going with all this?
So that's a simple for a second you are right
So what points are you right? I it really seems like a hopeless endeavor
Because really when it comes down to us you're to get the people it you don't need
To program the human species you don't need to put
For oxide or fluoride into their water. You don't need to
Fatter on with advertisements it's a libinal messaging to tell of you know that the human race as a whole are dumb scared
Violence to begin the visuals
No, that's the system has made us that way
That's why
This whole system of really the system of debt has has that's what there are different ways
There are different ways to construct our society. You know that would be a real long-term goal
But we're now we're in in fact quite the opposite we're all really intelligent beings who if fed love and light
Conflorish but without that now. I mean with the then you just get nothing you get robots
enslaved robots. That's what you're seeing add to that
whole host of
toxins that we're putting into our bodies
Whether it's constructed and but by design or not
We're you know we're limiting our our capacity our life capacity our consciousness capacity
So it's I think it kind of starts there honestly
That generally you have to be controlled to some way safer form because they're too
In confident to really run themselves so when you have that type of overwhelming power
You're just going to have this
cyclical cycle so yeah, Russ if you really believe that if you really believe human beings basically are just trash
Then you know to kill yourself. I mean that's crazy
I that it doesn't sit right with me now
It's you know maybe 10 years ago. I wasn't thinking about this stuff and I
Mind of
Certainly in in my lifetime said you know you gotta have all these rules because people just trash it
But if you get down to the fundamentals of people no, I think we're all good
I really do
And again, you know where we're we're all made up of the same material the same
Basic materials available in the universe
a lot of that being water and
I truly believe that the the system around us is just it makes us prone to
greed envy
And then everything that stems from that
Yeah, I know I think it could be different Russ. That's really that's really where I'm coming from so even if you are right
And even if we can make a difference and don't want to seem like what's the point? I'm 100 years from now
It's not gonna matter same things. I'm gonna keep happening over and over
Just like it has in the past and it's like it has in the future so yeah, they're really convinced me here curry
What's the point? So
This is Russell Minum again here next to the sea tag Airport and
Love you man. Me and it's right here. Hope you win
Whatever having the people actually saying that. I think you brought that up. I don't think we need anyone does this sign off stuff
No, no, no, no, except for the obligatory they work for us
Yeah, right just like everything else on this planet in theory anyway
Practicality bullshit really is anyway curry hey
You got your final speed to you damn my old die for the death
die
I would defend your right to say it to the death no matter how much I made disagree with it
So amen talk to you later. Bye
So I really enjoy that comment Russ because basically what you're saying yeah, it's pretty much all true
But you're giving up and saying what can we do about it? You know in my lifetime
I felt freeer than I feel right now
Even though my government wherever I was
Was probably up to no good at that moment in time as well
But we do have to fight for it and
This has been going on for for so long and people have been singing about this and and again
That's where I got a lot of the inspiration for the songs I'm gonna play for you today and
And we just shouldn't give up we should continue to try and let's try and stop some of this insanity
We certainly are outnumber anyone
Which I think is a pretty pretty small group, but it's just a huge pyramid of power trips all the way down to us
And yes, I am with you and in in the same layer of the pyramid, okay, and we just can't we just can't sit down
I mean what else if if you're looking for a purpose in life at least let'd be to try and free up some shit
So our kids don't have to deal with all of this crap
I certainly feel that the previous generation has let me down so I don't want to make the same
Stand up
Stand up for your right
Don't give up the fight
Reach a man on tell him heaven is on the year
I know you don't know
What life is really worth
He's a poor bad means of his cool
I'm the story and I've been told to now you see the right
Stand up for your right
Come on get up
Stand up
Stand up for your right
Get up
Stand up
Don't give up the fight
Get up
Stand up
Stand up for your right
Get up
Stand up
Don't give up the fight
Most people think
Great God will come from the sky
Take away everything and make a hit with that if you hide
But this and all what life is worth
You will look for yours on earth
And now you see the right
Just stand up for your right
Get up
Stand up
Stand up for your right
Get up
Stand up
Don't give up the fight
Reach a man on tell him heaven is on the year
I know you don't know what life is worth
You're right
God
Lord
Stand up
Keep us from the Lord
Don't give up the fight
Yeah
We're sick and tired of your exams
Kids in games
Dying and going to heaven
In the Jesus' name
Lord
We know when we understand
A mighty body's living man
You can't fool some people
Sometimes
But you can't fool all the people all the time
So now we see the light
What should we go to stand up for?
Right
Stand up
Don't give up
Stand up for your right
Stand up
Come up
Get up
Stand up
You don't give up
The violin
All right
We gotta united
You stand up for your last
A Tears
Alright
Stand up
Stand up for your right
You stand up for your right
Stand up
I know
Stand up for your right
You stand up for your right
over not certainly during this presidential election year and there's one
president that I just don't hear a lot of people quoting often and I ran
across as I was prep and I ran across a cool bit from Johnny Cash who
recites one of Lincoln's famous speeches the Gettysburg Address and I think
it's good to listen to that again you know and the Gettysburg Address
do you can you right now if you're an American can you tell me how it starts off
you should have said four score and seven years ago because that's how it starts
somehow it really it the the meaning really comes through a lot better when Johnny Cash
reads it so I'm gonna play that for you and there's a specific reason because there's
one thing that I am noticing this troubling that I've been here for moving up
on two weeks now and and you can hear the melancholy and I'm a little bit
homesick and I miss the girls but you know good inward journey here sitting
alone in the con now there is a division in America and is this red state
blue state thing that is starting to trouble me and the way I hear these so
cold sides talk about each other is bothersome and it used to be north and south
and now it's red state blue state and it pretty much seems like it's the coast
and then everything in the middle and I don't like it one bit and I want to remind
us that we've been through some of this crap before and we shouldn't go back to
those times again four score and seven years ago so begin the message of a war
weary president Abraham Lincoln a message written on the back of an envelope on the
train on the way to dedicate a battlefield where men from the north and south
had died at Gettysburg, Pennsylvania four score and seven years ago
our forefathers brought forth on this continent a new nation conceived in liberty
and dedicated to the proposition that all men are created equal now we are engaged in a
great civil war testing whether that nation or any nation so conceived and so dedicated
can long endure we are met on a great battlefield of that war we have come to
dedicate a portion of that field as a final resting place for those who here
gave their lives that that nation might live it is all together fitting and proper
that we should do this but in a larger sense we cannot dedicate we cannot consecrate
we cannot allow this ground for the brave men living and dead who struggle here
have consecrated it far above our poor power to add or detract the world will little
notes or long remember what we say here but it can never forget what they did here
it is for us to living rather to be dedicated here to the unfinished work which they who
fall here have thus far so nobly advanced it is rather for us to be here dedicated
to the great test remaining before us that from these on her dead we take increased devotion
to that cause for which they gave the last full measure of devotion that we hear highly
resolve that these dead shall not have died in vain and that this nation under God shall have a new
birth of freedom and that government of the people by the people and for the people shall not
perish from the earth.
Lost it flat and Ben Rouge waiting for a train on us being inspected as magic
Bob it thundered diesel dam just before rain and wrote us all the way into New Orleans
I pull on the harpoon and if my dear here it bend and I stay in soft love I'll be saying the
blood when she will I perspire for ten hours hold in Bobby's hand and man we sing every song
that javanoo
reading this just another word for nothing left to do nothing I'm in nothing honey today free
and he and good was he's an outlaw when he sang a close you know feeling good was good enough
for me and my body I am from the can and tucky home and forget to count upon your son
if I'm a share the secrets of my soul you all can's the weather to everything and we're done
you're Bob it baby help me alone you are one day on your sunny and slow home I landed in the
slip away he's looking for that home and now hope we're fancy but I train all amounts of
one say no I have to be in Bobby's body next to mine
reading this just another word for nothing left to do nothing I'm in nothing
Bobby left me but he and good was he's an outlaw when he sang a close
everything good was good enough for me and I'm from the can and tucky home and forget to count
me and my body I am from the can and tucky home and forget to count upon your son
and I'm from the can and tucky home and now hope we're fancy but I train all amounts of one
I landed in the slip away he's looking for that home and now hope we're fancy but I train all amounts of one
all right we youngins up there that's a chanus joplin
right just another word for nothing left to lose and boy she knew what that was about
now I gotta tell you I am living the dream right now ever since I was a young kid I always
dreamt about playing records for my buddies cool songs that I like and of course not really
records anymore and look at what we're doing man look at how the stuff is getting converted into
one to zero showing up in your earphones and this is good times good times to be excited about
even though there's a lot of crap going on so in a good football Friday tradition even though it's
the weekend probably when you're listening to this let's play it shall we play a little game
hey Adam this is hit this number one oh 41 and we're gonna start right away with intro
all right now wow 10 cc drive on a power day holiday it's funny because I play 10 cc's
Wall Street Chouple the top of the show number two
I'm gonna say hot chocolate everyone's a winner 10 and this is number three
10 10 and she's not there wow young awesome songs man definitely from the sound
track to my life you hit them all straight on I think I got six out of six and it's time for the
answers and this week they're all from and this is answering number one
this is fancy she dread like holiday
and I love it and answer number one 10 cc and this is answering number two yeah this is
cryoclet
This is a winner babe that's no lie
Answer number two hotshugglers everyone so winner baby
And this is answer number three
I love this.
So, this is Santana.
She's not there.
No one told me about her.
Don't let you lie.
She's no bother trying to find her.
She's not there.
I love it, I love it.
I love the way she wants.
I will be active, like color of her head.
I'll hold this often through her.
Who's she not there?
Santana's answer number three.
Hey, wow.
And that concludes hit us number one, four, one.
Yo.
So, Adam.
Yeah.
How did you do this?
Dude.
I hope I didn't disturb my milpy neighbor with the sing in there.
But six out of six, y'all.
I nailed them.
All of them.
Alrighty, that concludes this hit test.
Like always, hit test.
Mefio.com is the place to find the answers to the hit test.
And also the links to iTunes.
So you can buy the tricks featured on the hit test online.
Alrighty.
Thank you for playing, Adam.
Thank you, y'all.
Let me tell you one thing about my own focus.
In the latest episode, I take the audience sort of a tour of my studio.
Some sort of a lot of your experience.
You can hear whatever you piece of equipment in the signal chain is doing.
I'm switching it on and off.
That's very nerdy.
Cool to listen to.
So check it out.
It's at yonfolio.com.
Hello everyone.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I hope you'll be back with another hit test.
So until then, take care.
Have fun.
And, try to think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
Be back.
Hit test at gmail.com.
info.
Yonfolio.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T-D-A-G-O.
Jesus.
What the heck?
Hi, Adam.
Have fun games.
Weasel on this week's show.
I shake my maracas about with somebody.
Amiga on the Wii.
I get down and dirty on a quad bike with pure on the 360.
We have a little listen to a strange game called The Mushroom Men.
And you can win copies of Dinosaur King for the DS.
That's all it gamesweasel.com.
See you every hour and a half of the hours.
Go with us by the way.
We'll be a mini show.
Here's the news.
I killed me now.
We could all ride a ride.
Someone would've been like the iron and plastic bag.
We've been playing the game.
We've been playing the players.
We've had fun.
We've been playing the game.
We've been other than games.
We've had fun.
We've played the game that we've played.
we've played the game.
We've played the game.
We've played the game that we've played.
We've had fun.
We're going on some trips.
We've played the game.
Republican and Democratic debates that we've seen. I think we could get people to watch
But you know, it would take a lot of resources for sure and you really need like a hot-shit producer
Yeah, like one of these guys. It does the Emmys
I know those people in show biz land in California who were switched on and listen to the daily source code
If you have any ideas if you think we could actually drum up some people, you know, we could do it
But I'm afraid we were really running short on time. It was less than 30 days now
Yeah, listen that less than a month until until we until we hit the election
So I just don't see it happening. We're probably going to have to wait another four years before we can actually do anything
But at least now we can see and keep track of and keep score on what exactly is going to happen
Whoever gets into the White House
There's been a lot of promises made and well, you'll see all of them systematically broken as usual
They're just actors. They're not actually running anything the agenda is set
That's the way you have to look at it. So 20 years. No. I think we can probably in in four years
We could get the independence in a real show business like debate and eventually in another four years
So eight years from now we might actually have them in
In with the big debates that that could be possible
But and actually it might even be desirable as we probably go into a 10 year recession slash depression
Which is just the way it goes boomer bus cycle with the system that we have and we'll have time to evaluate that system
We got a lot of smart kids and school now
You know there are other ways to run the society absolutely
So by then we might we might be on the upswing
So I'd say eight to ten years is probably realistic
I had a parent on here. You know how we hopefully say
They work for us well I'd be thinking about it and the reality is
We work for them if you include all our direct and indirect taxes
We work about six months of the year for the government six months
Nobody escapes at every body pays sure they might work for us sometimes at all
But rain or shine we pay
It's a one-way relationship and that's the root of our problem the state uses its monopoly power on violence and money
To impose its will so naturally since it's the most efficient way to maximize profit
Special interest will converge to control the state and it's monopoly on violence to further its own ends
So in a state of system it will and can only get worse
So on that positive note
Are live your life will pass?
Okay, by the
Absolutely no of course
That's what I mean when we say when I say we're enslaved
You know there's no reason we should have to work six months out of the year for the man
That's horses
And we should stand up and we should say it even if it's a child like anthem just do it
We've got the right to do it
There ain't no way we'll lose it
This is our life, this is our song
We'll fight the thousands we trust
Don't make up, there's nothing wrong
You don't know what's yet out below
Oh
Oh, we are so proud to send it
We are always never ready
We don't want nothing for you
Oh
Your life is right treated
So far we've never seen it
And we're too fast
And we're all done
Oh
We'll fight
Yeah
There you'll see
Oh
Oh, we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we
we'll write ya and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you then we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you and we'll write you'' we'll write you and we'll write you we'll write you and we'll write you we'll write you so we'll write you and we'll write you write after we'll write it us if we'll write
Oh, we're not for the safety.
Hello, we're not taking it.
Any more?
At a Earth and Poland year, bad times, just thinking about how art reflects as a mirror to
what happens in the world.
I have so listening to no one else by Grandmaster Flash in the Furious Five, right?
So it's like a jungle sometimes.
It makes me wonder how I keep going under, ain't that right?
All I have to say at this point is, don't push me, cause I'm close to the edge and I'm
trying to end up telling you this, my head.
It's like a jungle sometimes.
It makes me wonder how I keep going under, ain't that right?
Think I'm...
So, proper's doing bad.
It's gonna be my mother's TV, says she watch it too much.
It's just not healthy.
All my children in the big-top, Dallas and night can even see the game or the sugar
rate fight.
To be able to collect it, they ring my phone and scan my wife when I'm not home.
Got a bomb education double digit and flavor can take the train to the job.
There's a spike at the station.
On King Kong standin' on my back, can't stop the turn around.
But, secondly, I got a mid-range my Grandmaster remember, sometimes I think I'm going to see
that swell.
I might not jack a plane.
Push me.
Call, oh, close to the edge.
Try again, not too loose my head.
It's like a jungle sometimes.
It makes me wonder how I keep going under.
A child is born with no state of mind blind to the ways of mankind.
Got a smile on you and he's frowning too, because only God knows what you go through.
You're grown in the ghetto living second, right?
And your eyes will sing a song, because he hate it.
The place that you pay at where you stay.
Looks like one great big alleyway.
You let my oven up for booktakers, ducks and bushes in the big money maker.
Got a big consman of 20s and 10s and you want to go up to be just like that.
Smellers, scammers, burglers, gamblers, pickpockets, pedellers, eat the pan hellers.
You say I'm cool, I know food, but then you wind up, drop a night of high school.
Now you earn it boy, all non-boy, y'all can round like you're pretty boy,
boy, turn stick up kids, but look what you done did.
Got a set of four eight year big, now you're man who just took it.
Your make-tags been the next two years as an undercover fan.
Being used in the future, so if I can't do one day, you would found her dead in the cell.
But now that I sing the sets that song, I hide your lips so fast and die so young.
So don't push me, cause I'm close to the edge.
I'm trying not to lose my head.
Drame out to flash, smelly mouth.
I know more feedback or news items from this point in, I'm just gonna play some songs, man.
You need to play some.
You know, this is a song that most of you probably only know from the Muppet Show and Kermit the Frog,
but it's originally performed as I know it by Willie Nelson.
It's just such a pretty song.
Why are there so many songs about rainbows?
And it walks along the other side.
Rainbows are visions, but only illusions.
And rainbows have nothing to hide.
So we've been told, and some choose to believe it.
I know they're wrong, wait and see.
Someday we'll find it, the rainbow connection.
The lovers and the dreamers and me.
Who said that every wish would be heard and answered,
when wished on the morning star.
Somebody thought of that, and someone believed it.
Look at what it's done so far.
And what's so amazing, that keeps us stargazing.
And what do you think we might see?
Someday we'll find it, the rainbow connection.
The lovers, the dreamers and me.
All of us under its spell.
We know that it's probably magic.
Have you been half asleep?
And have you heard voices?
I've heard them calling my name.
Is this the sweet sound?
It calls the young sailors.
The voice might be one in the same.
I've heard it too many times, too ignore it.
It's something that I'm supposed to be.
Someday we'll find it, the rainbow connection.
The lovers, the dreamers and me.
He really does represent what a true American is.
Willie Nelson and the rainbow connection.
Yes, we all kind of just like lovers and dreamers and looking for that rainbow connection.
Deep inside.
That's probably why I'm making such a fuss about trying to make things better.
You always born in 1964, which is a long time ago.
You are constantly reminded of your age when you go to a dropdown on the web.
You have to find yourself scrolling down much further to get to your birth date, your year.
But so the Vietnam War took place in my very young.
I don't remember much about other than a couple of my friends.
The brothers were going off to Vietnam.
But in the late 70s, there were a lot of songs.
Particularly this song, the video clip that went along with it.
Really showed us and taught us how horrible this was.
And these were modern images.
And for the first time, he was real blood and kids being blown up from the neighborhood.
And those of you who remember that, this should probably bring back some memories.
On Paraside.
We left us and made from our style.
And we were sharp.
As sharp as nice.
And we were so gone whole to lay down our life.
We came in space.
Like tables horses.
We left in a basket.
As number horses.
And we learned that.
To travel like.
Our arms were heavy, but our values were tight.
We had no hope.
We had no sauce.
They sent us freedom.
They gave us love.
We dug in deep.
And shot unsight.
And created Jesus Christ with all of our mind.
We had no count.
As you were the last game.
We first had time.
And we made our hostings.
And it was dark.
So talk at night night night night.
And we had our sweet joy.
I cried so round.
We promised our love as we rise.
We were all around.
We sent we all around.
We made our hostings.
The night and the night seem to last as long as it's weeks
On fire a silent, we held the course light, they held the high light
And they wish you a sharpest night's day
They had the home of the mountains, they counted the roses
And waiting for us to arrive
And we held the home of the mountains
Spilly Joel, good night's side gone
A song about the recruits who went to Paras Island six weeks
And then they were shipped off to Vietnam
Many other deaths
And when this song came out
And I remember parents everywhere had to explain to their kids
Because it was accompanied by a video that had the most shocking images you could imagine
And it was really, wasn't the little green army men that we played with
And it was really, it was a couple of years after the war I think
And it really brought a lot back and I think it started up a whole new social conversation
And I'm not hearing this in music anymore
I'm not hearing about our boys and girls in the desert
Who are being killed and blown to bits
I'm just not hearing it anymore
And I really, really miss it
And maybe that's why I'm playing all of these different songs
Because these types of messages I'm telling you
I just don't hear it anymore
And a lot of the independent stuff
But still not like this
There's something fundamentally different
And then a couple of years later after that
It's unbelievable
Now all of a sudden we were in the 80s
We were getting electronic instruments
We still didn't actually have digital recorders yet
Nor did we have cell phones at that point
It was getting close
And all of a sudden, out of nothing comes another
Like anti-war remembrance type thing going back to Vietnam
But in Vietnam as the song
And you heard Billy Joel saying we played our doorsteps
And then we had Billy Joel who sang Good Night Saigon
And then this must have been
I'm going to say it was maybe 80, 81 something like that
Out of nothing comes a song about the average age of the recruit being sent
Over to Vietnam, which I will wager
It's pretty much the average age of the new recruit going over to Iraq
Afghanistan and God knows where else
That average age is 19, Paul Hardcastle did this
In 1965, Vietnam seemed like just another foreign war
But it wasn't, it was different many ways
And so were those who did the fighting
In World War II, the average age of the combat soldier was 26
In Vietnam, it was 19
But how was fighting the last whole thing
And you know today, when you are alive, you're a person who's alive on
I was really sure what was doing on
In Vietnam, it was 19
It was 19
In swh, mudmump, mudmump
In 79, it's 12
It's still 7
According to a veteran's administration study, half of the Vietnam Congress veterans suffered
from what's a guy this call, post-cramatic stress disorder. Many vets complain of alienation,
rage or guilt. It stops to come to societal thoughts. Hate to 10 years after coming
off, almost 800,000 men are still fighting to be accountable.
None of them received the heroes welcome.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I
I don't, not, I know, I know, I, know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know
old field who you might know from tubular bells claim this was I think one of the first sample
copyright lawsuits surrounding the song 19 by Paul Hardcastle and so he sued Paul Hardcastle
and I think they did settle or had some money transferred but at the time Michael
Field's manager was a guy named Simon Fuller and I think they probably got some good
money because he wound up starting a company called 19 entertainment which has gone on to do
such things as manage the spice girls and create the worldwide television hit series
pop idol or American idol as we as we know it in the states so moving on a little bit more towards
the 80s there were still plenty of songs that struck a chord with me where I thought hey man
for the first time some lyrics actually mean something like this one
oh yeah from prints
so George was going on in the 80s and I climb up a money I'll tell you a story about the sign at the time
same at home now 70 year old boys and they're beautiful it's meeting again called the
telling you about it dying since the kid or maybe because he couldn't afford to feed it
we'll send the people to the moon except him and my cousin tried to read for photo
as right it is a sign at the time
you know there was a time before Britney Spears and
other mindless pop music reanna jalo there was there was a time when lyrics actually meant
something and there was a message there and there was something you could kind of agree with
and if anything we've lost ground on that we really have you know sure it's out there but not
of the mainstream media I mean do you remember the songs and the key of life album and
Stevie Wonder when he took you down into his village ghetto lamb
rock on glass is everywhere it's a bloody steam can we take the
stands
oh
yeah
it
THANKS YOU SHOW UP
Ham leaders by Indo Sulina
They shun wrongs the street
They be tied before the war
Infected by the clear
Now some folks say that we should be
A planet from what we have
Tell me would you be happy
Will it get no man?
Speed you under
Village ghetto land
From the songs in the key a light man
That was probably my
My all time favorite album
Double album no less
I hope this is the file size of this damn show isn't too big
Two more songs I'm gonna hokey on you now
Because this made an impact on me man
I was on television
I've been on television for like three months
And then this came out it was like
Wow
Someone gives a shit about the world
Can you name them all?
If so you're old
USA for Africa we are the world
There comes a time
When we heat a circle
When the world must come together as one
There are people dying
Won't it's time to lend the hand
To light the greatest gift of all
We can go on
Retending day by day
Because of some world
Soon we could change
And we all will follow
Lots of great big family
And the truth
You know love is all we need
Yeah
Beyond our dreams
We're the next one
There's a choice we're making
We're saving our lives
It's time to make a better day
Just you and me
Well, I'm listening to your heart
So they know that someone is
And that I will be stronger and free
Just go on the show now
And turn it so red
And so we all must live
Let me have
We are the world
We are the children
For making a better day
So let's not give me
Won't it's time to make a better day
We're saving our lives
It's time to make a better day
Just you and me
We're done
And I'll miss you
The whole better
But if you're just free
Stop when we can fall
But my way
The world
All that it's changed
Can all become
Where we
Should have never left
Won't it's time to make a better day
We are the children
We are the ones
We're the better day
So let's not give me
Won't it's time to make a better day
We are the world
We are the children
We are the ones
We're the better day
So let's not give me
Won't it's time to make a better day
Just you and me
We are the world
We are the children
We are the ones
We're the ones
We're the children
We're just you and make a better day
So let's not give me
Won't it's time to make a better day
saw my heart
Was I a dream
Me is the only honour
Tomorrow I get in
So let's not give me
Girl is the choice
We have a chance, we have a man, we say we're all alive
It's true, we're like a part of the day that you need
Come on, let me tell you, we are the world
We are the children, we are the ones who make up for the day
So let's not give it, we're the ones who give it
Let's just, we're making, we're saying our lives
It's true, we're like a part of the day
Just, you and me, yeah, we are the world
We are the children, we are the ones who make up for the day
So let's not give it, we're the ones who make up for the day
Just, we're born, we are the children, we are the ones who make up for the day
I'm ready
Feel free to lie
We are the one
We are the stupid
The reason for me
To love the fuck you
Oh man, almost forgot
Great Charles saw that
Yeah
He liked me
Did you not help me sing along?
Hey, it's proved
The 25 years ago we could at least point to the continent of an Africa
How we done so far, huh?
Yeah, it's great
There's no even more countries in Africa
With the tribes killing each other
We've got the Chinese in there
Three quarters of a million Chinese
Raping
Just like the Europeans, the Americans
We've taken everything
I don't think anything has changed
Nothing gotten better
Children are still dying
And we are literally
Literally eating Africa
25 years ago
That was the vibe
We had the right spirit
But we just fools
Did we not actually understand how this works
And shouldn't we really try and stop it?
Isn't it really just about time?
Anyway
I was kind of fun
Just a gem out of few songs after now
They're going to play one more
And that'll be the last one
This is
Let's see
Well, it's a song that
I found that on the podcast of music network
And I really liked the voice
And it's how I feel about all of you chuckle heads
Because you really are
Individually and collectively
Quite
Embraceable
Just one look at you
My heart grows tipsy in me
You
And you'll all
Bring out the tipsy in me
And I love you
The way you're
Is about you
I'm above
I'm with my arms around you
Don't be an option
Baby
Come to Mama
Do
My sweet embrace
Come to Mama
Do
My sweet embrace
Come to Mama
Do
My sweet embrace
Come to Mama
Come To Mama