This podcast is brought to you by Poncho and GoDaddy.
This show will give you a special code to get great discounts at GoDaddy.com.
Got something to say?
Log it with your frequent log from GoDaddy.
It's 6am.
This is San Francisco.
Head Delta Sheriff Charlie.
713.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
You're listening to the Daily Source code with Adam Curry.
And his audience have meant well, love him.
No, homo.
Yeah, we're right.
Running your pants through my hair.
It's made them loud.
They're like the jungle for us.
But at least you see what you're doing here.
This man comes and knows none of this magic is not known.
It's waving your wall in your ear.
Shots off.
Please, the woman's dead.
You give you back these problems to some of you.
But you don't even answer me.
I wanted to get on it.
Someone's got me.
Baby, give me his phone.
I'm freaking.
You see your 10 boys.
Break your love.
That's what I like.
I give the up 10 boys.
Break your love.
That's what I like.
In terms of goals, we're saddened.
My left and maybe.
In terms of best of what the smell of the scene of the fun.
I couldn't see who was the looks you were after.
Now you place me on your kid and shop.
I've never met you two.
I've never met you.
You're the one you love.
Break your love.
That's what I like.
Get out of your heart.
Break your love.
That's what we've had.
Break your love, get always up so good
In a way, you love it's a cup of
Break your love, get the up 10 boys
Break your love, that's what we like
Break your love, get always up so good
In a way, you love it's a cup of
Break your love, get girls to make it easy
Eyes to sex so crazy, my pretend is so insane
Oh, get it, I'm home
Oh, get it, I'm dying
So let it all at tonight tonight
Boys will be boys, no to livestream
Boys will be boys, no to challenge
The boys will be boys, no chance
The boys will be boys, no to challenge
Boys will be boys, no to challenge
Co unmotic boys, no to challenge
Well, that doesn't open up the deranity and you, I don't know what else will.
It's uptown, boys, regular, Tyler Burns from the Faud Save Music on the daily source
code episode 713 coming to you from the curry kind of over about it.
Now, let me ask you, if there was definitely one thing you wouldn't do when you were
going on the road, would you change your road base setup?
I bet you wouldn't, oh man, oh, oops, sorry about that.
Nice little fade out there, wonderful.
Yeah, here's what I've done.
Actually it was Franco from Rokostitalia who turned me on to the new version of Ableton
Live, which is now up to number seven.
The line I went back to my email actually and I looked, and I guess maybe the release
numbers correspond with the year that they were released because it was 2005 when I
last looked at Ableton Live and just like every other program for the Mac, really,
I think we've come into a beautiful crux kind of an intersection where everything
all fits together where we have the processor speed is fast enough, the software is
lean and mean enough where you can actually just plug in a microphone and there's no latency.
I mean, there is, there actually is a few milliseconds, maybe it's less than one millisecond
latency, which the program just needs to keep pace with itself.
So why don't you be along on the ride with me to find out if they actually hangs together?
I gotta tell you, it looks pretty, actually, you know what, why don't I make a screenshot
of it home on a second?
I think I can do this, who knows what will happen, right?
All kind.
Okay.
I don't know if that worked enough, but it seems like we're still recording, so I'll just
leave it as it is.
Yeah, it's actually a little bit past six a.m. it's now about six twenty five.
I got in last night, or actually yesterday afternoon, now I apologize because the
first of all, I thought I was going to be able to do a show on Tuesday, turned out
Tuesday in the city was a lot easier than I expected.
I didn't get home until relatively late.
And on the way home, I found out, oh, you know what, I really do need to go to San Francisco.
And of course, we have one of our infamous board meetings today, actually.
So, Lickley split, booked a flight, flew out Wednesday morning, flight, of course, was
nice on eventful.
I was actually, I slept for a couple hours, which is nice, maybe three, four hours.
Now, it just started watching this movie, I think it's called Shut Up, I think, or
it's about a WLDJ PD Green in Washington.
And I was about twenty minutes into it, and there was sales weasel Greg stand the next
to my seat, who was on the same flight, he had been in London, he had been working with
Vanessa, our sales weaselette in the UK office.
So he went down to the bar.
I've never actually sat at the bar on Virgin on a Virgin flight, and it was Greg, because
there was no one else there, and the minute you sit down, they start to serve you, you know,
it's like, can get you drink, you know, want something to eat, we'll mix them off to
noon tea, so it was nice, and we chatted for at least an hour and a half, maybe even two
hours.
It was good, we really got caught up on a lot of things.
And of course, I said, hey, you know, I would invite you to ride with me into the city,
but guess what?
I'm pretty sure that they're going to flag me and they're going to stop me.
So we went through customs together, lo and behold, and actually, you know, it happened
once again.
Custom guy said, hey, wait a minute, aren't you, um, aren't you, uh, that, uh, I said, yeah,
the MTV guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the MTV guys, you know, uh, I thought you would kind of, you know,
I kind of saw that look and I thought you look familiar and I said, you know, the look
you have on your face right now.
I've seen that for the past five times, I've entered the U.S., because you're looking
at me going, that's the MTV guy.
How come I've got to put a M on his uh, customs form?
He said, yeah, I don't know, man, but there's definitely something in there.
And it's an M, it's definitely an M.
I'm trying, I know one will tell me what the M stands for, um, I, you know, I, I just,
I can't even come up with anything.
So yeah, um, I had to go through, uh, and actually I took a little different approach
this time, um, you know, I was all smiles and like, hey, how you doing?
Oh, I guess I should go straight ahead there.
Yeah, I know where to go and he, you know, once again put my customs form, the little
blue plastic, uh, clicking on the thing and, uh, and walked me over.
And this time, there was a guy there who had, um, investigated me before.
And he's like, wow, man, you're still on the list, uh, yeah, this is, uh, well, how come
you can't get off of this?
I said, uh, I think you know the answer to that, to know, I have a piece of paper and you
can send it and I was like, yeah, right, that's the freedom of information, act piece
of paper that I got in New York the last time.
He said, yeah, yeah, it doesn't really make any difference.
Yeah, you're right.
But anyway, you're okay, go on through how about that, huh?
How about that for some service?
Hey Adam, Adam, this is Andrew from the Bay Area, uh, I'm way behind on the episodes, but
I just want to call you having a discussion about why you appeared on the Homeland Security
or Customs, no fly list, or at least check you every time you do fly list.
One thing that I hadn't heard about up yet is the fact that you're a pilot.
You mentioned that they have this database or this sort of checklist where you check
a certain number of boxes, then you get put on that list or you get flagged for screening.
So my guess is, uh, one of the big boxes you check is the fact that you're a pilot, if you
remember, obviously 911, the guys trained as pilot.
So, uh, in addition to you, you know, flying in and out of the country a lot, uh, the
fact that you and yourself are a pilot, okay, that has triggered something in their database.
Anyway, just not to you.
Yeah, well, interesting thought, and when I think about a little bit more, yeah, you know,
if you put it all together, the fact that I've been to Kuwait, uh, Kuwait, sorry, uh,
the fact that I've been to Iraq, uh, this was, by the way, all my previous passport, but I'm sure
the information carried over because I had to get visas, at least for Kuwait, I had to get a visa.
Uh, add to that a pilot's license, uh, remember there's everything from the DMV to the IRS
and his database and this illegal database, I might point out, which is not supposed to
exist according to Congress, but it is there.
Uh, the, the knocking and, uh, and all the, uh, sounds you hear is a combination of me sitting
at the, uh, at the table, I'm not at the Bakers' rack because basically, all I have now
was just my Mac, how about that?
I don't have 15 outboard pieces of gear.
It's the first time I've come to San Francisco without the Violopt laptop, which includes
cast blast.
So I was really taking a risk saying, you know what, if I'm going to do it, I'm just going
to do it.
See if I can get this thing to work, uh, hopefully so far.
So good.
You know, it was a, um, maybe it was, uh, the beginning of, uh, last week, or maybe even the
week before that at the end, I was talking about, uh, the Nokia N-810, the internet tablet.
By the way, uh, I'm the top seller so far, uh, from what I understand, uh, these are
unofficial numbers, it's actually work and people have purchased it at the best price
anywhere on the internet, 15% discount if you use the code daily source code, um, and, uh,
and thank you by the way for those of you who've purchased it for sending me, uh, you know,
nice little emails about how much you love it.
I told you I wouldn't steal you wrong on this thing, but, um, so maybe a week ago, two
weeks ago, I was talking about using log me in on, uh, on the tablet to get to other computers,
basically, like, uh, kind of like what Apple is trying to do with their, um, uh, back to
my Mac, which just doesn't work very well across all different networks.
I mean, I've tried every, every combination, um, and, you know, I really just want to be
able to take over a control of the screen of at least, you know, four of the computers
that are in my life.
Most importantly, the one that my wife uses because, you know, from time to time, she just
needs some help.
Hey, Adam, Jesse, and you can't hear you, I say, thinking about the last C had C I heard
and had a few things to say about it.
First of all, that log me in services, like in way cool, mm-hmm.
But because there's something like that to, uh, to help my mother, who, often needs health
points.
That's exactly what everyone is saying.
Everyone says, yeah, man, it was great because, um, my sister, my dad, my mother, my wife,
whatever, you know, she really needs, he, she, it really needs help.
And now, from anywhere you have a web browser, you can just connect to the thing.
It's, uh, and they should be paying me for that.
I should shut up.
And, uh, at least in the evening for me to get to our house and having something like that,
uh, it just works, it's beautiful when something works and it's free to go to home.
I was thinking about, that's a new to a power issue, mm-hmm.
And the seeds, the green seeds you're talking about, man.
They were talking about, uh, uh, was it something, uh,
who'd be your rod Adams called in.
We were talking about, uh, new power in the UK.
I'm not quite sure we talked about the green fees, so please do, do carry on.
Here in the state of New Hampshire in the US, uh, uh,
I honestly don't understand them all, but we're, I pay $100 a year and some sort of
nuclear decommissioning fees, uh, presumably something to do with the, uh,
because of power plants and seafood in New Hampshire, but for again, hey, man.
I, I, I'm paying my, uh, decommissioning something that's still operating,
and I'm still paying my bill on top of that.
That's pretty crazy.
Is that, uh, is that from the, uh, from the state government, and they're asking
you to pay these decommissioning fees, or is that on your energy bill, like, kind of like the
airlines will put on a special quote, tax for, uh, fuel surcharge, which is basically just
you paying directly for their cost of doing business, is that, uh, where's it coming from?
Who's billing you for that stuff?
Um, so sort of on that note of energy, I'm a guy that works for an oil company, and I'm
going to work in my hybrid car, uh, sort of interesting.
So I was thinking a good topic, um, sort of in the old vein of topics she had, like,
the Metro sexual home, it might be, uh, cars and car tech and, and gadgets.
I think that's a cool one of the discussions, um, I'd be interested to hear, for example,
how other people are listening to this, see if they're in their cars, and what sort of
tech is going on.
So might just be some good gadgets discussions, where I, I, I, I think that, uh, gadgets and
car talk would fit in line with your, your audience, make up, I think, anyway, maybe I'll just
Yeah, I appreciate the thought.
I, I don't know about that.
First of all, I don't really give a shit about cars anymore.
Um, I, I just don't, it's just the, I don't know.
It happened, uh, probably, you know what had happened when Patricia sold on my cars?
That's what, that's what, that's what had happened.
I have that on, uh, on, on video.
I actually actually put that up.
She sold every single one of them.
She said she was sick and tired of it.
And she was getting rid of all my cars.
It actually, she left the, uh, the outie at the time.
I should dig that up.
Okay, then, mode itself.
By the way, um, I, I wouldn't mind knowing who a little bit more about you guys, because,
you know, you're talking about the audience make up of the show.
I think we've pretty much ruled out the fact that any women listen.
So it's just us guys.
What are we, are we like middle aged, uh, middle class, guys?
Is that, is that what we are?
Is that who, I mean, it's okay because, um, we're the ones under the most pressure in the
United States.
Okay, granted, I'm upper middle class, but that's just, uh, because I've been around
longer than most of you fuckers, uh, had some time to build up a little, uh, a little nest egg.
But, uh, where the ones that are driving the economy, where the ones that get squeezed,
is, is that it?
Is that us?
So, you know, maybe now, uh, you let me know how old you are.
Um, or just say, uh, yeah, this is it.
So I'd say, uh, love you.
I mean, if I can remember it all.
Uh, love you, mean it, great hair.
Hope you win 43 middle class.
Something like that.
Now, maybe not.
podcasting.
I need to have no idea in, uh, actual bandwidth, how much I'm using, um, as a heavy, uh, podcast listener,
but it's got me thinking that I could in the future be seeing a very large bill.
You know, uh, and this is good.
Uh, I've been thinking about talking about this for a while and I appreciate you calling in
with that, Mr. No last name.
Um, so this is apparently a trial that time Warner, uh,
cable is doing in Beaumont, Texas.
And you can laugh about Beaumont, Texas, but I've been to Beaumont, Texas, okay?
I have been to a roadhouse in Beaumont, Texas, which is, you know,
that's all the story because I never get to talk about Beaumont.
At the time, I had, uh, Adam Curry's top 30 hit list.
It was a syndicated top, you know, basically a countdown show on the radio,
syndicated throughout the U.S.
And one of the stations, I forget the actual station, but it was in Beaumont, Texas.
And, um, you know, um, from time to time, I'd go visit the stations.
Usually around the time they had their summer jam or some other, you know,
thing where not just me, but a whole bunch of artists would come in.
Usually, you know, track artists.
So, uh, you got to think of, uh, Marky Mark and the funky bunch, you know,
so no, no, no musicians or typically no musicians, just, you know,
pure dat tape playing in the singing and dance and on stage.
And I would introduce them and, you know, participate in the summer jam,
everybody, Beaumont, Texas.
And so I arrived in Beaumont, which does have its own, uh,
it does have its own airport.
And I was picked up, uh, I'm trying to think the name of the club,
but the radio station, uh, pick me up in, uh, in a pink Cadillac convertible.
And I swear to God, with the big long horn on the front.
I mean, it was completely authentic.
And the gig was at this roadhouse.
And literally, if you've seen the movie roadhouse where there's chicken wire up on this,
on this, uh, and front of the stage and the stage is really elevated about shoulder height
off of the ground, that's the gig.
And it was necessary because, you know, it got pretty fraughty and crunchy on the, on the floor.
But I'll never forget because of this stage being so high up, uh,
there were these fans on the ceiling ceiling fans.
And, um, you know, if you were basically on the stage, you were, you know, pretty close to the
ceiling. I'm not, not like, uh, you know, I'd say probably about a meter,
yeah, about three feet, uh, from, uh, from the, from the ceiling fans.
And I remember it was, um, uh, EMF.
Remember those guys? You're unbelievable.
And they were unbelievable. They were just out of their mind, you know, that, that was such an explosive
track. And I think it was pretty much all they did, uh, at least that I can remember.
And at one point, you know, you may have heard this.
Oh, I should look this on, I'll be able to go to the, oh, down, down, to, down, to, and the guy gets
up on, um, a piano stool. And jumps into the air. Yeah, you guessed it.
His head went right into the fucking ceiling fan. It was, it was quite a trip.
Excuse me. Anyway, so Beaumont, Texas, they got a real airport. They got real, uh, uh,
people who enjoy popular music. They got internet. So that's where they're testing this thing out.
You know what? I think it's a great idea. Excuse me. That's the morning call.
I think the idea of meter band with this good. The question, of course, is what are we going to
charge for it? I think right now, if you were to actually measure what most people are using in
bandwidth and what they're being charged, you're being overcharged right now. Now, not, that's not to
say that there's, you know, that there's tons of people who use the same pricing. And of course,
they're downloading a lot more. Um, they may have, uh, some peer-to-peer programs running. I mean,
this is a lot more used of, uh, of bandwidth. And, and obviously, it's very, very difficult for, um,
for, uh, ISPs to manage all this traffic, particularly with video traffic. And, you know, I'm not,
you know, sucking up to the big man here. I think I'm just being very realistic because I do know a lot
about how, how traffic is routed and what it takes. And particularly what it costs, because it is just
not free. Now, here's what's interesting. By the way, I like the 4-pay model. And I would say,
you know, just make it, uh, you know, make it meet it all the way, you know, like, like your phone
system, uh, like, uh, like so many things. Um, what I like about the payment is kind of like, um,
like the supermarket, you know, where you get the, uh, you get the supermarket, the shopping cart,
but you have to stick a quarter or in the UK appound. You have to stick a pound into the,
into the little thing for it to unlock from the, uh, from the other, uh, carts from the other
shopping carts. Now, it's only a quarter or pound in, in, as the case may be. And it's not about
you stealing the cart. It's about you bringing the cart back. So it's cleaned up. That saves so much
money and aggravation and hassle for everybody. Because, you know, it's, you know, you just do, you want
your money back. You know, and it's like, uh, for the pound. Yeah, I'm not going to let some other
smuck it in my pound. I'm going to put the, the cart back in the, in the nice little row. I want
to get my pound out. So I, I'd like the, um, the psychological effect paying for something has
on, uh, on people. Now, I think that we're probably overpaying as it is because I know that on the
other end, when I'm sending ban without, when we're, because we pay for ban with to send you the podcast.
So it's a really valid question. Um, for each giga bite transferred, right? Um, we, uh, I can't,
I'm not allowed to tell you the exact price, but it's less than nine cents per gigabyte. Okay,
significantly. Um, and nine cents is pretty much the norm for anyone who's pushing a lot of
volume. You can get at least, uh, I'd say a lot of people are around 25 cents, but you know, we
push so much and the more we push the cheaper it gets, which is the way I believe it should be.
If I'm a huge user of ban with at home, I should be paying less for, you know, for the,
for the overage that I use. So it's the, it's all going to come down to the accounting. Um,
and obviously, you know, it's, they're not going to, I just can't believe that any company with
any brains is going to try and charge you $200 at the end of the month because you use 10 gigabytes
of information, uh, excuse me, uh, because it won't fly and then someone else will come in with cheaper
rates. But that is, that is kind of the industry standard cost of a gigabyte of, of data transfer.
Now, granted, if you go to Akamai or some other content delivery network today, and you say,
all right, how much you're going to charge me? They'll probably start off at $1.25 per gigabyte
transferred. So, you know, just by telling him fuck you, you'll get it down to 75 cents. But then
the rest has really got to come out of volume. Um, so I can actually see where almost like a
price line.com. You could pool your, your bandwidth usage together, buy and bulk, and then distribute
that cheaper to the people who are part of the system. I think that really will work because it
gives everyone a fair shake and everyone's basically paying for what they're using. But the four
pay model, the meter bandwidth will not work at today's prices, which actually are kind of expensive.
Does that make any sense? Uh, I'm hoping I'm starting off a debate here. Well, from the book, I drive
time podcast and the tone ranger. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Yeah,
hi. This is a message for a Jose Martinez. Mr. Martinez. This is Bonnie from Eagle Appraisal Service
for writer insurance company, or steer motor. All of us this are number 73. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. What the hell is that? Two, two, four, four, five, four, one. Thank you.
That's clearly a wrong number. Oh, man. Let's see. Who's this then?
Adam, I have Charles. Charles. He's over for January. London. I'm very good my friend. Not Charles,
the drunken Londoner, but sober for January only, but he is Charles, our friend from London.
I've been away quite some time. Yeah, and do I can show that is? Because I'm an easy. And also,
the lovely, it like what you gave me has just stopped working. However, I'd saved up and I went out and bought
myself an iPhone yesterday. Oh, I do with a max book as well since saving hard. Charles, I can't believe
you didn't go out and get a Nokia N8010 with my 15% discount. Well, you needed a file. That's right.
It didn't your car get broken into and your laptop and all kinds of, maybe it was. Yeah, I think it was
you. Did all your shit get stolen, man? Anyway, good to have you back on the scene, Charles. What
you got for me? And I'm loving them. So, I've just been listening to the latest show. Don't know
the note which it was on this iPhone. My first podcast on the iPhone. My second phone call on the
iPhone. In fact, excellent. Someone made a comment. I hope Patricia is recovering well.
So, we're having a bit of wait for a long time. I have no idea what that comment was about.
But I just thought I'd drop you a line and say, I also wish Patricia well. I hope that nothing
serious has happened. And, you know, good hair. Well, I hope you win. Yeah, that's sweet to your
Charles. Yeah, no, it was a appendicitis that Patricia had been walking around with for a year,
completely misdiagnosed. We caught it in time. And she went back to the doctor. She's in her recuperation phase.
She's almost back to normal. And the doctor said, you are lucky because it would not have been
much like. It could have happened at any moment, basically. She could have, it could have ruptured in.
Let me tell you, you got more than just a little blowhole of an entry wound there. If that happens,
then you're going to rip you all the way open. So, she's very lucky. We're very happy. And even
though, she's still healing. She is so, oh man, she's so happy about just having this pain gone.
This alien has been taken out of her, which is not, you know, she says that. It's funny because
reminds me because when my mom was very sick before she passed, she also had a really nasty tumor
and they had removed it once. And she also spoke of the alien. So, it was a very weird time for us.
In fact, I'm making sure she goes to visit her mom and her sister to chew out a little bit.
Because of course, you know my wife, right? She's walking around. She's still healing, you know?
And she just can't leave stuff alone. She has to have someone else take care of her. And of course,
so, you know, I can only, I guess I can only do so much. Okay, I've just noticed something here
on the Ableton Live. By the way, I will post this screenshot. I'm using it in combination with
something called SoundBite, which is another Mac program, which basically lets you
put a whole bunch of sound files into racks. So, you can kind of fire them off. Very analogous to
what Casplaster does for the PC. But I'm noticing on Ableton, I can't actually see how long I've
been recording for this. The time, I'm sure there's a way to, there must be a way to
to get the time scale here. Is it 194 something that I've been 194, I can't be minutes,
crap, I gotta figure this thing out. I do like this, this live thing because
you look at it for the first time and you look at the interface and you go,
man, that looks dumb. It looks like something out of Tron. You know, it looks like real
70s colors. It's not that typical, what do you call it? You know, the typical beautiful
rendering of a 24 track mixing board and all the knobs are really rendered beautifully,
quite the opposite. And I understand why now, because in programs like like a
logic studio, logic studio pro or whatever it is, which has all those beautiful interfaces,
there's latency that you can't get rid of and this thing, you could actually control the latency.
If I wanted to, I could actually delay myself or delay any tracking, there's all kinds of stuff in
here. I think Richard Blusty also uses this program and there's all kinds of routing, so tomorrow
on Friday, I'll be able to test the routing from the microphone and from the audio tracks
back in the Skype without feeding Skype back into it. For those of you who have tried that out,
you'll know what I'm talking about. When we do another no agenda show. Okay, let me see,
it's, I can kind of see the time. It's been about 22 minutes. So let's,
um, oh, when we do something sexy for Thursday, early Thursday morning.
Let's bring in Chuck, of course, who was hooked me up with my Grokha Kirstie Hawkshaw, Chuck.
I told my dad Adam's DSU 712. That was over the time. Yeah, you like that? That was excellent. Thank you.
Then that was just out of control anytime. Anytime. So hey, uh, I launched you a little link
for a vid to check. Um, you remember, uh, DRAMs, the show for back in the day, uh,
Kirstie did this awesome remake with, uh, guide of Salt Lake City by the name of Sleep Thief,
and they did a video as well. I didn't see it, man. You guys? I said I'm near in the email from
you need to resend the to me. And I didn't see that. I'd love to see that. I'll have to look again.
Of course, my email is hoes because it's just so much coming in. Please resend. Well, actually,
get a check. Hey, and I just had an inspired thought, um, you know, I was a avid listener of
uh, Natalie Doganti and uh, texture. Yeah. I mean, I loved it. Yes, she was, she was just a sweet
her to live room, you're on the show. And, um, you know, I don't know what your plans are for, um,
for fill in her shoes or, or if you're looking to fill her shoes, but, uh, holy cow, you know,
I know where this is going. I'd show you K. She's a tech girl. She's a geeky girl. She's all
about music. You know, how Natalie was there at the plus TV award, mhm, mhm, mingling with all
the music types. I mean, Jesus, thirsty, you know, those are all those folks. You know,
I'm liking where this is going, Chuck. I'm like, you know, I, I, I, I, I'm always very careful
because she's very dedicated to her music and I don't want to get it on a different career path,
because she's really, really concentrated. Uh, but I am like, are you setting me up, man?
Are you hooked on me up with a personal meeting? I, um, if only I could find a female
British singer for this show I have in mind. And what she's a geeky girl, man? Yeah, there's
a girl. I don't, um, we have someone lined up for texture. Obviously, I think the cat is pretty
much out of the bag. It's, uh, Becky. I don't even want to say any more than that. Um, Becky's
awesome. The only problem with Becky is her timing. Uh, at the very moment, we actually wanted to
bring her in. Uh, she was about to drop, uh, twins, which I believe has happened. So I'll get
an update on that, uh, Becky Warley. Yeah, that's who we have slated, but um, I'm digging your idea
here, Chuck. And she's cool. Yeah, it's cool. So anyway, that's my inspired top for the day,
and a career you rock, uh, who comes once again, man. I love you. Me,
need it. Great, right here. I hope you win. Middle-aged middle class 43. There you go. Hey, the, um,
A, A, I, B, the Air Accident Investigation Branch in the UK has, uh, released an update on British
Airways, uh, flight 38. This is, uh, in addition to their January 17th update, it came in yesterday.
Um, and this is, it's quite interesting. Uh, so let me just get through the Blom Blom Blom Blom
Blom stuff. As previously reported, while the aircraft was stabilized on an iOS approach, which
means it was coming in on instruments, it was on the instrument landing system with autopilot
engaged. The autoprust system commanded an increase in thrust from both engines. The engines
both initially responded after about three seconds. The thrust of the right engine reduced some
eight seconds later, the thrust reduced on the left engine to a similar level. This is interesting,
because, um, although I've never flown a triple seven, I'm pretty sure that if, um, if both
engines, uh, they throttled up, but then the right engine reduced after about three seconds, that plane
is going to veer off course. So that could have set a whole bunch of things into motion, which, um,
uh, you know, certainly the pilot would have probably disengaged the autopilot at that point
and taken over manual control, because it'd be, uh, ready to miss the runway, not not coming
up short, but left or right, just missing it, which could have also affected his, um, his glide path
on the speed and, and could have, um, you know, um, negatively impacted the glide that he was trying
to put into, make a, a smoother landing than what to, took place. So some eight seconds later,
the thrust reduced on the left engine to a similar level. The engines did not shut down,
and both engines continued to produce thrust at an engine speed above flight idle, but less than
the commanded thrust. Very interesting, uh, which means, you know, uh, obviously you're still
going to kind of come up short, but with this, uh, um, with the difference between the engines,
that could have really screwed up the glide path. So all possible scenarios that could explain
the thrust reduction and continued lack of response to the engines to throttle lever, inputs are
being examined in close cooperation with Boeing, Rolls Royce, British Airways. Interesting. I love the
fact that these guys are setting out, uh, all of these updates. That's, uh, that's something the, uh,
the NTSP, I don't think they do that do it that way. And, uh, and it's important because we need to
all of these aircraft are safe or not. All right. Um, let's do, um, no, um, you know, tomorrow,
which I may tape tonight, we got to get deep into some stuff like the Fed. We've got all kinds
of banking stuff going crazy. Uh, we had this rogue trader, uh, who, um, at the, um, what's the,
the French bank? Hmm, I can't remember the name of the, uh, I probably have it written down here.
A whole lot of my notes. It's another thing I got to set up. I'll tell you about the second
hold on. Let me just see what the rest of the new stories are. No, I didn't even put it in there.
Anyway, something like, uh, almost five billion pounds that they're writing off. It's like seven,
seven or eight billion dollars. A rogue trader. Yeah. I'd say, um, you know what I'm missing?
And this is the thing that I am going to see if I can score that while I'm out here.
Is I want to control surface? And what that is, because now of course, I don't have a mixing board
and even, uh, with my previous setup, I have a mixer so I can control the levels and
and twist them with my left hand while I'm doing all of the selecting of what I'm playing with my
right hand on the computer. Uh, but of course, now I only have one control input for both function.
So I need a control surface, which has some sliders and a control surface, basically all it does is it
just sends MIDI commands to the program so that I can then map these, uh, these volume, uh,
faders, these sliders, as you might recognize them, uh, to the individual channel. So, uh,
I'd be able to train, you know, to fade my mic up and down. I'll be able to mix this on the
sounds a little bit better. Uh, it's just a lot of stuff I got to work on. All right. I do have
one more song, which came to us from a mashuptown.com, which is so beautiful for a Thursday morning
where the sun is just coming up in San Francisco. It's just raising up over the bed. I think you'll
like this one. It'll get you into that mood by the bay, everybody.
Where do we go?
Go no no. Oh each day gets better. I just came, everybody.
It's kiss, kiss, we are, I just can't leave her now.
Thening goes with love that you wrote Yes, there is love in you
We'll never lose what is true, if it's so wrong, who's shining away
Looking and everything remain still in the sea
Will we go on even more?
Oh, you know, when each day is better, I just can't leave her alone.
Oh, no, each kiss gets sweeter.
I just can't leave her alone.
Oh, I don't want to live without her.
Oh, man, how pretty is that, huh?
Fwager who loving you better.
Those in the know will recognize mini-ripperton and John Legend.
Brought to you by mashuptown.com.
Oh, what a great track that is.
Love you.
And that is love it.
Hey, it's almost seven o'clock now.
And that means it's time for our sales call.
So I'm going to get on the phone with the sales Present.
Let me know what you thought of the sound if it works for you.
Obviously, I still got some bugs to work out, some kinks and stuff.
But I think overall I'm pretty pleased and all the still lot more experimentation to go through.
Whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop-whop,
told you about the N800's.
Of course, go Daddy, if you want an awesome deal on a domain name, in fact, you can't get
better anywhere else.
There's a couple of code you can use all the DSC, DSC12 or three.
The standard one, DSC3 is if you just want to get a domain name, real quick down, down
and dirty cheap for 695, DSC3 is your checkout code.
Atomoodpodshow.com, dailystorescode.com, I will get the show notes together, of course,
that's another part of the process, that is not as streamlined as with cast blaster.
So I got to figure out how that works and what the heck?
Love you, mean it.
Great hair, hope you win, live life with passion
and enjoy your freedom.
I'll talk to you tomorrow for the Fubar Friday.
Bye, everybody.
Another Pajo podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
I'll talk to you tomorrow for the Fubar Friday.