If you're not listening to Adam Curry's daily source code, then you're missing out on
a world of information.
But then again, if you're listening to this, you're listening to the DSC 735, congratulations
on being in the NU.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
Then the next generation radio contenting my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic. It's Adam Curry.
True story out.
Yeah.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
$16 million worth of aircraft strapped by us.
$16 million worth of airplanes strapped by us.
$15 million worth of drone strapped by us.
$15 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
$50 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
$14 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
$20 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
$15 million worth of airplane strapped by our airplane strapped by us.
$15 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
Wars back in beautiful Reverarta County,
$16 million worth of airplane strapped by us.
around y'all a seam go because he's headed to the coastline.
He's got born and arrived, painted on his tank,
brought a little bit of a lads, you can't think when he passed you by,
he'd give you one, because he's headed for the sunshine.
And you can bet on there,
don't get no better than that,
running three and living in the USA.
I can guarantee you that it's so fast,
sometimes you've got to get up and just get away.
You can bet on there,
don't get no better than that,
you're in the frame of mind,
let's have a good time,
can't you feel yourself out and leave your kids behind,
moving this at your back,
yeah girl, you're right on track,
you can bet on there,
don't get no better than that.
And you can bet on there,
don't get no better than that,
running three and living in the USA.
I can guarantee you that it's so fast,
sometimes you've got to get up and just get away.
You can bet on there,
don't get no better than that,
you can bet on there,
I've set it before I'll say it again,
you just don't hear enough country and western
shit-kick-room music on the radio anymore, now do you?
Happy to provide it to you here on the Charlie,
James Taylor Curtis, don't get no better than that,
from the pot-same music network you can find
and that pot to their cons slash music
and of course direct link in the show notes
at resourcecode.com.
It's Wednesday, everybody, the 19th of March, 2008,
and coming to you once again from the Curry Manor,
it's a great day outside, it's an early show for me,
it's a pre-nune recording,
which is a pretty spectacular,
actually, it doesn't happen very often these days.
Although, I must say, I was a week at five o'clock this morning,
a poor lady Patricia was coughing,
you know, a real coughing fit.
He was quiet through most of the night,
we went to bed really early,
which is partly why I got up at five once I was awake.
I think we were in bed at like 10, 30,
she was a wrecked man, so you got penicillin now,
because you can't get pneumonia, it's not not good.
So she'll be okay, but it did get me a pretty early,
so I plenty of time to prep the show before recording,
and I got a pretty busy afternoon.
I just a little knackered, a little bit tired from the weird hours,
but it doesn't matter because I got a full blown show
for you, a couple of more cool tunes coming up for you,
a couple articles I want to discuss,
and also some of my friends checking in.
I've not heard from Dr. O in a long time.
Good old Dr. O, beautiful, beautiful, young,
Londoner, calling in just to check in and tell us
how she's doing, happy to listen to it.
Hey, Adam, it's Dr. O's here, just calling in.
What did you say?
My cold tooth and morning on my way to work.
Just so I got checked in and say hello.
I've been alive, I've been here.
I've been listening, I've been reading this.
I should get a phone.
In how you and that out a lot on season next.com,
then if you're going to go yet, it's very fun.
Now, I hear a lot of people about season make,
and I think I've checked it out once or twice,
but unlike other flash video sites for some reason,
must be the routing or something weird.
It takes a long time to buffer and sometimes it stutters,
and I kind of ruins the experience.
And I don't know, I just haven't gotten quite into it.
I'm a little bit into Twitter.
I use it as kind of a notification system,
and that does seem to work fairly well.
But season making, I don't know,
you know what, I really don't want you to see me this way.
I need some kind of facade.
I want you, that's why you see that album art of me,
looking like the pod father.
I don't actually want you to see what I look like
without hair and makeup done.
I do, I do, I do.
It's exciting for Twitter.
That's a really cool people on that.
And they've introduced me to some new podcasts,
such as Mr. Mark.
So, the Iraqi cast, the voice, actually well.
You know, I know that Dr. has a really sexy voice,
but it just doesn't come across.
When she's walking down the street,
you know, there's too much ambient noise,
and I can't get into it.
And Dr. Dimensiony.com,
so I've been listening to new podcasts,
which also returns from South by South Wales.
So I think I was sitting next to the missing sound,
and my very first session,
that was then watching Mr. London do.
Yeah, it's good.
Austin was interesting,
and we learned anything new,
which is a little bit disappointing.
So this is to make some people including.
Yeah, I don't know.
If I'd known that you were going to be there,
Dr. I would have definitely gone to Austin
for South by Southwest.
But I didn't know it. I did I.
You got to call earlier, girl.
This is the future of the house.
Anyway, she's checking in.
She now single, those five next month,
they're in London,
hating it.
Oh.
No comments.
A ready,
paying for two.
That's another game.
Single, female.
35 next week,
living in London, hating it, no cats.
Girl, I'm taking you out on a date.
We got it. We got to fix your attitude.
I'll give you a call.
Hey, Parkey sent me an article from the Guardian today.
Now, you know, I don't read the Guardian for a number of reasons.
Yeah, I basically, I check out everything online,
and then I will read the Financial Times,
which also had some great articles today.
But there's this gentleman from the Scotland Yard.
He is his name is Gary Pue, I think, P U G H.
They're Pue.
And he's the new DNA spokesman for the Association of Chief Police Officers.
And he's saying that a debate is now needed on how far Britain should go
in identifying potential offenders,
given that some experts believe it is possible
to identify future offending traits in children
as young as five years old.
I love this.
Okay, continues.
If we have a primary means of identifying people
before they offend, then in the long term,
the benefits of targeting younger people are extremely
Yard, large said Pue.
You could argue the younger the better.
Criminologists say some people will grow out of crime, others won't.
We have to find who are possibly going to be the biggest threat to society.
And kill them.
He doesn't say that, but you might as well think it.
Kill them, incarcerate them.
You have bad DNA, you five-year-old child.
Geez, Louise, what is going on with this, huh?
That's like, that's like out of control.
A recent report from the Think Tank Institute
for Public Policy Research,
but I don't know as the IPPR,
called for children to be targeted between the ages of five and 12
with cognitive behavioral therapy, parenting programs,
and intensive support.
Prevention starts, young, it's said,
because prolific offenders typically
began offending between the ages of 10 and 13.
Do you realize that this is 1984?
This is, you know, this is thought crimes.
This is, so really, so now we can tell through DNA
that you're a bad person.
Well, I'm not giving any swab near my cheek bone.
I'll tell you that.
They'll block me up.
Does it hopefully you guys see how wrong this is?
This is, now this is just a discussion in the calling for debate,
and I'm sure that this will go nowhere,
but just the fact that it's out there and actually being suggested
to me is just totally outrageous.
Hey Adam, Jack, the podcast,
they're formally known as Jack.
It's interesting to talk about this three strikes in your outlock,
because I actually did it.
Yeah, this is, this is more about the UK.
This is the, the ISPs, the government said,
you know, we think that you guys should be tracking what's going on
with people's internet traffic,
and which is set up a three strikes your out system.
So if you're downloading a legal content of any form,
then you'll get a warning, then you get, uh,
your, um, your service will be canceled and finally terminated.
And I guess they come down and take a DNA sample of you and kill you.
Kill you for your DNA.
So this is not new.
It's happening in the States as well.
That's what the podcast,
or formally known as Jack is calling,
it's about calling about.
It's show about that last year,
show no longer available, sorry.
But, um, yeah, when I was living in Virginia,
my friend, uh, who's on Comcast was downloading some sopranos episodes.
And, uh, the interesting part of this, which your other color mentioned,
is that he left the torrent running all night,
and my friend also left his torrent running all night.
And in the morning, his internet service was cut off by Comcast,
and they told him, you get three strikes.
So that was strike one for downloading, uh,
protected or copyrighted content.
And, uh, if he did it again, I had been doing it some myself,
but I noticed, you know, when I downloaded one, I'd wait until I got my torrent
complete, until it shared back one time,
which is good for the health of the torrent network.
And then I would shut it down, leaving it open all night,
leaves you open to detection because you're basically serving the thing back up,
to others at that point.
And I think that's what triggers, uh, uh, the ISPs to notice what's going on.
So anyway, uh, I love your great hair,
I hope you're going to bother me, uh, see you.
Hey man, I love those pipes.
You should call it more often.
I'll, uh, I'll crown you a savant.
Yeah, so I, so there's a lot happening with this.
There's a lot happening at the ISP level.
And remember that, you know, the ISPs, uh,
traditionally are just meant to pass on traffic and not do anything else.
And I believe that this is prop, this, um,
the ISP has to be involved somehow some way, uh,
because apparently there's now companies out there,
judices who, um, yeah, it's pretty easy to find out where you're downloading a torrent
from if someone else is uploading it.
You know, that's pretty trackable.
There are ways to block that as well, but it is trackable.
So they must be going to the ISPs and saying,
hey, um, I'm from the ESA or whatever alliance.
And we've noticed that illegal content is being downloaded through this IP address.
You got to turn it off.
That's actually pretty simple to do.
I have, um, uh, I've emailed, uh,
ISPs about, uh, abuse, usually there's an, uh,
there's an email alias abuse at fill in the name of your ISP.
Whatever, uh, people spamming me, uh, although that doesn't really make too much
difference these days because of Gmail.
You just kind of set it in a rule and send it all to the bit bucket.
Doesn't really tie anything up.
Just can be annoying, uh, but that's pretty easy because ISPs will always air on, uh,
on the side of safety for themselves and, uh,
shut it off and ask questions later.
Um, there's something else that's going on with the company called, uh,
form phormform.com.
And actually, I'm not going to talk about it on the daily source code.
I want to talk to the, the agency to work about that.
So we'll do that on Friday, but there's clearly a lot of stuff going on.
People are monitoring everything and I think that what people, you know,
companies, governments.
And I think we're just now kind of starting to figure it out and notice it.
Although not all believe in in the conspiracy, I certainly do.
Let's just come back to those millions of cameras here in the United Kingdom who
weren't that are watching you, watching your every moment, every move, um,
the oyster card, which is, um, the public transport system.
It's a credit card.
Of course, you're being tracked where you go, every tube station, every train station.
And still, people don't want to believe it.
Adam, it's a game. There's something more well.
And I'll know what we should be quote.
So I'm thanking the priest.
And then this is like they make a picture thing, you're not hearing anything off anybody
and written about flashmops or very few people.
But it's because nobody's interested.
All right.
So this, of course, is my call once again that I think we need to stand up and protest.
Oh, wait a minute, you're not allowed to protest without a license in the UK.
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
Uh, no, no one's interested.
Apparently, and James says, says it, so it must be true.
Because people don't realize they're not being watched.
Like this plan from 50,000 feet to the folks at watching from 50,000 feet.
It's huge.
Dude, have you ever looked at Google Earth?
That's from a satellite.
That's much higher than 50,000 feet.
I can zoom all the way down into my backyard.
How about you?
Of course, they're watching you, not James.
Just a big experiment.
As far as I'm concerned, I'm thinking about our license, big experiments, change this interest
great, see what happens.
I give out this type of rubbish, see what happens.
Somebody higher up, not a government, but somebody higher up is just playing games and singing
how things change when we do, if you want, and search the different people, it's simple as that.
You're not being watching it, you know, pretty much.
Yeah, I am being watched, and I do agree with you there, James.
Yes, of course it's being done by people higher up.
It's called the banks, the richest people in the world.
I mean, look at the Federal Reserve.
Again, a commercial organization, a secretive commercial organization,
because they do not publish numbers.
They do not publish their members list, which of course is all banks.
And over the weekend, when the markets were closed, they just decided to print up some greenbacks.
What they didn't consult me is just devalued the dollar and handed over 30 billion to bear
Oh, it's horrible, dude.
And it's not just here, it's everywhere.
Yes, you're absolutely right.
By the way, the big distraction is of course the Clinton Obama battle that's going on right now.
You know, keep talking about that.
Well, all this other shit happens in the background.
I mean, it's a perfect, perfect opportunity for the people that truly run the world,
which is the banks.
And in this case, the richest families in the world who owned the banks,
were founded the banks, you know, their shareholders, their majority shareholders,
and the Federal Reserve and other central banks.
But the Federal Reserve is without a doubt doing nasty stuff.
Right now, in fact, I'm not a financial expert, but this was actually sent to me.
Let me see, I have a comment on this that was pretty good.
John Kits, he sends me a lot of stuff.
He said that given the U.S. inflation is hitting 4%,
and the Fed is now, of course, cut its rate again,
which is nearing 2%, the interest rates.
In fact, they're giving the money away.
They're giving the money away, okay?
It's free money.
Free money for the banks. By the way, I checked in my mail.
I didn't see any free money offered to me.
Now, of course, not. It's only the richest people in the world.
In a contrary to popular belief, I'm not a part of that club.
Come on, anybody, what you got for us today?
I did Mr. prolific program. I have from San Francisco.
I had some thoughts regarding your willingness to do a flash mob in the UK.
And to get the word out, there's a gentleman that has summoned them,
and realized that he's probably not the most popular MP,
but he seems to be very much into this kind of protests and the rest of it.
Give me reached out to comments or at GeorgeGalloway.com.
We might want to reach him.
Contact me with more information.
Is that plug-done prolific program?com?
This PRO, L-I-F-I-C-P-R-O-G-R-A-M-M-E-R.com.
Slime the ratios.
Prolific program, thank you very much, my friend.
Yeah. I'd love to start a flash mob, or at least be involved in it,
but the British people have got to stand up.
I'm not going to do all this by myself.
I know, I've seen Galloway. He was on big brother,
and although I like him, I've never met him, but he seems like a pretty cool guy.
He has no credibility. Everyone here thinks he's a cook.
But of course, everyone thought Ron Paul was a cook, and you'll see.
You'll see. The first thing Ron Paul said was get rid of the federal reserve,
and right now they're bankrupting our country.
The United States that is.
And the same thing's happening over here. It's going to happen everywhere.
So, yeah, I'd love to, man. I'd love to get the flash mob going,
but I don't think we need politicians in this game.
We need to show the power of the people.
In fact, going back to that DNA story here's a thought.
Sure, you can take DNA from my daughter, okay?
And to see if she's going to be a criminal,
but we start with all members of Parliament first,
because if you have the wrong DNA,
we'll have to kill you!
The B&B is Pongosterior on a solar-systemation,
featuring the best of all genres of the electronic music.
This is BZUKJO, and this week on solar-systemation,
which, by Legendary Nietzsche,
a tune recording artist, Aman Tobin,
or a retrospective mix of his career so far.
I think the way it affected me personally,
is in that means my thing is that I never had to drive it forward.
You know, it's unfamiliar territory,
and I think that's really good things in general.
It's a good place to be, I think, out of your depth.
If you're trying to discover things.
Listen to the best of all genres of electronic music,
each week on solar-systemation.
If so, we'll all be in a fire stairs,
and see you next time, don't cough.
It's a guy in town, thinks that I'm a little crazy.
Uh-huh, he's a sweet talking guy.
He's gonna talk his way into my life.
No matter who you are,
no don't hesitate,
because I got to know before I rest with him.
If we're gonna decide, we're gonna play.
If we're gonna pull us,
smile on your face,
whenever you call me,
I'll be around you,
if you're feeling better.
If you wanna be my friend,
you can get a little closer.
If you wanna get high,
better, rather, rather close up.
Oh, how long don't feel satisfied,
shine, don't hesitate,
because I need to know before I sleep.
If you're gonna decide,
we're gonna play.
If we're gonna pull us,
smile on your face,
whenever you call me,
I'll be around you,
if you're feeling better.
Oh, how long don't feel satisfied,
now it's forever.
I'll be around you,
Oh, how long don't feel satisfied,
now it's forever.
If you're gonna decide,
we're gonna play.
If we're gonna pull us,
smile on your face,
whenever you call me,
I'll be around you,
if you're feeling better.
If you wanna be my friend,
smile on your face,
if we're gonna pull us,
whenever you call me,
I'll be around you,
you know,
has really nothing wrong with a good
pop tune on the Charlie once in a while,
I hate it.
Creamy.dk,
we got the time,
they're from the pod save music network,
I kind of liked it,
you know, it was one of those real FM
top 40 poppy hits,
I like it.
No talent required,
they may be very talented,
I don't know,
but a lot of voice pressing,
processing, going up.
Oh, whatever,
link to that song on the on the pod save music network,
in the show notes,
of course,
the dailysourcecode.com.
For God's tell you over the weekend,
I had a chat with a reporter from Billboard
magazine at Amazon TV,
and I knew that she was out doing the rounds,
because I got a couple notes,
see from Jersey Todd,
and a couple other folks,
as she asked them,
you know, she was asking for interviews
and questions about pod save music.
And so I spoke to her finally over the weekend,
and nice, you know,
she lives in New York,
works for Billboard,
I think she's younger than I am,
I'm not quite sure,
you know,
sounds like she's in her late 20s.
And I said,
you know, I've been waiting three years
for this interview to happen,
I really have a really,
what does all that smoke outside?
Wow, hold on.
Is that coming from us?
Something's burning in the backyard.
Oh well.
I said, I've been waiting three years
for this interview, Evie,
to talk to you about how important
the concept of pod save music is.
And there's other places where you can
get music to play with permission,
without having to pay for it,
purely for the promotional aspect of the artist.
And I'm really hoping that
that she recorded the interview,
which is good,
because then you,
wow, it's starting to stink up the attic here.
I should close the window.
That one's really,
something really bad is burning.
I got, I got a,
I got a three alarm fire out there.
Anyways, I'll keep you up to speed on that.
I think she was showing it to her,
to her editor today or tomorrow.
So hopefully that'll come up pretty quick.
It'll be interesting to see.
And I really did say a couple of things there
that if she prints it,
should get some attention from some people
in the industry.
I'm just going back just thinking about that.
That DNA stuff,
that's really bothering me,
particularly because it's coming from a think tank.
Think tanks also, by the way,
rule out the world,
think tanks come up with the strategy
and pass those on to politicians,
but it's bothersome.
You know, let's take some DNA,
see if your kid is fucked up.
Well, you know what,
why should you just do an amniocentesis,
you know?
And if the child has the bad DNA,
just rip it right out of the woman,
kill it!
Ah, remember people,
the government works for you and for me,
this is wrong.
Comic strip,
of course I didn't mean the comic strip
blogger is wrong.
I just meant that whole DNA thing is wrong.
Here's our friend, our EU correspondent
with the latest report.
Welcome, Adam, my pal, Kerry.
Do you know why GSM has become the most popular
standard of mobile telephony on this planet?
Please tell me.
It was because EU countries made it a compulsory standard in EU.
So do you know what is DVBH?
It is digital video broadcasting handheld.
And EU has just decided that it will be
standard for mobile television in all EU countries.
So next time you buy your mobile phone,
please feel free to demand DVBH as one of its features.
Okay, yeah, DVBH digital video broadcast handheld.
Ah, it's interesting.
Well, if the European Union sets it as a standard,
it has a good shot of becoming the standard you're right.
I'm pretty sure that's exactly what happened with the GSM protocol.
And still the state's not, I think sprint still is on a different type of system.
I like the GSM standard quite a bit actually.
You know, it's funny because last night,
I came back from the, from the office.
Now what I do is I take the train in on the mornings,
but in the evening it's such a hassle to get from the east side
where in shortage, where our office is to the west side,
where Waterloo Station is that I just take a car all the way home.
I mean, that last bit, once you, once you're, oh man,
I never should have recorded that shit with Patricia.
Now my system is messed up.
Anyway, once you're past the west side,
you know, then it's pretty much like 20 minutes and I'm home, right?
But it's all that piece in the middle.
So I'll take a car service all the way.
And, you know, it's, you know, just have a regular car service.
But I got lucky and it turns out I got lucky because the guy
who drove me a driven me before when I had got lucky previously.
The lucky part is instead of a quote regular sedan,
he shows up with a Mercedes S series.
I don't know, 500, 600, 8,000, whatever it is.
And S series, beautiful.
I mean, you can adjust the back seat.
It's got heating.
For the same price, by the way, is as the regular quote regular sedan.
And the reason why is because when these guys come on,
foreign, or between four and seven and like four in the afternoon,
they can actually look at the list of jobs that are coming up.
And so they know that Gilford is a nice trip.
And so they'll kind of be handy if they can.
They'll hang around in my general area.
Then the computer says, oh, wait a minute.
Because of course, those guys are tracked.
Hey, they should take their DNA and kill them.
And so then they automatically get the job.
So this guy, you know, he was hanging around
and I got in the car like, oh, nice.
Because they have, in addition to all these wonderful seating features,
they have television built into the headrest of the front seats.
So you can sit in the back and you can watch TV.
Now, I've been taking limos and different forms of upper-scale
transportation since I was, I don't know, 19.
And particularly in the States, in and in New York,
you know, lots of limos, and they always have a TV in there.
You know, and it's pretty useless.
It's always been completely, you know,
they've got the boomerang antenna on the back,
which although looks very cool, it's just useless,
particularly in the city because, you know,
you only get VHS for UHF stations.
It fades in and out.
So usually it used to be used for VHS cassettes or DVDs.
But, you know, I don't want to watch a DVD.
And, you know, I'm bored.
Show me something, you know, like news or whatever.
And that's interesting.
It's the same as jet blue.
You know, it's not really comfortable.
It's not a lot of service, but you got your direct TVs.
So you're not bored, and you got something to do,
and it passes the time.
It really works.
Live TV broadcast, fantastic.
Now, what they have in the UK is something called free view.
This is a brilliant system.
This is really, really smart.
So I don't know how long ago this started many years ago, apparently.
The analog system, the analog broadcast towers,
also transmit a digital signal that can be received
with a non-subscription-based cheap jack set top box.
So you can buy them for like 50 bucks these days.
You know, a lot of TVs come with it built in.
It's all built into the box.
And it gives you digital television.
And I think you get like 25 channels.
All the important ones you want to have,
and then you can subscribe to other ones.
So even though it's a non-subscription-based
is for your basic package, you just buy it.
No one knows who you are.
If you want to get more, I think they'll have some softcore porn
and stuff so you can order that.
And it's been, it's a revolution.
It's the biggest system in the UK.
I think there's, I'm going out on a limb here.
But I believe that there's 15 million of these boxes
that are being used.
Maybe even more than that.
So you sit in the car and for the first time ever,
because it's digital, there's no static.
Yeah, cut out, maybe four times.
It just kind of faded it in and out real quick or cut out.
But it automatically mutes, so you don't get horrible sound.
But everywhere else, we were driving a work
and it was a great experience.
So I'm thinking, I wonder, is that the same stands?
Well, I guess, so that is DVB digital video broadcast.
I wonder if the handheld is the same protocol
if we can get free view on our handsets.
I believe in that.
For faux show, I believe in that.
That could be pretty awesome.
Thank you very much.
Come extra blogger.
One of the many savants on a daily source code.
Here's an interesting question that popped up that I will get an answer to.
Hey Adam, I have a 2020 question for you.
When you're living in the cottage,
Patricia was always complaining about the headaches
or pains, body aches, because you guys thought it was related
to the cell towers.
And you guys moved, got a new place.
And you mentioned that we didn't hear anything else from that.
Was it if they continued or what was going on?
Now that you found out about the appendix,
is do you think all of that was related to the appendix
or to the cell sites?
Yeah, good question.
And I will ask the lady piece.
You'll come on the show.
Maybe for Friday, I'll certainly get her in,
I hope to get her in next week.
She may be going away next week.
I don't know, she's really busy with that got talent show.
But I just, you know, went back into the history myself.
No, I mean, the whole thing with the appendix
that started a year ago in January.
And we had already moved or just on the cusp of moving out
of the cottage to the manner.
But I have to say, I have not heard any more complaints
from her about that.
So I think the appendix thing happened when she was doing dancing
with the stars, so that was a year ago.
But this all predates that a year and a half to two years
before that she was complaining about what she thought was the cell tower.
And I have to say, I haven't heard a word about it.
So I will ask her, but I have the feeling
that it's that her issues are gone in that respect.
And I don't think it has anything to do with the appendix.
Because she didn't have it at all.
As far as I know, for the year that we've been living here,
I will find out though for sure.
And I really want to get her on.
But this got talent show.
She's making a ton of money with this by the way.
Like, out the added another date for this for that.
And you know my wife, she didn't do anything if it didn't for money.
I love her that way.
So I think she's going to be buying our daughter a new car once she turns 18.
Or actually, when she turns 18, she's taking her driving test
and I think two or three months.
Worst fear for a parent ever, eh?
So Adam, Jason from San Diego.
What if I wanted a full-time job in a team mainstream TV?
What would I need to do?
What is it that I'd have to give up?
Just curious.
Okay, you're referring to the pilot that I was offered,
which I will do, by the way, the game show.
What do you have to do?
Well, in order to be in mainstream media, of course,
you have to give up all your morals.
You have to give up your soul.
Um, you know, my first born is already safe.
So I guess if I had another kid, I'd probably have to give that up as well.
But I think really the morals, you know, you can give all that up in all control.
It's a fun show, though.
I think it'll be cool.
We'll see what happens with it.
Okay, let me see how long we do in this now.
It's how, yeah, I didn't make just have a short show for you guys today.
I don't want to overdo it.
Yeah, 34 minutes.
You know, let's play one more song and I'll get out of your way.
This is a song that I found over at mashuptown.com.
And I thought it was just such a great song for kind of a,
well, it would have been better for a Sunday morning or Sunday afternoon.
But when they'll work as well,
Fuego, he's matched up beautiful, easy girls.
I know you're gonna love it right here on the Wednesday, Charlie.
You're happy, so excited.
It's always side of what you say.
Over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
They only want to do you dirt.
They'll have you, so excited.
So excited when they say it's over.
See, it's hurting that no part used to chill after dark.
Oh, and it took my heart.
That's when we fell apart, because we both thought that love,
last forever, last forever.
They say we're too young to get ourselves strong.
Oh, we didn't care.
We made it very clearly our souls said that we couldn't last together.
Let's together, let's together.
Shaky, shaky, shaky.
Go away to beautiful girls.
That's why you don't have a word.
You're happy, so excited.
So excited when you say it's over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
They only want to do you dirt.
They'll have you, so excited.
So excited when they say it's over.
It was back in 99, watching movies all the time.
Oh, and now we're in the way for doing my first cry.
And I never thought that we was gonna see each other, each other.
And then I came out, my people fell down so full.
I went my girl, who I thought was my word.
It came out to me that she wasn't the girl for me.
It came out for me, it came out for me.
You're away to beautiful girls.
That's why you don't have a word.
You're happy, so excited.
So excited when you say it's over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
They only want to do you dirt.
They'll have you, so excited when you say it's over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
That's why you don't have a word.
You're happy, so excited when you say it's over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
They only want to do you dirt.
They'll have you, so excited when you say it's over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
That's why you don't have a word.
You're happy, so excited, so excited when you say it's over, down my own knees, beautiful girls.
What a perfect match, Sean Kingston, beautiful girl, and Carmino's, of course,
easy like a Sunday morning, matched up.
They just sound fantastic together.
Love that.
All right, body, let me see, I think we'll do another show tomorrow, Friday.
It'll be a four-day Charlie week, close, close, close, close.
All right, everybody, thank you so much for listening.
Adam at podshow.com, dailysourceco.com as we can find the latest episodes.
The show, of course, so show notes, more or less details you can find.
I'll put in those links to the DNA stuff.
You gotta read that because before you know it, they're going to come for your children.
So please, whatever you do, don't let anyone swab your child's cheek.
Live your life with passion and whatever you do while it's still last.
Enjoy your freedom.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.