From the New World Order, to the Secret of Life, it's all on this edition of the Daily
Source Code.
Delta Sierra Charlie 800, it's a footballer Friday everybody!
800, more than 800 shows from the DSC, I'm gonna wake up, I put it on the drop
send it all to Adam Curry, I'd rather back and it's good to see, I'm still here and
still from CSB, while we're at it, don't forget about another little song from Young
Boyle, 800, more than 800 shows from the DSC, and there's one more thing we need, a little
more lady to you!
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation
radio content in my ears!
I like to think I'm flying to the future!
This is Adam Curry, and the Daily Source Code!
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, it's all on this
edition of the Daily Source Code!
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, it's all on this
edition of the Daily Source Code!
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Delta Sierra Charlie, $ 16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million worth of plane strapped to my ass
Delta Sierra Charlie, $16 million.
Baby, power to you and me
There's one old man Spends his life growing flowers
I'm caring for the beat
Power to the beat
There's one old lady
Spend his days making a wine
The wine tastes to find
Power to the vine
Power to the boys and play rock and roll
I make mine a lot so sweet
I do the girls a new before
So I'm yet to be
Power to all our friends
We don't need to take the blame of the beat
The people we want to be
Baby, power to you and me
There's one strong man
Plowing in the valley
He's living off the land
Power to the land
There's some young girl
Land down in the morning call
Laying in the sun
Power to the sun
Power to the boys and play rock and roll
I make mine a lot so sweet
I do the girls a new before
So I'm yet to be
Power to all our friends
We don't need to take the blame of the beat
The people we want to be
Baby, power to you and me
Power to the boys and play rock and roll
I make mine a lot so sweet
I do the girls a new before
So I'm yet to be
Power to all our friends
We don't need to take the blame of the beat
Baby, power to you and me
I gotta kick her
Baby, power to all our friends
Surf Cliff Richard
You know this song is from
is from, oh man, I don't know, this has got to be from early 70s and I can still sing the words
almost, almost the whole song through. It's kind of hokey but it's just one of those sound
tracks in my lives and you know what, it is a song about power and we are going to need to band
together and bond together to get through those and to prepare to change things every single step
of the way. Again, the first, the first way to do that is just by awakening the rest of the
world up to what's really going on. From the BBC, this article, and this is from earlier in the week
21st of October. Of course, we all laugh about the nut cases who say, hey, there's a movement towards
a new world order and it's going to start in finances. In fact, title of the article,
Sarcosi, that is the president of the European Union currently, the president of France.
He wants a European Union economy team. Here comes French president Nicholas Sarcosi has called
for a European economic government to ensure a more united EU response to financial turmoil. Now,
just follow me for a second here with what happened with the European Union.
It started off as kind of like a trade agreement and economic union. And then, well,
you know, we might as well have some money together. That's where it's started to go wrong
because you control the money, you control the entire, you control people and they are controlling
and now they want to have an economic government to really control everything you do.
Oh, man, it's happening. It's so happening. The 15 countries that use the Euro agreed on a massive
bailout package earlier this month. I mean, make no mistake. This is not because of people not
paying mortgage in the United States. This is all part of the system. It has seen interbank lending
dry up threatening the wider economy. Yeah, yeah, yeah, bloody, bloody, bloody, bloody blow.
European governments must follow up with bold steps on the recent commitments. This is, uh,
the usual troublemakers who are recommending this the international monetary fund, the world bank.
Those guys seem to be laughing quite a lot, though. Don't they? So it didn't start in America.
Yeah, we got our problems and there's definitely a lot wrong here, but this is happening globally.
And I can tell you that many countries in Europe are a lot further down the road. You just don't really
know it yet because I don't know. Maybe because it's your, you got too much American television.
You think you're actually free, but you're a lot further down the road. The Netherlands has an
example. They're already talking about work credits. So companies will be forced to take you to work
for them and you'll be forced to work for them with you. Wanted or not because the government says,
so, come on, this is not right. One thing I want to reiterate, this is not something that's
started with mortgages only in America. This is something that has been coordinated globally,
certainly the United States, certainly the European Union. Whatever you say, it didn't start here,
it was coordinated. The global, they're doing it to us that trying to bring us down, stay awake
and we'll be safe.
We've got a new queen, we'll see it all in a variety, set fire, let's go buy it in the store,
let's buy it in the store. We've got this, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world,
this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world,
this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is always the world
this is the world, this is the world, this world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world, this is the world,
All the fun is just a lot of time
We need to solve the fire
We didn't mind it, but we tried to find
Little rock, half the night
We make you mad, I can't watch
What we need to show a light
We don't know where we're going
Love and love, I'm trying to go
Can't fall, you may stop
But no harm, I tried to knock the little mic
Oh, oh, oh, oh
And then the space will keep my fear
We can't stop, it's a little no-go
Do you know if it's in the ring?
Hey, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
So far, so far, so far, so far
We didn't stop, but far
But we did find it, but we tried to find it
I mean, why I chose Stranger industry land
A little in Berlin, may it be the nation
Law and 얘는 are burningits, be your way
Ole Miss Jorn, Glendis, Can Be You Fails
All knowledge, great about attention
So just keep him safe, blow away
What I do, I have to say
Take me strong, I'm alive
There's always women, so far, so far
We're here, free, thus far
We did so the fire
It's pretty much a little history lesson for you there
You hear all that crap that went down
That song really Joel says we didn't start the fire
At first we didn't they started it
They've been burning with it for a long, long time
I'm so happy to tell you that
I'm going to share the secret of life with you my secret
I'm going to be able to articulate it
How you can change your life
And subsequently since we're all connected
Change the world
It's almost like an experiment we're going to do together
I guarantee you're going to have results
You're going to be reporting back to me
You're going to be sending invoicemails
You're going to be making an entire audio montage
How happy you are that you've discovered this secret
And it is just a bright shining light
That will help all of us get through what's happening now
What's coming
No matter what happens
You can change it
And it's a...
I'll manage some holistic shit
You're going to love it for sure
I've had a lot of teachers in getting to where I am today
Understanding how the world fits together
After obviously having been a part of the system
Having been a part of the big lie that television is
Yeah, very minor stuff and entertainment lies
And editing lies and editorial lies
But it is a part of a mind control machine
And that same box can be used for good
It is given me tremendous education
And even things that I heard a year ago
Or two years ago or ten years ago
Or people that I've been following
It all has become so clear
And I know it's all becoming clear to you as well
As you've been listening and following along
With what's happening on this very show
No matter how infrequent it appears to be
One of those people who just has been a tremendous teacher
To me and to millions of others
Unfortunately passed away earlier this year
I want to play a piece that some friendly chuckle had popped up on the source code
Drop.au slash daily source code
Because it once again just reminds you
Reminds you who's really in charge
So take it from a man who was around long enough
And saw it early on in his life and his career
George Carter
But there's a reason
There's a reason for this
There's a reason education sucks
It's the same reason that it will never ever ever be fixed
Never going to get any better
Don't look for it
Be happy with what you got
Because the owners of this country don't want that
I'm talking about the real owners now
The big wealthy
The real owners
The big wealthy business interests
That control things and make all the important decisions
They get the politicians
They're irrelevant
The politicians are put there to give you the idea
That you have freedom of choice
You don't
You have no choice
You have owners
They own you
They own everything
They own all the important land
They own and control the corporations
They've long since bought and paid for the senate
The congress, the state houses, the city halls
They got the judges in their back pockets
And they own all the big media
All the big media companies
So they control
Just about all the news and information you get to hear
They got you by the balls
They spend billions of dollars every year
Loving, lobbying
So get what they want
Well, we know what they want
They want more for themselves
Unless for everybody else
But I'll tell you what they don't want
They don't want a population of citizens
Capable of critical thinking
They don't want well-informed, well-educated people
That doesn't help them
That's against their interest
That's right
You know something
They don't want people who are smart enough
To sit around the kitchen table and figure out
How badly they're getting fucked by the system
They threw them overboard 30 fucking years ago
They don't want that
You know what they want?
They want obedient workers
Obedient workers
People who are just smart enough to run their machines
And do the paperwork
And just dumb enough
To passively accept all these increasingly
Shittier jobs with the lower pay
The longer hours the reduced benefits
The end of overtime
And the vanishing passion that disappears
The minute you go to collect it
And now they're coming for your social security money
They watch your fucking retirement money
They want it back
So they can give it to their criminal friends on Wall Street
And you know something? They'll get it
They'll get it all from you
Sooner or later
Because they own this fucking place
It's a big club
And you ain't in it
You and I are not in the big club
By the way, it's the same big club
They used to beat you over the head with all day long
And they tell you what to believe
All day long beat you over the head in their media
It's only what to believe
What to think
What to buy
The table is tilted folks
The game is rigged
And nobody seems to notice
Nobody seems to care
Good on us hardworking people
White collar blue collar doesn't matter
What color shirts you have on
Good on us hardworking people
Continue
These are people of modest means
Continue to elect these rich cock suckers
Who don't give a fuck about them
They don't give a fuck about you
They don't care about you
At all
rotational
As everything
Squinds
In theELL
In the K Expl catalyst
The government told us that
Because the land you love is freedom
It's just that the land is regulated
And if we hold him together
We can bring him back to USA
In this land
We like to be in this land
We're talking to USA
Bring back the U.S.
Say it!
Tenacious D, the government totally sucks
You know, on the daily source code
Yeah, they totally suck
We let them suck
We forgot to remind them continuously
That they work for us
So this thing is hitting home
And I've decided that I've got to share
Friends of mine
What do we talk about?
Who, man?
Was it four weeks ago when I got here
And Christina, who takes care of the condo
Forming and basically cleans up after my ass
She had lost her house
Because her mortgage skyrocketed
Her husband or lost his job
Yeah, you might have heard
One of our investors
Sequoia Capital had an all-hands meeting
A couple weeks ago
Where they had they started off with this
You know, this big power point
And it was like RIP
Rest in peace the good times
And everyone has to cut
60-70% of course
This is really for companies
They're not making any money
So a lot of companies are going to go out of business
I heard that the electric car company
Tesla is essentially shut down
Everyone who put in their money
Maybe even lost their money
Because they were using it to develop with
We've got
Boeing laying off people
We've got forward laying off people
We've got banks laying off people
It's hitting every single industry
This is exactly what you heard
Peter Schiff and Glenn Beck talk about
You're going to get inflation
You're going to get huge unemployment rates
And it's hitting our own
Chocolate heads
It's hitting our own
Matt, who was often contributed to the source code
Sent out an email to a lot of his colleagues
And people who's been working with
He's a great guy
I've known him for quite a long time
Done business with him
I just want to share his email with you
Since it was clearly not directed
Only to me
But at an email list
Clearly to his associates
And just to share this
And you know
To feel his pain
Because we're all going to feel it
One way or the other
High he says
Sadly, the financial health of Porter Noveli
is taken another turn for the worse
Porter Noveli is a PR company
They had another massive round of layoffs
This week
Unfortunately, I was among them this time
This was especially surprising
Since I was busy all the time
And in fact, I had to hire on
Four freelancers just to keep up with the work
In my department
If you hear any positions, please feel free to contact me
At this address
I can get you my resume
After 10 years of collecting dust
All the best
From that
And this is what really really bugs me
Okay
So we have this
Trillion dollars
Which is probably more like
Three or four trillion dollars
After the central banks
Get a hold of the so-called cash
They're receiving
It's going into fixing this BS
Financial system
It's bailing out people
They're taking the money
They're buying places down
They're getting ready to flee
Well, the crap comes down
And we have to sit around with all the
All the debris and the pieces that are left over
And people like myself
You know, mevio
It fits in the small medium business category
And the small category
You know, we don't have more than 75 people
Worldwide
In fact, it's less than that
You know, we work our ass off
Travel, not seeing families
Working on weekends
Not just myself, not just my partners
And co-founders and upper management
The whole company's working
Really, really hard
They're pitching in
They believe in trying to build something
We get nothing
No, in fact, we get screwed
We're only getting taxed more
We're going to get totally bone
Where is the whole backbone
The whole concept of America
Is that you work hard
An honest wage
You have a vision
You believe in something
The law of attraction
We're going to talk about the
Secret of life
And you move forward
And all the other people
On the high end
They're getting bailed out
On the low end
They're getting handouts
What is this supposed to...
What is this going to come to?
This is not the way it's supposed to work
Where in the world can we have
Something that is like
The true American dream of work hard
Play hard
And enjoy the fruits of your labor
I don't know, but it ain't here
Chocolate heads
Filming
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh no it's not that's all right
If anyone can bring a bag, it's us.
David Bowie, Pat, Petty, this is not America, I think that was the Falcon of the Snowman,
was the only thing.
You know, I just realized it being well past midnight, I haven't had any dinner.
I got back from our final meeting of the week, I did have breakfast, I did have lunch,
but I was so excited to finally get downcrackin', just spend a couple hours prepping
the show, gettin' ready, and, well, there you go, I don't think it's a good to eat this
late.
But I'm not done yet, ah, ah, ah, this is going to be probably one of the longest
shows I've ever produced, but it's 800, so you know, maybe it's one of those you keep
around, and if not for just the history of what we talked about on this show, then maybe
for the music, for the soundtrack to our life, which I've put a lot of research into this
one.
Really broke out the old archives.
Let's see another chucklehead who left a comment on the source code, drop.io slash daily
source code.
Adam, Eric from Portland.
Wow, of course, Eric from Portland, a frequent caller.
I heard Joe Biden the other day say that there's going to be a crisis, a generated crisis.
Wow, you know, the tape was all greeny and it wasn't clear, it sounded like this was
not supposed to be on tape.
I'm wondering if you think this is a projection of a false bike terror attack, is this
international politics putting in there?
I'd love to hear you take on that.
Yeah, I told.
That's it, yeah.
Which reminds me, please visit our sponsors.
Go to the show notes of daily source code.com or in this source code entry at curry.com.
And I use them, please use my codes for domain names, for cool stuff at Brooksstone.com,
what else do we have?
Budget, run a car, e-music, if any of those things, if you're going to buy any of that
anyway for whatever reason, just use one of my codes.
You can't get a better price.
That's why they're there.
That's what we do in negotiate those prices so that you have the best deal available.
Why waste time going somewhere else for those categories of stuff?
So yeah, about that Joe Biden comment.
That was actually, he was at a fundraiser in Seattle.
I believe this was Sunday a week ago.
And yeah, and of course the audio was all over the source code drop, but it's, it's not
going to be legible by the time it goes through multi-MP3 compressions, et cetera, into
your earbuds.
Well, I'm your speakers where you may listen to this particular format of show, the longer
format source code.
So here's what he said, because it, and of course, this is, you can find the link in
the show notes.
Mark my words, Biden told donors at a Seattle fundraiser, Sunday night.
You will not be six months before the world tests Barack Obama like they did John Kennedy.
Wow.
That's big there, right?
So I'm just going to say that means a political incident, a global political incident.
The world is looking.
He says we're about to elect a brilliant 47 year old senator president of the United States.
Watch.
We're going to have an international crisis, a generated crisis to test the metal of this
guy.
You hear that?
A generated crisis.
This is what the financial crisis is all about.
It is coming.
It's known.
It may even have something to do with that secret meeting they had in the House of Representatives
where they'd locked everything down, kicked everybody out, and it was something was told to
them that were not supposed to know, well, I'm pretty sure it was about this.
Because they know about it.
Don't be fooled.
Biden goes on to say, he's going to need help to something something to stand with
them because it's not going to be apparent initially.
It's not going to be apparent that we're right.
Not quite sure what he means by that.
But I'm sure it does relate to the fact that it's known, that it's coming, and I'm
pretty convinced it has to do with the American dollar.
So some say we'll be somewhere in January, could be late.
And I think it'll probably start somewhere in January and around spring, summer next
year, is when it's really going to hit, they're going to say screw it.
We don't want your dollar anymore.
That's the only thing I can imagine that this is about.
And it doesn't matter who becomes president of the United States.
They both work for the same people.
Okay.
They were working for big corporations for Wall Street and directly for the banks.
Just follow the pyramid all the way up and you come to the same true owners of the earth.
It was funny, by the way, in that, how that hearing, congressional hearing, where they
are talking to Greenspan and to, was it, cocks and to snow?
At a certain point, the Republican, which is named Davis, I believe.
He said, he asked the question to this panel of three, these three thieves, and liars, said,
in the past 20 years, gentlemen, do you have any idea which presidential candidate
received the most donations from subprime mortgage lenders?
In other words, Wall Street does nothing to do with what the company did as long as it's
a Wall Street company who deals in crap money and making up money and lying and cheating
and stealing from us.
In 20 years, gentlemen, which presidential candidate received the most donations, basically
from Wall Street?
The answer, Barack Obama, but it's only a little bit more than John McCain received,
so neither of these jibronies deserve to be running anything but the taps in the Lincoln
Bedroom.
It's a farce, and unfortunately, I'm not going to be here to share with you what's going
to happen after the election.
After November 4th, I'll be in Europe, I'll be reporting in from there, and I'm sure
tomorrow, I know a gentleman, John C. Duboric, and I get together will be talking about it.
About the hypocrisy of this American electoral system, and about how the entire world
has been snow jobbed into believing that you can only choose one of these two candidates.
Yes, one of the two tribes who will go to war over control, over us, control by the same
slave masters.
One is all too bad, so one, one is all too bad, so one, one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so
so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one you all so bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so one is all too bad, so two was all too bad,
It's time for you to be alone
We're all alone
I'm sure you're alive
I'm alive
All alone
I swear we're all alone
Love and love
This is the worst thing you can follow me
Thank you, John, John, what is all that you can do?
John, John, John, what is all that you can do?
We got such a chance, and you're the one we got the way
All of them ain't here
We got a chance, and you're the one we got the way
Got a chance, and you're the one we got the way
machine works. I'm going to read you one paragraph from this TV and the social construction
of reality. Okay. Let me say that again. TV and the social construction of reality. So check
this out. The technical events test, which is a test you have to do. I'm not going to go
into it right here, but the technical events test dramatically reveals the functions of
the political institution of television in A, training us to shorten our attention span,
be making ordinary life appear dull and see injecting a hypnotic quality into our ordinary
awareness and decourshing us into its reality. This happens continuously and it happens
in drama. It happens in news. It happens with particularly with so-called reality shows with
which have nothing at all to do with reality. And it's really part of a very old concept.
This is not new at all. It's just a 20th or now a 21st century version of something
that's been around for centuries.
Yeah, I'm scoring. Hey, you're a crazy bastard, but let me show. I love no agenda too. I've been
reading about the Roman Empire and read an article or a section today of a book that
I was in a pretty industry and in light of what you've been talking about lately. It says
but the gladiatorial games served a purpose beyond mere entertainment to the Romans, the
games and other forms of public entertainment, the field both a political and a social
need. Certainly they served it avert the idle masses from political unrest. It was said
of Emperor Trojan that he understood that although the distribution of grains and money
satisfied the individual, spectacles were necessary for the contentment of the masses. So in
other words, he knew he had to give him things, give him grain, and I give him money to
keep him satisfied, but they also need to be content with some diversion henceforth.
Now we have the American Gladiators.
Hey man, thanks for the show.
That's right. That's just one version of a spectacle. We've had a spectacle that's been
on television for 10 years by now.
Over here of the Cherry Springer show.
Now here comes our next dance and it's a squad best because it's a true and trash brother.
If many acres back in Crackets like when animals attack they all exhibit reprehensible
behavior and if in the no sir of their clothes they're on their toes and how it goes
they get so violent they have to sign a waiver. There was worry because they can't find a
twin blame on the air they don't care they got no shame. There was a good one true for
the little strange way and he found out that his wife had a sex change. They have a
dinner seat on screen when he else tells a link. They have a history of reviving
after Jersey's baby. So they had to find. We're the same twins and they're the best
night. Five days since that awful ball. They still haven't got the blood off the wall
and it's bad. Three days since the bitter. But when they gank you in a game you
always like to get a. Finally done on me. We're done with time on that cherry
Springer. Baby, I'm a sleeper with your sister.
Oh, which one? Oh, what happened sleeper? We got that friend Jay.
Oh, damn. Oh, me too. I'm a sleeper with your dog, woofie.
What the fuck? What the fuck? I'm a sleeper with your pet go.
That ghost doesn't love you. Just don't watch it. There's just no stopping. Your brain
shuts down. That your eye goes dropping. Jerry's the king of confrontation. He's
a sensation. He puts a sense of indication. It's totally worthless like a bad check. It's
like a train wreck. Don't want to stare but you gotta look away. I felt he just
he beat us up shows. But with my weirdos, the ratings are being higher every day. If you
see the show, well then you know it just as low as you can go the gas or tacky and they're
raging and freezing. So I'm ugly with them and the room and that is cool. I'm in the face of
some motherfucked drag queen. What is the game that show where people scream of
Venetese? Can't get here from a chair to their hobbies. Jerry, during all the crowds
heard their favorite chant shit. I heard of my TV. I just can't. I have a tendency to
watch a ring that you see. I have a history of taping each one. It's bad.
Whoa, he says the show about. I know girls with problems. They should work out.
Five days, that's the big surprise. So I'm worried for the cheese to leave. What do you
say?
Yeah.
It's alright, man. As long as you realize what's going on.
We live in the society of the spectacle. Something that was discovered centuries ago.
Good book written about that.
Like in 18900 something or other.
Man, that's another link I got to go find for you. Hey, just a reminder, the secret of life
is coming up, which is going to save you. It's going to, it's been saving me for years.
And I'm going to share that secret with you. I mean, it's not a big secret. It actually
is called the secret we're going to talk about. It's been documented a book, which
really puts it into context. But it's all part of themes and theories and
different, different learnings that that I've come across throughout my path and life.
And we are hand on such a high note. You're going to be just zinging through the weekend
and for many, many weekends to come. Just taking with television for a moment here because
there was something really funny that showed up on the drop. This is a cure of
Phillips from CNN. And sometimes the truth really does shine through on television.
It's, it's fascinating when it happens.
It, you could call it a Freudian slip. And if you want to call it that, well, this one's
to do this. And the battle for the White House, from two of our favorite analysts,
Roland Martin, well, I don't know. I'm a go favorite there. CNN political analyst and
you know you love me, you know. At least, Leslie Sanchez, Republican
strategist and CNN political, kind of contributor is always on time.
Let's hear that one again. And as Republican strategist and CNN political
kind of contributor is always on time.
Oh, that's funny. That's funny. She meant it too. You know she meant it.
I want to get back for a second to our international chuckle heads.
Just need to talk about Europe for a second here as I stated earlier that
what's going on in the world is really going on in the world. And it's not just the
United States. Let's shift over to Europe for a second.
This is following on on what I said about the European Union.
This is actually from the European Parliament. It's just a great piece of
video. Now, in the United Kingdom, a lot of people do not like this guy,
Farage, I think his name is, who was of the UKIP, the United Kingdom
Independent Party. And I think just listening to what he has to say, he
may just be getting a bad rap. I have no idea what his history is
with, you know, with his political career in the United Kingdom.
But hearing him stand up in European Parliament, saying the following
really gave me once again great respect for this guy, at least for his
thinking and his current words because it's spot on the month.
From 8th of October.
President, what a funny old European Union it is, isn't it?
Last Saturday afternoon, after a Johnny Good Lunch at the
Alize, the European leaders stood on the steps and they talked with
very weak smiles about solidarity. The smiles were weak, of course,
because President Sarkozy's U.S. star bailout plan had already
clapped in the bed of dust. But nonetheless, United
Wastand is what was said, and yet with almost comic hypocrisy,
the German Chancellor decided that German interests come first,
and European interests come second, and she acted.
Perhaps for the first time in years, she got louder applause from her
own electorate, because it was the Irish that started this trend,
the week before, by going their own way, and my admiration for Ireland,
I have to say, grows by the day.
But I think for the last week, it's going to prove to be the
watershed moment for this entire European project.
You see, the only way to stop countries acting in their own
national interest is to take that power away from them, to form
a treasury department, there in Frankfurt, that has power,
over tax, and power, over government spending.
And indeed, I've heard some of the EU extremists,
this afternoon, effectively call for that.
Yet, you can't do it, because it won't come on public support.
In fact, to do that, there'll be even more unpopular than your
hated Lisbon Tracy. No more likely is that what's happened
in the last week marks the beginning of the end.
The markets are saying it already.
Italian government bonds now yield 1% more than German or
Frenchist youth, government bonds.
The markets are saying that economic and monetary union
will not last, and I'm not surprised, because it never
was an optimal currency zone.
One interest rate could never fit all these different countries,
and you've never had proper public support.
But it must be one thing or the other.
It's either a full EU state that controls everything,
or it is disintegration and back to national control.
The credit crunch is hitting and hurting all of us,
but I see a speck of light at the end of a tunnel.
I see a dividend, possibly the beginning of the end,
of this whole mad and unwanted project.
Fantastic.
You know, I have no idea why he gets such a bad rap in the UK,
perhaps it's because maybe they've set it up that way.
You know, whoever controls the media can put anyone in any kind of
light they want to, but this guy is spot on.
Either Europe, the people of Europe of all the individual
countries who already work together, who already like each other.
We have the love parade together in Berlin.
We do all kinds of stuff as normal people.
Forget about what our unelected representatives are doing
in the European managing Europe and the European
unions top there in Brussels.
Forget about all that, okay?
What he's saying is correct.
They want to control everything.
They want full control over you.
I believe that Europeans, possibly, are more awake than the Americans
and you can start doing something about this.
Start fighting again, something that Bob Marley identified
decades ago as the Babylon system.
It is a vampire mass.
We refuse to beat.
What you wanted us to beat.
We are what we are.
That's the way it's going to be.
If you don't know.
You came and you came down.
Or you'll eat the words.
I'll put your energy in the mouth.
Talk in love, I'll bring those.
Leave them free, Bob.
And the energy.
It's just for every image.
I didn't know why it came.
It's much too low.
It's the rhythm.
As we've been tried, it's the one way.
Ride with words too long, treat it.
Leave it.
It's Bob Marley's 언제 It's the vampire.
Yeah.
Again.
Have come to hear it.
with the Mayors.
What we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if
we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't
tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have
teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them let's do this today we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them anything but we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have taught them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell people you have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you what we have to teach them if we can't tell you
Uh, please see last two bar Friday for an explanation of that one.
You know what, I gotta get into my bar Marley mode here.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, much better.
I feel good now.
A wonderful fade out once again.
Okay, something here for a new check-out.
The chuckleheads formerly known as the arrowheads who I used to listen to my,
my program in the Netherlands, however short it lasted.
Of course, that was, that's what you get when you try to tell the truth and
open people's eyes and mainstream media.
Eventually, the financial system comes in and stops it all.
Um, the president of the Dutch, uh, central bank,
not velling.
And, uh, there's a link in the show notes for you guys.
It's in English, so other people can participate, but just to show how it all fits
together, you've probably heard of the trilateral commission,
which was set up by one of the true owners of the globe.
The Rockefeller's David Rockefeller, along with the Chase Manhattan Bank, which, of course,
is now JP Morgan Chase.
Um, he was a member.
Oh, it has been a member of the trilateral commission since 2005.
These are the guys who actually have put out the blue prints for this, for this new world order,
for this first, the financial collapse, taking control over the finances,
then taking over governmental control.
Look, I don't mind if we're all called the same country, but I kind of like the idea that,
you know, they're different cultures and, and some different things when you cross the border.
And that's what makes us beautiful as a, as a, as a people as a population of the globe.
Is it, we're not all the same, that we are a little bit different.
But to have guys like this guy, just looking at his picture makes my stomach turn.
These are the people who are all in this, it's like the builder group.
Only the builder, which, by the way, was set up by the Prince of Orange, Prince,
Baron Art of the Netherlands.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, there's, there's a lot, there's a, there's a reason why I'm doing this stuff.
There's a reason because I lived in these countries.
I'm living in the UK, I've been in America.
For whatever reason, this is currently my destiny, I guess, to bring this information to you.
And, uh, boy, it's, uh, you know what it is, it's the way of the world.
The way of the world that we're going to change.
And I'm going to teach you how you can use your inherent power and the law of attraction,
what you own to change the way of the world to change it and make it better.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
If you're hard to solve, I don't have a treat
Cause the worst is gone
Stay young at home
I call you never and we're all in the world
And we're all in the world
Yes, we're all in the world
We're all in the world
That your flowers are so beautiful
It's a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell of a hell
Oh oh oh oh
I'm going home, I'm going home
You, you, you, you
I'm going home
We can't get up on special day
So long as it's not clear
And I can't give touch of some days
Right, good job, there's a plead
We will hold you home
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, we got thisbout, cuidado, Oh, I appreciate it,
Yo, eight's90.
Sorry, we got it.
Wait folks?
I knew it that way, I knew thatsoo had plenty of
the stuff, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah pot, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah we gotChef, that hoodie.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah. Dedado La La La La La a sixties, yeah yeah.
19 years old, you know, 1819 they really didn't know worth when in fire. So share this
with your kid with you or if you're a kid, enjoy. Because if you're 1819, yeah, you're
grown up, you're still a kid in my eyes. Just a couple of updates on the things. This
is actually some homework for you, shakalheads, the shakalheads and shakalheads
in turn, not your now. This is a great link from Dr. Jim Howenstein, MD, and the
title of is it why you should avoid taking vaccines. Now, there's been a lot of talk,
you know, I've been doing my bit to warn people certainly of the dangers of these new
vaccines, which are intended to be cash cows for the pharmaceutical industry. Oh, another
hairball. Excuse me. That helps. Oh, man, they went down the wrong tube. What he does
he breaks down beautifully, how vaccines actually have done very little to stop a
horrible diseases and how actually a lot of the natural development of the world
and our knowledge of what is good to eat and how to take care of ourselves. Probably
helped a lot more. If anything, a lot of the vaccinations detracted from or it made
the really hurt. Let's put it that way. And it goes all the way up through through some
of these newer vaccines that they were talking about. So just to help spur on the conversation,
I'd like you to take a look at that link in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
or in the Charlie Entry at curie.com. One other thing for those of you who I am skip that,
I'm just gonna rid of that. I'm done with that one. I'm trying to think what I should
do next. I am suggesting with this, this is a great idea. Hey Adam, hey I'm doing it. I'm
doing it. Okay, that's number 144 and we're gonna start right away with intro and
be one. Oh boy. Oh man, that sounds like oh, y'all and I don't know man, I can't get it. Number two.
Hey, come on. Is that like, hey, come on. There's a party over here and a fantastic voyage.
And number three. Oh, hey, that's earth wind and fire. Let's group tonight. I believe. So it's
probably all from the 70s. I couldn't get the first one. Let's see how we do. And it's time for
the answers and this week they're all from. Oh, take that one. And this is answer number one.
This is Carol Gianni, hit it on the lover. I was nervous. I was nervous. I was near the 70s and
we went.
Carol Gianni is answer number one. And this is answer number two. This is Lakeside.
Okay.
Yeah, fantastic voyage. All right, Lakeside is answer number two. And this is answer number three.
This is earth wind and fire. Let's group. Let's group tonight.
Uh-huh.
Earth wind and fire. Let's group. And answer number three. And let's conclude.
It's a number one, it's 44. So Adam. How did you do this week?
What do you do this week?
I'm poorly young.
I would say that is three out of a possible six doors because they got the name of the
band Lakeside ROM and you get the titles.
The answers to this and the other hitest and also the links to the iTunes you can buy
the tricks.
Featured on the hitest online or to be found at hitest.mifio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Thank you for listening.
Next week I'll be back for another hitest.
So until then take care, have fun and remember to write a thing with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
We'll be back.
Hitest, that's email.com info, youngpullet.com, date and p-o-l-c-t.com.
Oh man.
Thanks, Yon.
Funny that we both had a earth wind and fire.
Totally different vibe, totally different songs there, but thank you so much for it.
Was it hitest number 144?
One little update on Steve Fossard who went missing on my birthday actually, September
3rd last year, of course he was, well I think they found his wreckage and they're not
sure if they did actually, you know I should get an update on that on the situation there.
If they ever found any of his remains, some hikers found his, found this billfold or some
of his personal possessions and indeed it would look like wreckage of the airplane.
But I remember telling you that Richard Branson had said that it was really unfortunate
because it was working on this top secret project, something that was supposed to be really
awesome and it had to do with submarines and this video showed up on the drop, it's a video
from LiveLeague.com.
I'm going to play this for you because it explains exactly what he was doing, link in the
show notes so you can actually see the whole thing.
His big secret project, this was to make a record dive to the bottom of the planet.
This is the deep space challenger.
It looks like a plane, but is actually a winged, submersible, capable of diving to the
Mariana Trench, a lowest spot on Earth, 37,000 feet below the surface.
Until now, the ship has been kept under wraps in a Richmond warehouse.
I would have dramatically, dramatically open the oceans for exploration.
It would have been a game changer.
Graham Hawks says the craft would have flown to the bottom of the ocean in an hour and
40 minutes and then rocketed back up.
He wouldn't say what it cost to build, but it was almost ready to launch when faucet
disappeared.
You would finish testing.
All the systems have been tested under pressure at the Department of Defense facilities.
We were four weeks away from splashing it in.
But now that faucet has died, the project is on hold.
Deflight challenger is just, I think, an extraordinary beautiful machine to my eyes.
And it's not like anything else has been seen on this planet before.
We've really got to see this thing.
You've got to check that video.
It's just absolutely awesome.
And of course, it begs the question, if it was so close from actually making that deep
dive, and he passed away so mysteriously and did he actually pass away or he disappeared,
you've got to ask yourself the question, is it coincidence or is there something at the
bottom of the ocean that someone doesn't want us to know about, will there be a true
secret down there?
The secret of the ocean.
Stay with me, Chocol-Heads.
The secret of the universe is next.
Do you want to know the secret of the ocean?
Do you promise not to tell?
The Beatles. Do you want to know a secret? Well, you came to the right place, my friends.
Chuckle heads. Something new to wind up this extraordinarily long episode of the Daily
Source code looks like we're moving up on two hours. So if you're still with me, then it's
going to pay off, I believe. This is now the other day after we had one of our management meetings,
you know, we're gearing up to head into the economic tsunami, head on my partner, friend and co-founder
of mevio. We've been in business together for 14 years now. He said, would you mind just walk
with me to the bookstore? I want to go pick a song up and he was going to go pick a book up and I said,
sure. And he picked up this book, which is actually, it's a really small, very small book. It has a companion
DVD, which he offered me. But I said, no, I'd be much more interested in the book. It's called the secret
by Ronda Burn. And I believe when this book first came out, let me just see if I can see when the
first day it came out. I didn't read it at the time. But remember there was kind of this who
plot around it? Does it say here? So I'm going to shoot stir, it doesn't actually give us the,
well, not quite sure when it came out. But anyway, I'm going to recite a bit from this book.
And you definitely need to pick this up because, you know, ever since, probably a 1989, 1990,
I started, you know, becoming interested in things like a neural linguistic programming that's
what we used with the sense say or experiment those of you who've been around long enough actually
you heard a throwback to that earlier in the show where I could anchor your thoughts to something.
So, whenever I burped, then you would automatically think since sale, the positive of power,
the power of positive thinking, the Anthony Robbins, I've listened to all his tapes, I've read many
many books. And I'm, you know, I've tried a lot of these, you know, business self health books,
but that's never really worked for me. But I, I've always known that there was something
within us all the way up to recent times where I've been in contact with people who
talk about what might happen in 2012. And of course, visitors from outer space and our natural
frequencies, the human frequencies of the earth. Even some of this goes to, to, when the energy
elite captured or hijacked the development of energy and basically forced us into fossil fuels,
things that people like Tesla were into. Anyway, it's the book is called the secret and I'll just
start off from going to read a couple paragraphs here for you starting off with what is the secret.
This is, and I guess what they did is they went out the interview to hold a bunch of people and this
can be found on the DVD. This is a Bob Proctor. You're probably sitting there wondering,
what is the secret? I'll tell you how I've come to understand it. We all work with one infinite
power. We all guide ourselves by exactly the same laws. The natural laws of the universe are so
precise that we don't even have any difficulty building spaceships. We can send people to the moon.
We can time the landing with the precision of a fraction of a second, wherever you are, India,
Australia, New Zealand, Stockholm, London, Toronto, Montreal, New York. We're all working with
one power, one law. It's attraction. The secret is the law of attraction.
Everything that's coming into your life, you are attracting into your life. And it's attracted to
you by virtue of the images you're holding in your mind. It's what you're thinking.
Whatever is going on in your mind, you are attracting to you. Now let me continue here.
The greatest teachers who have ever lived have told us that the law of attraction is indeed the
most powerful law in the universe. Poets, like William Shakespeare, Robert Browning, William Blake,
delivered it in their poetry. Musicians such as Ludwig von Beethoven expressed it through their music
artists, such as Leonardo da Vinci, depicted it in their paintings. Great thinkers, including
Socrates Plato, Ralph Waldo, Emerson, Patagarras, Sir Francis Bacon, Sir Isaac Newton,
Johann Wolfgang von Goethe, and Victor Hugo shared it in their writings and teachings.
Their names have been immortalized and their legendary existence has survived centuries.
Religion, such as Hinduism, hermetic traditions, Buddhism, Judaism, Christianity, and Islam,
and civilization, such as the ancient Babylonians and the Egyptians delivered it with their
writings and stories thousands of years ago. Recorded throughout the ages in all its forms,
the law can be found in ancient writings throughout all the centuries. It was recorded in stone
in 3000 BC. Even though some coveted this knowledge and indeed they did, it was always and
has always been there for anyone to discover. The law began at the beginning of time. It has
always been and will always be. It is the law that determines the complete order in the universe.
Every moment of your life and every single thing you experience in your life,
doesn't matter who you are or where you are. The law of attraction is forming your entire life
experience and this all-powerful law is doing that through your thoughts. You are the one who
calls the law of attraction into action and you do it through your thoughts. A perfect example
to demonstrate the secret and the law of attraction is this one. Now you may know or heard of people
who acquired massive wealth, lost it all and within a short time acquired massive wealth again.
What happened in these cases, whether they knew it or not, is that their dominant thoughts
were unwell. That's how they acquired wealth in the first instance. Then they allowed fearful
thoughts of losing the wealth to enter their minds until those fearful thoughts of loss became
their dominant thoughts. That tip the scales from thinking thoughts of wealth to thinking thoughts
of loss and so they lost it all. Once they had lost it, however, the fear of loss disappeared
and they tip the scales back with dominant thoughts of wealth and wealth returned. The law responds
to your thoughts no matter what they may be. Well, of course, is just one example you could
wish for health, you could wish for happiness, you could wish for anything you want. That's the beauty
of the law of the attraction, the true secret to the universe. Janasarov says in the book,
the simplest way for me to look at the law of attraction as if I think of myself as a magnet.
And I know that a magnet will attract things to it. You are the most powerful magnet in the
universe. You contain a magnetic power within you that is more powerful than anything in this world.
And this unfathomable magnetic power is emitted through your thoughts. Now, I know this sounds
crazy, but I wouldn't be reading this to you if I didn't absolutely 100% believe it and have
seen this happening in my own life time, oh, and time again. And this is the interesting thing.
When you're thinking these thoughts, the thoughts, the magnet doesn't understand the word
don't or can't or any negative connotations. You can't say, I don't want to become sick.
That doesn't work. You have to think it positive, I want to be healthy. It's not like I don't
want to become poor. If you're thinking, I don't want to become poor. You're going to become poor.
Whatever poor is in your realm, whatever poor is in your destiny, but thinking in a negative
connotation does not work. That's not how you turn the magnet on.
Okay, here's another favorite part that I liked in this book. Thoughts are magnetic and thoughts
have a frequency. As you think, those thoughts are sent out into the universe and they magnetically
attract all like things that are on the same frequency. Everything sent out returns to the source
and that source is you. Think of it this way. We understand that a television station's
transmission tower broadcast via a frequency which is transformed into pictures on your television.
Most of us don't really understand how it works, but we know that each channel has a frequency.
And when we tune into that frequency, we see the pictures on our television,
which shows the frequency by selecting the channel and we then receive the pictures broadcast on
that channel. If you want to see different pictures on our television, we change the channel
and tune into a new frequency. You are a human transmission tower and you are more powerful than
any television tower created on earth. You are the most powerful transmission tower in the
universe. Your transmission creates your life and it creates your world. The frequency you
transmit reaches beyond cities, beyond countries, beyond the world. It reverberates throughout
the entire universe and you are transmitting that frequency with your thoughts. Pictures you receive
from the transmission of your thoughts are not on a television screen near living room. They are
the pictures of your life. Your thoughts create the frequency. They attract like things on that
frequency and then they are broadcast back to you as your life pictures. If you want to change anything
in your life, change the channel and change the frequency by changing your thoughts. Chocolate heads
by using the law of attraction, the secret of the universe. We can change the world and make it a
better place. Think about the generations and they want to make it a better place for children
and their children's children so that they know it's a better world for them. They can make it a better
place. There's a place in your heart and I know that it is not. It's a place
was brighter than tomorrow. If you have a try, if you find there's no need to cry, it's a
place, but there's no better sorrow. There are ways to get there. If you care enough for the living,
make a little space. Make a better place. You'll do whatever you want. Make it a better place for you and
me and me and I are human beings. There are people right. You care enough for them and make a better
place for you and for me. If you want to know why, there's a love that cannot lie. Love is strong,
you don't need care for your forgive me. We try, just see, and this place we cannot feel.
Stop existing and start living. There's a better ways, love is going
Make a better world. Make a better world. You'll do whatever you want. Make it a better place for you and
for me and me and I are human beings. There are people right. If you care enough for them and make a better
place for you and for me and I are human beings. There are people right. You don't need to cry for you and
me and I are human beings. There are people right. You don't need to cry for your forgive me. You don't need to cry for your
happiness. There are people right. You don't need to cry for your forgive me. You don't need to cry for your
and make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better place for you and
for me and I are human beings. There are people right. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better
place for you and for me and you are human beings. Make a better place for you and for me and
me and I are human beings. There are people right. You don't need to cry for your
and for me and I are human beings. There are people right. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world.
Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make
a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a
better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world. Make a better world . Make a better world. Make a better
create the picture in your mind, make it happen in that picture that is changing your
frequency. It is turning on your magnet. It is attracting different particles of the same
frequency to your magnet to your life. And because we're all connected, if you make your
life better, all of our lives are going to be better. And focus on what you really want
to achieve. Because we're going to have to do it. And the only way to do it is to become
aware. Not to become aware of the world around us. We talked a lot about that on today's
anniversary episode of the Daily Source Code and 800 episodes. I've never thought how
it would get here. But we're here. And we have this opportunity. And now that you
know that there is something within all of us. And this is my personal, you know, my
own secret. And it's worked very well for me. I've been extremely happy, extremely
healthy and very successful. And it's not just because I'm a lucky bastard. You create
your own luck. You created by attracting that, attracting what you want. You're going to
need that. It's a part of your tool set. We're all going to have to bond this together.
And if we all focus, and if we all create a better world in our minds, and I want to get
a lot of feedback from you guys. There's a voicemail number. You can call, uh, listed on
the drop, uh, drop.au slash daily source code or upload something. Tell me your experiences.
Tell me that if you've been using it, if you've tried it out, if it's worked for you,
you will be absolutely amazed when we all bond together. And we create a massive magnet
on one frequency. I'm telling you, we'll be unstoppable.
Juggle heads, thanks for hanging out for this special edition of the daily source code, 800
episodes. Next week, when I get back to the UK, we're going to pick up and do a couple
a week. And there'll be a little bit shorter. But I think the format is kind of working.
Until then, enjoy your freedom, enjoy your power, and live your life with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation. Stick it in your ear.