That of course was a wikacity with never going to give you a chance to get so long
has been running through my head for quite a few days now.
Well it's about time for me to get out of here and clear the booth for Adam Curry here
on the WDSC, he's got a mix of the soundtrack of our lives, the indie music from the
PodSafe music network, political commentary, of course you recalls your emails and your
tweets.
All in his Delta Sierra Charlie 741.
That's here on WDSC.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
That's a wikacity with never going to give you a chance to get so long
has been running through my head for quite a few days now.
That of course was a wikacity with never going to give you a chance to get so long
In the 70s there's only been a handful of fatalities and I'm sure most of them were
due to pilot error.
Very interested of course to see what happened but it was quite tragic the way this went down
in the crash into a couple of houses.
This made the news in the United States the fact that the French president was over here
not much but the fact that a jet went down big deal.
But it is of course always tragic a bad day, bad day for aviation.
It was really sweet everyone was like checking and saying hey man is that you I was getting
Skype messages, I am and tweets and all kinds of really concerned people and that was of course
appreciated but I'm okay.
Had it been a little bit different I had the lady Patricia not been in the Netherlands.
I would have had my ass out on the west coast because on Saturday it was a surprise birthday party
and I was really planning on being there.
I actually already pre-books but I just had to stay here with the house and the teenager
you know dangerous combination.
And of course I had known about this for months and a lot of people were new about it
and I think we kept it from it.
I don't think he had any idea what was going to go down.
I hope he had a really good time and happy 40th birthday mark.
Welcome to the club my friend.
You are now just as screwed as the rest of us.
Kind of cool though I look like everyone is figured out the live 365 live stream
apparently in order to get it to work you might have to refresh the page a couple of times
until it says that the station is actually online but for the past like hour and a half
I've been just playing music in a couple of jingles.
Oh yeah it's filled up now.
Now we got like 150 people listening.
That's good.
Although it maxes out if you're not registered or if you're not a VIP member I'm sure that
means you have to pay money which kind of sucks.
There's like a 60 person limit but there's lots of VIP members on so that's good.
I'm paying 99 bucks a month for this service and I'm not really happy with it.
I also don't really think those limitations are great.
However any music I play they do pay royalties to the artist or at least that's part of their
pitch so that's why I chose to go with live 365 we'll see what happens.
Lots of other ways to get a clean high-deft stream out to you guys but right now just
have to leave it at this.
It's about five minutes to five and very busy here today.
Lots of conference calls of course we moved over to British standard time I think.
So we moved the clock ahead an hour now we're back in tune with the United States with an eight-hour
difference between London and San Francisco and five hours between London and New York.
And still one hour I guess one hour difference with the rest of Europe.
Yeah all of Europe changed.
Interesting.
We're all on track.
I got some cool for you.
So what I wanted to say is the lady Patricia probably should be home in about an hour so she
may come home just at the tail end of the show.
I'm looking forward to seeing her she's been away for an entire week so.
And I've been playing Mr. Mom.
It's been challenging to say the least.
You hear the damn dog.
Whenever I'm up here it's been this way all week long.
The dog just keeps barking.
I bring him up here and then he wants to go downstairs.
It's like 15 years old and he's a Yorkie and it's not very mobile and it sucks.
Just looking at the Twitter messages coming in from that hour and a half of music I was playing.
Kieran Johnson said now it's exciting kind of like a concert waiting for a gig to start.
And we've got to truck our loo listening in from Grand Rapids.
Michigan through a sprint broadband internet in his tractor trailer,
waiting to unload some chocolate chips.
And everyone else seems to be good to go.
I got a premiere of sorts for you today.
Let me just see if I can find the actually it's probably fine that email.
A couple of weeks ago, let me see.
Hold on.
Sorry not incredibly prepared for this one.
A couple of weeks ago I received when the when the credit crunch crisis just started off.
I received an email.
And this of course is what I'm looking for.
Hold on.
Wait.
Where is it?
Ah, here it is.
No.
Here we go.
Got it.
Okay, of course.
I got it from Paul Parkinson.
There you go.
He sent me an email.
So this is doing the rounds in the dealing rooms and back offices of the city of London today,
which now this is 11 days ago, March 20th, when he sent me this email.
And essentially it's a, it's a, it's a, a parody, parody lyrics.
Written to the tune of Queens Bohemian Rhapsody.
And of course this is typically now.
This is what these traders, they'll send all kinds of stuff around.
And it gets really, really viral.
And so I'm thinking to myself, hey, this is interesting.
So I forwarded it to Jeff Smith and said,
dude, might be a hoot to record.
But took a couple days and Jeff got back to me and said, oh, man, I've been sick for the past week.
The voice has been shot.
Just getting my pipes back.
I think it's an interesting idea.
And I even said in the past seven days, you know, I said, hey, man,
the crisis will last.
Don't worry.
It's not going to go away.
And I knew that these lyrics are really funny.
If you're in the financial business, so nylon, pay attention.
This is for you, my friend.
But others of you may also appreciate it.
If not, if not for that, for the fact that Jeff does this just an amazing job on stuff.
So here it is.
It's the Bohemian financial rhapsody Jeff Smith on the Charlie.
Is this the real price?
Is this just fantasy?
Financial landslide?
We're escape from reality.
Open your eyes.
Look up at your buys and see.
I don't know a boy, boy.
Heilin' casualty.
Cause I bought it high.
Watch it blow.
Rating high.
Now you'll know.
In a way the fan goes doesn't really matter.
To me, to me.
Mama, just killed my friend.
Could it sitios instead?
Pulled the trigger now it's dead.
Mama, I had just begun.
These sitios have blown it all away.
Mama, I still want to buy.
Sometimes we should never let go of it all.
I see a little silhouette of a fan.
But I can't but I can't say the whole market.
But I don't know the new, yes.
Where did everybody be?
Super senior.
I never go.
I'm on a surprise video fantasy.
Easy come, easy come.
You, let me go.
Oh, I know it's over!
No, no, no, no!
Get out, get out of the door!
Oh, for me, for me!
So you think you could find me and spit in my eye?
Then the bottom and call me and leave me a tie.
Oh baby, can't do this to me baby.
Just got it out, just got it right out of here.
So you think you could find me and spit in my eye?
Then the bottom and call me and spit in my eye.
Sorry, I don't know where to go.
No price really matters, no liquidity, nothing really matters
No price really matters to me
Just Smith with the Bohemian Financial Wrap, you can find Jeff at thejfsmith.com
Jeff Spell, G-E-O-F-F, thejfsmith.com, fantastic
And I know the guys in the city and Wall Street are going to love this
I have no idea how Jeff wants to release it
Obviously it's completely covered under fair use because it's a parody
So hopefully this will make the rounds
I'll just link to his website in the show notes at dailysourceco.com
So you can find either way to download it or whatever Jeff decides
But awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, I love it
That was so cool
Let me see, speaking of the Fed, I love that bit in the song
I see a little silhouette on the Fed, Barnaki, Barnaki
Fantastic, a lot of people sent me this link
I think the New York Times had the exclusive on this
The Bush administration is now suggesting that they give the federal reserve power
You gotta love this, to regulate the financial sector
As a part of a financial regulation overhaul
This, of course, is laughable
A superagent key, I gotta talk to him later
It's laughable because the Fed is, of course, responsible for what has happened
Not necessarily directly responsible for the credit crunch, but responsible for everything else
In the way they're dealing with it already
By basically printing money, causing inflation
And I hope you had a chance over the weekend to look at that documentary
I told you about the money masters
Now, I also discussed it with John C. Dvorak and asked him to watch it over the weekend
Because he wasn't familiar with it, he hated it
He thought it was full of lies, the quotes were bullshit
He even felt that had an antisemitic twins to it
Which I didn't pick up on
And so while I think he's pretty good with his research in his history
So a lot of the stuff that he's talking about
May, or that he says is BS, may indeed be BS
A lot of things, particularly when the story picks up around Andrew Jackson
And you look at how the second bank of America was put together
And the concept of fractional, or the fact fractional reserve banking
Or lending
Once you understand those concepts, which do kick in after the first hour of this documentary
Well actually the beginning, even if the quotes are on true, the concept remains the same
And that concept is that the people who really control the earth
Who really control what your rent is going to be, or what your mortgage payment
Or your car payment, or how much money you'll have in your pocket at the end of the month
Is determined by the central bank
For the United States, the Federal Reserve, which has nothing to do with the government
It is not a governmental organization, it is a commercial bank
Who have the exclusive right to print dollars
And lend those dollars to the United States government
Okay, that's how it works
And those dollars that are lent that are printed out of thin air
And are lent to the US government
Are guaranteed against taxes
So every single time you see the Federal Reserve printed up some money
That's going to cost you one way or the other
Same, interestingly enough, goes for the bank of England
Which is also a very deceptive name
The bank of England is not belong to the country, to the government
Or to the Queen
Again, it is a commercial bank
And they have the right to print the money
And lend the money to the government
So, as a part of this, and I can tell you what's coming next
Excuse me, I get all worked up, but I just got a burp
But I think about what's going on, it makes me nauseous
The next crunch you're going to get is the credit card crunch
You can be ready for it, take a look at your statements at the end of the month
You're probably paying anywhere between 20 and 25% interest
And these guys can raise this rate at any time
They can change their terms of services
It's really, really a bad deal
And you watch again to you, that's the next thing everyone's going to be focusing on
I think we're talking about that
And we're going to find out that we are royally, royally screwed
Gotta comment here, which was actually intended for no agenda
But I gotta tell you, we had such a good show, we did it on Saturday
I wanted to play this for you because I think this guy is right
In his analysis of why that show was working, which is basically just two old guys talking crap
Oh James, second time around it's Dan
New Yorker and Fort Lauderdale
And by the way, Dan, you got to call into the Charlie Moroff
And I love you, man
New Yorker and Fort Lauderdale was up Dan
In 1990, I know you guys are going to talk about the lady detained by the TSA
And for us to remove a nipple rings
Now, interestingly enough, we don't talk about newsworthy stuff like that
Dan, in fact, we tried to stay away from the stupid shit that everyone
I'm sure they talked about that on Twitter
Now, that's not what we talk about
But what I really wanted to say, although John is amazing
And he's wonderful person too
He's different to listen to with Adam is talking with him
Adam is a catalyst in the whole dynamic changes
And everything and everyone both you guys become better
So, to listen to Adam and John on Tificate
And talk about the days of your and whatever else
That you guys want to comment on is very interesting
But it's different than listening to the daily source code
Or text five
Or even John's occasional clips onto it
No agenda is more dynamic
Because the ingredients match well together
Something to do with that you guys screw in your own juices
And it's very savory
Dan out
No more hope you win, Bonnie
Alright baby, thank you
Don't tell me you were from Brooklyn
Because I got to feeling, you know what I'm saying?
Dan from former New Yorker
Living in Fort Lauderdale
In exile, I'm sure
I agree with you
I totally agree, I've been analyzing this
Actually, you know, and if you listen to the daily source code
Give that show a listen, will you please?
Will it kill you to listen to it?
A particular last one, which was episode number 24
By the way, if you think you're hearing bells in the background
It's not its birds birds because the sun just broke through
And they're waking up in their saints
Springtime, yes, we set our clocks forward, we're ready
Um, we really do a lot of work on the show
Without actually doing any work on the show
So while we don't do any preparation
Except maybe individual preparation
You know, it's like, oh, I'll bring this go
It's just like, I'm calling the guy, right?
And we've been doing this during the week anyway
And at one point, you know, I just say, hey man
We had these great conversations
Maybe we should consider recording him
And just putting them out as a show
So, but we really think a lot about the format of the show
Which, of course, there is none, but the timing of the show
And actually we left you with a cliffhanger on Friday show
And we'll see how we handle that next week
But it says quite an interesting experiment
And I really, yeah, I really enjoy doing that
Emiel Calloff sends me a tweet here on Twitter
And he says, yeah, it's not money backed with gold
Yeah, so that of course is the premise
Is that the money the central banks print
Is secured against gold
Well, that went away many, many years ago, my friend
It is
Who's someone here saying the Bank of England is wholly owned by the state
I don't think so
Pretty sure that's not true
I could be wrong, but I'm doing a show
And I'm pontificating, so I got no time to check that out
Graham Shaw
Of course, I got a lot of comments about Friday show
As I discussed, Fittna
The movie
And I wanted to point out some things that
To me, we're pretty obvious, but I don't think
They're coming through just looking at some random
Postings around the net
The main reason, first of all, I wanted to discuss this
And the issues that are plaguing the Netherlands
And in other countries as well in the United Kingdom
These issues are also starting to bubble up
Is because I don't hear people talking about it
You don't hear people speaking their minds freely
And saying what they, what they really think
Because they're afraid of being labeled a racist
Everything from a racist to a nationalist to a Nazi
And I think that the Daily Source Coach
To be a no PC zone, okay?
No political correctness, no condemnation
All right, so if someone has an issue and they have a problem
Like in the Netherlands, I think this was the point of this movie
It was not meant to shock
I think it was meant to show the disfads satisfaction
With the incumbent indigenous peoples of the Netherlands
About what's happened to their country
It was more a strong message to the government
Of course, if completely responded inappropriately
And I can't imagine they're actually missing the point
But it seems like they are
You know, they're defending this
Is saying, you know, week, we condemn this hate of Islam
And I don't think the movie was about that
I think the movie was about saying hey, look, here's what's happening
In our country
And I did that with a number of newspaper articles
And as a large majority of people
Maybe it's not a majority
I think that needs to be found out as well
But I believe it's a majority, a silent majority
Who are really worried about their own culture
In this non-immigration country
Please remember, the Netherlands is a little bit different
Than most European countries
Because of its size and population density
I believe it is the second most densely populated country
On earth after Japan
Maybe after China
But it's in the top five, I'm quite sure
It's a little pimple of a country
And there's 16 million people living there
Most of this country is underwater
It wasn't even above ground until the 50s and 60s
And that's where people are living now
Literally they reclaimed land
And built on a huge cities
Literally in the poles
And the culture has changed dramatically
Not just with becoming a member of the European Union
Giving up their sovereign funds as the gilder
And moving to the euro
But also just in general the way politics have worked
And the concept of integrating a multicultural society
I just don't think people are ready for it
But now everyone's worried
And I see this happening everywhere
Things that people say in private
Amongst a couple of people or maybe a group
Well, well, well vetted out to make sure you don't piss off anyone
Who's in the group
It's very different from the political correctness that people are
That's coming out of people's mouths
In public
Certainly in mainstream media
So if this media that we're doing is worth anything
If it's worth any shit at all
It's got to be that we can have a conversation
Without people going off the handle and yelling about racism
And not seeism and anti-anythingism
Okay, so we're going to keep this a politically correct free zone
Because it's really important
We can just talk amongst each ourselves
And not immediately get a label slapped on
Okay, because that is just not productive
And as long as people are just talking
I think it's a relatively safe
Oh, James, second time around
It's Dan
Oh, sorry, wrong one I meant this one
Hello, Adam Curry in the Charlie
Billion here from the mildly affluent suburb of Irving Texas
Known as law coiners
I had started to leave you a message earlier at him
But got cut off, my basic point is
And I'd love to have you bring this up on the Charlie and on no agenda
It's just seeming like more and more people in the US
And I'm not sure how this is working out in Europe now
Just absolutely cannot, cannot factor, cannot mitigate, cannot determine
Risk in their lives
And you know, the heightened sense of terror that we have
is part of the problem
But it's also, you know, with people's ability to eat
Appropriately to exercise
Just it seems like every single thing we do in our lives
We're just not factoring the balance
Correctly anymore
And we're unbelievably frightened by something
You know the airport security
Or dying in a plane crash
And yet at the same time, you know
Everybody gets on a major highway every day
Even though traffic fatalities are
One of the top killers
And it's just one of those things
It's got me sociologically
Interspot is there a phenomena there
Has that changed in 50 years
Maybe it's all the same
Anyways, I'd love you know homo
Great hair, hope you win
And let's keep talking man
It's good stuff
It keeps the dialogue open
We've got a lot of everybody know that
The world's got to change one day to time
Thank you
Absolutely, thank you
I'm just trying to expose everyone to as many things as possible that I find interesting
At least you look, I'm not forcing you to listen to this show
So that's exactly the point
I guarantee you in today's newspapers
You'll read about a business yet
Where two people died tragic
Particularly because they were well known, famous people
But you did not know unless you're listening to this show
About the French president
Calling for a strong new brotherhood between France
And the United Kingdom
Which can affect millions of people
And talking about forces in war areas
I mean it's a lot going on, you know
So yeah, it's the same thing
It's all the part of the same thing
Like I'm really afraid to fly it
Yeah, I'll drive on the highway and nothing's wrong
It's like my daughter, it's like it is teenage or attitude
She doesn't like flying with it
Not particularly if she can avoid it
She's like flying it all, she's afraid
Understandably so she's grown up with all kinds of disaster movies
And all kinds of great coverage of crashes and air disasters
This is a show in every single night here
Which is called air crash investigation
You can always can't avoid it when you're flipping through the channels
Yet she can't wait to jump in her car and drive around
The A3
Where the average speed is 70 miles an hour, 60 miles an hour
You know, and I think I know better
By the way, for people who say that the Bank of England is state owned
That's the history
The federal reserve was also
Initially funded 20% of it was funded by the United States government
Of course the other 80% was put in by commercial banks
But the way they did that is this fractional lending
So by law a bank can lend out 10 times more
Then it actually has
Got it
So they got the 20% from the government
And then lent that out 10 times over to other banks
Who then turned around and put that right back in
And said, here's our contribution
It's a great scam
It makes me want to get into banking, I'm telling
Let's see some more comments over
I think fit in other movie and stuff that people were looking at over the weekend
Hi Adam, this is Justin
Two things maybe to watch this week
And the first one I think was money masters or something like that
I think I saw a movie similar to that
Basically what I talked about was
Money or a rather sea out currency equal debt
After seeing that movie I thought
I need to go by gold because if I'm not wrong
Isn't gold inflation proof?
Well that's a well inflation proof
It depends on how you define inflation
But gold is of course very valuable right now
A thousand dollars more over a thousand dollars of Troy ounce
And this always happens when there is
And there are fluctuations
Or inflation in the market
Or risk of inflation people run to gold because
Fuck everyone else does
I don't know
I'm not the hell
Where's the nylon when you need him
I wonder if the nylon still has a job actually
And is that why we all need to buy gold
Is so that we can be free from
Inflation
And then the other movie you told us to go watch
Was over on a live leak
I think
I don't know how to pronounce this
Feet no
Feet no?
So I went over to live leak
And I said oh we had to take the movie down because we were going to
Frate we were going to get
Kill death threats
Whatever
So I went over to a good friends at Pirate Bay
I entered it
And I found it so I'm downloading it now
And hopefully I can watch it here in a couple minutes
Alright peace
Alright man
Very curious to see what you think of both of those
Yeah I saw they removed it from live like
Because they were getting threats
Yeah whatever
It's all just a conversation
First of all we can't be afraid
To just talk people
We should be able to speak our minds
Amongst ourselves
The freedom of speech is not number one
Everything forgets this political correctness
You just can't be afraid to offend people
So again here on the daily source code
You can't offend anyone
Okay it's a politically correct free zone
No one should feel offended
It's just words we're just talking
Just trying to figure stuff out
It's look I'm old
I'm going to be 44 in September
Now I got nothing left to prove
I trying to make this world a little better place
Trying to understand it
So I can pass some of that on to the next generation
Who I have to admit
Even though my daughter is creative
And brilliant and smart and beautiful
These kids
They had nothing looking forward to nothing
Not that there's nothing to look forward to
They got nothing that they're looking forward to
There's just some care
They just are
This is not good
Yeah we need to inspire them
We need to
We need to lead by example
Adam Jason from San Diego
I just
I'm calling as your bunch
So not drunk
But San Diego
Okay
You know I love people who call up drunk
Because they always tell the truth
I understand why initially
You played that
The video about multiculturalism
And Islam
Not being welcomed in
That's areas
Or the Netherlands
Yeah so
Let me just state some other thing
It's not about Islam
It's about immigration
You know what you could call
If in fact I believe the most Dutch people
If they're speaking openly and freely
They'll talk specifically about Moroccans
They feel that Moroccans are troublemakers
Not all Moroccans are muslims
And I think this
I think someone else is promoting the anti-Muslim agenda
I don't think that is necessarily the people
They just see Moroccans
And look
Of course it's not all Moroccans either
But they are guests in the country
In fact the Netherlands used to call immigrants guest workers
I don't know if that's still is used anywhere
And I think that they might have had some similar problems
In the past maybe with the English
When they came in lots of English word guest workers
And they would beat everyone up and get drunk
And mess up the bars
Yeah, so this is not new
And it used to be maluckers
And whenever there's a new group that's migrating
Into the country it causes issues
Because it's not an immigration country
It's not like the United States
Where what truly is a multicultural society
In my humble opinion
And there's so many entitlements
In the Netherlands being a socialist country
So many entitlements
That you get if you're out of work or sad or poor
Or incapacitated
Or for instance don't speak the language
And just might not want to do anything
Or also have nothing to look forward to
No immediate future
No culture that entices you to learn the language
Or follow the law
I mean this is all these little little things build up
And I think people get extremely frustrated with it
All right, backslash
I understand it now
The first time I heard it
I thought it was just rhetoric
Stupid, you know, racist rhetoric
I understand why you played it now
I don't see it as much as racist
However I do see it a bit like
Nationalism
You know
Anyway, that's just my two cents
Yeah, I can understand where the nationalism comes from
But again, we're not going to call each other names
Because nationalism immediately implies
Fascism or Nazism
And I think people are very proud of their country
You know, I can't make jokes about the Netherlands to my wife
I will from time to time
I'll say hey, how's that Holland's got no talent show
And she'll get really pissed off
She says, you know, don't talk about my fucking country that way
Okay, and she's proud of it
She's proud of being from Rotterdam
She's proud of the country
She doesn't want to live there
Because she doesn't like the way the government is managing things
She just doesn't like the way the place is being run
So that's why she's happy to not be there
But she loves the country
Does that make her a nationalist or just proud of her heritage?
That's the question
Nationalism for the Netherlands
I think that it's that it's one person's view of the Quran
You know, if somebody, if he could say that he read the Quran
Versus people telling them what it says
Me having read the Quran or at least a large portion of it
Having read the Torah, having read the Bible
Because those very interested in religious crap
I understand that all these religions have a fundamental goal
Which is life
And like you say passion
They all have that fundamentally
They all have some small parts of violence
They all have it
They all have some negative aspects towards women
But you know what?
They all talk about how it is important to love their neighbour
And respect each other
So I'm going to leave it that day
Before I continue on and sound stupid
No way man, not at all
And also we should make it a
Charlie a religion free zone
This is not about religion
That is probably what the Bush administration wants you to think
Because that plays well into their war on terror
Plans
It's not about religion
It's about immigration
It's about adhering to the written laws
And yes, yes
In some ways to the cultural laws of a country
Some things are just not done
Here in the UK
Even languages
Things
You can't say
Certain things
If I were to say
Bloody, some bloody messed up
That's actually
Consider a lot worse than the UK
Than it sounds in the US
And the use of certain words
Which I won't even repeat here
Like the C word
Is used in common conversation all the time
All the time the Charlie uniform November 10
You know
You don't use that in the US at all
Ever
Not even guys amongst each other
We'll use that
But here in a small group
People will use that word easily
It's
That's quite amazing to me
So anyway, so when you have immigration
We have migration of any form
And by the way, war causes migration
There's a lot of Iraqis living in Western Europe right now
I think probably 2 million at least fled the country
And drove by the way
It's not that hard to drive from Iraq
To further west or wind up in Holland
If you want to
These are
Refugees
Not Muslims
The refugees
Okay
And that's another point of contention
The way refugees are handled
In these small countries
That are not immigration based
So there's a lot of stuff that we can talk about
And I'm just kind of spouting here at the hip
Coming in on Twitter
Seemless slavery says Adam
Same here in Belgium with the Moroccans
Again, that's a generalization
But it is an immigrated group that is immigrated
And there seems to be issues
Then I think probably people are not happy with the government
Is addressing them
If I read anything
What really seems to piss people off
Is when you have these enclaves of
Anti-social behavior
Let's just call it that
And the elected officials
Of the government go and
And hang out with religious leaders
And drink tea and talk about integration
Yeah, no
It's like that's just not the way it works
The people of countries, all countries
Are held
Almost as slaves by taxes, by laws
And you look over to the left
And you say, wait a minute
These guys
They come in here, they get all these entitlements
If they break stuff
Or if the kids are causing the ruckus
Then the kids aren't thrown in jail
Like my kids would be that seems like they're getting different treatment
That's and whether it's true or not
That is the perception
And at the end of the day, perception is reality
One more
Amy will call off
It's not just the kids
They lack upbringing
They just happen to be Moroccan
They should go after the parents
Absolutely
Go after the parents
They do that in for
In other countries
They're starting to think of doing a lot of that
Here in the UK
With these anti-social behavior kids
I mean
All right, I need a break for a second
This is on the pod save music network
Which I kind of dig
Because I know you're going to recognize
The song from the MacBook Air commercials
Check it out
And you so I came to this train
World open
I could learn a bit about how to give and take
But since I came here
Felt a joy and I'll fear
Biting myself making every possible mistake
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
I'll teach hate, try to come and eat, hate, fight, you trust and love is not always easy to make
This is a happy end, cause you don't understand
Everything you have done, why's everything so wrong?
This is a happy end, come and give me your hand, I'll take you far away
I'm a new soul, I can't get this great world hoping I could learn a bit about how to give and stay
But since I came here, felt the joy on the field finding myself making every possible mistake
When we're all alone, we're not alone, nothing's very straight away
I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone
You're alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone, yeah
I really liked that model you know, the way this was set up
So first it's far as I know, first there was a commercial for the MacBook Air
And then so the artists makes their money.
And then they release it anywhere and everywhere.
Just go enjoy it.
That's a great model.
I really like it.
Not a lot of room to do that
and that every commercial will work that way.
But wow.
Y'all nagging, I think as I pronounced the name of that young lady,
new soul and it's on the pod save music network.
Of course, links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Just following up on the tweet,
see Miss Leavery says easy for the populist to blame.
One ethnic group, especially if that group
is not trying to integrate absolutely Jamaican in New York.
The kids everywhere are starting to lack up,
bringing the same thing as going on in Jamaica.
Well, that also is an issue.
Although I think that is an issue.
You know, there's a look at the United Kingdom.
All the kids are drinking themselves to death.
I'd say that's an issue right there.
Before I forget today's episode is brought to you
by Acute.com.
I have a feeling that as we move closer
through this non-religion, non-political correctness zone,
I might want to think about some life insurance.
So I'm going to call them myself.
I can get up to 70% discount on life insurance.
You can go to acute.com slash DSC to get your incredible discount.
Or you can call a US and this is for US resident only, US phone number.
1-800-410-7214 and then over thought
I'll be selling life insurance, huh?
I love that.
All right, everybody.
No show tomorrow because I will be doing
Mucho Plento meetings in the city.
So of course, I'll be back for the hump day edition.
Thank you all very much for listening
on the live stream at live365.com.
Everyone stayed on.
It's like no one dropped off.
It's cool.
And perhaps perhaps we should be taking phone calls
in the near future.
So I'm pretty much set up for it.
So whatever you do today for the rest of your day,
if you're winding it down or for it's tomorrow
and you live in Australia, live your life with passion
and enjoy your freedom.