Delta Shere Charly, 8-0-5
$60 billion worth of airplanes trapped by us
To the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need lots of digging trees
I like to think I'm flying into the future
I'm casting his allegory
A long distance, direct me assistance
And I'll control you
To say, hey, Moses, Mr. Millewon
He said hello with me on hold
Said he's the cat who has come to sit
To call us, child who call you
I think I'm outnumbered
I've seen that guy in the world
To call us
I'm extremely firm a friend of a pre-U
Said he's the truth with you
To meet your loving stator
You just have to do
Hey, I said
To you relate to a Cat attract him
And he know the bank for funds in the new
He said lol
Don't call us To help him
Call you
All you boys
Yeah, it's a slacker, jump on the door
We went, we cut a heat, I'm gonna try to be it
With the sun, we said it could be you
And then we pulled the legs and the shoulders
To the upper end of the street
We got the signature coins and lousy joins
And all the glitter we can use
My myself, who called us, that will call you
We got the signature coins and lousy joins
We made it just more than we thought
So listen, can you pay more than call
And we went, that will be all for all
We got the signature coins and lousy joins
So it's my become the new mantra for our politicians
Don't call us, we'll call you
Three, two, one, two, one, two, three
You can count on it
Coming you on all of it
Everybody, hi, do, then he chose code
Episode eight, zero five we've got
Australia, Energy and Corridor
Obama, the officer of the president
elect the bail out of the economy
Deadly vaccines and of course the climate
What else do you expect after I haven't been, uh, been with you for, uh, what is it now?
Uh, what was the last time we had to show? Like Tuesday, Wednesday, uh, crap.
It is Tuesday here in the United Kingdom. It's the 18th of November, 2008, everybody.
It is, uh, daily source code. I've been rummaging through the source code drop for the past.
At least the past two hours. Um, I think I went back as far as nine pages, so I wouldn't miss a single song, a single link, a single YouTube video.
I could actually spend most of my day going, just keeping up with the stuff you guys are posting.
It's outrageous, but a fantastic companion to this program.
So a little update. Let's see what's going on.
Of course, I was in New York for a week.
Uh, I had hope that I would be able to eat out another show, at least make a two show week last week, didn't happen.
Um, most of the day was spent, um, up and down, Madison Avenue.
And a couple other spots, not all advertising in New York isn't just an unmatis nav,
but obviously, in fact, very little of it is these days.
It seems as that business has changed towards media buying agencies, having all the money and the creative agencies having none of the money.
But I have to say, very positive.
Um, we've got to some new sales guys.
Uh, we were in New York with, um, my partner and co-founder Ron Bloom, uh, who is now chairman of me,
uh, Jeff Carp, Jeff Carp is our brand new CEO.
I don't even think we've done a press release about this yet.
We've been just so incredibly busy.
This guy came in from electronic arts and he's been going full steam with us, uh,
since the minute he put foot in the door.
Uh, when I'm planning on doing his interviewing him for the source code.
And, uh, so you can get to know him a little bit better.
Because I do spend a lot of my time there.
And if you're, you know, if you're like me, I guess,
that I haven't been able to do as many shows as I'd like to recently.
Then, uh, this guy's, uh, partially to blame.
At least he, he knows, uh, he knows a lot of things that, uh, that I don't.
And he's going to be a real, uh, real asset to the organization.
Uh, so, uh, that kind of wraps up the, uh, the past almost eight weeks on the road.
Um, spend, you know, going back and forth from time to time.
But essentially spent in San Francisco, Los Angeles in New York.
And now, of course, with six weeks left until we have to be out of here,
we've, uh, got this place checked off the list and the new one,
which I don't even have a name for yet.
I'm thinking of, uh, maybe the curry terrace,
since it's, uh, a terrace house.
As we're moving into the actual city away from the affluent suburb of Surrey,
known as Gilford.
And I'm very excited about it, which, you know, of course it means another reboot.
We can go through these periodically.
Um, and in the next six weeks,
I have to essentially decide what I'm going to keep and what I'm going to toss out.
And tomorrow, Patricia and I are going to the, um,
uh, to the storage place.
When we moved to the UK, we had tons and tons of storage.
I pay rent for my shit.
Or I'm sorry.
It's called stuff.
Someone else might view it as shit.
Uh, so we're going to have to, I mean, we got to bite the bullet.
I mean, I, I really, I haven't, I had this conversation with Patricia yesterday.
So I have all this stuff, which, of course, she calls shit.
And a lot of it is, you know, um, ranging from, you know, my, my first laptops and computers.
I mean, not all of it.
Obviously, but, you know, I, I like to carry stuff around some papers, some books, some documents.
You know, things that I would think would, if I had the Adam Curry library,
it would be of values, uh, someday.
And Patricia says, no, no, don't get the shit.
Don't care about your stuff or your shit.
Just throw it out.
And she's probably right.
I mean, I've lived without it for four years.
I haven't looked at it once.
So, you know, what I don't know about.
I, I guess I can't really miss, but I know I'm going to go through these boxes.
I'm going to see stuff.
I'm going to be like, oh, it hurts so much.
So what I am going to do is I'm going to minimize on equipment.
I have so much equipment that I've assembled here in the attic.
And essentially, I'm using very little of it.
I always want to have all the right wires and plugs and
processors and compressors and whatever it is for any project that might pop up.
But honestly, I mean, I've really, we have one small Patricia will come up with an idea and
that I'll need to rewire stuff.
But I'm, I'm really rethinking the whole office, rethinking the way I want to do it.
I want to go very minimalist on the actual production stuff.
I'm going to finally get a proper 18 inch rack.
I'm going to install the stuff that I absolutely want to have available in that rack.
And then it's just going to be monitors wall to wall.
I'm running all kinds of cool stuff.
But this is going to be a lot of work over the next six, six weeks.
Patricia, of course, is still working on her show pop stars in an Netherlands.
So, you know, that means it's going to come down to me.
Me and the teenager, the 18 year old, we'll see how much she wants to help out.
But it's exciting.
And I guess we'll just document some of that along the way.
I mean, think about it.
All this, all this nasty shit that I have to get into,
like setting up the postal mail forward.
You know, new banking office.
All of the, just so many changes telephone internet,
although I do have to get my order for virgin media in ASAP.
I want some of that badass cable bandwidth.
I'm going to get DSL.
I'm going to get cable.
I'm going to get everything I can.
Because I'm so, so tired of the, you know,
literally the 1.1 megabit down,
300 kilobit upload that I've had to deal with for the past two years.
And this particular location, finally getting into London,
should give me some actual,
yeah, actual throughput, which will be how it may not be nice.
And I want to set up a green screen in the new studio.
It's going to be cool.
I got the ground floor right next to the kitchen.
You know, it's, it's, I'm very excited.
It really is, it's going to be awesome.
It's just that moving thing.
That, that doesn't excite me at all.
So, let's see.
As I said earlier, today we're going to handle a lot of different topics.
There's no way I can make a short show out of it.
I'm sorry.
There's just too much to talk about and too much to highlight.
Too much stuff coming out in real mainstream news.
It is different than most people believe,
and we're just sitting around like sheep will not do
in a single thing about it.
So, time to kick some cans.
Hi Adam, it's Matt from Gamesweasel.
With the recession kicking in and everyone's staying at home.
What better past time to keep you entertained than playing video games?
So, this week I'll give you role playing game Fallout 3.
Swing into action with Spider-Man Web of Shadows.
The brand new Mortal Kombat vs DC Universe comic book based around the game.
And you come in copies of XEDS for the DS.
That's all it gamesweasel.com.
Before I forget, we have a new sponsor across the media network,
which is this thing called Rovio.
I don't know if you've seen it yet.
Actually, one is in my name at the San Francisco office,
but it's been captured and has been taken down
for doing daily segments or, you know,
they're actually using it in video production.
This Rovio is a four-wheeled robotic device
that has a webcam microphone and speaker built into it.
You can control and Wi-Fi.
You can control it from anywhere in the world through the web interface.
And I believe that I also have an Apple iPhone
or iPod Touch applications.
So, you can also essentially remote control this
from wherever you are in the world as long as you have a net access.
And you can talk to people on the other end.
You can hear what they're saying.
You can, you know, you'll see the picture of where it's driving
through the webcam.
This thing is absolutely stunning.
It's only a couple hundred bucks.
And I want you to, if you're interested in this,
go to the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Crossposts at acccurry.com.
And check out one of the segments.
I think Nick did down in the basement studios
in San Francisco headquarters of the Rovio.
I believe the website is meetrovio.com.
It's a fantastic device.
I mean, mainly jealous that I have not received mine here in the UK,
because boy, I got some ideas on how to play with that puppy.
So, in the show, it's check out that video.
You will not be disappointed.
Okay, a couple things I'm selected under the header of they.
As in they, they don't like it.
They are doing this.
They work for us.
A couple of people started sending me stuff about
the social worker system where the child protection system,
I should say, actually.
And of course, we've discussed a little bit about how my previous radio show
in the Netherlands was abruptly canceled.
Coincidentally, after I started to unearth some of the highest people in the
justice system throughout the Benalox being involved in,
I have to say, allegedly being involved in a child pornography.
And so, you know, I think this is pretty rampant.
Oh, I know what I forgot to look up.
Something came out earlier today.
Let me see.
Let me see if I can find it.
This is about the Isle of Jersey.
Oh, man.
Isle of Jersey.
All of a sudden, this is so funny.
Shit, I don't have that link.
All of a sudden, there was reporting that, oh, there were no children
tortured, no sex taking place with, with minors.
That bunker down there, those bones.
No, those are just animal bones.
That's not any, no, no human remains down there.
After they replaced the chief of police, you know, judges been switched around.
And I literally get email from people saying, hey, you've got to correct yourself.
It says right here in the news that it's not true.
Oh, please, please, please, please, please, please.
This one comes from the Daily Mail.
Now, you know me, I've got nothing against porn.
But when you read this, you got to be pretty concerned.
Your senior social workers responsible for child protection are at the center of a computer
porn investigation.
It is understood that the men all managers with dev in the social services.
This is here in the United Kingdom, of course.
We're suspended last month over allegations of, quote,
inappropriate material on their office PCs.
None of the allegations has thought to involve illegal images,
but the police have not been called in.
Well, of course, they haven't been called in.
Why would they actually investigate their buddies, their friends?
Demincounsel refused to name the men, which, of course,
whenever someone else is accused of illegal pornography,
they're immediately named in the newspaper.
Demincounny Council said, we have suspended some staff while an investigation takes place.
Internal investigation.
Of course, no police, no law enforcement called in.
This is the stuff that is running rampant throughout our society everywhere.
Even the Lima-Nata man called in from the Netherlands,
he's pretty pertubed about this kind of thing.
I was kind of angry on you for not being straightforward about the true reason
your radio show was discontinued.
As I was convinced that the only real reason you had to leave,
arrow was misademic.
Well, so now you know, but it wasn't directly that way.
It always goes through finance years,
and the money supply gets cut off if you don't shut up.
And so I decided to keep the honor to myself.
And I said, that's all right.
You don't want me to do a show like this,
even though you asked me to do exactly this,
then I'll just stop in the story.
It's remarkable the only party's who questioned on him
and has representatives who were young math and later we'll listen.
So what he's talking about now is Dutch politicians.
This is about the Secretary General of Justice in the Netherlands,
who is deeply involved and is not being investigated
at all and is being protected.
They both now hold the record for the quickest ever answer questions
and at least media exposure.
Well, in the media, well, this is being ridiculous.
Almost every single thing he says, he now got no attention.
Well, as usual, his discretion seriously matters.
So this is a politician who is perceived to be right,
very right-wing, builders, and he's calling this stuff out.
And of course, when you tell the truth the first thing that happens
you get ridiculed.
You're a cook.
You're not job.
You're a wacky sound familiar?
The best end episodes of the DSC.
I had kind of shorts, shorts, shorts, shorts,
or a shirt with in my mind.
Yeah, I can tell.
In the item, the story of your life,
I hate your first birth crossing on national radio in the Netherlands.
You were replacing Barcelona.
The next episode of this item told you were hanging out with the developer.
The song Animal was played.
It's video clip was recorded in the very north of North Holland at Circus Holiday.
Later that Circus became a mobile KGB office
with a couple of joints, but that are irrelevant anecdotes.
Yeah, I like it.
It's video clip of Animal.
Showed Barton Lava, his partner.
Any normalish alcoholic.
Oh, I mean, this is interesting stuff.
So now he's referring to Raymond soundtrack of your life,
where Raymond Ray on the Charlie has been,
had been, he kind of ran on a material,
but he was doing nice little historical pieces on my life.
And so indeed, Def Lepard did their video,
the music video for Animal,
they recorded in the Vistlord Studios in Hilversum in the Netherlands.
That's where they recorded their hysteria album.
So the video clip in the Netherlands.
And so now you're telling about the guy I replaced on the radio,
his partner.
Was it known alcoholic?
This is new to me.
Night after night, I was amazed how a person can control a car,
but so much alcohol.
So one night, I took the shot conceit.
Then I was told that in the days of the Veronica radio show
has for the cut, the killer of Andrea Lutter was hammered
with paranormal forces until he would confess.
They received a confession on their secret phone line.
I was mentioning him.
He had knowledge, which only the committee of the crime would know.
Okay, I get it.
So there was another radio, this is crazy.
I don't know how, only people in the Netherlands really understand all this.
I think with all these names, but anyway.
So the guy that I replaced on the radio, he had a different radio show.
It was like a paranormal kind of invite crazy people,
cookie people to speak to the dead.
And so apparently they got a confession out of a guy
who committed a murder.
And I guess it was an offense against a child.
I presume.
And I tried to file the confession, the confession.
The police said, admitting a crime is not criminal,
and therefore they could not file it.
It's amazing that you have a dead corpse,
forensic and all the infestigation teams on the case.
While the local police claims they have no case.
Even when doing serious attempts on higher level,
there was no way to testify about this confession.
And we never heard it in the media.
Meanwhile, but from the other way, it's part of the diet,
of kind of the natural region.
And I guess the other person who received this confession seems to be
to me, silence down.
But if you think the media silence,
what do you think about all lawyers are being tapped by default?
And on one single lawyer, they're to stand up and protest against that.
It's sick.
And indeed, the next to be tapped by default,
where does you lose?
Exactly.
If you have nothing to hide, you don't need to be afraid.
So you're talking about phone tapped. Oh, yeah.
Absolutely. Well, the Netherlands is the worst
because they have a professional judge system
and they don't work with a jury, a trial jury.
So the judge basically decides, and from time to time,
they put lawyers in as judges.
It's kind of a rotating system.
If you want a favorable outcome,
then what you need to do is you need to hire
the law firm of the judge that is presiding.
And it's crazy the way that works.
Sorry, yeah.
So if you're point there,
limonata, if your point was that the whole system
is pretty much infiltrated with corrupt people,
then point well made and taken,
because that's exactly what it is.
I mean, just consider that one out of every 100 people
is completely psychopathic.
I mean, that's thinkable, right?
One percent, I think that makes sense.
Now if they find each other,
and one of them starts off decades ago
working in the justice system,
wherever you are on the total pull right down
to the feet on the street, the cops,
all the way up to the Secretary General of Justice,
the highest level of office.
And if you don't think that this doesn't go
to royal families in certainly well documented
Belgian royal family, Dutch royal family,
the British royal family, to the White House,
you should Google Lawrence King and George Bush.
Senior.
Now this is, this stuff is taking place
and they're protecting each other
and I'm standing by it.
Some some great secrecy going on.
This has been brought up on a couple of shows.
The first time I heard about it,
was just before and during the last,
this week in tech that I did with John C. Dvorak,
and I think we've talked about it
and I know agenda as well.
I put a link to this story about actor.
This is the, let me see with the acronym stands for,
the anti counterfitting trade agreement,
which is apparently pretty much worldwide,
although I believe it might exclude China,
it may be all about China.
That's the whole point is we don't know.
Title of this article, EU Council refuses to release
secret actor documents.
So the council of the European Union,
which, yeah, you can say that they are elected
because they're elected officials in their own countries,
but I didn't elect any of the other council members.
We only elect the one that represents your country.
So it's kind of like a Starfleet command.
And then our refusing to release secret anti counterfitting
trade agreement documents.
Oh, this is from the freedom,
the free freedom information infrastructure,
which is a foundation.
They request these documents on the Freedom of Information Act,
of course, and they're not receiving it.
And the question is why,
well, there's a couple of questions.
Why are these being hidden?
Does that not go against the entire grain of a democracy?
And why is no one angry about it?
Why are we not paying attention to these things?
We should be calling our ministers of parliament.
In Europe, call your minister of European,
you know, it's really easy.
You can find their names, their email addresses, their phone numbers,
and they do respond.
And if you want me to call them up and put them on the spot,
not a problem, then tell me who you want me to call
and set it up and we'll do it.
We should be getting answers to this.
I think I have to, now that probably not until the new year,
but when we roll into 2009,
and we'll have more time during the day
to actually create shows.
I'm just going to have to do it.
I've got to put more people on the spot.
We've got to get answers because if anything,
the general populace is not doing it.
We're not calling anyone to the table and saying,
hey, this is bullshit.
Now, of course, we're talking a lot more about stuff,
just like that as we move on to Australia
and the bailout and the economy in general.
But notable, notable.
And I'm really confused about this,
mainly because of his position as a member of the Royal Family,
Prince Charles, who just turned 60 the other day
and had there was a fantastic show on here
on television, kind of like a comedy variety show
to a celebrated 60th birthday,
which was hilarious.
Robin Williams did a great set.
I recorded it, so maybe I'll play a piece for you
in a future episode.
But he keeps coming out saying all these things
that I really agreed with,
like genetically modified food is horrible.
It's going to kill us.
I mean, these are the things he's literally saying.
And now, I've put a link from,
what is this, the Guardian,
about critics who are now saying, hey,
this Prince Charles, he's got to be carefully
can't be saying too much stuff
because according to, I guess,
Republican law, which I'm not quite sure
how that works over here,
once he's the monarch,
once he's the king,
which he, I don't know,
doesn't seem like that's any short-term plan still,
his mama's hanging in, just fine.
Then he needs to shut up about all these issues.
And I'm like, well, then don't let him become king
because the guy's actually saying
some pretty good stuff.
He's coming out against,
really against a lot of different issues
and as far as I can tell,
I'm totally on his side.
Check this article out and give me some feedback
by leaving on the drop, which is drop.io slash daily source code.
Because he's,
yeah, there's something about the guy that,
that I like.
And please don't go suggesting I call him,
that might be a little bit difficult.
Hold on.
Although you never know,
he's the resources of the chucklehead.
Just test.
This is hit that number of 147.
Right on.
And we're going to start right away
to show number one.
Wow.
It sounds weird,
but it's like,
some pop to my head is building a bridge to your heart.
Two.
Uh, that's, uh, Alice and Moye,
they all cried out.
I think the first one,
wax, maybe building a bridge to your heart.
I, I really couldn't catch the first one.
That was Alice and Moye,
they all cried out.
No, that for sure.
And this is number three.
Chuck,感,
I feel for you just took a,
justМC,
Chuck can,
Chuck can't let me rush.
I'm not too thin,
this week the answer for all from
Pentagon.
And this is answering number one.
This is Arcadia.
Oh yeah.
A lucky day.
Wow!
That's a good one, y'all. Totally missed it.
Also, not a big fan.
Durand Durand, well, sort of, Arcadia.
As answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
This is Brian Farrow's shift, and a lot of them.
Two down.
Sounded just like it though, didn't it?
Can't believe I got that one.
Slave to love Brian Farrow's answer number two.
And this is answer number three.
I feel for you.
This is Shaka Khan.
And this is answer number three.
Shaka Khan, I feel for you.
And this is a Bluetooth number one, four, seven.
So, Adam.
Yeah.
How did you do?
Well, disappointing actually.
I thought I would at least get the last two.
I'm going to messed up on Brian Farrow there.
So, one out of three, that's two stars on a possible six.
I stock young.
Yeah, you should play to find the answers to this hit test.
And then the older hit test, by the way.
And also, the iTunes link, so you can buy the tricks.
Featured in the hit test online is as always hittest.medio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Thank you for listening.
Next week.
I hope to be back for another hit test.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And try to remember.
Think with your heart.
Bye-bye.
See back, hittest.medio.com.
info young.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-D-T-A-S-G-O.
Now, last week on the hittest, John mentioned that he had the new version of SoundBite,
which I used as a cart machine in my productions.
And he said the new version had all these new features.
And I checked to have the latest version.
Yeah, I'm not quite sure what the new features are.
You know, if they baked a MIDI controller into that thing, yeah.
Or at least the ability to read a MIDI controller to communicate with one,
and that would be a big feature.
So I'm not quite sure what the new features are.
Damn.
I was so convinced.
Now, of course, I got to play Alice and Maria all all all cried out.
I'll play that on the upcoming episode.
Maybe tomorrow, although Patricia's got me.
First, as I said, at the storage.
And then after that, we have to go to IKEA because, you know,
she loves getting some of these articles,
which I usually wind up having to put together.
That's exactly my favorite.
In the meantime, why don't we go head down under?
As we continue to talk about what's going on in Australia.
Of course, the economic crisis has hit there as well.
But a lot of interesting alternative energy coming out of Australia.
And I'm quite excited about that.
It is the impetus for me to really think about doing a trip down under in 2009.
Probably I would want to do that.
I guess when is it start to get colder?
Does it get colder around July?
Is that really when the winter sets in?
Because I was there once.
I can't remember if it was, maybe it was even earlier than that.
Maybe it was April or May.
And it got cold at night, man.
It was like freezing.
Of course, we were in the outback.
And that's another thing that doesn't compute.
You're sitting in a desert like dude.
Why is it freezing?
To help me out.
Chuckle heads down under.
Let's really put something together here.
And I want to hook up with people who are making these magnetic engines.
And that's really what I want to do.
So it's a big country.
Help steer me in the right direction.
And I'm noticing some other things we're talking about porn from down under,
which just kind of came up in passing conversation.
It does happen from time to time on this show.
And I'm seeing that there's a very interesting pornography culture in the land of Oz.
Just looking at the, first of all, the lack of real Australian pornographic websites.
I seem to be kind of getting the same three or four from everybody.
But also, they really like their own natural vibe.
And masturbation for some reason.
Here's an email from Daas from Melbourne.
Here's a bunch of Australian porn.
Even if not much of it is made its way to you.
I used to be a member of two of the following sites,
which is in large part all Australian content created by Australians,
even though they are marketed internationally.
And really, so it's I feel myself dot com.
I shot myself dot com, which is not of the, of the gun kind,
but of the photographic kind and beautiful agony, which is kind of funny.
But it's, it's interesting.
That it's, um, the Australians like real people,
not fake pumped up boom porn stars doing real people things,
which in honesty don't look all that good on film.
They just, you know, it's just not a good look.
But that's what you guys are into.
That's, that to me is very interesting.
Yeah, moreover, it seems like a very natural,
human desire or desire, a culture of desire that is going on in Australia.
And it's, uh, and check this out.
You'll enjoy this.
You know, now, of course, we're talking about the Australian government placing
filters at ISPs to filter out the bad pornography.
Well, it's certainly not homegrown unless you guys are all down there,
but the guys and girls, I should say.
Unless you're all vibing on US porn.
Let me know.
It seems like, uh, you know, just to be honest, you don't have to identify yourself.
Would please leave a message on the drop of voicemail.
That's pretty simple.
It shows you how to do it.
Go to drop.io slash daily source code.
Links are always in the show notes.
And, uh, you have to call the number then type in the pin code.
Leave a message or upload a MP3 file.
I don't care how you do it.
As long as there's some sound, so we can share it with the whole community.
And I don't wind up reading my whole inbox.
Let me know.
Are you watching Homegrown Australian porn?
Are you watching Asian porn?
Uh, let's figure this out.
It certainly seems like you're not making any of the stuff that we typically see here,
or in the United States.
Um, I've seen some British porn.
Ah, man.
Yeah.
I bet you the Brits really like their own, their own porn.
Anyway, there's a sex party in Australia, and they're taking their sex very seriously.
Let's listen to this video from, uh, over the past 20 years.
The sex party attitudes to sex and the sex industry.
This is Fiona Patton.
She's the Eros CEO and a Senate candidate in Australia.
Open up enormously.
Unfortunately, governments have not kept up with these changes.
They are still responding to pressure from minority religious groups and ignoring the rest of us.
We now have more censorship of adult entertainment.
Then we did two decades ago.
If you've had enough of waozorism and political interference in your bedroom, help us make a change,
and join the Australian sex party.
We're serious about sex.
Right on.
Good on you.
She's milky.
Yeah.
I'll endorse you.
Hmm.
I'm sure she sure there must be something else on the agenda of the sex party.
Let's just take a look at the link here.
Since we're all just kind of hanging out.
Uh, six party dot org dot AU.
Okay.
I'll gotta hate this bandwidth here.
It sucks.
We're serious about sex.
I'll have basically the same message there.
Okay.
Our policies, sexual rights, freedom of sexual speech, gender balance,
and outing sexual hypocrisy when we see it.
Yeah, right on.
Come on, man.
Shouldn't we be allowed to stick anything we want in any office in our body at any time in the privacy of our own home?
Shouldn't that be?
Didn't that just be your own private shit?
Or stuff?
If it's your, if it's yours, it's stuff.
It's stuff you're doing.
If you're doing it, it's shit you're doing.
Uh.
Interesting.
The beautiful Aggie and Agony dot com.
You should look at that.
It's pretty funny.
Um, okay.
So here's a comment from down under.
Want to make sure I get that in.
Hey Adam, it's full calling in from, uh,
Is it in Australia?
I feel compelled to call in after listening to a daily source.
Uh, you're angry with three.
I'm just trying to, it's global warming.
Um, a couple of callers called in about it.
You played some of their voicemails.
Yeah.
Let me before you go on, though.
The conversation as far as I'm concerned is no longer about.
Climate change versus global warming versus global cooling.
It's about finding an alternative energy source.
Because if we find alternative energy,
then we'll solve if you believe.
And that's fine.
If you believe that people are the are killing the earth.
We're killing people killing ourselves.
That's for sure.
But if you think our actions are killing the earth and the earth will not survive.
Uh, I'm, I'm pretty sure you're wrong there.
Uh, will it, it might make it uninhabitable for us.
But not just through CO2 through all kinds of shit.
We're putting in the air in the water.
And your government, by the way, is responsible for a lot of that.
But at the end of the day when it comes to fossil fuel,
it's just a dumb system because we're all in slave to it.
We're all in slave to oil.
And the energy elite who control it,
they can control it because we've become accustomed to having electricity and energy in different forms.
So if we can find different forms of energy, then we all win.
So I'm not really going to go back and talk about it,
but I'm happy to hear what you have to say.
To add a my own take on it.
So global warming is definitely here.
And you're giving the impression that it's not coming off.
It's a bit of a crackpot.
No, I am a crackpot.
A cook, another job.
That's what they always say about people who are actually telling the truth.
Uh, of course, now it's your word against mine because you're just saying,
it's here.
And I'm saying, it's not here.
And uh, show me the measurements and I'll show you my measurements.
Who can you believe, who can you trust?
Um, it sure doesn't feel much warmer here in the United Kingdom.
That's intended or not.
Yes, in some places is getting colder,
but in a lot of places is getting hotter.
So that's a good point.
Does that even out?
Does that strike you across each other off the list?
What is the ideal temperature for the earth?
I wouldn't mind it being a little bit warmer being here in Britain.
No problem.
A little bit of global warming is not going to kill me.
And maybe if you live in a Canada,
you may be happy if it's a little bit cooler.
Or less cooler, I should say.
warmer.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
But I'm not just taking it like that.
I'm happy to talk about it.
I'm happy to listen to all kinds of conversations.
But the minute it gets ramrotted down our throats into the CO2 carbon tax and credit system.
No.
Then I just got to stay stop on against it.
And wait around for someone to prove it.
They've already got the laws written for the shit.
And we're still discussing it over here.
Who's running this place?
Don't call us.
We'll call you.
And on average, the temperature is going on.
But I think every person missing the fundamental point,
which is, isn't man made or not.
Now, you mentioned the sun, you know, as a source of life well.
Well, all warmth comes from the sun.
End of story.
That's where it comes from.
Okay.
So if you got clouds formed by whatever you get less sun, you get less heat.
It's the sun.
The sun's being blocked.
It all comes from the sun.
Is it being man made?
Uh.
What happens is the sun was going through a period of cycle.
See, every million years where it got slightly hotter.
Well, actually, we just went through an 11-year cycle.
Where the sun spot activity stopped all together,
the month of October.
Uh, yeah, October.
Um, and that could kick up again.
You know, ham radio operators know this.
We used to do something that was generated by the ionosphere,
uh, particular due to sun spot activity.
And we would utilize something called skip.
We could bounce your signal halfway across the globe.
This is, this is not new.
Of course, the sun is responsible for all one thunder.
Which makes the air sense lightly hotter.
You know, there's no human record that goes on.
And the Earth, by the way, is not a G.E. light bulb.
It's a bunch of explosive gases that, uh, you know, it's doing shit all the time.
It's, it's a living organism.
It's, uh, it's spewing off a regular heat.
That's just what it is.
Uh, far back.
So the fundamental question still stands is is global warming.
Our climate change caused by burning up fossil fuels.
And the whole introduction of this carbon credit is based on no evidence to say
that the change in the climate and global warming is because of what we're doing to it.
It's bullshit.
Um, I just want to pass that on.
Uh, also, well, one of your coming to Sydney, let this Sydney listeners know.
So we can, you know, set up a meet and greet.
Um, great here.
Hope you went.
Um, and that, yeah, we can, can you stop things for cities?
But all those President, you know, what happened to, you know, some love, like the
prostate cancer prevention course.
Uh, anyway, they are supposed to work for us.
Right on well, then I suggest that you help me out my friend.
Uh, I need lots of Australian porn stars helping me find Australian energy, alternative forms of energy.
So, uh, we could have some fun with that.
with that could we just not just have a meet and greet come on let's have some people
come out we've got a stand for a by the way do you guys actually have a freedom of expression
and freedom of speech in Australia it shouldn't sound like it and the same thing happening
here in the United Kingdom but seems like they're a little bit further down the road there
in Australia and I look at these sites man this is like adult people doing adult stuff
what and it's nothing illegal as far as I can tell so let's get some of those get me the
the woman from the sex party can I talk to her can you reach out to her will have some fun
yeah I definitely want to come down but let's not just let's not throw anything away in a meet and
greet let's actually get something done I want to visit these guys who are making these these alternative
engines with magnets and and and Joe sells and hydroxy based hydrogen things you know this is
the stuff we got to look into we've got to bring it to the forefront we've got to make
YouTube videos I guess and post them far and wide and and try and professionalize a little bit
because I think it was just taken as seriously you know it's another bunch of cooks in the garage
doing some crazy shit and it doesn't work now that stuff works
tough to us chuckle heads but there's more of us looking at the stats ever since and I know that
you're bummed out man we don't talk about porn enough but I'm trying to up the quotient
the numbers have almost doubled on this show it's absolutely astounding how many people are
tuning in and from so many different corners of the earth. Adam high Lars here in Kansas City and I
just dropped a song called Revolution Sun by an artist named David Zooming from Kansas City as well
and man I think this is gonna fit in great with your show I think it says it all it's a
but it is a song hope so give it a spin and please please stay stoned first take of Revolution Sun
this is the question that I want to ask you have you heard the coming call the disaster
yeah it's clean the trouble coming fast now for a reason that it's telling you
it did the feeling that they want to throw us we best see and only play
photos they keep you secret and they're gunning for more trust don't seem right
it ain't what we do to the rave of a new Johnson it's shining down on everyone shining down on
everyone shining down on every home yeah it's clearly and it's coming faster
what will you do on the morning after we got a father put you calling us faster it's
why do you curse us when it isn't for the rave of a new Johnson it's shining down on everyone
don't you say
Red blood, Red blood, Red blood, Red blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock White blood, Rock
Oh, yeah, it's clear the end is coming fast
What we do, home morning after
We got to find the books you call on the best
What do you curse when it isn't true?
Yeah, right on man, I like that Revolution Sun
On a daily source code episode number eight hundred and five moving into our president electing the United States
President Obama and what better way to get started then
With our European Union correspondent
Comic strip
No, you see as me come on in
Hello, I'm Obama my carry
You see as be your EU correspondent
So EU has reopened talks with Russia
Despite objection from Lithuania
And Poland has withdrawn its objections about it
Yeah, that's that is indeed quite interesting
And I am keeping my eye on that
And I appreciate you doing the same there CSB by the way
Yesterday
Oh man
Yesterday I saw that CNBC was in Russia
Aaron Burnett
Oh man, I love this girl
Aaron Burnett was in Russia
And she was trying on
Free hats in a hat store
And she's so cute
I told Patricia yesterday I said
Because you know I think most couples have a list
If you don't you need to institute one
Just as a hedge it's really important you never know
I said I mean you want I'm taking Angelina Jolie off the list
I'm replacing her with Aaron Burnett
And Patricia said interesting choice
Anyway that was my sorry
Just I drifted away into Russia for second CSB sorry
So Silvio even Silvio Belusconi
The just President of Italy you know he likes to joke
Even invited Russia to join EU
But Russia declined
But personally I have to say that I want to see Russia as a full member of EU too
And by the way good luck to your daughter Kristina
In her acting career
You
What's that?
People were happy
Are you glad that Barack is there?
I am very very glad that Barack Obama won
I have no idea what that is
Under the end
Thank you CSB
Well yes
Keep in my eye on this
Because you know it's so easy to become distracted
Or just tune out or zone out
I think that's what's happening
I've seen two videos
One is the 60 minutes piece
That was a sit down interview with the President elect
And the second is the weekly address
Which is getting
Actually a lot less attention
than I thought it was getting
You know how the President does a weekly radio address
Which I subscribe to you can find it in my channels
Go to Adam.mevio.com
And you can actually subscribe to
With one subscription you can subscribe to every single show I listen to
Well that's need to hear no or there
So the Presidential radio address is always one of them
I just have to laugh because I think oftentimes
It's like Donna just this kind of an afterthought
Oh yeah we got to the radio address
But a lot of people actually listen to that
So now Obama is doing the his weekly address
He's putting it on change.gov
Which by the way
The agenda has still
Not been put back into place
Remember the entire Obama agenda was scrubbed off of the website
Uh-huh
There's a little article from the
Washington Times that put in the show notes about that
But this YouTube video
So you know what?
Cheapsville
Frick and Cheapsville
It does not pay attention
And what they're doing
Because there is a lot of
There's a lot of people out here on the interwebs
Pay attention to stuff
And you know so I guess we kind of let it slide
Yeah, all right so change.gov
Change the agenda's been it's not even a menu item anymore
They've taken it all fall together
Which is always suspicious
Although you can still pretty much find the same
Information but not always the full detail plans at Barack Obama.com
I saved all those pages and I'm so happy I did
I want to be able to refer back to them from time to time
But the video is just cheese
And when will the
I love I love the signage
It still says the office of the president elect
It's it made up
It doesn't exist. There's no such thing
He's still a I guess still a senator
That's it
But anyway
So everyone wants him to come out and say some
And okay, I think we all pretty much realize
No one can fix the jam that we're in
But he keeps it is basically what he's saying
Well, it's not going to be easy
He's not saying anything
He's not giving us any insights
Into what is policy is in fact
I thought it was pretty insulting
When the interviewer on the 60 minutes
Was trying to you know
Ask questions about his cabinet
And would he actually appoint Hillary Clinton
And you know, instead of some diplomatic answer
Like, well, you know, I have to live and finalize
And I want to talk to everyone and weigh all my options
Instead, the president elect is saying
You're not going to get that out of me
You're not getting more out of me
You're not getting anything out of me
That was that didn't feel right
Doesn't feel right to a
A Georgia congressman
I saved this link earlier
This is from November 10
Quote, it may sound a bit crazy
Enough base, but the thing is he's the one who proposed this
National Security Force representative Paul Braun
Instead of a bond, I'll buy my day interview Monday
With the associated press
I'm just trying to bring attention to fact that we may
May not, I hope not
But we may have a problem with that type of philosophy
Or radical socialism or Marxism
Hmm
So some people, someone's speaking up
That's good
Not that anything's being done with it
It's being completely ignored
Ah, let's see, where is it?
So I made a whole bunch of notes
About the CBS interview
Now links in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com
And crosspost it at curie.com
So just some, and I'm not going to run through the whole thing
It's like 18 or 19 minutes, but just some notes
First of all, this piece is heavily edited
It's funny, Christina's not hanging out with Dexter a lot
Dexter has a little production company
And he does, I don't want to say which show he does
He edits one of those paranormal shows
That's on television
And Christina is saying it's amazing, you know
He suits all this footage and it's kind of lame
But then he starts taking out all the shit
The guy got wrong and then he's actually replacing words
Where someone said no, he puts in the word yes
And of course that's the way television works
That's show business, that's entertainment
And it's no different for news
I became a profit center
It used to be a huge loss leader
Doing investigative journalism, sending reporters on the road for weeks
To get a story, they don't do that anymore
Just read press releases and pieces even come in
Pre-package video already edited
So this piece has been heavily edited
The first thing on the present elects
Mine slash agenda is national security
And this is about this, and this is frightening
I would have to agree
The president elect has already called for a national security force
That means living amongst us that are equal in size
And equally well funded as the armed forces
That's going to be a lot of hardware walking around
So national security first frightens me
Then the economy, okay
Then energy and health care
When asked if he's in sync with the
Secretary of the Treasury's actions
President elect Obama did not answer the question
He just said, well he's worked tirelessly
More about that in a minute
Dennis Cassini had a great quote for a Neil Cushkari
Which is a Paulson's little butt boy there
Running around doing his dirty work
But yeah, sure
Paulson's been working very hard to give his buddy bonuses
And remember that Obama took money from Wall Street
So he can't just all of a sudden become the enemy
Just like he can't become the enemy of the unions
He took millions from the unions
Like the United Auto Workers Union
And so he's totally if they don't get a bail out
From the current administration he's going to bail him out
This is just how it works
So no surprise
But of course
President elect Obama says, well you know things could be a lot worse
So I guess something that Paulson is doing is working
But he didn't really say if he wasn't sync with him or not
And then of course
Came the whole the bail out discussion about the auto industry
And why he pulled out the bridge to nowhere
Thing with another fun little quick
You know I want to build a bridge to somewhere
But he's still campaigning you already got the job man
You know now speak to us like normal people
I'm ready for it
And then he goes into this whole wrap about
Well the banks aren't lending yeah, but you think that what Hank Paulson is doing is he's working hard
Making it work well it's not working
It's complete contradiction
Anyway, where's all this money come we're going to come
I'm just distilling this whole interview for you
It's worth it so when asked the question where the money for the bail out would come from
And the president elect said we're not going to worry about the deficit
So in other words it's going to take it either from taxes or it's going to print it
He promises to shut down going Guantanamo Bay
Promise is to stop torture Iraq he says as soon as he takes office
The plan will be executed to draw down troops from Iraq and send them to Afghanistan
Don't you see and no one's complaining of oh, yeah, well Afghanistan
Yeah, that's the yeah, we should be there. That's the right place to be yeah put our troops know of good
Is that why?
Tell me why we should be in Afghanistan besides to protect the poppy fields of the US government can truck it into the US
Bin Laden's not there
If he's alive, which is highly questionable
I got a link in the show notes about that in that you'll find it right right in the Obama heading
Plenty of data points that could lead you to believe that Osama bin Laden does not even it's not even alive anymore
So yeah, how many troops it was the plan all right, so we're taking our troops out of Iraq sending them to Afghanistan
So we're not actually bringing them home
Stamp out al Qaeda still high on the president elects agenda
Well, I think we should identify what al Qaeda is instead of what it really is which is just a list of names that the US government put together
Capturing bin Laden the critical aspect of that he's the operational leader who's planning attacks on US targets actively panning and planning attacks. It's what he said they're planning attacks. I should we better put our security alert to high
And then what really really makes me laugh is now he's talking about Lincoln
And I believe that's because Lincoln was known for having Republicans and Democrats in his cabinet
But the real cool thing about Clint about to Lincoln is first of all Hillary Clinton also said she's been reading up on Lincoln
How interesting is that
But Lincoln and this is the reason why I believe he was ultimately assassinated by the by the banking cartel is he came up with a whole concept of greenbacks
Which was money handed out by the government and it was not did not involve the central banks
And it was really a beautiful system and to this day we still talk about greenbacks
Although that we don't really know the history of it go read up on the green the wiki pd has a reasonable page about the greenback
Read up on that and then you'll see why it's highly likely that president Lincoln was assassinated
For that being one of the one of the reasons is that he just didn't want to play with the bankers
Okay, into the bailout now I have put a whole crap load of YouTube clips into into this section which you'll see in the show notes
Because it is so phenomenal to see that on mainstream on television a lot of it's from C span
But it's now being a sniped and clipped and edited and put out there is the empirical proof by admission
That this bank bailout of
700 billion dollars which was the official number even though there's another two trillion on that which was lent out by the federal reserve which they refused to report who they lent it out to your money
My money they're refusing because of course we all know by now that they're handing it out to their buddies their buddies are taking huge bonuses
And Congress thank God some members are
Starting to get really annoyed by this
And they're starting to call these guys on it so here is I just got to play a couple of these for you
Let's see
Which one is this
Okay, this is this is actually the what's his name. I like this guy. He's the the ticker guy ticker tape guy
Whatever's name is so he he actually had a little I couldn't find this YouTube clip but I'm going to play it for you because he played the audio of it as well
And this is one of these congressional hearings. I know it sounds really boring and you know G why should we watch that but here's the you're going to love this this is actual admission
That 350 billion dollars of the 700 billion dollar bailout was actually intended for foreign investors
Not even for United States citizens or corporations here listen to
Questioning you'll test carry. Yeah, here we go. Listen to this.
Just to send it wasn't in the meeting where Secretary Paulson came in with the vice president and Fed Chairman Bernankey
And made all these assurances that there was absolutely a critical immediate need to get rid of the corrosive derivative products
You know this is this is how they went into the into the Congress into the Senate and threatened everybody that if you know the world is going to come crashing down
We're all going to die if we don't start put it this money and immediately we've got to buy these toxic assets
And of course now they're not doing that anymore
And listen to this bit all the different names for this and you know ubiquitous, you know
Sub S retraided credit default swap blah blah blah blah blah
Okay, but they they talked about them as though they knew what the hell they were
You got the money and you immediately said what items what auction
Would you please respond to under oath
When did you go from what you did what you told members of Congress in open and closed sessions was the absolute reason to have this money immediately to buy a specific group of assets about
350 billion in the US about 350 billion held by other countries and and other funds outside the US
So they even knew when they passed this bill they knew
That half of the money was to bail out foreigners there's they're meeting it
This guy may be all heavy handed on cash carry and on Paulson, but same time he's incriminating himself
Here's Elijah Cummings. He had a nice little quote for Neil Cushkari
You'll hold this Mr. Cash carry
In the neighborhood I grew up in and it's a cash cash carry. I should say this Elijah Cummings
Representative he's a Democrat from Maryland 7th district city of Baltimore
One of the things that you tried to do was make sure that you were not considered a chump
And what chump meant was that you didn't want to see when people see you as just somebody they could get over on
And I'm just wondering
How you feel about an AIG
Given five hundred and three million dollars worth of bonuses
Out of one hand
And except in a hundred and fifty four be in
From hard working taxpayers
You know because I'm trying to get I'm trying to make sure you get it
You know I mean they got a shot of a space here. He's going like oh, you'll you'll think I'll go through all
And you know what would really bothers me
Is because all these other people who will land up yep
They say well this guy's good. This Elijah Cummings all I can is cash carry a chump a
Chump we can just go in there and I'm not saying they are I don't know
We can go in there
We'll get to money and you know what AIG did they even will tell you they coming back for some more
And they have the nerve
The nerve to grant some five hundred and three million dollars worth of bonuses
Oh, man
I mean this is out in the open
How can you not be outraged by this I am
Call your congressman look him up look up your senators
If they voted for this bailout package you need to send them a very clear message
And if they didn't you need to send them an equally clear message
There'll be a lot less of you sending that message by the way
And support them and say good on you people need positive reinforcement as well
You know don't just sit there listening to your fricking eye pod listen to me bitch about it do something about it already
You gotta do something about it we have a representative government take them out take them out if they're not doing what what they should be doing take them out
By voting obviously not suggesting anything else
Here's another great great quote. This may be Kushin it's Kushin it's Kushin it's
Oh, no, this is coming again
Thank you for the opportunity to be here today
Just to Mr. Cummings
I don't know how to work any harder than we're already working and I take your feedback very seriously
That's why we're working as hard as we are and we're just going to keep doing and trying to accomplish and meet your expectations
Thank you very much if I may
Take the bragged best chair to stay out of the anyone
Questions Mr. Kushin
That you're working hard
Talk question
You're working for oh
Beautiful you won't see that on the news who you're working for I love it
There's a whole there's a couple more I'm not going to play them all for you there is one one great link which you should read through
It's a titled who is hand who is Henry Paulson and we see this guy's history. It's no wonder the a in fact
He's been in government before here. Paulson rose to the ranks of Goldman Sachs becoming a partner 82 co-head of investment banking in 1990 and
Chief operating officer 94 in 1998 he forced out his co-chairman John Coursine who is now governor and New Jersey in what amounted to a coup according to New York Times
And where is this this is great piece here?
There were questions at one point because there's a whole bunch of guys
Here we go Goldman Sachs is perhaps the single best connected Wall Street firm. It's executives returned routinely go in and out of top government post
Coursine went on to become US a senator from New Jersey and it's now states governor exactly
Coursine's predecessor Stephen Friedman served in the Bush administration as an assistant to the president for economic policy and as chairman of the National Economic Council
Friedman's predecessor as Goldman Sach CEO Robert Rubin
served as chairman of the National Economic Council later treasuries secretary under bill Clinton these guys are all over at the banks have taken over and now we're going to make it legal
America has been given 100 days to comply with what Europe is setting up the IMF will be in the middle of it all go look at what the G20 talked about what the news they released over the weekend it's all on the drop you can all find it in show notes and it drop drop dot AOS slash daily source code
IMF which is another group of private bankers they're going to sit in the middle of it and here come the CO2 credits you watch on their way
Let's see and just the long actually this kind of leads into the economy in general but American Express which of course we know is a credit card company
Most people would notice a credit card company is now become a bank so they can also receive money from their buddy Paulson
And the meantime had the foreclosure slow down has been easier to get alone for a car purchase
How's your business doing this is the stuff we need to be looking at
Tens of thousands of people being laid off sometimes on a daily basis
And we're going to go out and we're going to bail out the auto industry
Hi, I would like to suggest an automobile industry bailout package that will result millions of dollars being spent on high price tookters sushi bars and trips to Vegas
This is how it work.
Well, it sounds kind of boring.
We go to Bernie Frank and say, Bernie how much money is available for bailout he says 50 million dollars or whatever
Next, using the same process that is used to determine who may receive an economic stimulus check
We determine who may receive a certificate for a brand new car
Now when you receive your certificate you go to a Ford Chrysler or General Motors dealership look around pick out a car you like
And over your certificate you go home with a brand new car
The dealer he collects payment from the government
You know, and that could be negotiated
Maybe cost of the car plus 10% whatever
The salesman gets paid
The dealership gets paid
Automobile manufacturer gets paid
Everybody wins on this except for maybe the high price sugars
So think about this
Suggested to your congressman and now I'm driving 11 year old car and I can really use a new one
Thank you
You know, it's really sad to me that this is the kind of thinking that's going on the United States because
The sooner we realize that someone has to get hurt from this economic downturn
Let me just call it that and the better
Because
Something has to go something has to budge
And right now it seems like the only people actually about to get hurt is going to be the middle class
Whether it's directly through taxes
Because someone has to pay for these bailouts
I mean it's just not free money
Yes, it's free in the regard that you can print it
But then you get it back in inflation and the prices reflected it at the grocery store
So there is no for that as I say there is no free lunch
And it's time for someone to step up
I mean the way I see the auto industry
Yeah, are you kidding me this thing is far reaching it is a huge part of the economy
But it's failing now anyway
And that's a mindset we're in this mindset that we're killing the earth
We need to consume less. Okay, we're good little slaves we're doing our job
And now it's we're going to because we're doing our job and being good little slaves and buying less crap and being less less of a consumerist
Which of course is exactly not what the government wants since our entire economy
Revolves around consumers buying stuff and borrowing money to buy it
Now we're going to be penalized on top of that no with taxes or inflation. Oh, that's not what should happen
Let the auto industry fail
I definitely think we should honor the pensions
I'm not quite sure how much money that is it's clearly going to be billions, but
Take care of the pensioners. So we'll split the difference. You know what there's new car companies
There's tons of them give them incentives let them take over in the marketplace
They're still
Manufacturers who are non unionized who are doing okay. There's Japanese manufacturing going on in the United States of Japanese vehicles
It's not like the entire auto industry is dead
And we'll have new cars
Within a year we'll have new new businesses and people can go to work at these new businesses
Well, I've fact reads that the new car companies can
Can roll into
I don't you know there's a million different thing go buy the assets of Ford Ford Mondale
Whatever it's called in the States great drivers car built the keep that as the chassis now put your battery shit on there
And your windmill and whatever else is going to drive these things there's tons of things we can do tons
Bailing out
Not the option I'm looking for
Not a good idea
Several months ago it seems actually maybe it was a year ago I sent a note to Jeff Smith the Jeff Smith and I said Jeff dude
These lyrics are floating around Wall Street
It's to the tune of Bohemian Rhapsody
I really think it'll be funny if you if you cut this track
And I of course we played a lot of it a year ago a year ago when all this crap started to hit the fan and it's just as current today
Is this the real price
Is this just fantasy
Financial landslide
No escape from reality
Open your eyes
Look up at your buys and see
I'm now a boy
Hailing casualty
Cause I bought it high
Watched it blow
Rating high
Now you'll know
Any way the thing
Cause doesn't really matter to me
To me
Mama
Just killed my friend
Could it sitios instead
Pulled the trigger now it's damn
Mama
I had just begun
These sitios have blown it all away
I still want to buy
Sometimes we should never let go of it all
I see a little silly way to open
Keep it a kid
Can you say the old market
I know the new is very very funny
Super senior
Super Senior
Super Junior
Super senior
So you think you could find me and spit in my eye?
Then the bottom and call me and leave me a time.
Oh baby, can't do this to me baby.
Just got it out, just got it right out of here.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
No price really matters, no liquidity, nothing really matters.
No price really matters to me.
The Jeff Smith Financial Rhapsody.
Thank you, darling.
My lovely wife just brought me up.
This is an official club sandwich.
Hold on, let us tomato bacon, that sounds like a BLT.
Thank you, darling.
There you go.
This is actually something really good.
But again, it just frightens me to read how we're thinking.
This is about the Aspire Visa card and you can find this link is from consumeraffairs.com.
What Aspire essentially is doing is closing out a lot of its accounts shortening the or tightening the credit lines.
And so this is a page of consumer complaints.
And when you read this, people don't understand that the complaining about debt that is being slowly closed down on them,
exactly the right thing to do.
It makes so much sense.
You should not be complaining about Aspire Visa, maybe going out of business or whatever, clearly they have financial reasons for closing down their lines of debt.
But you should be happy.
This is a message to you because they're telling you, hey, you know what, you should kind of look out with your behavior.
You can't just keep on using the credit card, save some money, save some money.
By stuff on lay-away if you have to.
I think Walmart is even doing that these days.
But you look at this page just complaint after complaint about, well, you know,
I was being closed down.
My credit rating is going to go be shit.
You know what?
You need to be closed down.
You really do and to and check yourself.
Take a look at what you're buying.
Seriously, there's no reason to be spending your money on shit.
And you know, and every single time I went shopping, I went shopping and then I've, you know,
and you see that great little piece of clothing you really, really want.
I can just put it on the card, it'll only be another 10 bucks a month.
So you get dragged into the hole that's 17% interest rates.
Stop it.
Please.
Yeah, I'm this is Hans from Canada here.
We're in Canada.
I'm calling in about the, but all that carbon dioxide stuff.
I know that you don't think that the climate is changing.
I still think we should have the smallest footprint, but that's all.
No, I do think the climate is changing.
I just don't think it's going into a Solomon Gamora like an inconvenient truth.
The least thing.
What's quite interesting though is that I'm reading up more and more about the carbon dollar.
And I just listen to the weather makers on an audiobook.
And even he talks about the carbon dollars, which is really interesting.
What baffles me is that the easiest way for the US to introduce the carbon dollars would have been to,
to accept the Kyoto protocol and they haven't so.
Well, this of course presumes that you think that the carbon credits,
they're not talking about carbon dollars, but about carbon credits.
This is because you assume that they're for good.
They're not.
They're there for their benefit.
That being the, the bankers and the rich families of the world, the true owners of the globe.
That's, if it was Kyoto, they would have no control over it.
Then it would be like a consensus.
Uh-huh.
No, no, no.
This is controlled.
This is set up by private bankers again.
I was setting up these, carbon credits, by the way, is great.
Because you just say, okay, this is how much carbon you could produce.
That's the finite resource, and then they can make that as expensive or cheap as they want.
It's much easier to manipulate than the actual currency.
So it's about carbon credits, not about carbon dollars, and they, in the United States, they,
being the people who run our politicians, clearly, who force them under dress,
to vote for the bailout for money in their pockets.
These guys, that's who one carbon credits.
They make it all run.
They run the show.
I'm not quite sure if that, if the carbon dollar is the master plan, why does the US not just simply
agree to the Kyoto protocol?
Because that would be the easiest and quickest way.
Anyways.
Um.
Alright.
You got something else here because you're repeating yourself now.
Yeah.
It's just gone completely out of hand with all the carbon stuff.
I guess I saw in London that you can even have your own, uh, carbon neutral, um,
offset, uh, mortgage from giraffe.
Yeah.
Right.
Everyone's jumping on the ban wagon.
Because whenever there's a trade of anything, and there's a, uh, a party in the middle,
they're taking some money off the top.
That's why it's, uh, it's hip.
It's like Nike shoes.
Got to have some carbon offset.
Even you said the beginning right there, the top of your comment.
Bro.
I don't know.
I got alarms all over the place.
What's going on?
I'm meeting.
Fuck it.
Um.
Even you said right at the top of your comment there, uh,
well, I think I should be reducing my, uh, my own footprint.
Bullshit.
Yeah.
We should not be burning fossil fuel.
It's unhealthy for us.
That's the whole point.
We're killing ourselves.
But it seems to be pretty much a managed process right now by the people who are controlling the energy.
I, yes.
Oil.
One of the true currencies of the earth.
I had this as Justin.
Um, daily source code number.
But it's eight zero four.
Once again, you're talking about oil, gold, and drugs.
And you know what?
I agree.
Mostly except one major detail.
Um, first you're saying it in the complete wrong order.
Because if you say in a slightly different order, one could argue,
there is a fourth tower pulling the strings.
Now, you know what?
I'm about to piss off a bunch of chuckle heads.
Uh, most of your people.
They're just listening.
So, um, please send me your hate mail.
It's back at last podcast.
But I read it when you say it as gold, oil, and drugs.
Yeah.
Right?
I mean, in my opinion, people will kill blindly for an all powerful man in the sky.
Yeah.
And they don't need anything in return except for the promise of what is it?
72, 73 virgins.
Or maybe by that's rising of the dead.
Um, or the rising after you die.
I don't know what it is.
Living forever.
But I do know that if you ascend the wrong religious groups,
they will kill you.
I don't know.
It's just what I'm thinking.
I love your show.
I don't know.
I love what he done with it.
Um, great hair.
Peace.
I do like that, though.
Because first of all, it isn't either the order.
If you look at, uh, valuable, uh, currency in order of appearance in world history.
Gold first, oil second.
And drugs.
Uh, drugs may have been early on.
Uh, who knows, but I do like the GOD acronym that's pretty funny.
Okay.
From now on, that's official true currencies.
The world, gold, oil, and drugs.
And fast food.
Of course.
Ah, great report.
If you ever go buy a burger anywhere, read this.
Haha.
Oh, from a study, American fast food is almost entirely produced from corn,
according to a chemical analysis of dishes served at McDonald's Burger King and Wendy's.
The study is published in the journal proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences,
whatever the hell that is.
Uh, using a stable isotope analysis of carbon and nitrogen to determine the origin,
molecules, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
It's pretty much all made out of corn.
Haha.
I have a hundred and sixty food products.
We purchased at Wendy's throughout the United States.
Not one item could be traced back to a non-corn source.
Now, you ever see, um, high fructose corn starch.
You know, that stuff, it makes you fat.
It makes you obese.
And if 98% of all the food you're consuming because you're using your credit card
and McDonald's is making you fat, here's your answer.
You need to, oh, this is a big argument here at the, at the curry manner.
You know, um, Patricia will always say, well, why can't people just make something healthy?
Because it's too expensive.
Go on and buy some vegetables.
You can't, they, they even have on television.
They, um, this is for, I think it's for Kentucky Fried Chicken.
Uh, I don't know if it was in the, I don't know where I saw the commercial.
But it's like, okay, let's go make our own Kentucky Fried Chicken and they go to the grocery store
and they get the chicken and the little girl says, do you have any magic sauce?
You know, whatever it is with a special sauce, the secret sauce.
And so they can't put it all together because it will be way too expensive.
It turns out the fast food, of course, is a lot cheaper.
But it's not really food.
Ah.
And the food banks are now, um, if you've never been to a food bank, go look your local food bank up.
And there's a pretty good article on the money central their MSN.com,
which is in the show now.
It's under the economy section for today's program.
Uh, a lot of people rely on these to actually survive.
41% more food distributed in October, 2008 than they did in October, 2007.
And it's pretty pretty normal people.
It may be even, you know, your neighbors or your colleague at work.
And there's stuff that you can donate to these food banks.
Money is, of course, the number one that will help the most.
But look at these, uh, different categories of foods.
And, you know, consider bringing a couple of those into your own home and keeping them for a while.
Because when the shit hits the fan, which is coming very, very close to my friends,
when it really hits the fan, you're going to want some food.
It'll be the most popular Christmas gift in 2012.
Right there, this is Matthew Ebel.
And you're about to hear a brand new song called Lost on Block Island.
It's a song that I wrote while I was out on Block Island, Rhode Island, all summer long in 2008.
Of course, if you like this song and you want to own it,
you can go over to MatthewEbel.net and sign up for a subscription there.
Of course, you better do it soon because this song's only going to be available for another month.
But there's plenty more where this came from.
I'll be sending out brand new songs every single month to the subscribers and only to the subscribers.
So please check it out and I hope you enjoy the song.
Again, Lost on Block Island.
Nine miles of dry, and that's all you see.
But somewhere between water, street, and the drugs I meet,
I lost my head and got caught in a current calling me out to the sea.
It's hard to find peace out on Block Island.
Said the peace you make, night ain't no lie.
Everywhere there's tourists talking at me, and it makes me want to cry.
Still I try, try, try, try.
Shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you, shout out to you.
Try to stay dry on Block Island.
Try like a mud slide at the door.
Well if I can just numb the pain with the room in the rain,
I just say I don't think that I can drink much more.
Can I get lost out on Block Island?
Can we get lost down our love?
Man, such a big fan of Matthew Evil.
Saul, this one's Eekin' Up The Charts and The Pods have Music Network.
Music.podshow.com.
Music.mevio.com.
And you can include it a handy little intro there.
Lost on Black Island, Matthew Evil on Daily Source Code.
Episode 805.
I know I'm going to sound like a broken record, but I just got to once again lay into the vaccines.
And I want to break this down for you a little bit further than maybe I've done in the past.
Or maybe just summarize why I'm so adamant about telling people about what's going on with vaccinations.
Now the entire Western world has pretty much always laughed about the United States and their commercials on television.
You ask anyone from the Continental Europe or from the United Kingdom.
You say, how about this TV commercials for all those pills?
And the general consensus is, in America, they got a pill for everything.
You're not feeling well, you're not feeling right.
You're not feeling happy, you're dick-done work, you're dick-done work.
There's a pill for everything.
And that's our pharmaceutical industry.
And it works.
People have been taking all kinds of pills and medication for decades, which has been pushed on them by the legal pushers of the pharmaceutical industry.
Inclusion, of course, with government for regulation, deregulation, etc.
Luckily, though, and I've lived on the other side of the world for many of those decades, we live at that.
We sit here and go, party silly, freaky Americans, taking all your pills for all that chip.
So they were never really able to expand with their medication and their magic potions and all their problem solvers and mothers, little helpers, etc.
And I believe that what the pharmaceutical industry has now found out successfully is that the concept of a vaccination endorsed by the government is a very, very good
sales tool.
So they're coming up with vaccines for everything.
Now, of course, the motherload, the big one, is going to be for the avian bird flu.
All right.
Now, this is already in the President-elect's plans.
He's looking to make $4 billion available for preparedness for the avian bird flu.
I mean, Bush wasn't able to do it.
Clinton wasn't able to do it.
Maybe Barack Obama will be the President.
It can actually give the pharmaceutical industry what they really want, which is a massive scare for avian bird flu.
Oh, my gosh.
Von Trips disease.
We're all going to die.
Take this shot and it'll be all cleared up.
These guys that you're going to have in their annual reports, it's in their pipeline.
What they call it?
In the pipeline, they've got billions of dollars that they expect to make on vaccines against avian bird flu.
But, you know, there's a lot more to sell you in the meantime.
So the one that I hate the most, currently, is this Gartazil.
There's actually another similar vaccine called server acts, I believe.
And they supposedly, they prevent cervical cancer by injecting it into nine to 13-year-old
girls.
And this is just not proven.
And there's links in the show notes today.
Some links that have already put in there.
You know, it's the human papilloma virus vaccine fraud.
But Dr. James Hollenstein, you need to read that.
There's another link here.
I love this one.
This is a great one.
Australian scientists to unveil skin cancer vaccine.
Oh, it gets better, doesn't it?
Professor Ian Franza told the Sunday telegraph that test of vaccine animals had proven successful
and human trials could begin as soon as next year.
Oh, they want to get the shit on the market before the quarterly report, of course.
If we can get encouraging results, we'll try and push it on as fast as we can.
He told the paper.
Fraser, who would deliver his findings to the Australian Health and Medical Research Congress
on Monday said a skin cancer vaccine could be available in five to 10 years, although Middle
Data.
It would be used on children between ages 10 and 12 to prevent them from developing skin cancer,
a disease which causes some 1,600 deaths in Australia each year.
This is the same guy, by the way.
It's somewhere in here.
Yeah, is the same guy who helps invent, oh, this is fantastic.
The new vaccine, it says, would target a papaloma virus, a common infection that can turn abnormal cells
into cancer.
So now it's for skin cancers.
Well, it's the same guy.
Yeah, it says my entire career has been focused on understanding the interaction between
papaloma virus and the cancers.
This is so untested, so not right to be injecting this into our children.
I was, and more and more people are getting on to this about the flu vaccines.
Very good friend of mine, I had dinner with him in New York.
And I, you know, I was talking about the show and then I started kind of laying down,
you know, talking a little bit.
And then I said, I'm really, this is what really pisses me off against these vaccinations.
And he says, oh, man, his wife has MS.
And she insisted on getting a flu vaccination.
She has not walked without a cane since.
Since that.
She's a piece of audio I wanted to share with you.
This is from Lou Rockwell.
Because, you know, please, I'm, I'm not a medical doctor.
Don't take my word for it.
I'm just reading.
Okay.
I'm reading.
I'm listening.
I'm paying attention.
I want to spread this news on to you.
So we can actually save ourselves.
Yeah.
Listen to this.
This is the Lou Rockwell show.
This is good.
So great today to have us our guest, Dr. Donald Miller.
Don is a cardiac surgeon.
He's professor of surgery at the University of Washington at Seattle.
He's at Lou Rockwell.com columnist.
Take a look at his archive.
It's full of fascinating pieces on such things as fluoridation, AIDS,
and other revisionist topics.
But today I want to talk to him about his wonderful and important point about why you
should not get a flu shot.
Hey, Dr. Miller, tell us why.
Well, the flu shots don't work for most people.
And they're dangerous.
The evidence that the flu shots help this week and has been
discredited and the safety studies have not been carried out sufficiently.
So that there is evidence that after the first two or three weeks when the studies have stopped,
bad things can happen like Alzheimer's disease,
arthritis, and various serious allergies.
Yeah.
And I mean, there's a lot of horrible things.
Autism is being blamed for it.
And kids are dying.
They're absolutely dying from this.
You know, build up some resistance.
Of course, polio.
I think we got that one covered.
We got that one figured out.
There are obviously valid vaccinations that have worked for many centuries
before the pharmaceutical industry grew into what it is.
And it's like, alchemy that's being performed on our children.
And luckily there's a lot of parent groups working on this.
It's, you know, look around for it, Google it.
That was the girl's name was Mary to, uh,
What's her name now?
Just actress.
She was on MTV.
And her kid has autism.
And she's a big spokesperson for, uh,
against the flu vaccination.
Man the Tory.
By the way, if you want to put your kid into a kindergarten in New Jersey,
and that they cannot, that is, that is unconstitutional.
You, you should not have to force that onto your child to have your child
in kindergarten.
It's not true.
You should take them to court.
All right.
Well, I guess, uh, the next step is to start
D stripping the studio here.
Uh, as the move gets underway.
Uh, you'll be a part of it one way or the other.
And, you know, let's, let's just, let's just, let's just try and
stay a little bit sane and, and pay attention to what's going on
and watch watch our leaders and call them to the mat.
That's how we started.
Don't call us.
We'll call you because we should be calling them.
What are you doing?
Right?
How do you do?
What I'm doing?
What are you doing?
I'm doing everything.
What is you doing?
Whatוחat?
What are you doing?
Traveling again where I Could swim alone
Thank you very much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video
see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you on the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next one, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, these next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, there you on the next video..
That's just one of a couple songs in the pot set music network on that today.
Show a little bit of low-end your quartet bouquat bouquat, why?
Why not?
Well, there you go.
You know what?
You got kids?
Pay attention to them.
I mean, like really pay attention to them.
Observe their habits.
We're observed what they're doing, observe how they interact with technology and recognize
that your children are yet another level in sophistication in evolution of man, okay?
Inspire them to be creative, inspire them to be something beyond what they see on television,
let them read a book.
You know what?
I'm really not down when we look at all this stuff.
If we look at the bailouts and President-elect Obama and his promises and the economy
and the climate and the vaccines, it's, you know what?
Because I'm still allowed to make this show.
I'm still allowed to speak my mind and there's still a lot of people who are waking
up to the true reality and in general life is really beautiful.
It sounds kind of corny, but go out, you know, sniff the flowers for a change.
Right now, get out of your car, go walk, walk around the block, find a park, you'll
see what I mean.
So, enjoy that freedom, use it wisely and above all live your life with passion.
Another fine, medium presentation, stick it in your ear.