Critics say that Adam Curry is trying to brainwash us, but he's trying to get some message
across through some blinnable messages through his mind tricks or something and I just
don't see it.
I've gone back, I've analyzed older shows and I don't know, I went back to the San Seo
days when Adam would burp and say San Seo and we all kind of caught onto that.
Then he tells us how to make a great cup of coffee.
Pump that, that's like that bad boy up and down.
You pump it, you pump it, you pump it, and then all of a sudden it becomes frothy.
Then with Trinity, trying to get us into biofuels where you basically went, you got
vegetable oil and grease and stuff from a fast food restaurant.
Instead of pumping gas, you use the vegetable oil and you pump it, you pump it, you pump
it, then the fitness craze hit and of course with any Mac, he told us all to pump it,
you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, and now here we are trying
to prevent cancer in Adam's solution to that is to pump that, that's like that bad boy
up and down, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, you pump it, and then all of a sudden
becomes frothy.
So I don't see how the critics can say that Adam is trying to shove some message into
our head.
I mean, it's just ridiculous.
We'll see what new he is to say on the DSC 763.
We'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what
we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do,
we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what
we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we
will see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what we can do, we'll see what you can
Oh yeah, don't become the way in the game
I've come as often as I can to the end
You don't stop me, I don't come to the count
What do you want, seems so up to
But again, I know I'll go ahead and tell me you won't be a game
But I'll see that the old kid and I don't want any of my own friends
I used to go rock, this is a hole
They're not funny, stop smiling, still don't move
But the money, but now I've learned to earn
Because I'm right, dude, I feel free
To maybe I might do so four and nine and five
If I thrive, maybe I stay alive
So I'll walk up street with this feeling
Our place was manned by a mist
A pen and a paper, I stare with your taste
From me and everything in a nice big plate of this
Which is my favorite dish
But without the money, it's still a wish
To try to like scream about deep in any
So I dig it through the books of the vows that I made
So that's let's see if I got pulled
If I still be yo, cause I'm paining
Ah, looks like party band Taylor made it for this particular source code
Hey, bump on the door now
And that's right, we're pumping it, we're pumping it, we're pumping one out for frosting
Cancer prevention
Yeah, we know the pain
Oh man, if you love, I love the energy you put into those over as men
That's been so cool
It is the source code episode number 763 coming to you from the afloat of
aufs you yeah, effluen suburbowsori known as a ge offered everybody how you doing
It's good to be back apologies about Friday
But of course, I had four warned that I was doing the support for the lady Patricia for her final live show on
Holland's Got Talent which went off without a hitch and might say fantastic show
And we had a good time actually took us super region Keith along
Who hasn't been to Amsterdam or anywhere near, even in the Netherlands at all, for like
16 years or something. So it was funny having a big grit along for the ride. So when
who's very accustomed to BBC standards and practices and boy, that he have a good
time at the studios. So I think that's really how much to say about that, because just
you know, it was basically, I left on Thursday flew over. Oh man, it was horrible weather.
Just absolutely atrocious. So that meant all the fun of flying for me. And then at least
on the on the Dutch side, it was very, oh, so bad. When I was flying across the English
channel, the bad weather was right in the channel. And in fact, it started to come inland.
So somewhere around Canterbury, I started to hit some pretty awful conditions. And I was
talking to a manston approach. I don't know if his manston radar or manston approach at that
point, they did have radar contact with me. And I see, you know, they followed me all the
way to the boundary. And it was so nasty. And I was so happy that I had, you know, some radar
flight following so that he would know, you know, and alert me if any planes were in the
area. Which there weren't many actually heard people calling up big and hills saying, we're
returning due to bad weather. And as I signed off as, as the controller, manston released
me to talk to Amsterdam information. I said, I just couldn't help myself. I said, you know,
and by the way, major props to your boys with this shit in the 40s without GPS equipment.
Yes, we're proud of them. That was great. Anyway, it was nice because Christina was along
for for our little trip. So it was kind of a hangout. And she, of course, was her delightful
self being extremely funny. Crack an ass off. Then it's nice, man. When your kids like
funny in an adult way, not necessarily adult humor, but just your timing is impeccable. I love
it. So the racks are stacked today because I didn't get a football Friday out. So of course,
you know, that means that I have a hit test standing by and lots of comments regarding nylon from
762. In fact, I have stacked in the rack 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9 different responses. I have an idea
of what I'm going to do with them. But first, let's check in with something very important that
it's troubling many people and it's keeping quite a few of the chuckleheads busy.
Hey Adam, this is Hans from beautiful and sunny Niagara region. I'm just listening to the DSC
761, yes, I'm a little bit behind there and had to laugh from yards off when I heard,
oh, done. I'm going to guide talk about, about rubbing one off.
That was sales guy, you, who's who's Dutch, but in Germany yet, he really has a problem with me
talking about the prostate cancer prevention quota. Because whatever he's polishing the Pope,
or anything of the like, he says he has visuals of me, which of course is not the desired effect.
And ever since you've started this whole topic, it came to mind what happens to when we
actually have some fun with our ladies. It counts. It really does. There's no reason why it shouldn't
count. And in fact, your ladies can participate in cancer prevention of the breast kind
at the same time. In fact, there's things you can do together to kind of both be rubbing one out
for cancer. Do we release our clinicians into them? I know, this is the gross, but that is gross.
Yeah, do we just transpose our cancer prevention to them? What's going on there? Think about it,
do you think about what you can do together? Anyways, I saw that I pointed out
because I much rather do the little cancer prevention with, with me lady. Anyways,
28, 24 times. And I'm behind a normal grade here. Hope you win. Bye. Don't forget they work for us.
That's the final sign off that's new. Yeah, of course, what is referring to here is the news
that unless you've been living under a rock, you know that minimum of five times a week
severely reduces your chances of prostate cancer. So use that sucker while you got it, I'd say. And
since since most of you have been kind of bummed out about associating me with the procedure. Well,
luckily here's one of the, uh, child rescue. It's Terry again. Oh, Terry, how are this time? I'm chiming
in to lend a helping hand to sales guy Hup and remind all of you men to indulge yourselves in the
spirit of prostate cancer prevention and rub at least one out today for your health. Have fun. Bye.
Oh, very, thank you so much. I really hope to meet you in a bit of thyroid.
Oh, so she's networking. Yeah, that's right. It's all bullshit. And the ad bastards that
comfortable will tell you what's bullshit, what's real and also check us out on my team. Remember
Ad bastards, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip, comic strip,
you correspond that is here once again as name is commister blogger and he checks in with a report. Hello,
Adam shaved down under Terry. You slay me dude. You see, be your you corresponded. So you say it's
now complaining to what's greater organization WTO that European Union is putting to high taxes on tech products.
I didn't know about this. That's interesting. So European Union is putting high, uh, I guess
import duties on tech products. Mm. Yes, it is fucking crazy that Euro currency is much stronger than
dollar, but anyway, say one can get some products much cheaper. In fact, I can only recommend USA as a
tourist destination for just to go and buy stuff for all EU citizens. So just go there by yourself,
laptop or other electronics. And then just pretend that you had it on you before arrival. Easy
PC lemon squeezes. So go to USA young man. So thank you. Let's say for the can care for us EU citizens.
Yo. Okay, CSP. Well, I, you know, this ties into a lot of different things. But of course,
that I have to do with the currency exchange, but yeah, man. You know, the, the, the rumor is out there
that the new iPod 3G is coming out. And, uh, yeah, I'm very interested in that device. I mean,
use the iPod touch for a while. And I absolutely love the web browser. And I wouldn't mind, you know,
I think I'll finally switch over get a UK number. Put myself on the grid as it were. Unfortunately,
I have to do that, um, you know, in order to get any decent, uh, type of bandwidth package,
they don't do it. They don't, they don't, yeah, pre-paid is just not enough. I believe me, I've,
I've looked at all the options and you've sent me so many over the years. Um, but I may wait.
I may wait until I think third week of June, I'm going to be back in San Francisco,
and I'll probably pick one up there. And that is, of course, if it's even going to be
available worldwide when it's announced. Even if the June 9th day, it's true. Who the hell knows,
right? So as I said, we have plenty of responses to, uh, to nylon checking in after a yet a prolonged
period, still undercover under a pseudonym. And, uh, well, here's one reaction I want to play in full
because it's from atomic rod. And as you know, he works for us. And, um, he's always got something to say
about, uh, nuclear energy. Hey, Adam, atomic rod Adam's here. Just want to say thank you for your
comments about nuclear energy on the F.C. 762. Just wanted to share with a little Washington
moment here. It's a gorgeous sunny day in Washington, B.C. And, oh, by the way, the people in
Washington have the same feeling about one water as they do in London. If you pay my drift,
yo, yo, I agree with you about nylon, the man should come out from under the cover and tell
you who he is. I worked with my own name, tell you what I do, and try to share my, uh,
passion for nuclear energy. And one thing I want your chocolate to think about, who do you think
benefits when people are afraid of a proven alternative to fossil fuels? You know, I got a great day.
Yo, yo, I think so much. Remember, you work for us and he really does. And your comments
are always highly appreciated. A lot of comments about this. A lot of people saying, hey, you know,
it really is, um, you know, just a kind of an image that we have about nuclear energy. And, uh,
you know, these new pebble reactors are much, much safer. I've gotten, uh, you know, comments about
there being at least three atomic subs on the bottom of the ocean. And, you know, it hasn't killed
us yet, uh, even responses to my saying that, hey, you know, I'm sure the CDC, the Center for Disease
Control doesn't keep their virus as very safe. And, you know, so people checking and listening,
there's a lot of stuff. I could start a whole conspiracy website just space upon this.
But really, let's say, let's keep looking at this nuclear energy. Remember, we're
rebranding it at new clear, because it really is new. And it is clear. And I think it may be
safe enough to use looking at the UK Gordon Brown now coming out. Uh, he's got to do something, right?
And he's saying, you know, we have to be really aggressive here in the UK, because, you know,
this oil is not going to be sustainable for anyone. Uh, we're stuck with these high prices
for a while for the foreseeable future. We can't just wait for new reactors to come online by 2020.
We've got to get going now. We've got to push and push hard. We've got to have lots of extra
capacity coming. In fact, he even said, and I think I agree with this. He says, this is a tremendous
opportunity for the empire, because that's how sometimes they refer to it, the British empire.
Ah, it's nice ring to it, doesn't it? Hi, Adam. This is Eric from Portland.
I'm just going in. I've been listening for a long time, and there was a wired magazine article
about three years ago. And that turned me on to really the whole podcast thing. And in that
time, there's been three shows that really stood out. And they're all when, when you really
feel attacked and push back. And, you know, mentioned those, some old chuckle heads may
recognize them, but there was this guy, Mad, wineful Dean. Yeah, I remember that. Who accused you
a lot of things, uh, one of which was being a homo foe. And, um, I think he said the story's great
with him, like clearly. Um, another guy named Dave Winner. And, uh, I heard of him. He just
wanted to be famous, man. And I hear that guy sometimes another, uh, another podcast and man,
what a annoying guy. And now the nylon, he doesn't have quite the status of the last two, but
here you get, uh, up in arms and, uh, defend yourself, uh, good for you. And, uh, good for you.
Keep it up. Um, they work for us. Yo, don't forget that. Have never.
Yeah, no, I appreciate that. And, of course, I did let myself go. And I think even said it,
it's almost as good as sacks, you know, just letting go and yelling back at someone once in a while.
You know, particularly when someone with such BS, like, uh, like nylon, now I know he's listening.
And I'm, you know, he even called him with another comment, but I'm so tired of it. He's just,
you know, just repeating himself. So I'm not even going to play that. I will, however,
and I've been thinking, you know, I could play these back to back, but, you know, they're all,
they're all so nice and, which, of course, in its own way is self-serving. What I'm going to do is,
I'm just going to play, like, nine or 10 comments, just all through each other. Just so you can hear
all the love that just streaming out from the chuckle heads. There's nothing more that I can say.
Then thank you so much because, uh, it reminds me that, uh, you know, I'm not alone.
Does that make sense? Yeah. You know, and, and yeah, there's one guy who's, who's yelling at me,
but, um, you guys are there for me, and I really do appreciate it. Listen to this.
Adam, son of a bitch, just finished listening to that red and going back in.
MyCarl, you know, it's so easy, isn't it?
The white and it's easier.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know the kind of silhouette I felt when I was young
I don't know, or, you know, just not like that it was really the all the way around, that is something you better than, you know,
It's a funny heart that's smiling your eyes
It's slowly fading with the last days in July
The year is drowning like the calendar rose thin
And sail away against your back against the wind
And when the cold wind blows your gun
And I will hold my head again
But you can run from the truth
Oh, the light and red
Thanks to everybody, they have no idea how good that made me feel
As long as going out to the nightlight
Some of the beaches from my world
There's cold and weak
Don't press me flowers and the pages of the diary
You're cute, it's still filled with spotting sign
I mean a bit of a huge sleep
As a calendar of peace
And when the cold wind blows your gun
And I will hold my head again
But you can run from the truth
Oh, the light and red
Thanks to everybody, they have no idea how good that made me feel
As long as going out to the nightlight
Some of the beaches from my world
There's cold and red
Thanks to everybody, they have no idea how good that made me feel
As long as going out to the nightlight
And when the cold wind blows your gun
And I will hold my head again
We're the living, the London rain
There you go
All right, I think we should now close the chapter
That is known as the nylon
Because I'm pretty much done with them
Thanks again, everybody, that was awesome
I actually sounded pretty cool in years
Like a million voices all showing out at him
Since we missed the football Friday
We still need to extend some of the freight train
Maximum music extravagance of festivities
And this is the hit test
Hit it test
Young pole
Hey Adam, hi doing
Good, better late than every hour
This is intro number one
Oh, yes, oh, yes
I know this one
Damn
At the car wash
Haven't you done this one before?
You want to be done car wash?
That's Rose Royce
Of course anyone from the 70s would recognize that one
Number two
Another one from the soundtrack to my life
That is love unlimited
I'm so glad I'm a woman
That's it
Yeah, I'm a woman
And number three
I thought it wasn't a roll there
Uh, I give up on that one y'all
And it's time for the answers
Test
Answer
Number one
It's from 1977
This is Rose Royce
Power
Oh, I'll sing along
Sing along to the hits of the 70s
Everybody
Ooh, ooh, ooh, yeah
You might not ever hear me
It's for the end of car wash
Working in the car wash
Yeah
From a woman singing with me
Car wash
You're with the feeling I
Yeah, give me that
Rose, it's answer number one
Oh
And this is answer number two
Yes, yes
Love unlimited
And I'm so glad I'm a woman
That's it
In the morning when I wake up
As I call my head
So big
I'm a woman
I'm a train of
I know I want to make a
I'm so big
I'm a woman
Two out of three
Love unlimited
Answer number two
And this is answer number three
From 1987
Madonna
Oh, Madonna
You're mad
Causing a cushion
Baby
I know that you will be a great person
I've got to move right back
I'm done the motion
We got together with the cousin
Come on
Madonna
Causing the commotion
Number three
And that concludes this week's hit test
Number 124
So Adam, how did you do this week?
Well, I was pretty confident there
I got two out of three
And messed up on Madonna
But what can I say?
I tried it
Alrighty
Hit test.meepio.com
Is the place to find answers to the hit test
Also the items links
If you want to buy tricks
Featured on the hit test
Online
Adam
Thank you for playing again
Everyone else
Thank you for listening
Next week I'll be back for another hit test
So until then
Have a very nice week
Take care
And remember
Try to think with your hearts
Bye-bye
Be back
Hit test
Emile.com
Info
Young pull-up
Come
And be a wealthy team
Go
It's always as good on
It's almost like
Like leftover spaghetti
You know
It tastes even better on Monday
When you had it on Friday
And we didn't have it on Friday
So it was
Leftovers I'm touched by human hands
Young pull-up
Thank you very much for the hit test
124 man
Cranking up the numbers there
Good one
I love love unlimited
I got to play that song
On the next week or Friday
Which I think
We'll happen this coming Friday
Schedules
Schedules permitting of course
Hey something
Pretty funky happened here in the UK
Saturday night
Going into Sunday
As we discussed on this show
And also on a no agenda
The show that I do with
John C. to War Act
No agenda.meavio.com
Boris Johnson
The brand new mayor of London
Put a new law into effect
That started on Sunday
June 1
Where
Travelers are forbidden from
Drinking
Or even having an open container
Of alcohol and public transport
And I for one
I'm a big fan of this
Of this new law
Because I often
Act fact
I've stopped
Almost
Completely unless I can
You know
In less as a reason
I'll stop traveling back from London
To Guilford by train
Which I do in the morning
On the way in quite happily
Mainly because
You know
It's even in first class
Oh the horrors
You know
There's drunk people
And they're sitting there
Drinking getting drunk
And it really really is annoying
And you know
They're loud
And they're obnoxious
And it's just
It's annoying
And no one does anything
No one says anything
Because you know
Let's face it
I don't want to get beat up
I'm pretty scrony guy
Particularly
There's been a football match
From one of the teams
Down South
Yeah
It's just
It's not okay
And a part of this of course
There's no actual
There wasn't a law
To stop this
Certainly
No control
No controllers
No law enforcement
I have yet to see how
That's going to work out
In fact it didn't work out very well
Because
They had one last to raw
One last farewell
To drinking
In public transport
Saturday night
And
Liverpool Street Station
Which is not far from
The London HQ
Over there in shortage
Was a complete Madhouse
People just drinking
Pugan, you know
Broken glass
Everywhere
A big ass mess
And you'd think
Which one of the chucklehead
Or better yet
Which is a bond
Do you think
Mind
Just mind
Have gone to such a party
Hmm
Let me think
I don't mind
Charles
The
Extremely hungover
London
Swan in the afternoon
Not just working out
But I'm feeling
Right
So as you can hear my voice is about
Six octaves low
And then he's normally
I must say it actually kind of
Sounds kind of sexy
They're Charles
I just want to
I wanted to
Just throw something in
About just
Not no drinking
On the underground
Boris Johnson is forcing
I understand why he's doing it
And I do believe
And he's social behind
And he's to be
Clacked down upon
Certainly assaults on the staff
And choose
Workings
It's just that place
In that city
Out of order
And needs
To be
Playing
To do
to test
To be
The
Moomin
keep that in mind okay the word liberty they was that they were
protesting and unfortunately when you have people protesting people
do take it to a level and for at least they got noticed at least
Charles
uh... people weren't doing that to get noticed they were doing it because it was a party
that's what happens i did as a party let's go drink over there this was not
maybe the first people who came up with the idea
and organized what i would say is an and outstanding flash mob but for all
the wrong reasons
i think uh...
no i don't think it was a protest i think people were just out for a good time in a
party
got the message out that we're not happy about
having hours out of the uh... freedom's infringement
now you didn't get any message out uh... Charles the in the message of any
they got out is uh...
to a bunch of drugs
subreddit was it was completely without any
demeanor discretion
any message
it was just about
well
if anything
it did show that there's a high level of frustration and that it's uh...
very volatile
not in control no one was in control of the situation Charles no one
it was not organized it was not a protest
it was a party
and everyone gate crashed that's pretty much what it was
i'm just not gonna accept this uh...
protest stuff about your liberties being taken away
but there's it's the point is
people don't get drunk on the tube
they will get drunk when they've been on the tube yeah okay so uh... it will
be okay with me
if people were drunk before they got on the tube were on the train
and then just let it off
but no they just tend to get drunker
and i'm saying this from first-hand experience uh... Charles i'm not a limo baby
i love taking the train in fact this makes no sense to take a car into the city or
out of the city
unless you want to avoid the drugs getting drunker
and they go out and then they get on and then they get on the tube while drunk
it's nothing to do
with people drinking
yeah except uh... i've seen completely
completely to the contrary
completely different while on public transport
it's everything to do
with people being anti-social and that's what really needs to be cut down upon
if someone's spending their time trying to take a can of a kind of fear of me
is not going to
improve safety
it's not
it's not going to improve safety
you could be right although i must say i felt reasonably unsafe in certain situations
on public transport
for this very reason
but i'm sure you're going to say as it's uh... it's not you're not going to let them take
their liberties away from you right
i'm going to do anything
all this going to do is piss me off
yeah and that's all that you're going to get when you're trying to take down
call for people
so dude how come you're not pissed off about uh... let me see
the complete breakdown of uh... mobility in the country
you can't get into London
and you can't afford to get into London anymore
the trains are overloaded to capacity
fuel is being taxed up to the hilt
you know this is why i was so proud of the truckers who
blocked off the west and that's a protest
that's again something that's that's against being stolen from
by the government who are supposed to be working for you
don't give you this bullshit about your beer being taken away
you out of your mind
and
so it's a ridiculous law it's a hollow law
it's very very very typical of someone like boy Johnson
not what's very very typical is to see that this is the one thing the one law that
everyone is up and arms about
because we're all too drunk to notice what the fuck is really going on in these countries
not just the united kingdom but also in the united states wake up people
who wants to be seen to be doing something in fact he's holding more problems
that's why i wanted to be London's mayor uh... and there you go
you watch man you watch this guy could really turn things around
he could really start to do some massively good things
and to start with he can get rid of all these stupid cameras which are completely
ineffective either that or my other suggestion which is sell the entire rights to all
cameras from London
to end them all and make it a big ask reality show
they were for my friends they said were for us
yeah they do they do charles
now give you a little leeway there because you clearly were
not thinking clearly a bit clouded
oh boy
i can't believe in having this conversation
all right uh...
let's talk about fuel for second shall we i'm going to end it and i'm you know what
no way to make let's uh... let's promote something placed on there we're going to talk
about fuel and i've got something so stunning at the end it's going to bring it to you
oh
jesus
this, you say
A little bit longer, just for the heat, a little bit stronger, heavy nose, you've seen the
rough and tumble, along the road, we've had a few stomples, and when you can't believe we'll
believe, she wanted everything to be, and it's just a train that's best right, tomorrow's
everything to go, but it always comes on time, it's all we've got to say today today,
the weather else to be with you today, today, today, today, today, you are standing at the crossroads, shining
the light in the middle, saying hello, saying like you need nothing, I want to feel it, if you see the
world feel it shine, so we walk away, till time, it's just a train that's best right, tomorrow's
everything to go, but it always comes on time, it's all we've got to say today today, today, today,
the weather else to be with you today, today, today, today, today, today, today, today, today, today
today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, but it's all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go,
tomorrow's everything, tomorrow's everything but it always starts all we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, so we've got to say today, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to stay, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's everything to go, tomorrow's
Any any independent producer was a member of the pot set music network and play it in his or her show next the video
Whatever enjoy and share with friends
And of course you can find links to all the songs played on to do show today show in the show notes at
DailySourceco.com. All right
Last we spoke I asked if anyone could help me out understanding the
The price of diesel and how it's affecting you or if you even understand why the price is shot up so
Astronomically and of course all you have to do is call out the trucker Tom and he's there. Come on in good buddy
Yo Adam
Tom while Sir aka trucker Tom and Friday source code you were asking me
Person comments regarding I guess most of the fuel prices the high fuel prices now. I am a company driver
I drive for a company. I do not own the truck. Okay. I was wrong. I thought you were probably an independent
There Tom so okay your answer is going to be different than the maybe what I wanted but still want to hear it
I would not touch that business with the 10-foot pole
There's just too many things that can go wrong as you as demonstrated by the
Rising fuel prices by the way it's on it sounds like you're actually sitting inside your fuel tank as we speak it's an awesome sound effect
Now what's happening a lot a lot of marginal
Operators are going out of business because they cannot
Forward the fuel only the strong the strongest companies are going to be able to survive this
Now
What the companies are doing they're starting to clamp down on their
Expenses
Mainland biggest one is a fuel yeah after fuel by the way comes people
In fact, I'd say that probably well that's because of specific to the transport business
But probably people is the number one expense in any organization so
As predicted this is going to cost jobs and livelihoods and it's going to weaken economies
Now the company the die drive for they they're slowing the trucks top speed down they do that by plugging a computer in and
Slow you know just setting the speed so now moderately literally slowing down the economy
Truck will go 62 it used to go 65
They're asking us to reduce the idle time to 10% now that's pretty much impossible
Because hey, I live in the truck
In order to stay cool or
Warm
I've got to idle the truck because my truck does not have what's called an alternate power unit
And so therefore I have to idle the truck as I am right now in order to stay cool right now. I'm in
Georgia
Area and it's kind of hot here
So I'm going to stay cool. They can gripe at me all they want but
I'm going to stay cool you can find all of my rants and other web 2.0 social goodness at
Trucker Tom podcast calm you and they work for us
Yeah, Tom. Thanks. Okay. That answered that. Let's see what this one's about
Last message was too long. Take two. Hi, I'm Mike. It's Mike. I live in northern California Bay area. I've noticed
After watching regular and diesel gas prices where I buy gas
That unlike a year or two ago where diesel was one to five percent less than regular
It's now 20 to 30 percent above the cost of regular gas. Exactly. This is what I'm trying to get some answers on
Why the hell has this stuff that used to be really really cheap now become more expensive than regular gasoline?
I just checked San Jose gas prices.com and in Gilroy which is about 50 miles south
Gas is $4 and 2 cents diesel is $5 and 25 cents. Here's my question
Maybe you can ask your petroleum savants
What's behind this recent significant difference between regular gas and diesel?
I have a suspicion it might be related to sweet crude
Which I think I read sweet crude is used primarily or is preferred for
Producing diesel fuel and sweet crude is very scarce. Wow, it's not amazing
I thought I was convinced that it had to do with like carbon emission taxes
You're telling me the actual basis of diesel was just gone up because sweet crude is so hard to get a hold on
I thought I mean I thought yeah, you can burn anything
You can burn anything you want to diesel you can almost poop in it the thing will run
That doesn't make any sense. Are they making diesel that's too clean?
Wow
Is sweet crude the issue for the diesel prices is that what China and India are buying for their
Significant you know build out oh wow. This is a great question. I'm glad you got a little bit deeper than I've been able to get okay. This is good
And then more maybe more importantly
Is the US government
Which is buying sweet crude to fill the strategic petroleum reserve is that are those purchases?
Actually forcing the price of diesel up and
If so what impact would it have if the US government suspended purchasing
sweet crude
in order to
Push down the price for a diesel
My understanding is the strategic reserve is at 98%
It's big but you know suspending it for you know six months
To bring them the price of diesel fuel if that's possible which certainly make a lot of sense
What are your savants think about that?
Hope you hear
More discussion around this thanks a lot. Well your time you could not have been any better because I've got the economics of bond
I think that economics of bond has an answer to this and it's been from a
Your economics on
I give you a quick hope
You're talking about gas taxes and
Got me thinking I'm actually driving back from the gas station right now just paid for 29
Oh, man, can you believe that you know I?
I filled up the Delta Shira in the Hilversum at Hilversum Airport since
Farrox has no fuel that literally out of fuel they've been out of fuel for four months
They can't afford to have a full fuel truck show up anymore
Okay, this is a busy airport
People have to fly to neighboring airports to get fuel
You know they can't operate the field anymore. I paid two euros fifty
For a leader
That's like ten bucks a gallon
So the car put in a little over fifty dollars in gas into my little infinity g twenty um
Getting rid of gas tax a little wouldn't do much good
Forers in the long run. I'm going to be able to get it here in California. I pay roughly sixty two cents a gallon in taxes
Some days pay a little 30 cents in total
18.2 18.3 cents that goes to the federal government now
Why this wouldn't do this any good is the vast majority of the funding for
I was bridges streets all that stuff that you drive your car around on comes from those gas taxes
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. All right
Is now what we paid tolls for aren't the tolls supposed to cover all that?
You can't tell me all bridges and all tunnels and stuff that that's just now possible
We paid tolls especially for the maintenance of that
You only get the cash tax you drive that's worth of funding almost completely and road tax don't we pay the license fee
Registration fees not a road tax kind of built in
Road deteriorate they're just fall down that things happen
Can't drive around gas tax is one of the few taxes. That's actually good tax in that the people who are generating the tax
So the people who are using the service the go-to-long with this not kind of like general tax
When you have where kind of the angle pot the pot comes out whenever home the more mild I drive more gas
I have to buy and more wear and tear and putting on the road
Of course, that's not entirely true
Diesel fuel is used in many aircraft these days
Diesel fuel is used in boats it's used in generators
Trucker Tom is burning diesel just to stay cool to stay warm. He's not using one one inch of road
Well, only the inch he's standing on
That's not entirely fair and by the way the European Union is working on changing
Tax not necessarily the gasoline tax but other special taxes they have on audible bills and
They're now more figured into a pay as you use tax which means
They get a little black box in their car, which tracks how many miles they actually drove
And then they get a bill at the end of the month for that usage
Which is all fine and dandy
If you're want the government to know exactly where you are at any given moment
Cranky
To maintain those roads and whatnot, so
What the hell's kind of explain things politicians like the float this is an idea kind of a populist type movement gets people fired up
Because I think oh what they're doing something for me, but yeah in all honesty when I'm seen for 30 a gallon
I'm not gonna know safety and sense
Gas is still expensive, but it's also still a really good deal
Especially here in the states
You're up all the other countries that tax it like there's no tomorrow at the different story
So that's what I got
Love you man
Stoomin it no mama all that jazz
And remember they work for us
Hell yeah
You know I was actually planning on playing something in
I had to make different at the end today
Which actually is about 11 minutes and length so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna say that for tomorrow because it is quite beautiful and since we're on such a roll
I have one more
one more
Voice mail to play and by the way if you're looking for the voice mail numbers
I don't play the jingles anymore because they kind of got annoying and got on my nerves
But you can find him in the show notes a daily source code dot com listen to what our monetary scientists has to say
This is trace in San Diego the monetary scientists
I am a couple of a couple weeks have been traveling and I really get a friend of mine
Got no very bad car accident is a nice interview and
I spin in some time with him this man. I'm sorry to hear that man. No, it really fits
It's like in perspective so I hope all the truck loads are yeah, that'll do it too
Really cherish those relationships. They got
Anyways, I've heard a lot of talk on the
source code about the gas and a little prices and diesel
etc
All right, bring in home monetary scientists. Let's get some closure to this and
I'm actually going to be speaking on this topic at
Cambridge House is
2000 investment conference up in Vancouver
Excuse me. I mean, we don't just have any savants stop them by on the Charlie. You know our chuckle heads got some props got some rep got some background got some baggage
House.ca for more information. It's free to if you're through register with you to it and so any trip roads up there
Anyways, one of the big problems we've got with our oil and gas prices
is
In 1933 the securities act was passed which governed
Stocks and whatnot 1936 the
Commodity exchange act was passed creating the CFTC the commodity future trading commission
No, I want to I know it's kind of hard to hear but I want you to really focus I'm going to shut up I want to interrupt I want you to really listen to what he's saying
About this act that was created and who's really responsible for this rapid rise in the cost of oil
Pay attention
Yes, you see
Anyways, it's at rules about
Like who can invest in what and how much when it comes to wheat and oil and silver gold
And remember
Currents is only good for what it'll buy
So when we have this runaway spending by Congress and this carry trade with the Japanese yen
The loose lending standards by the Fed and when they bail out stuff like their sterns
Boeing bubble after bubble all the past monetary inflation and then the fractional reserve lending of our modern banking system
Of course the dollar
loses its purchasing power and it goes for all the occurrences rose in
British council whatever and
People with hold those they need to
Preserve their purchasing power so what do they do they want to buy real things like oil?
So now we've got tension funds that have 1.1 billion
barrels of oil in future contracts that they've bought and they keep rolling them over months to month
Anyways, there's a ton of capital that's starting to pour into commodities
We haven't even seen anything yet as far as what it could be and that's one of the things that's really feeling these price increases and you can't see it's a bubble because
The inventories are not
Being stocked up the oil's been consumed anyways run to gold dot com love your hair
Uh
To know home of
To good work man
Because you're writing a bank hard
And I really appreciate what you're doing
And thank you're keeping the contract and I feel unjustly and rich from benefiting so much from the show
Thank you so much buddy. It just under the three minute time limit too
Okay, so this is something I've I indeed have from other sources that it's really what's going on as you have these
Insurance companies now insurance companies have a you know, it's a very very simple business
They take your money they invest that money they get a certain return on it. They've all kinds of spreadsheets and models and they know what the
Percentages are chances and likelihood of you either
Getting into an accident hurting somebody breaking something
Dying your house burning down or
Losing your job or just getting horribly ill. You know this is or getting robbed
This is what they do and they calculate that premium
You know based upon who you are your risk profile, which I think is pretty much just made up at birth these days
And you know the way that against
You know how much have to pay out an insurance claims and you know by the way
They're always kind of tight on paying out. You gotta gotta gotta go to go through a lot of rig and we're all sometimes to
Get your money back from insurance company and so what they're doing is you know they're saying the other they're seeing the opportunity
They just want to make more money. That's what they do. These are some of the wealthiest companies in the world some of them of course
You know
Run into trouble when there's huge natural disasters, but they're pretty good at not paying out. I'd say in general
And they're they're making bank they're rolling it over there
You know, they have they fit within the regulation they can buy oil in fact
I understand that there's so much oil that there's now actually a shortage of tankers because the
tankers are literally sailing the seas with no particular destination no port to go to
They don't want to go to a port although kind of you know the layout and international water outside of a port
Ready to pounce to go in and offload their oil at the minute the cell order comes in. I mean there's actually a shortage of tankers because of this
And you know this is this is where the outrage should be this is people speculating
On on our economy, you know using our economy is collateral it's it's so wrong
Yeah, a lot of people are gonna get very very wealthy
Man, you know what I'm tired of it. I've been thinking about this for too long
But something's got a break something will break you watch when the price of gas goes up to about
67 bucks the shit's gonna hit the fan and then the price of oil will come down the dollar will go up and then we'll probably see
McCain
Elected president and then the stock market will she was shoot up and well, I don't know man
Then we'll probably need some kind of some other kind of a 9-11 like event to bring us back down to earth and to scare us all back in submission
You never know but rest assured. I'm gonna keep my eye on it
As will the rest of the chuckle has and if you're new to this show welcome to the family
So daily source code not always daily but always full of passion
Don't you let me live
Turn it all out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it
out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it, out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it, out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say up, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out, you say it out,
So here we are, missing me, in the eye we'll leave the ring
From the school, in the sun, dawn is one thing, and the chair must go on
To come on, oh, with the round of high, and to let me live
Oh, and the reason that I'm dealing, I can't rely on, I'm tired, I'm tired
Oh, and the reason that I'm dealing, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired
Oh, and the reason that I'm dealing, I'm tired, I'm tired
You and I, there are some positive too, and the positive music network, I, there are some elder
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired,I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I
Of course, more kick-ass pod save music, and we'll continue to remind them that they work
for us so until then, remember to live life with passion and enjoy your freedom.