There was a basic radio, terrestrial radio, and then there was satellite radio until the
prices brought us back to Earth.
Finally, we had the daily source code.
We could enjoy, we could take it with us, we could shove it in our ears.
So here's Adam Curry with the DSC 770.
Only boys and your lonely girls hear the end of the lonely world you're finding out
if there's someone to cry about, only girls and your lonely boys playing alone with your lonely
only boys will not be blue because there's no one to play with you.
Yes, I've forgotten yourself, no you sure.
I can't recall myself, but it feels good.
Yes, I've forgotten yourself, take my advice.
I can't recall myself, but it feels nice.
When the lights come on and the parties through there always feel with nobody to do.
Well, now don't despair, you'll eventually get there.
And then while all of the lonely ones hear what you do while you wait for the sun to rise above,
the only is kind of old.
Yes, I've forgotten yourself, no you sure.
I can't recall myself, but it feels good.
Yes, I've forgotten yourself, take my advice.
I can't recall myself, but it feels nice.
When the feel lights come on and the parties through there always feel nice.
Yes, I've forgotten yourself, take my advice.
I can't recall myself, but it feels good.
Yes, I've forgotten myself, but it feels good.
I'm gonna find yourself in the ocean
I got to put myself in the sea to the sky
I'm gonna find myself in the ocean
I think this clearly falls under the prostate cancer prevention
Kota songs
Seven Sonic all about chemistry
Get a grip
I got a grip on myself and it feels good
And would you like to get a grip on someone else?
No
I found that on the source code drop daily sore
Drop that I always slash daily source code
Yeah, fits. It really does fit
Of course, you know all kinds of metaphors for getting a grip on yourself like
Hey, how you doing everybody?
It's daily source code number 770
I got a firm grip on myself here coming to you from the curry manner upstairs in the atoms attic
We're on the west side of G-town
The affluent suburb of Surrey known as Gill
For not a very nice day today. It looks like we're in for a kind of some shitty weather for the next few days
It's all been kind of down south near France and Spain and Italy actually
Not Spain but Italy and France
Oh, you notice I'm slipping more into my UK accent every single day
I got to be careful of that
Hey, I had a pretty interesting experience this morning
Something I'm trying to set up for the chuckle heads out there
I spoke to a member of European Parliament
He's a Dutch guy. His name is Tuan Mondeurs
I think it is. I'm going to check. Yeah
And
You know because I'm kind of looking for people who are
Well, first of all, you know that I own of course voted no in this Lisbon treaty
And now we have to see what happens
Remember even the president over there at the commission or
Or parliament or whatever it is
That's so complicated
He said there's no plan B
You know that's that was kind of the message
If Ireland votes it down if they votes down
Vote down this Lisbon treaty which is kind of a version of the constitution that was voted down in 2005 by the Dutch and by the French
Then that's it, you know, then they have to go back to the drawing board
And you know, so immediately after the Irish voted this down
Yeah, there's all kinds of rumblings going on in Brussels and Strasbourg
Because of course the European Parliament doesn't just have one seat of government
They have two places to sit
That's that's a whole story into itself
And
You know there's all kinds of posturing and people talking about well maybe two out of three
We'll do another vote
So I'm looking for people who are really in the midst of it all
And so this guy is not just a member of the European Parliament
But he's also
He was actually angry
And here and I spoke to him in Dutch but the guy speaks perfectly
I'm going to invite him to come on to the show and see
So it won't be until next week because they've got all kinds of meetings going on this week
In Strasbourg and they're trying to figure this out
But essentially he said that it was unconscionable
That 800,000 people from Ireland could hold half a million people in Europe hostage
He literally used the word hostage
And you know, that's like, you know when Comister blogger says it is like one thing
But to hear a minister of European Parliament speak that way
Well particularly when his own country the Netherlands three years ago
Apparently held Europe hostage by voting no to the Lisbon Treaty
But of course he never used those words then
Then it was like, oh well we didn't explain it properly
Or we have to do a better job next time
And it's obvious if the French had voted no
Then maybe the Dutch would be the old Irish
So now the Irish are the new Irish
And he went on to say
The things that our European correspondents of Ontario fellow chucklehead CSB
Has indeed said verbatim
That Ireland receives a billion euros a year
And that thanks to participation in the EU they are what they are today
And they've got big multinationals flowing into the country
And that this is really just a bunch of sheep farmers
Can you believe this shit?
He said a bunch of sheep farmers
Who just want to hold on to their subsidies and don't want taxes to change
And he said just the top it all off
We're going to find out where Ireland wants to be a member of the European Union
Or not in essence saying well you know if the rest of the so there's eight
More member states that have to ratify
I believe Britain ratifies today I think
So they have a total of 26 with this just iron on this leftover
They're going to get kicked out of the EU
And this is crazy
This is absolutely nuts
And what just surprised me was the aggression
Which with which he was talking
He was like whoa you know hold on man
Look everyone's in this boat together
And the deal was all everyone says yes or or it's no go
And of course the Irish were the only ones who got a referendum
I'm pretty sure if more
Members states were allowed to hold a referendum
You would have had more nose
And it's not even the context of the content of the document
No one understands what's in there
I certainly don't
I've tried to figure it out right here on this very program
So anyway that's just my European update
I was just flabbergasted by that
So we got to keep our eye on the situation here
John C. Dvorak over the weekend on no agenda
I had no agenda.mevio.com
He said it sounded like a fascist state takeover
Which you know
Wow you know I wouldn't want to go that far
But why not? It does sound a bit like that
It's crazy stuff going on my friends
It's big forces at work
Really really really big forces that we have
Absolutely no idea what's really
I mean well we can only have ideas and thoughts about it
Here's something there's another thing on the on the
The source code drop drop dot IO slash daily source code
Look for this title cbc
It's an audio show the current
As I think what the name of the program is
So that's a Canadian broadcasting corporation
I'm just going to read the caption for this because you got to go listen to this
To this 26 minute piece
Ready for the Wall Street types to screw up food prices just as they have oil prices
It reads seems there is rampant speculation going on in the agriculture industry
Everything from farmland fertilizer and grain silo companies are being bought and sold at record prices
Once again
Just like oil right now
This is not necessarily a complete supply and demand issue
This is a loophole that you know now the law is not past yet
But this is going to be closed sometime by October
And this is the same one that end that end run used before that loophole is closed
To cause rolling blackouts in California
It's a scam people it's a freaking scam
And we're being diverted in all kinds of directions and where's journalism at this point
Yeah business journalism is catching on to it finally
But please let's show who these people are
It's the guys wearing dockers and khakis and blue shirts and yelling into telephones at 430 in the morning
And a lot of it a lot of that trade is taking place right here in London
We've got to stop it, you know, this is this is an outrage
And we're getting mad at the wrong people and we're protesting in the wrong places
Because it literally is happening on the trading floor of the commodities stock markets
Or the commodities markets
Trading markets
And now this shit with food
Oh man and you know, so now the latest news came out yesterday inflation
Remember I talked about the word stagflation
Which means that we kind of have the economy is slowing down yet prices are going up
That's exactly what's happening. It's this unfortunate combination of
Of oil going through the roof
Well, we have a financial crisis which essentially messed up interest rates
So you know now it's like everyone has to choose both the United States and Europe now from from everything I'm hearing
Particularly in the UK where inflation and rose
Fort will will have risen to 4% by the end of this year
Which means people have to have more money
You know that's we're going to have a lot of striking going on in a country like the like England or Britain
United Kingdom you'll see a lot of those
And you know there's less money available
So do they raise interest rates to stop the inflation?
Which of course suppresses the economy even more because it's harder for people to borrow money
Or do they lower interest rates so that there's more money flowing people can have access to more cash
We can get back into buying houses, which is almost at a standstill
But then of course you know you risk
Hey, I know I'm no economist as you can tell but this is definitely a messed up situation
Oh, yeah, yeah, anyway
Actually, I had to know about something about the UK inflation
Let me just see what that is. I'm going to just open it. Oh, it's Sanders research associate. Yeah, it's it's a complicated issue
But you know, please where is it where is the the mainstream media on this are they just lazy or they're not understand or they're just
Just buying the the answers that are provided for them. I mean come on
This is like the biggest secret now. It's driving me nuts
All right, let's go on over to
Actually, so I did you know on Monday there was just so much that came in over the weekend
Mondays are just getting tough it like takes a long time to go through everything
So I still want to crank out shows on Monday and then have someone that's spill over on the Tuesday or Wednesday
So the question that was posed to our Savanta do nuclear atomic rod was you know just how safe are these nuclear power plants now
We've been talking about this for quite a while. I'm getting pretty convinced here by atomic rod who by the way does work for us
He works for the for the US government
I'm pretty convinced that these the new technology the pebble reactors are much safer than of course three mile island Chernobyl etc
And the nuclear waste is much smaller much more convenient to take care of than we ever thought of before certainly seems like there's a lot less of it than I imagine
And then of course the I guess like the final thing that people always want to demunk nuclear nuclear energy on is terrorism
That's a big one for our administration. Of course our oil guys and don't want us to try much else
Uh, and that would be the strength of of these plants and can someone blow them up and will we all die?
That of course or whatever one wants to know so atomic rod doodifully calls in
Hey Adam it's atomic rod. I'm here and I'm here to answer a question from Steve and the Bay Area
With regard to the vulnerability of nuclear plants to terrorism of terrorists attacks all I can say is I'm extremely confident of their ability to withstand damage, especially compared to all other energy sources
I've been at nuclear plants that can tell you that the containment buildings are about three to four foot thick reinforced concrete with the
We bar that reinforces a concrete about as thick as my forearm. I'm not real concerned about any release of right out to materials from an attack on a nuclear plant
And then our sea of pretty much agrees with what I have to say lots of other energy facilities have been attacked many times since night 11 oil pipelines gas pipelines refineries tankers
But there haven't been any real attacks on any new clear plants terrorists are probably smart enough to avoid the hard targets
You know they work for us and by the way I'm looking to you from watching DC sitting in freedom of square
So I'm looking to protect your freedom by and we know you are rod and we appreciate it very much
Some of them do indeed feel that they work for us. Yeah, that's a good point. There's been all kinds of terrorist activity on the
On fossil fuel bay stuff
But yeah, the hard targets just seemed to not be there and of course this was due to a comment from Monday show where
I forget who it was who called in and said look you know a lot of talk about two nuclear plants in the Bay area
And there's no extra protection that's going on because it's not needed. That's the bottom line. So all this expensive fuel
Ah, we're being we're being duped. I'm telling you I am not the only one saying this pass it on. It's not just it's not just the big oil companies
It's not just the government with their CO2 emissions taxes on on engines if they they all may be in cohorts for all
I know, but it's definitely unnecessary
Hey, I found it's Mark Mark's thing cool. I mentioned how extensive flying is and here in the United States
There's a way to fly not so expensively. Can't wait for this
Recently, they came out the new light sport license which
Okay, a smaller planes to see their planes. You're flying about 120 knots which are like this. No one 50. I'm steroids
And it costs about half of the cost to get your license.
Yeah, yeah, Mark. Absolutely. I mean for for flying and learning how to fly absolutely there are definitely alternatives
I mean you can even start off with the gliders, you know, they can go to a motor glider, which I think some of the even work on batteries
But you know, I use my aircraft for transportation mainly because I just, you know, I can't be wasting an entire day
Hopping across the puddle from the UK to the the main continent and it takes that, you know, with all the security checks and just
It takes so long and it's getting more expensive and less flights are available. I need more flexibility
So I use it as transportation and the LSAs although certainly great aircraft and fund a fly not appropriate for the real transportation as I need it unfortunately
I add a mixture of color. I did the number constant on your field consumption to your plane 60 liters an hour
Covering under 70 miles across the ground. Oh, I'm so happy he finally did this. Okay, so I was talking about the price of fuel to fill up the Delta Sierra
Which is it's not a huge plane, but it's not it's not a you know, such as a trainer or anything. It's a 180 to retractable gear
It's fully IFR you can fly instrument on it. It's a it's a great plane. It's the flying station wagon
Okay, the family roundabout in the skies and it is about 16 gallons or a little over 60 liters per hour that I burn
And it's you're going to be interested because Pete whenever people hear me talking about flying in a you know in a plane versus driving or any other motor transportation
You know or I often am accused of being a huge polluter
Because I'm flying through the skies with my aircraft listen to these statistics so you're right
I'm doing 150 knots about 170 miles per hour at a fuel burn of 60 liters or approximately 16 gallons for the same time period
Now here comes the number crunching
It's apparently good actually sort of 0.85 miles per imperial gallon
10.72 miles per US gallon
Yep, or for continental measurements 22.06 liters per hundred kilometers
You'd be hard put to do 170 miles an hour in a car and still come out with nearly 13 to the gallon
So that's pretty good and of course you're going in a straight line to cover the same ground in a car
Yeah, we have to do more miles and you see more fuel exactly
I don't need to worry too much just yet
Yeah, no, it's absolutely true. It's absolutely true. You know, that's the big joke is it's a it's a like calming engine
It's like a sports car engine like a
In fact some I believe some aircraft actually have a Corvette engine in them
So you know, it's something like that
You know, it's a couple hundred horsepower. Now of course it's running at 75
Most of the time your flag is about an average of 75% of the engine. So you'd have your engine revved up for 75% of its power continuously
So that's why it has needs a lot of maintenance and it's you know, it's got to be hanging together there
But it's a flying car. This is why I keep telling you the flying car exists. It just doesn't drive too well
I'm sorry, I want pilot error sorry
I'm pretty Jones this reality podcast quick word fuel. Yeah, I said it's some guy on the news
Petrol station on a down in Devon southwest of England selling unleaded for one ninety-nine
Alita crap two pounds a later and you feel I feel raped is how I feel two pounds a leader
So that's
That's four dollars
Times three
So it's 12 even more 12 13 bucks a gallon. Yep. Yeah
Also big left the Charles a drunk and Londoner Charles. Yeah, real star and a real character keep up the good work
I don't think you're very much. I'll speed you again. Yeah, I work for us. Thanks buddy. Yeah, and he's not just Charles the drunk and London anymore
He's now known as Charlie Delta Lima and I told you I had one for call that I had from from yesterday or from Monday
Just listen to it and and of course
I play this because I love
I can't help it. I drink there four lines drunk
Uh
Yeah
I tell me things what's raining now. I'm actually on a phone apartment was gonna say
Uh, but does anyone else
Sort of lying in bed
Closed your iPhone in through it's evening charge because like you say Charles doesn't last for more than
A little while so
Closed your iPhone in
You see how the other they say children and drunk people always tell the truth
So now it's coming clean on the on the battery life of his iPhone
Yeah, it doesn't last long so he's plugged plug it in at night and then why it's not a 3G I phone
But you know what through his iPhone's changed the way I work the way I live
Uh having it a bit faster
Doesn't mean my life will be fast or will be improved
There you go
Alright get to the point Charles
But as anyone lie in a lie in bed
You plug your iPhone in and it's just kind of sitting on the edge of the bed and you turn the light out
And you think I made us to put that on the the chair extra bed or the dress or whatever
And you reach over and you cut it and it feels like it's vibrating
Mm-hmm anyone else had that
It's weird seeing there's something to do with the texture
Now let me just say you of course you were wondering why my playing Charlie Delta Lima to this extent
It's for this very point because I too have noticed and not with of course my iPhone
You know took a
Tank and fill in the toilet and I don't touch that anymore
But I have the iPod Touch now. I don't have it with the iPod Touch but on my old power book
Or MacBook. No, it's not so Macbook. Yes MacBook
Which is now downstairs in the kitchen which Patricia uses very often when I close the cover
I get that like it's it's so the weirdest sensation is like a friction type thing that feels like it's actually vibrating
I know exactly what you're talking about Charles
It is the weirdest thing and I bet you're more people have noticed it
Of the silvery fact of the iPhone that as you brush your hand over it gently
It feels like it's vibrating sort of vibrating
It's something to be detected and it's weird. I've never felt this with any other material
By the only other sort with the iPhone
I'm not entirely sober
It's not the only time I feel it
And there's nothing mark cannot be alone here
Go to me
What?
I'll instead know
Yeah
Treaty
No, you're going to have to hope
No, I'm not happening
Yeah, who knows
But why do I feel this?
Because Adam Curry told me to say to Felix
All I can say to that is then say oh
Oh come see
All right, now you're confused Charles
All right, all right, come down now
I
I love it, though, man
People tell the truth when they're drunk
Another great story that came in
I love this
The performing rights society, PRS
Which is the UK version of Ask Cap BMI
Which collects royalties from musicians in the United Kingdom as accused
Lancashire police of committing copyright infringement
By playing music and police stations
And to callers on hold without an appropriate license
In a RIT
And that's like a
Legal letter
In Junction or whatever
Whatever a lawyer or a lawyer
Whatever a lawyer rights is a RIT
In a RIT submitted to the high court
The PRS is called for an injunction and payment of damages
Now, boy
The PRS contains a playing music that is audible to others
Constituents a public performance
Meaning that it can be done without
Can't be done without a license
The Lancashire police stations
Play music in the background
At office parties
And in staff gyms
And even though they have not purchased licenses
That are enabled to do so legally
PRS has its attempted to collect license fees
From police all over the country
But Lancashire is one of the eleven
That are refused to pay up
Which is decided why they've decided to take legal action
Isn't that amazing
When you know that these guys are ready to take on the poll lease
You know they mean business
Holy crap
And how can I get me some of that money man
What if the cops will listen to my show
Can I get some of that dough?
Why is it only limited to music?
Because you've got the Mafioci on your side
That's how it's possible
Frick it nuts
And of course
Football is raging over here in Europe
And then I'll get on to some other topics
But it's just absolutely raging
Everyone's crazy about what's happening
The Dutch are kicking ass big time
They won from Romania last night
So they're only one of seven teams in history
To score this many points in the European Championships
So it's a big deal
And boy there's a lot of talent on the team
And I got it man
I'm following it
I'm not watching every single game
But the Dutch, yeah
I think they're definitely on fire
And even though I'm a little late in playing this
Where this was one game from the Dutch ago
I did want to share with you something that came in from
From Ray
Who loves to be on the Charlie?
All we want you tonight is Ray
Hey Anna
Hope it's time to be a part of us again someday
But are you ready for some sucker?
Oh no
This is the Marco from Boston Show
Okay, first I got to give you some facts about the sucker in my life
I don't watch a lot of sucker
Haven't seen the Champions League
It's spite of the final game
I don't follow our national cup or any other 22 men
Running behind the ball on the field
That sometimes looks more like a swimming ball
Or a nice field
Switzerland couldn't be any more orange than last Friday's city colours
Bergen turned into one big orange nation
Got you Marco from Boston Show
There's a real full bar Friday thriller cast
Wow
I don't know about you Adam but isn't it the most awesome myths
You've seen in a long time
The sound of Le Maseez
That's the French national anti by the way
Turned after 93 minutes into an orange feeling of love
Love
For the emotional shots of our guys
Hawking their kids after a full one win
The French were really not that bad
But the way our 11 nights of the queen
Move their asses over the green grass
Was absolutely a thrill to watch
Did it get a player of Liverpool?
Scores our first goal
Oh no no no no
I didn't see the ball
It is there again
Did you make up
Ha ha ha
Is it lecker?
Rubbing from Perci
The guy with a bad season at Arsenal
And most wanted Dutch soccer playing
According to our national being cake community
Booked the second floor
It's from Perci
No no no no no no
We're starting up play now
Are you a robot?
Our road runner from Real Madrid
3-1
The ball is on the right
We're starting up
Oh yeah
This is the Robiner like Wesley Snyder
A little new one
Recently moved from IX Amsterdam to Real Madrid
We're starting up play now
And we're starting up play
We're starting up play
Rafa Helfer in the fight
It's been from their side
Johnny Phillips came in Markov in Boston
Hell yeah
This was exciting
This was the one on the point
The point of your chair
Real soccer freely cast
Next Tuesday
And no matter what match meeting
With Romania
And then up to the hills of Basel
Europe will be orange
We are going to
Yeah
I'm not sure if he's done yet
All I've done right
I love that montage
And so please
The reason I'm playing
It was because you put so much work into it
And I just didn't get to it before the game yesterday
And of course I didn't even
Manif we win our lose
In fact, they would actually
Would have been to the Dutch's advantage if we lost
Because they neither Italy or France
Or I think Sweden
Whoever
We wouldn't have any of those good guys in there
And now Italy is through
Because the Dutch beat the Romanian team
By 2 to 0
I love that right
Fantastic
What a great job man
Thank you really really appreciate it
Yeah, it's European cup fever
Over here everybody
It's like the Super Super Super Duper Bowl
In the US, only
Different
All right, let me see
What else do we have here
Oh yeah, I want to talk about
Different forms of
Energy for driving cars
We talked about the Indian Tata
The Tata
Which has uses compressed air
There's electric cars
There's all kinds of stuff going on
And you guys out there
The chuckle heads you're talking about it
Hello, Adam, this is Peter
And we are slowly less than that
Pointless above Essex
No, no, no, don't be that way Peter
In Chelsea
That's a good spot
Make a quick point about
The idea of compressed aircol
And it was all a story on the BBC
About that
About French compressed aircol
It was well
But I have a video where it
But he sounds like
Boxes out
So cupless skeletons
Why didn't you just get 10
No way wrong
Wait
What did you call that?
Boxes out
So cupless skeletons
Why didn't you just get 10
No way wrong
Okay
Hey man, I mean
No one said you're going to get laid
By driving one of these vehicles
Okay, you might save a little bit of the planet
And you might save yourself some money
But I've never quite heard an engines describe that way
The sound of it is like two skeletons
Wanking in a biscuit tin
I have to remember that way
These alternate fields
Could better mind
Not a long ago
The UK government was looking at
Sort of satellite tracking
For a speculative road pricing
Interfects
So just the same enjoy these
Sort of nearly free fields
While again
Because they want belong before
Once they catch on
The government will be charging them on
So
Okay
Love you no no
Great how do you win
And they work faster
Yeah, there you go
Bastards
Of course there's no avoiding taxes man
You know that
Only two certainties in life for death
And taxes
Of course we're going to get tax
And this is another part of it
Maybe we're not
Maybe we shouldn't even be looking at trying to
Come up with alternative fuels
Because our economy will tank if we're not
If we're not using patrol even the way it's tax
And of course the alternative is
Whatever we're going to use it's going to get tax
You're absolutely right
But for a while there's going to be a good period
I think probably five or ten years
We can do all kinds of experimenting
And save ourselves a couple of bucks
I like this
So not just the Indians but the French
Also seem to I guess that
It's not the ta ta guys who have the
Two skeletons wanking in a biscuit tin
Maybe he's the French guys
Jason over in San Diego
About the air car that's supposed to be made in India
The French are making one
Some vehicle designer decided who's going to
Make some air compressed car
And he has a
He has a little coupe
Kind of like a
Minivan kind of I guess
Yeah
Like a small SUV looking a little thing
And he says you can hold up to like
Five passengers in the big one
And get about 120 miles
To the PSI
I guess
Whatever it is
The metric is almost unimportant
I mean it costs like 30 cents to fill up your tank with air
Which is everywhere
Anyways
When you buy the car it's only about five to seven grand
And you get a free air compressor
Takes about three hours to fill it up
And I'm going to try to figure out if I can get one of those over here
That would be to hold your sweet
Yeah, does anyone have a link to that
French company or like dealer sites or something
I don't want to look into this
I mean we should really support this
This is a great idea and it's just genius
You know compressed air
Duh
Get away from the explosion bit all together
And just use
Physics
Love it
Right now I just filled up my car
Actually I didn't even get to fill it up
75 bucks
Yeah
It stopped because the pump
The gas pump stopped at $75
And I don't want to swipe my car again
It's still the pain for another whatever it would be
And I don't drive a truck or anything like that
And you drive VA
But
Yeah
Well I mean you're a man of course you drive a VA
I got you my friend
Yeah
Yeah, so let's approach the problem from two ends
Let's look at these new types of vehicles
New types of engines
Which really really I think is incredibly smart with compressed air
And in the other hand those guys who are
Driving up the prices by trading
Let's take them out back and shoot the fuckers
Hey, I don't know this is fall from
Lake Forest, California
You remember the new clear energy guy?
Sure, buddy how are you?
I don't get a
Single after just too cold do I?
Uh new clear energy guy
I didn't think so
Well I'm sure
So you know do the atomic rod is right about
How much nuclear waste there is in the world
But I do know that wasn't nuclear waste watching up on the shore
Friends William sound back in 1989
Really?
And you know it's not here again
I'm sure that was a different form of waste
Technology has improved and I don't know about this
I'm sure some will send me a link to this story
New clear waste washing up on shore
Uranium that I'm currently paying for 30 wait no for 40
I'm sorry for 50 a gallon
Yeah, going for these days
So that's not why I'm going
I'm calling because in DSC 757 you actually could pay in separate
References to bike ride for curing breast cancer
And the Tata air power car
Yes
And all type of me obvious connection between Tata's
And I thought I'd mention other
There's another way for Chuckleheads to
Sport these search for a cure for breast cancer
Okay
And let's accompany all save the Tata's
Amazing what they do as they sell
P-shirts and other stuff with cute low bills
I like this saved the Tata's
I'm digging it
And they donate 5% of the growth
That's the growth
All the money that comes in, not the profit
The actual growth
Nice
To risk cancer research
Now
And you can get the shirts for both guys and girls
And they've got
And you can get those all at the website
Yeah
Save the Tata's at home
Hold on
I made me wondering why I'm bringing all this up
Yes
The Julia, the founder of the company is a friend of mine
Ah, okay
I've done solid by me
So I'm doing a little solid by her
And also if you are wearing a Tata's shirt
Maybe you can actually get laid
Well, I'm just writing it
Excellent
Full circle
Probably the point I'd like to point out that I am trying to make my way
The photographer, so if there are any female Chuckleheads
I'm really really nice naked pictures too
Oh, I can certainly help
Dude, I'm looking forward to it
Thank you
Crown conclusion
Yes
I don't care if you're working in Washington, Westminster, or Brussels
You work for us
Hell yeah
If you continue to forget that then in the words of that great philosopher
Donald Trump
You're fired
That's right
I'm looking at the site right now
Aha
Great campaign
Finally
This is a breast cancer awareness campaign
That guys can participate in girls
Comparticipating
And it's a nice site
SavetheTata's dot com
And the t-shirt says savetheTata's
Ah
Fantastic
I love it
Humor when the chips are down
Because it is a really serious matter
But finally a way to bring
I think they'll bring a lot of awareness to it
I can use to imagine the academy awards
Instead of just a little ribbon there
Something, you know, t-shirt
SavetheTata's baby
You know what I'm saying
All right
Let's see how we do it on time right now
Wow, it's already 415
I got so much to do
And we're getting close to the 40 minute mark
Okay
Here's something that a couple people sent me
Links to I think I also saw it on the source code
Drop.au slash daily source code
My sister sent me a copy of it
So I want to play it for you
It's a video
If you haven't seen it
You'll want to see the video
After you hear the audio version of it
It's about two and a half three minutes long
It's from a website called
I'mvotingRepublican.com
And the site consists of basically this video
Titled I'm VotingRepublican
Enjoy the audio
It's basically people
And although you may not be able to hear exactly what their
Vocations are because those are listed in titles in the video
You'll catch on pretty quick
We're voting Republican because we don't like shopping
It's small neighborhood stores
We don't want the problem with choosing where to shop
And we just love cheap plastic crap from China
I'm voting Republican because I don't really want to cure for AIDS
Or breast cancer
I'm just gazing
I'm voting Republican because I think new drugs should be made available
Immediately whether they've been tested properly or not
If the major pharmaceutical companies bottom lines are healthy
Then I feel healthy too
But maybe have a good day
I'm voting Republican so that my little Caitlin can be in the classroom
With at least 30 other children
That way she can be challenged by fighting for attention
I'm voting Republican because women just can't be trusted to make decisions
About their own bodies never ever ever
I'm voting Republican because I've already seen a great outdoors
Contouring used to fossil fuels truly is far more important for preserving our natural audums
We're voting Republican because we like a conservative majority on the Supreme Court
We really like knowing that even if we're separate we'll still be called equal
I'm voting Republican because I need to be told who I can love
I told you honey, I need the government to tell me
I just need them to tell me how I can best show a lifetime commitment
And Republican just the folks to do that sweetheart
I'm voting Republican because corporations should not have to pay to clean up environmental damage
The EPA is an outmoded idea
If people want clean water
Buy it in a bottle
I'm voting Republican because I don't want to know if the food I'm eating
Spend genetically modified or exposed to radiation
I don't want to have to live with that fear, you know?
So if the label says it's food, that's good enough for me
I'm voting Republican because I really enjoy being screwed by the utility company
We need more minorities in prison
Because hypercars
I just don't feel I deserve health insurance
Because sexist needs more billionaires
I'm voting Republican because sometimes the Constitution is just one big inconvenient headache
I think the whole world should be run by one big corporation
I think it'd be so much cozier
Because all other countries are inferior to us
We should start as many wars as we need to keep it that way
So I can stay in Iraq
So I can go to Iran
So if you were thinking about voting something besides Republican
Don't bother
Stay home
We've got it all taken care
You're getting a sack with you deserve
Yeah?
It does lose a little bit without the video
I have to say what men is this fantastic or what the irony is
It's just so wonderful
I'm voting Republican.com
Have a look at that, my friends
I'll speak to tomorrow
And while it lasts, enjoy your freedom
And live your life with passion
Another fine, medium presentation
Stick it in your ear