Autistic, here's the Battle of Curry.
The power of the Lord is coming.
Well, everybody how you doing?
Saturday night coming to you from Curry Cottage in the UK.
That's right. We are here. We have arrived.
Can't say the same for the connectivity,
but it's time to put on our little show.
The power of the Lord is coming.
The show known as the Daily Source Code. My name is Adam Curry.
It is Saturday, November.
I hope the heck are we today.
November 20th, 2004.
Coming to you from the United Kingdom from our brand new home.
It's been, I don't know, she was a bit about three days
since I've been able to do a source code.
I've been doing so much.
Basically, I'm packing boxes.
The number one thing that I've been doing.
Getting situated, figuring out the neighborhood,
figuring out where there's Wi-Fi.
So, you know what I want to do.
I want to take you on a little tour of the Cottage here.
I want to walk through some of the halls.
Maybe give you some of the outside sounds.
Since what we have compared to comparison material,
we've heard outside sounds from Belgium.
It would be nice to hear them from the United Kingdom.
Right off the bat, just because I really want to share some
some vibe and memories with all of you.
I'm going to have to say, fuck the RIA, sue me.
I just have to play this one for you.
You placed the flowers in the vase that you bought today.
Steering at the fire,
for hours and hours,
while I listen to you,
play your own songs all night long.
Oh, me, me,
only for me.
Going to me now,
to my nest,
to head for just five minutes.
Every thing is gone.
Such a cozy,
such a cozy window,
so I don't need to buy anything.
So, shine through them.
Fire regions for you.
Only for you.
Our house is a very, very, very fine house
with two cats in the yard.
Life is to be so hard.
Now everything is easy because of you.
No, no, no, no no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
the first floor of the house. Or is that the second floor? I guess if ground floor is
first floor then this is the second floor. Or it's the first story, whichever way you
want to look at it. Got it really nice set up here. Basically all the stuff that
Christina had hijacked in the bar at the castle. I now have to myself. I've got my
what is it cinema display monitor, which is now hooked up to my own power book. I've got
all my audio stuff, my breakout boxes. Actually I'm doing today's or this
this evening show partially at least on my sure SM7 microphone, which is I've actually
have no idea how it sounds. It sounds a little, I think it's a little bit of hiss to it,
which I think is probably let me see. Maybe that's probably the mixer I've got.
I'm going to have to figure out the best settings for all the stuff that I've got here
and certainly for this microphone. I also have the wireless mic which I'm going to switch over
to in a second so we can cruise around the house. I'm trying to think where to start, man.
So the last time we spoke we read the castle a very, very empty castle at that. And we were
getting ready to leave. Let's see, we left on Thursday. Patricia and her sister Iván
were already here. And they were basically working with the movers on packing stuff. Patricia
called somewhere around Thursday and she said, oh man, I don't know. I don't know what to do.
There's just too much stuff. I'm going to have to send stuff back. And when you think about it,
we probably moved about three houses worth of stuff. We pretty much emptied out the bunker and
Amsterdam. That's now been rented out to that reality show. The next Moscow beats is the name of it.
Moscow beats is a name of very famous trial lawyer in Holland who represents all kinds of people.
Showed his piece of people but also criminals. Everything but war criminals because he's Jewish and
he refuses to represent war criminals but he has no problem with any other type of criminal.
But he's a nice guy actually. He's a very celebrated attorney. And so I guess there's like 10
candidates or whatever. They move in tomorrow. In fact, and two are going to fall by the way,
so I'd almost immediately. But they're all going to stay in the bunker. They work in the bunker.
And the house is actually not that far from from Moscow beats. In fact, it's just around the corner
from Moscow beats is office in Amsterdam. So we had to move all that chunk out. We moved everything
out of the castle. We still had stuff from the states. And what happened is it arrived here.
And this house is the rooms that we utilize. It's probably not much smaller than or let's say
it's probably two thirds of what we utilize in Belgium at the castle. But the house itself is about
an a quarter of the size. So that means that you're lacking in storage space. And we had all this
stuff that just was kind of stored in cabinets and closets and rooms and whatever. And it's just
it's turned out that we got a shit load of stuff. So more about the stuff in just a second.
So Christina and I, I had booked a buddy of mine, yapped the fissor. He has a, he has a beautiful
airplane. He has a twin engine. It's a pipe or Navajo. It's an old old beast. But it does the job
perfectly. Cruises about 160 knots. So perfect to leave from Antwerp, which is about 20 minutes from
our house. For an hour and 15 minute flight, right to, and by the way, I'm not mentioning on the podcast
exactly where it is. We moved because the last thing I want is the Dutch press showing up here,
you know, going around. Because it's the town of small enough for people to figure out where we are.
And I just don't, you know, that's one of the reasons we left. So until everything was quieted down,
we'll just leave it in the middle. Although I can tell from all of the well wishes that I've received
from, and it was really beautiful. All these people from the UK welcoming me, leaving comments saying,
hey, you know, if you want an Earl Grey in the split, look me up. That's great. And I will take
some people up on those offers, believe me. But a lot of people have already kind of figured out
where we are. So there's an airport about 15 minutes from our house. It's a small airport. It's a,
it's a, you know, one runway. It is a paved runway. So it's not a grass strip, but it's just about
a level above a grass strip to be quite honest. And we had announced that we'd be arriving
from a different country, which you have to do, because it's not a, it's not an international
field. Excuse me. So what the, what the customs do is they send someone out. And they don't
actually, they don't even usually send someone out. But in this case, they did. And so the lady asked
for my passport and Christina's passport and stamped it. And we had a nice little chat. Didn't ask
anything about the dogs or the cats. I had both dogs and both cats in the plane. And, you know,
so I just kind of left the door closed. I figured, you know, shit, why go through, you know,
two hours of paperwork if I don't have to. And besides that, our cats Cindy, Cindy is the,
we found him at a, at a gas station in the States when he still lived in New Jersey.
When he was like three weeks old, nurse him to health. And he's become this ferocious,
amazingly strong animal. Just beautiful, very sweet, but man, he, I mean, even the vet
who does horses is afraid of this cat. And Cindy cannot handle traveling. Oh, man, he just gets so
motion sick. And, you know, so he thinks shit coming out of him from all ends and orifice is
really sad. So the plane stunk the high hill. Anyways, I would just left that door closed and
lady, the lady left after stamping our passports. And so I got the dogs out and got the cats. They were
in their nice little baskets. And we had two calves waiting and put the cats in one cabin,
Christina and I and our suitcases and the dogs and the other and drove off to the house here.
And where everyone was waiting. And you know, that we had two trucks here. The, the movers were here.
And then I saw what Patricia met. You could not walk in this house because of the boxes. It was
unbelievable. So the garage, I mean, the garage immediately, we decided was not going to take cars.
And I brought the Audi over since there's still a year on the lease and then I'll, you know,
I'll get rid of it after that. That has a great GPS. I love the GPS. It immediately recognizes
the UK and where I am. So I'm really happy with that. So I can focus on driving on the left hand side
of the road. Which, by the way, is the correct hand side. And I found out why. Because
back in the day when roads were kind of still first invented, I guess around these parts.
And you'd be on your horseback. Let's just say, I'm the night in shining armor. The white
night, of course, boogin' along right there on the left hand side. Because if I see all of a sudden
on the right hand side, there's the black night coming towards me. I want to draw my sword in my
right hand. So it makes a lot of sense to be riding on the left if I'm going to jouse this guy or
chop his head off while he's coming towards me. Unless, of course, I'm left handed, but I guess
pretty much in those days, everyone fought with their right hand. So that means that left is the correct
side to drive on. I presume. And you know what? It really doesn't matter. It's kind of funky
when you're turning corners or you're going around about, or definitely, I find myself waiting
being very cautious and then hammering the accelerator to make sure I get around the roundabout.
Because you go around in a different direction, yeah, you go around in a clockwise direction,
instead of counterclockwise. It's just getting used to it. And probably it's going to make me
smarter doing this because all the neurons are firing and reconnecting and trying to figure out
which way it goes. So I guess that's almost proven to make you smarter. So I'm kind of happy about that.
So we made a very conscious decision. What we already did that when we moved here, we said,
you know, guys, we, you know, we're going to get rid of a lot of our stuff. And now we have
totally gone all the way and we said, look, we're just going to get rid of all of this stuff.
You know, we have too many clothes, just too much shit. And we now have four full boxes
that are ready for for charity. And there was just a big charity kind of like a telethon on
last night, which is for the children. They do it every year here in the UK. It goes from,
I saw like 7 p.m. went to 4 o'clock in the morning. It was unbelievable.
Excuse me. So we have an address to send stuff. And, you know, we got like Gucci shoes.
And just we're rebooting our life, basically. And I'm so happy for it.
And notice I didn't throw out any of my or recycle or give away my technology bits. We got to keep
some of the stuff sane. But, you know, we got chairs and tables and desks and couches and just,
you know, too much. So we're getting rid of all of it. Can't use it. Give it away.
Give it away. Give it away. Now. Oh, by the way, you're listening to the daily source code.
It is 930 Saturday evening here in the United Kingdom at Curry Cottage. Let's see,
what else do we have to talk about? And I'm going to walk through the house in a bit and
admit it and give you just some of the, some of the highlights of it. And that you hear some of the sounds.
Oh, so we got in rather late or rather late. We're on 4 or 5 in the afternoon and, you know,
freaking out about all these boxes. And then we, you know, Patricia and I basically, you know,
found our bed between all the boxes, went to sleep, Christina slept in her own room.
Any von Patricia Sisters still here helping out. And the next morning, let's say around 10, 10 o'clock,
there's a ring at the doorbell. And it's a gentleman who says, hi, I'm from the, and I can't
remember what he said. It must have been the, it sounded like Homeland Security Department. But of
course, it wasn't. And he said, I'm here investigating for illegal animals that you brought into
the country. And we're like, huh, illegal animals. And of course, we had all the paperwork, but essentially
what happened is the airport where we landed. You know, so I guess someone noticed that we brought
all these animals out of the, out of the plane after the customs official had left called the,
and it's a big deal here, because they used to have quarantine for six months. And now you can
get in as long as your pets have been microchipped. They've got a passport. They have their rabies shots.
They have their tick and, and, and, and lint worms, uh, uh, uh, inoculations and all that. You've
got to have all this document. And so we had all of that. Um, so we had to go through the whole thing,
uh, and exactly what I thought it took about two hours. But the guys were really nice.
Now the guy had to come over with the, uh, with the microchip reader. I guess it was kind of an RFID chip
that they shoot into the pets, uh, neck or whatever. And, you know, registers, registers, registers,
everything all checked out. But wow, they don't mess around, man. And it, they used to be that
they would actually dispose of the animal immediately, if they caught it illegally in the country,
because they're definitely afraid. I've been, been that way for hundreds of years,
definitely afraid of rabies because basically you're on an island. And once you get that shit,
you can't get rid of it. Now, remember, they have more problems with agriculture, uh,
particularly foot mouth disease, uh, and, uh, and, uh, NBC, uh, mad cow disease, all those kind of stuff
that you just don't want happening on an island, uh, which makes imminent sense.
So let me see a couple of the things we had to do to get set up. Um, there was no connectivity.
There was no phone line. Um, uh, didn't even really, um, have any TV. There's no, uh, there was no cable.
Uh, cable is not, um, a big thing in the UK. Although it is around, hold on a second.
Just wanted to reset my, uh, audio hijack there. Um, so no cable in this area, although I,
case you can't get it if you want. Everyone basically has, uh, satellite TV sky is, uh,
is the big, uh, the big satellite provider. Except just recently, they came out with this new thing
called free view, which is free to air digital television. Let me see if I can explain this.
And so essentially, they still, um, you know, use areas and tennis and those one here, uh,
not on the roof, but uh, in the attic. Uh, so it gets a good enough signal to receive BBC
1 and BBC 2. And I think you can get Channel 4. There are three commercial stations,
ITV, Channel 4, and, uh, Channel 5. Um, and if you're in the right area in your antennas,
pointing the right direction, you can pick that up. What this free view is, and this is really cool.
It's, uh, basically you can buy a box, you buy it one, one off box for $40.
And you hook it up to your existing antenna. And what it does is it then goes and brings in
digital signal, which are being broadcast by the same TV transmitters that are broadcasting the
analog signal. Of course, only now you're talking 60 channels that are coming in free to air coming
right into this digital box. It's a great digital picture, great digital sound quality. And the only
things that you don't get, like the porn channel, you have to pay for extra. If you want an
MTV, it has to pay for that extra. If you want the, uh, Turner classic movies, you should pay extra
for that. But that's about it. All the rest is already on there. They've got sports. They got,
oh, there's no CNN, but, all right. So we've got, uh, BBC News 24. We've got Sky News. We've got,
uh, two other news channels. Because it's digital, there's that they even have a special setting
where you click it, and then it shows you four, um, news broadcasts at the simultaneously,
with the sound and the picture muted, except for the one you have highlighted. I mean, just amazing
shit. And then if you want to, you know, if you want to unlock any of these channels, it's just a phone
call. And then the, you know, given their, essentially your device is, uh, address number or whatever,
you know, like it's almost like a MAC address on, uh, on an Ethernet card. And, uh, and it'll open
it up. And you just take by credit card, every one of pay. And if you stop paying, it won't, uh, give
you that channel. So totally amazing. It really blew me away because, you know, there's no satellite
dish to put up. There's no, yeah, just none of that stuff. It's seem like there's so incredible
easy and so plug and play. It's just a slim little device that sits on the top. And it's like
antenna in antenna out. Power, boom, it's got a remote, and it works unbelievable. And have to say
the same for British telecom for the, for the phone system. We didn't have a, well, I thought we had a
phone line. I thought we had our phone number, although the previous, uh, tenant had basically
moved that number with them when they left. So I had to go to the neighbors, nice neighbors,
by the way, Jimmy, my neighbor here, he was a retired accountant. And, um, and so I used this phone
I called him and within, you know, I got through, I got to a real-life person with only had to go
through 10 menus, which is not bad. Um, and, you know, I explained the situation within 15 minutes,
our phone line was connected. It was rockin' ready to go. Um, couldn't order the, uh, VT broad
band just yet because after waiting till Monday to all the billing system cycle through. Um, so I
broke out the airport extreme, uh, got myself a dial up account, um, and just plug it into the wall,
which means I can basically, um, if no one's using the phone, uh, Christine and I can get online
do a little bit of email. I let my mail run pretty much for about two hours, uh,
last night just to get all the, uh, all the spam and filters and everything.
I can see that there's probably about 300 megs worth of audio comments that people have sent me,
um, that of course I couldn't download via telephone while I could, but I decided not to.
So when this is done, I'm going to go into town. It's just five minutes drive. I can actually stay
in the car to pick up the Wi-Fi, uh, and I should be able to, um, uh, upload, uh, from the car later on tonight.
So I'll probably go around 10 30 11 o'clock. Um, so I was really pleased with the phone.
And it's just all these options and it's, uh, you know, it's advanced, man. They really got their
technology down here. In fact, now I'm going for the cell phones. And of course, you need,
and unless you want to do a, a pay as you go and I'd rather just pay on a monthly contract, uh, we,
you know, our bank is still, uh, we got a retail bank here. So we're just getting an account open there.
Well, we need all that stuff to, um, to get the cell phones, but they've got, um, uh, third generation
not GPRS, but actually UMTS with voter phone live, uh, and, you know, you pay nothing between
handsets if you're on the same network. Excuse me. Damn. That's better. Um, but, uh, you can do
a video chat right from your mobile. And it really works. So, uh, I'm going to get those.
It's going to get three handsets for sure so that we can all be very cool together. Uh, the
same time I'm getting the BT broadband, which gives you, uh, voice over IP phone line in addition to
the one you already have, uh, I'm vibing, man. Just totally love the technology they've got going on
here. And it's all in English, by the way. In case you hadn't noticed. So, I don't know, is this,
uh, I wonder how this microphone sounds. I, it sounds like I'm probably getting a more intimate
feel than, uh, well, actually I'm going to switch over. Let's, let's listen to the
other mic for a second. Hold on. Okay. So, this is, uh, the one that you used to,
this is the love microphone. I'm going to use that to actually, why don't we do that now
since I'm wearing it? Uh, what do we have? 22 minutes. Damn, I've been yapping away.
So, we'll just, uh, do a quick little, uh, tour. My, um, study overlooks the front of the house.
Lucy, if I open up the window, is any? No, wind it all tonight. It was kind of stormy.
It was a bit stormy last night and it snowed a little bit.
So, let me just, let's go out here. So, this is, um, the hallway of the top. This is, uh,
our bedroom. You can hear the acoustics a little bit. Let's see, Christina's probably in her room.
No, I guess she's not, let me see. Nope. So, walk downstairs.
Christina's got the TV crank and that's what's going on.
Hello. I'm recording. I'm recording for the show. I'm recording for the show. I'm recording for the show
doing a tour of the house. What's this? Is it loud enough? We're all dead.
Is it loud enough? What is this? Is this, like idols?
Each, each jewelry member has several legs.
Oh, okay. All right. Okay. And now let's go out to the good show. Very good show.
Okay. Good. I'm just going to walk around to a little tour.
Oh, Sharon looks great. Excellent. Okay. New reality show on here.
So, this is the central hall. The dining room to your left.
Study right ahead. That says to be the TV hangout. Now we're in the kitchen. Kitchen is absolutely
phenomenal. Very happy with this kitchen. You know what? I'll just grab a coat and we'll go out for a
quick walk. Hold on a second. Okay. Here we go.
Okay. We'll do as we'll go out the back way. Okay. What I maybe I should put the mic
on the outside of the cup will be better. Okay. All right. This is the back.
Now what I'll do is I'm going to walk all the way out the back yard.
Let's see if we can pick up some cool sounds from what they call the downs. The downs is essentially
about 50 miles of land between here and the coast that is nature.
Okay. Some ramen at the gate. I hear a little bit there. Someone's got a
kind of machine running. Okay. Now we're walking back towards the house. It actually looks pretty
nice. I haven't seen it in the dark. Looks cozy. Go around the side. Out to the front.
And then from the front back in. It's dark here.
Mind your step. I should have a life clicking on here. Yeah. There we go. Okay.
Right. So now I'm at the garage. Here's the Audi walking down the driveway. It's a nice
cold sack with the end of it. Here a plane in the distance. Why not? Nothing with that plane.
And it's cold. Just about freezing point.
Okay. Let's go back in. Kind of get my bearings here myself.
So obviously we're not going to be doing a regular source code today where
play all kinds of cool clips and comments. That door's locked. But we will do that starting Monday.
And hopefully I'll have some kind of real connectivity here in midweek or maybe the end of the week.
Back in. Yeah. Okay. Reposition the mic. Go V.
Got really cold out. That's one thing. The weather is of course not going to be any better.
And then Belgium. But still I do get the plug in the phone line here. It's like
going online if I want to. Cool. Okay. I have the feeling that the
that it's somehow brighter. I don't know what it is. Well actually it probably is because we're
different altitude. There's actually hills, foot hills. You know, terrain here in the UK is
opposed to Holland, which is not only flat, but about 10 feet under sea level. Okay. Back up I presume
the mic picked that up all the way through. Let me just switch microphones. There we go.
Turn that one off. Perfect. So. All righty. So we're, what are we? 29 minutes into it. By the way,
even though I'm pancing, Don, you'll know, still haven't smoked. Yeah. Don has really helped me
with that. At least tobacco. And quite honestly I haven't smoked anything. I've only been
doing one split for day, just at night. Around this, this is about my time, you know, 10 minutes
to 10. So I'm pretty proud of myself, whereas, oh, that's been times in my life where I'd wake up at
you know, seven o'clock and have a nice little joint there with tobacco and with weeds. So I'm
really trying to work on my health. By the time you hear me this time next year won't be pancing as
okay. Let me see. What else do we have going on? The town is great. It's great being unknown.
It is absolutely fantastic because I can really be myself without being self conscious of people knowing,
you know, who I am, what I'm doing or, you know, if I make a joke, then people just take me at
phase value, not because I'm some, you know, some guy from TV. Now that by the way, may change
slightly as Thursday, you're not going to believe this. They called the BBC, we're freaking out.
So they wanted to, I told you the tape to got messed up of what they did at the castle.
So they then they wanted to do it at our place on Friday. Yesterday and I said, you know,
no way. It just can't be done. You know, we're too busy. Patricia's going to kill me.
Even if you don't show up, it's just too much moving going on. And they want to know if I
could come into London. I said, no, absolutely not. I can't come into London.
You know, you guys have to come here. So we kind of had it all set up for Friday. And then the
technicians at the BBC figured out how to get the the tapes working again. So I guess they can
be able to edit a piece after all. And it'll be on on the BBC on BBC 2 on the culture show.
This coming Thursday at 7 30 local time. And you can watch an archive of the show on
on the website at cbc.co.uk slash culture show. I believe I'll put a link up to it.
And I guess now that we have such good digital reception, I could probably get one of those
digital video recorders and record an impact myself. So yeah, I'll see if I can do that. Otherwise,
I'm sure someone will record it for us. And hopefully it'll turn out okay.
Hey, listen, I've been doing this for about 31 minutes now. So I was not to completely bore you out of
your skull. Well, I know we call it a day. And on Monday, hopefully I'll be able to bring you a
a regular source code with all the clips and bits and everything that you use to. So thank you very
much for your patience and for tuning into the source code. It's was your daily source code where
users and developers party together no matter what country we're in or what continent.
For Saturday, November 20th, 2004, 10 minutes to 10 and I am going to get out of here. Of course,
you can always leave your comments at adamantcurry.com or at live.curry.com. I webloor.
And for all the latest source codes and the archives, it's daily source code dot com. And of course,
the RSS 2.0 podcast feed is daily source code dot com slash RSS dot XML.
I will talk to you, Monday. Once again, from Curry Cottage in the UK,
until then, take it easy to get a good weekend. Bye bye.