Hey everybody!
No, like, hey everybody!
Hey everybody, indeed!
Welcome to the Daily Source Code for Tuesday, December 14, 2004, coming to you from Curricanage
in the United Kingdom of the Great British Isle.
It's your source code, let's party.
It's our source code.
It is intellect.
Some are beginning the question of this.
Is it the power of pure intellect or something completely unrelated?
Alrighty, it is coming up on the evening hours here and once again it's been quite a day of
excitement here in Good Old Guildford, UK.
I've had my trip to Starbucks to upload and download and transfer all kinds of
bits and bytes.
And I've got promos and pod-said music.
And a lot to talk about for users and developers as there's lots of stuff going on in the iPod
world.
It's about before.
I continue.
I want to play the entire promo that I started to show off with because it was so incredibly
cute.
Listen to that one more time.
Hey everybody!
No, like, hey everybody!
Alright, anyways, my next generation podcaster, my son Zika, learning how to do the
ever pod at.
Anyways, it's Earl from iampodcasting.com and just want to let you know the podcasts working
now.
So, stop on by, check it out and where we talk about how to market your podcasts and how
to make some dough with your podcasts.
We're just still in a need here.
Take care and we'll talk to you later.
Alright, Josh, since Zika to do the intro, you get to do the outro.
Let's hear your best boyly-ly-ly-ly.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, well, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Microphone that is we see does actually have a type rating on it somewhere. It says
That's stupid
And I spent all this money on getting the hyped up. Oh, here it is. Oh, no, I'm sorry. I have p799
It's the memory one gigabyte FCC ID
QDmi fp799
Battery 1.5 alkaline double a size times one a symbol in China
Okay, so I got this because what I liked about the specs. Well, first of all
It takes regular sized jacks the the Samsung yep that I was using before
Doesn't take a regular jack. It has to have like some mini mini plug its own proprietary cable
This one does have regular sized three and a half
Whatever jacks, you know the regular headphone and lining or mic jack. Here's what I like about it
First of all, I river it's like you know, I thought it was going to be like a really big
Independent kind of vibe of heard a lot of people about about the company and that they've got some good stuff going on
And they also I guess they do some video
Versions of this this is like one of those it looks a lot like the yep actually. It's kind of
You know triangular and shape and and tiny can slip right into your pocket
the interface
Wasn't too hard to learn basically it's got a file system and you route around the file system has a very rudimentary way of setting up a playlist
Other features which very much like you know, I told you this that has to be one chip said that it's just come out that everyone's
Using because it has a tune and FM tune or in it which you can record from
It does what I do like it has it can switch between a microphone on the the in jack or a line
And you can set your recording all the way up to I think a hundred ninety two
Kilbitz at a 44.1 case sample and that's really what interested me in it
Um
a couple of things are a little well some strange and summer outright disappointing
The first is it appears to be a USB one not a USB fast
USB 2.0
Which is all actually kind of a mood point because when you plug in this
The I River the 799 into the USB port on your computer at least on my Mac and I'm pretty sure it's gonna be the same on
Windows it doesn't mount your
Device as a drive as the yep did or as you'd expect with any other kind of like storage device
No, in fact you have to use their manager
Wait a minute. Let me see if I can bring that up. It's called the
I River music manager
Boeing bad Boeing because you know, I'm not like I'm managing podcasts here not music
So I want to talk about that and a few other rather strange things
But first let's get out to all the the positive part of
Of the I River is that on the built-in microphone
I was extremely impressed how well it functioned how well it could pick up a conversation
Because it's kind of most just made a plastic it you know you have to be careful shifting your fingers around if you're kind of holding it as a mic
In fact you'd almost want to have an extender
Beton that you could you like slip it into and then you know just use it as a microphone because I tried it out Sunday night with with Patricia here at
At Curry Cottage as she was cooking now she cooks almost every single night
I literally have to drag her away from the kitchen to say let's go eat out
She likes cooking and she enjoys it and now that we have a kitchen that I can kind of fit into and has more workspace
Yes, I too I'm
Following along I'm the sous chef du cotage. I am learning very much and here's and we've always talked about doing a podcast
We're Patricia would actually cook so this is not it, okay?
This is us basically drinking a glass of wine and her talking about dinner and we don't drink at all
So even one glass of wine kind of makes us a bit tipsy
But this is just a precursor to what it could be and it was a handy test at the same time
to check out the I River
Wait a minute what's the model the IFP-799 MP3 recorded this is recorded 64
Kilbitz and a 44.1k sample
As we were in the kitchen at the cottage Sunday night okay
Another test this is without the automatic gain control okay
All right
Today today dinner is
Pointy Cabbage pointy habit point
Well, there's a cabbage with a big point and we have sweet potatoes
Said like yes, which we gonna yeah, which we're gonna prepare with
butter
By the way
Check out the Madonna accent on Patricia there
Give the girl one glass of wine and she's the material girl butter cinnamon cinnamon sugar a little bit of nutmeg pepper and salt
Dash of milk
Skin hole
Whatever you prefer and then you can mesh mesh it and
I think it's a lovely combination with my pointy cabbage. Yeah, how are you preparing your pointy cabbage?
Also a little bit of nutmeg a little bit of a flower and a little bit of milk and
because I really diced it really small a
Piece of butter just really little piece of butter and some some pepper some black pepper
And we have some meat today the meat is a turkey thigh coming out of the oven
From Saintsbury that from Saintsbury nicely. It was two for one, but I forgot to buy to get the other one
I saw that oh my saw
Buy by one get one free and you want one, but you forgot your free one and I forgot my free one
Yeah, I'm not used to that, you know
Now because somebody else always did the grocery shopping
But how much better is it now that you do it yourself? Well, I think we have
I think I have a nicer
Fantasy
Oh, yes, we can't put yeah, nicer combinations and I think so and we
I've prepared it right now and he saw that and what the important thing is you go while you are cooking
Yes, have a nice
Glass of symphony out white symphony though. This is why it's it's pinky
We call it whites in from the I get ripped off
It's a car
It's oh, what do you think it's official colored? Yeah, it's not official. No, it's not
But um, make sure you have something to drink normally we don't drink, but it's always nice on a Sunday
And we thought why not it's called outside have a nice glass while you pretend dinner so
Enjoy
Cheers
Okay, so
The hell was that I was me turning it up oops, sorry about that
So in all
Considering that was just the built-in microphone, which sounds
Reasonably shitty. I tried one test with the automatic gain control on and it was all over the place like a
Big compressor, you know bringing up all the silent noises and you can set this thing
Basically that you can use it as a spy recorder and put it somewhere and
It can be voice activated or sound activated and it can record at this high quality of this quality that you just heard it can do 36 hours
You know, so it's it's perfect in a pinch just to carry around you know if you if you want to record something and you need to be able to
To get it at a good quality and know that it's gonna work. It'll be great and even better if you plug a real microphone into it
So but in a pinch it's it's perfect and I'll be using it some more
Also, you can just plug it into any any line out and you can record a really you know a decent decent sound
As an MP3 player itself, it's interesting because you know the interface you you really just looking around in this root file system in fact
It even says root and
So if you open up the
I river media manager
how man's this
lame they have it for windows and for
And for mac and tosh for OS 9 and OS 10
I don't want to mess with it right now. I'm opening up but basically what you have there is
A window and in that window it represents the same file system tree that you can kind of see in the device itself
And you can drag
Drag and drop folders and or files right in there and that's kind of cool because you know you drag it in
The downer as I said earlier is that it doesn't function like a USB drive
That's the way it should be it's just mounts a drive and drop it right in
So you have to go through this thing and I was like why the hell do I have to go through there particular window?
Which you know I haven't seen the API for it or any other information
It looks like that might be quite a barrier to entry and
Well even worse so because there are a couple of songs on it which were MP3s and one of them actually was really cute
It was like the I river song hold on let me just start this sucker up hold on a second
Yeah, there it is
Just go back
It's called I river
Catch
Hold on catch the digital
Flow foul
Catch the digital
Flow
So I thought that'll be cool. I'll play that on on the source code very everybody
Everybody
So I dragged it out of that little super duper window onto my desktop and it went bloom
Actually, I took a screenshot of it to include
Today with the hell that I put it oh man, don't tell me I lost that what happened to it
Oh
Hold on I'll do it again. Oh, no, I can't
Anyway, it basically I will find that that picture weight that I trash it by accident hold on
I see
How can that be I wouldn't have thrown that out that was too fucking good?
I'm bear with me folks. Let me just scan everything. It looks like it's definitely not here. Okay
Anyway, so it said cannot copy this because of digital rights management not allowed to copy like I would just want to play the song
And what I don't have is I don't have a wire that will connect
From the out well wait a minute. Do I have that? Do I have a wire that well? Oh, maybe I do hold on a second
What an excellent idea. We're gonna root around the
Hold on. I know how to do this wait let me in my bag. Oh
This is good. This is good. Okay, so I'm gonna rout around their digital
What am I looking for I'm looking for my
cables
Oh, she just love this
Okay, here it is. What's our time right now? How are we doing 14 minutes good? Okay. Yes, I do have one
I have a cable. So this is basically I'm gonna take this three and a half inch jack which is a part of my
second
This is a part of my
Wireless mic set on plug that into the power book here into the mic in all right. This is gonna be cool
Now take the
headphone jack out right
Now I just have to figure out
Let's see so
Let's get
Line in here. Oh, this is gonna be awesome. Oh, we're stealing from the man
Check it out everybody
Okay, we're gonna send it out to 16 perfect built in
Audio from line in oh, man. This is gonna rock if this works
Okay, hold on
Here it is. Let's see
Okay, oh hold on of course
I
Everybody rock out down
You
Hey kids was that totally worth it or what
There's more on here too
So anyway, so that that totally sucked and then
I thought that
That was actually recording an MP3 and what it does is it records in its own funky format and doesn't actually
Compress it into MP3 until you transfer what it will you drag and drop it out of this funky
I River MIDI music manager
Onto your desktop then it says do you want to make this an MP3? Would you like to leave it in this unrecognizable format?
So of course you choose MP3 so
Mixed feelings about this very mixed feelings like it a lot
But and you know it's like
I thought that you know these guys wanted to be different and all it seems that they're doing in the
Differentiation game is you know different digital rights management, but I'll play with it some more
Again using it purely for podcasting purposes trying to figure out you know what's what's the best
Stuff to use and for the past
Week of shows actually all of last week. I've been using audio hijack pro
I think I should tell you about my new setup
Ever since I got the breakout box which is the M audio two in
Eight channels out. I'm only really using it for the microphone inputs whenever we clean up my office here and I get the
Sennheiser when I find out where that is then we'll have a second, you know Mike that's plugged right in and
The great thing about this is I'm basically hijacking the audio interface sending it to the
To the headphones which I'm to the headphone jack in fact, which I'm wearing the headphones
So I can crank up the sound nice and loud
Haven't been able to do that because I was monitoring always monitoring off of the the Samsung yep as I was recording on to that
So now I have an array of effects all set up
Recording in AIFF and I compress to MP3 post show and I use the voice over plug in
to basically channel sound flower 16 where I send all of my
Quick-time players with MP3s anyone who knew with that just meant please write it down as we can
Gotify what the fuck I just
All right
So more
More fun tech stuff later on right now time for some music. I'm not very coral
Through Howard Reenstein and he was he was so kind now is to
Actually spell out his name because I've been this but I'm really good at bordering names
It's Greenstein g r e n s t e i n which of course. I'm sure I've said was Howard Reenstein or
Um, and I met him through the web
I think we I think we knew each other from the MTV days and
He basically
Well, I'll read you this email which is a part of the production show notes for today's source code out of my favorite rock star and sister
Barry corals about your release her second record
Our next record and would love you to premiere track on the daily source code next week
It's Barry's best for see record yet called confessions of an indie girl and it's officially available star
December 12th at www dot Barry corals dot com b a r i k o r a l
And the last time she was actually she toured in Europe for
Little promotional tour and I was doing the big radio show at the time and she came on the show and a perform live
Somewhere I still have that recording. I've been dying to dig it up. She's really talented
Great great sound
Totally right. I think for for pod safe music and more than happy to
Present to you aspiring angel by Barry corals
And think that he would all be less and not stuck comedy
I didn't know that every night when they wicked the best to me
Well, I just gotta get through this world
I'll just gotta get through this world
I just gotta get through this world
I've been inspiring many times
When new lessons feels like getting questions I'm all flat to read
Keep hanging on to the old that it might all come back for me
Well, I just gotta get through this world
I just gotta get through this world
I'm spying in the angel
Just the only girl
Not just the only girl
The people you've got love is hidden everywhere in the darkest nights
They're lining boxes that shine for you and you can't see the light
Well, I just gotta get through this world
I just gotta get through this world
I'm spying in the angel
I just got to get through this world
I just gotta get through this world
I just love hanging on to the old
Not just the only girl
Not just the only
On safe and nutritious and good for you, Barry Coral, the planetary premiere on the Daily
Source Code, aspiring angel more information about that in the production show notes for today's
Daily Source Code.
Today is Tuesday, December 14, 2004.
And briefly just today we went to look for Stables for Christina's horse or herpony, Princess
Arletta, who has been living back at the trainer's house, Luke's house for the past
a couple of weeks.
Christina was really antsy, of course she wants to see her baby.
So we've been looking around for Stables in the Guilford area.
This would be a major hint, anyone listening if you have any good ideas, something
close by, it'd be very nice.
We need like half-livery option, you know, during the week where they basically feed it so
it doesn't starve and then we can show up four or five times a week and ride and have fun.
But no, seriously, so we're shopping around, you know, it's a lot of horse-horse-suffices
here.
Can you tell that I'm not really a horse guy, but I really love my daughter who loves
her horse.
I do love her horse too, so we'll figure that out.
Something else that we've been dealing with in the past couple of weeks, noticed a growing
number of complaints about the accessibility of the daily source code MP3 files.
Now, in all basic probability, I'd say 99% certainty, this is because of the enormous
amount of subscribers to the show and we're seeing bits and pieces of the internet start
to creek and to crack.
And this is interesting because, well, you know, if this is happening to me now, it's
going to happen to other people very soon if it's not happening already.
And we're seeing some intermittent problems, basically what's happening is we're seeing
downloads of the show fail.
And Dave and I have been tracking this for quite a while.
We basically, in November, at BloggerCon, I did before BloggerCon, we bought servers,
as you probably remember, I was talking about that.
And we got one or two servers with unmetered bandwidth.
Now, it's a limited pipe, it's, you know, I believe it's 20 or 30 megabits.
But in essence, you can pump only so much through it so that the 30 megabit pipe, but
you can do that all day long without any penalty.
And we have a couple of shows running on that server.
The big ones, of course, would be source code, dawn and drew morning coffee notes and
trade secrets.
What we're seeing is these downloads fail and there's a whole bunch of different thoughts
and ideas and really after doing a test today and before this show went up, I actually
pinged the list that, of course, I'll point to in the production show notes, the list
that the Dave set up, the little comment list there, where people could check to see
how it was coming in from there different locations.
We're seeing that most browser transfers are going quite well.
Some of the iPodter clients, sometimes they'll break, sometimes they'll stop, then it'll
be, and it's really it's unreplicable.
You can't really figure out what the problem is.
I'm pretty sure it's not going to be the iPodter clients because, you know, that's just
and everyone's making an HTTP call, so it's somewhere along the line, it's failing.
I don't know a lot about networking in bandwidth, this is also not Dave's area of expertise,
but we have gotten a number of very good comments and good information.
The basically says, okay, well, the problem is you're sitting on a tier three provider
and, you know, the bandwidth that you've purchased is basically crap or not, you know,
there's no service level agreement, perhaps, or, you know, there's a whole bunch of
different issues that have to be looked at.
That's part of the problem.
You know, also, we're just, we're growing, you know, this stuff is getting so big,
that it's going to come down to, well, a couple of different ways to solve it, eventually,
I think there's just not going to be any other way, but to go with, you know, 100% bit
torrent integration and everyone has to be able to support it and it has to work.
And I think I'm going to start using bit torn pretty soon because no matter how many
providers we get, you know, eventually, I think, when to get up to this point where it's
just going to start breaking because there's too many iPod or clients and people who are interested
in subscribe to the show, trying to get these MP3 files simultaneously, so spreading it out
in a P to P fashion makes a lot of sense to me.
Something that the, that the iPod of developers could do, it would certainly help me and
and don and drew, and I'm sure more to come as the bandwidth crunch gets worse.
And having developed an iPod or I know that this is something that may not, it's just
basically a loop that you, that you could put into the program.
If the download fails, it would be great if the iPod or client could not say, you know,
skip it or put in the cash is not there or gone or whatever, but maybe you could go back
in half an hour or 45 minutes and try it again or just some random time.
And also, I, and I saw iPod or X do this, it sets up random times of grabbing the
file for, you know, your iPod or goes out, not at the top of the hour, but at a random
time that it's set, excuse me.
So all that stuff is really going to help, and yeah, that would be the number one, the number
one cool thing that we could do with our iPod or clients is to have some kind of
resumable functionality.
And I think that let me see Doppler had it in there.
I'm looking at the comments here that, of course, are in the, in the show notes.
Let's see this is from Erwin from Doppler Radio.net.
Welcome early and flanders this day, download your lady, latest daily source code, heard
you talk about download problems with a daily source code.
I'm happy to tell you that Doppler 2.0, which I will release into the wild, is, supports
resuming downloads, also known as byte-ranging.
There you go, which helped me a lot to overcome the download stalling problems as you described
in your podcast.
Okay, thank you very much, Erwin.
That would be great if we could get the other iPod or developers to do that.
Because this is something that's, if it's happening to me, it's, you know, and of course,
I'm going to work on finding new bandwidth solutions, and it seems only logical that
we're going to run into, you know, bandwidth providers who are going to have some great ideas.
But in the meantime, it would be great if we can definitely help each other by, you know,
working around some of the, the nuttiness of the internet, if stuff breaks, that we can go
back in kind of unbreak it, or at least try to still deliver on the promise.
I'm also, hold on one second, and I just, sometimes I got to hijack the signal again,
because I delay set signal.
That's when you basically hear me talk like I'm drunk, that's when the delay sets it on
my headphones.
I got to figure out why it's doing that.
That's not right.
It also is going to say, um, but we had that about, oh shit, I don't know.
You know what?
You know what I need right now?
You know what I really need?
Put your hands on your iPod or your MP3 player at this moment, my brothers and sisters,
and feel more cowbell.
After a series of staggering defeats, Blue Oyster called assembled in the recording studio
in late 1976 for a session with fame producer Bruce Dickinson, luckily for us, the cameras
were rolling.
Alright guys, I think we're ready to lay this first track down.
By the way, my name is Bruce Dickinson, yes, the Bruce Dickinson, and I got to tell you
if fellas, you have got what appears to be a dynamite sound.
Coming from your Bruce, that means a lot.
Yeah, I mean, you Bruce Dickinson, this is incredible.
I can't believe Bruce Dickson digs our sound.
These guys, I put my pants on just like the rest of you, one leg at a time.
Except once my pants are on, I make gold records.
Alright, here we go.
If you don't feel the reaper, take one roll, one, two, three, four.
Wait, wait.
First, could you come in every second, please?
That camera's going to be a great track, guys.
What's the deal?
Are you sure that was sounding okay?
I'll be honest, fellas, it was sounding great, but I couldn't use the little more cowbell.
So, let's take it again, and Jean, really explore the studio space this time.
You got a Bruce?
Really?
Yeah.
Explore the space.
Okay.
I like what I'm hearing.
You're all there.
One, two, three, four.
Stop, Bruce, I'm sorry, could you come back in every second?
Fellas.
No.
We just wasted two good tracks.
This last one was even better than the first, but it's just that I find Jean's cowbell playing
distract.
I don't know.
If I'm the only one I'll shut up.
No, it's pretty rough.
You know, I can pull it back a little if you like.
Not too much, though.
I'm telling you, Fellas, you're going to want that cowbell.
I'm gonna drag.
You know what?
It's fine.
Let's just do the thing.
Roll it.
One, two, three, four.
Come on, Jean, don't do that.
No.
That, that, it doesn't work for me.
I gotta have more cowbell.
Don't blow this forest, Jean.
Could be, could be itself a scene.
Can I just say one thing?
There, baby.
Just say it.
I'm stare at here, stare at rock legend, Bruce Dickinson.
A cock and a walk, baby.
And Bruce Dickinson wants more cowbell.
We should probably give him more cowbell.
Hey, baby.
And Bobby, you are right.
Ambex selfish.
But the last time I checked, we don't have a whole lot of songs
that feature the cowbell.
I gotta have more cowbell, baby.
I'm gonna be doing myself with the service.
And every member of this band, if I did perform the hell out of this.
Guess what?
I got a fever.
And the only prescription is more cowbell.
Thank you, Bruce.
I think if I just leave and maybe I'll come back later,
and we can lay down the cowbell on, baby.
Jean, wait.
Why don't you lay down that cowbell right now with us together.
Do you mean that, Eric?
Yes.
Thanks for all of us.
Thank you.
Baby, before we're done here,
y'all be wearing gold-pitted diapers.
What does that mean?
Never question Bruce Dickinson.
Go.
One, two, three, four.
Yeah, everybody.
Class, et cetera.
All right, mine.
Lou, it's the call.
And of course, Christopher Walken, need more cowbell.
And it also, so typifies the big,
with Dave calls the monoculture of entertainment.
We have the producer of Walken, the legendary Bruce Dickinson,
who I only know is,
Bruce Dickinson from Iron Maiden, I guess.
And needs more cowbell.
Need more goddamn cowbell, otherwise it'll never be a hit, gentlemen.
Need more cowbell.
Love the cowbell.
I wrote this down with a link to a post here.
Okay.
We were talking about the yesterday, actually, after I posted the source code,
I was saying, you know, in the source code itself,
I talked about the opml files and how we're going to link that together.
And all of a sudden it hit me, or at least the part of it hit me after,
you know, after we were talking about it,
and I was listening back to the show,
I kind of sample through it and listen to different bits,
listen to the sound levels.
And it hit me like, wouldn't it be cool?
So here, so let's presume that from the directory.
And when I say the directory, I kind of mean it like a big virtual thing.
Yeah, it's the directory that's at the ipod.org site,
if you go to podcast directory or podcast directory.
You'll see the directory and I filled up a couple more.
I have a backlog about 150 new podcasts that have to go in,
just from this past week and a half alone.
So working on that.
And if it takes too long, ping me again,
let me know there is a suggestion link, please.
But there's lots of stuff still flowing in there
through all of the multiple nodes that I'm not maintaining at all.
But it's also the same directory that you see in the ipod or x ipod or client,
in the ipod or 11 client, in jpod or in most of the ipodters,
because it's a format that programmers, developers can use,
and kind of, you know, it's a consistent format,
so they can pull stuff in and use that,
and it makes it easy for you to subscribe.
They can glean new data from that.
The ipod or x top picks and most subscribe to databases,
a combination of their information and our data.
So, you know, we're trying to share as much of this as possible.
And what would be cool, of course, if you have your show nodes,
as a part of that directory.
So that's one part, which I'm trying to figure out.
So basically, you should have an attachment.
If you're in the directory, and again,
it could be an HTML version of that directory.
In an ipod or on your mp3 player itself,
there you should be able to drop down into the next level,
which is basically my production show nodes.
And here's the cool thing.
So let's say, like yesterday, I forgot half of the things
that I was supposed to, you know, post along there,
and links, and other mp3s to link to,
wouldn't it be cool if all you did,
if you saw something in my outline,
basically my production show nodes and said,
oh, I have information for Adam on that.
And you sent me a link to an opml file itself.
I could copy paste that right in,
and would expand the information that I don't have,
so you can contribute to it.
So we have this big metadata thing
that we're, you know, basically it's connecting
a tree to each other.
It's a lot like weblogs kind of tilted on its side, I guess.
I know if that makes any sense, but I got pretty excited
by the idea that you could add just like you're adding
a directory with an opml file,
you can add information to my podcast show nodes,
which will basically show up anywhere.
They'll show up in the directory,
in the HTML version of the iPod or directory,
but they can flow out to anywhere that the directory is being used.
And you can kind of walk along this directory
and do all kinds of cool things where you can look for new stuff.
You could search it.
It's really wonderful the way I understand it,
which is still quite minimal.
And then I just want to leave you with a couple of things.
Well, first let me hit you with this one,
because this is another great of
another piece of great work from our daily source code listeners,
as we almost wind down the show for today.
Hey, they're Adam.
It's fun time Ben over a tracks up the tree.
Just sending you this audio comment to tell you
that I'm going to be at the Bitty's Holiday Party.
This Tuesday, December 14th,
at the living room.
You mentioned it on your show,
and I said, hey, I should be there
being that I'm a Manhattan resident,
or at least I work in Manhattan.
Hi, Adam.
It's Dan, fun time day in,
from fun time Ben's tracks up the tree.
Podcast.
I just want you know,
I've been sitting in the other room,
and Ben has been in here recording over and over
and over again,
his audio comment that he wants to leave for you.
He wants to get it just right.
But it's taking him a while.
So this is what I thought I'd do.
I just want to come in here and let you know
that fun time Ben would love to invite you
to join him for a,
the Sylvie's Bitty's show at 11 o'clock
in the living room at New York City.
I'm at those street.
I think it's 145.
Let me say I've heard about 700 times
that I think it's 145,
let those street.
Sorry, 154,
And he would love to meet you
if you'd like to come down and see the show.
And he's going to be wearing,
he's always in Britain.
He's not coming to the show.
Then why are we leaving this audio?
I'm inviting the audience.
Oh, sorry.
Adam.
I'm sorry.
We're inviting the audience.
I didn't hear that part from the other room.
700 times.
But he's going to be wearing a yellow shirt
with unicorns making love on it.
And that's how you'll know it's him.
Yellow T-shirt, right,
with two unicorns making love.
So dear listeners and Adam,
thank you so much for your time,
your patience,
and we hope to see you at the show.
All right.
Take good care.
Bye-bye.
Don't say I can't go with other boys.
And don't tell me what to do.
Don't tell me what to say.
Please, when I go with you,
Don't we be on this planet?
You don't don't need me.
Don't try to change me in your grave.
Get out on me.
Don't time me down because I'll never stay.
Bye-bye.
Don't try to change me in any way.
Don't tell me down because I'll never stay.
I don't tell you what to say.
Don't tell me what to do.
Just let me be myself.
That's all that I ask of you because I'm young.
Yet I'll love me.
I'm free.
And I need to be free.
To live my life the way that I want to say.
And do whatever I please.
You don't own me.
You never have.
You never will.
You don't own me.
Check it out.
Be these backmasking.
Oh, that's for me, everybody.
Remember I was telling Analy.
We'll interview you for a while that the biddies did a backmasking song.
Let's play that backwards and see what they say.
Here it comes.
Can I do that?
Yeah, here we go.
Play backwards.
That was kind of disappointing.
What the hell was that?
Good night.
That's what they're saying.
Backwards.
Tonight at the living room in Manhattan.
It's the most serious bitties make sure you catch the show.
And that's it for the source code for today.
You're walks over.
A little bit long, but you deserve the long walk.
I just want to leave you with a thought that Ron Bloom.
Dave and I have been talking with considering our new venture and podcasting,
where we see each other at the beginning of the new year.
You know, the iPod really made it hip to download music.
But it's the podcast that you're determined just how hip you really are.
Depending on what you have on your iPod.
Or comfortable and be three players.
With digital rights, music player management crafts.
All right, everybody.
Tomorrow I will be back.
We've got Clark Boyd from Boyd.
Boyd from WGBH coming into town into Lovely Gillford.
Doing a piece about me and my lack of bandwidth.
Oh, British telecom.
You're going to love this because it's a co-production with the BBC.
Oh yeah.
What was the chairman's name again?
Thank you.
Everybody.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.