The Power of Dark.
Coming to you, Dritz.
From Curry Castle in Belgium, it is...
The power of your influence.
I've got a lot lined up for you today.
In fact, today is a special day because if everything works out with the technology in,
then I'll be recording the new show that I've been teasing in the past week.
It's a show with a co-host.
And I actually tested out some of the technology locally here today.
And it works.
Looks like I'm going to be able to record both of us,
almost as if we're sitting in the same room.
Although, believe me, there's no one else here in Belgium
I would want to do that show with.
So first, that's clearly somewhere else.
And we've got a name.
We're working on a tune.
And today we're going to record.
And if it turns out OK, then we broadcast it.
But basically, this will be a show.
and we talk for however long it is, no longer than an hour, certainly, and then we end it.
Anyway, this is the source code, something completely different.
It's where users and developers party together, and if you've ever seen my weblog at curry.com,
then you've probably seen the title of my weblog, it wasn't say Adam Curry's weblog,
but underneath it says, there are no secrets, only information you don't yet have.
And boy, that really came true.
Yesterday here in the Netherlands, a respected news organization, RTL News,
announced that they had obtained the national budget,
let's see, three days before its embargoed release to the press.
And the way this works here, we have what they call Prince Day, Princeius Dach,
and that's the third Thursday in September,
and that's when the Minister of Finance presents, he has a little briefcase actually that says
Thursday in September he presents the budget, the budget for the coming fiscal year and
the Queen does her annual how-to-do and she talks about, it's basically a state of the
union or a state of the kingdom address and RTL News somehow obtained the entire document
so which basically says, you know, here's what the minister of economics is planning
on doing and here's what the government is planning on doing in 2005, giving of
course everybody kind of a head start, a weird head start since you're not really
supposed to hear this until everybody hears it on Thursday but then again, you
know, there's no secrets, right? And it's, I think it's going to cause quite a stir.
I also think it's pretty unbelievable that even though the press got a hold of
it and they really didn't even discuss much in the in the documents on the
RTL News, they said, hey, here it is, they did, they made it available via
download on their website which almost impossible to get because it would just
got totally swamped and
They didn't really discuss much of the content. It seemed like the scoop of them having it.
The fact that someone had leaked that to them was the story all by itself and what almost went
unnoticed is what's in the budget. By the way, not really good. Let me see. Oh, yes. Slash.
Pointed to ipodder.org yesterday. Now the correct verbiage I believe is that I was slash.
Or we were slash dotted ipodder.org. This happened to me I think once, maybe twice before.
And it's really fun because you notice it. Your email starts pinging with all kinds of people
responding to whatever the site that's linked to. Sometimes you get all kinds of messages that
your servers are burning out and running down. Now in this case, I have to say the load was not
on me because ipodder.org is actually hosted by Radio Userland when you buy Radio Userland.
You get, I think it was $35 a year.
You get an annual license for radio user land
and all their updates.
And you get storage.
And I think I've purchased additional storage,
but you get a certain number of MEGs that you can use.
And since iPod.org, I just kind of routed that as a category
for my web blog.
By default, it goes to the user land server
and it held up beautifully.
So thank you very much user land.
May I say, well worth the price of admission for that service.
I didn't go unnoticed by some of the other folks
who were working on iPod.org and on programs
and shows of their own.
Dave Slusher, who brings you the evil genius Chronicles,
noticed that iPod.org got slash dotted.
And he had some remarks about it,
which I thought were pretty funny and some things
that I also noticed as well.
I'm going to play a bit of Dave's audio blog,
or actually his show from yesterday,
which was titled Mr. Microphone.
We're going to skip the Mr. Microphone.
and listen to him about slash dot what he feels about it.
slash dot is what it is in general. It's interesting. So here's Dave Slasher from evilgeniuschronicles.org.
Today, the iPodder link was slash dotted. And you know, I used to read slash dot a lot,
and I just kind of stopped. And for a similar reason that I've actually considered stopping
reading boing boing, which is that all the really good stuff that I care about comes
in from either was from other sources that I already read before it was there,
or somebody's going to post a pointer to it. And both of them have a lot of crap that I just could not give a shit about if I tried.
You know, on boing boing, it's, you know, Cory Doctro, God love him, great guy, great writer.
Man, if I see another post about Disney, I am just going to vomit Mickey Mouse ears.
You know, I don't give a shit about Disney. And I especially don't care, you know,
I post seven posts every day about Disney and Disney World and Roy Disney and Michael Eisner.
Who gives a fuck? Fuck this.
Disney. So, you know, and so, you know, if I were in like, Jenny Jordan or however you
pronounce her name, you know, robots and objects shaped like Hello Kitty, you know, after a
while, Jesus Christ, how many things can be, you would assume that eventually Sanrio will
shape everything, including, you know, enema balls, be like the, you know, the Choco
Cat enema ball. So, after a while, the novelty is not there anymore. Now, were
I a boing-boing contributor, everyone would get sick of seeing more like
Mexican wrestling stuff, you know. No one else cares as much about your fetishes.
That's the nature of the fetish. But I get tired of it. And same thing with
Slash. After with Slash. It's mainly the commenters. And the only reason I ever
got a Slash. account in the first time, because I really don't care that much.
And I once cared and I just stopped. So that I can log in to my account and
then just put the comment threshold up to five. And often I don't, I just
go out of my way to not even scroll down low enough to see the comments.
And if you look at the comments that are kind of on that iPod or post,
it is prototypical for the horseshit.
It just makes me not care anything about slash dot comments
because you could easily machine generate all the threads on there.
You have like a probabilistic script that will say,
okay, certain percent will say, that's already been done.
Certain percent will say, is that all there is?
And a certain percent will make stupid jokes about something
and a few will be completely unrelated.
And a few will tell other people what an asshole they are for thinking this.
It's just nothing to it.
If that was the only thing I knew about online communities
was slash dot comment threads,
I would think that was the worst shit in the world.
Why does everybody talk about this? This is nothing.
So it's amazing to me.
The kind of, it seems like, you know, I don't know what percentage of people actually leave comments.
I'm guessing probably, you know, 0.1%.
Almost everybody reads and probably very few people leave the comments.
So you kind of self-selected for a certain kind of person.
And that kind of person, one is kind of an asshole.
And two, has really bad reading comprehension.
I don't know why everyone on there, for like the first 100 comments, seems to think
the iPod has something to do with streaming, either outputting streaming or reading in streaming,
when that's sort of not quite the opposite, but almost the opposite of what it's really about.
It's not about streaming.
So that was something.
And I just hope the slash dot storm, you know, doesn't kill Adam's bandwidth on it.
Hopefully, you know, the fraction of people who are actually interested will kind of stick around
and the assholes will move on, as assholes do.
As I said, Bandwidth wasn't too bad on my end because I paid my $35 and I got a good deal
out of it.
But indeed, it's funny because I was talking to Dave Weiner a couple days ago about, I
don't know how we got to talking about it.
I said, you know, it's so hard, often to be taken seriously.
This by the way is, you know, don't cue any violins for me.
Oh, wait a minute, maybe we should.
That'd be kind of cool.
Hold on a second.
Let me see.
I wonder if I have any violins.
When it hun.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Nice cup of tea.
from my wife.
Uh, let me see.
I've got some.
Do I have any violins?
Come on.
Give me some violins.
How about...
So...
That's not sad enough.
Let's try this one.
So whenever...
I try to post something seriously, it...
I just don't get taken seriously.
Did I still talk about my...
What the Queen?
Downtown Julie Brown.
Enough of that.
OK, looking at the iPodder developer mailing list,
which is great because this is anything but a developer
mailing list.
It's for developers and users.
And because of the slash dot link,
a lot of people have been catching on to what we're doing.
And one thing that says a lot of talk about within the
iPodder community is about screen scraping.
And part of this is due to, I guess, is iSpider.
I think it's the iSpider program that will allow you
to subscribe to RSS 2.0 files with enclosures.
But also, if you just give it a URL,
we'll scrape that, the HTML, and we'll
download any MP3 that's attached to it.
And Dennis, who has a great site called scrapfeeds.com,
which for RSS is absolutely fantastic if a site doesn't
support it but you do want to subscribe to it.
He's also jumped into the conversation.
I have to say, I'm not for the screen scraping.
I think it's great.
People talk about how you can do it with.
Excuse me, regular expressions and therefore also download other files except for mp3s
that are on a web page.
But that's kind of beyond the point.
Then we should call this ice scraper.
The whole point is that you get something that you know is going to be there, it's
going to be there more or less consistently as long as you're subscribed and consistency
depends upon the published times and dates.
But for serendipity maybe, just to have a feed of stuff like the blog digger feed,
that's fine.
I love getting stuff just kind of out of the blue.
But I think the whole point is we have to get the solid base down first of subscribing
to RSS 2.0 files with enclosures.
Or any, if Adam is out there, ATOM and they have enclosures, we're going to have to
support that as well.
I think that's where we need to support to start.
Something else that I think is great, I forget who mentioned this, but OPML support.
And I think this is probably
the perfect way to deal with the subscriptions because we kind of been and I think you know
also this has been tried right you know the with web blogs the little orange white on
orange XML icons it's not going to get much easier than you know the way we do it now
by just having a feeds dot text file or whatever and adding a an RSS URL to an RSS and that
file however if we have OPML that could be interesting because with OPML then you
can read in collections of
subscriptions and you could also open up that
OPML file in an outliner. It should be any outliner that supports it
but you know there are a lot of good ones out there that already support OPML.
You can easily manage your subscription. So I think that's something good that we
should be looking at.
And I got an email. Let's see. This is from Andrew Clark.
See where's Andrew from? I don't remember. He's talking about
the long-term of actually starts off by saying I think in the long-term
storing MP3s in a web server won't really scale. He's done the math and he says my
daily source code MP3 is already total 438 megabytes for just one month of shows.
I don't know if I've been at it for a whole month, maybe half a month.
And he says well sure that's not a problem for Adam but it may be for a lot of people.
So what he eventually winds up saying is you know this is and by the way I
don't think the storage is a problem because even if you're using BitTorrent
which is what he leads up to.
You're still going to need the storage, whether that's locally or on a server.
Granted, most people don't have the luxury of a server sitting somewhere with just gobs
of gigs laying around to be filled up.
This is definitely a problem and I think BitTorrent is indeed the way to go.
So the next step is how do we publish RSS files and their enclosures?
What do we put in the BitTorrents?
How do we get it from A to B?
That's a really big step that we have to take because it's not the storage that necessarily
is the problem.
It's the bandwidth.
You don't want to know what kind of bandwidth I'm pushing.
It's unbelievable, especially after the iPod or slash dot.
A lot of people start listening to the source code and every single time someone fires
up a new install of iPod or boom, they're going to get 10 of my files.
So that's roughly around 200 to 300 megs.
So you can do the math on that.
Obviously that's not going to scale.
I think BitTorrent is totally the way to go.
So I'm looking forward to anyone integrating
any type of BitTorrent functionality into an iPodder.
And I bet you there's someone out there
who knows just how to do it.
A little bit of politics on the source code for today
is we're 15 minutes into the show,
really based upon two pieces of audio
that I want you to hear.
It's about Bush.
And the first bit that I'm going to play for you,
about three minutes.
And the great thing about the show, of course,
or any show within the iPod platform
is if you don't like what you're hearing,
you just skip ahead, right?
It's just like Tevo, real simple.
But I think you'll be pretty enthralled to listen to this.
It's a BBC radio documentary.
Now, I listen to the BBC World almost all the time.
We get it on AM, or you can get it on AM
in almost all of Europe.
And I think you can get it online.
You can listen to them as well, bbcworld.com.
You think it would be .co.uk, but it's bbcworld.com.
And they do great.
I mean, just phenomenal documentaries.
And this is one of their radio documentary series.
And it's about the Skull and Crossbones Club.
I guess it's a fraternity at Yale.
And the reason for them to go find out about the Skull and Crossbones Club is because three
of the past four presidents were members of the Skull and Crossbones.
So that would be George Bush Sr., Jr. and John Kerry.
So if he's elected, of course, then, oh, wait, that was presumptuous of me.
And so this reporter took a little trip out to the Skull and Crossbones headquarters and
spoke with some people there and actually walked up to the door and just gives a little
bit of insight about this very, very secretive organization and what's behind it.
Now what I need to do is figure out where this came from because it is from the BBC.
I know that, but it was delivered, how do I find it?
Probably another blog digger score.
So I don't feel comfortable just republishing it in its entirety.
It's about 28 minutes long.
So you'll have to hunt around for it.
But it was apparently released on the 12th of September 2004.
It's called Scullin Crossbones.
Listen to this piece.
I think you'll enjoy it.
My search for the secrets of Scullin bones begins on a wet spring afternoon on the Yale
campus.
My guide is Peggy Adler, a tenacious researcher who helped investigate the Iran Contra scandal
in the 1980s and has been probing into Scullin bones for almost 20 years.
We're on the way, Scullin bones headquarters intriguingly named Tomb on one of Yale's main
thoroughfares.
So this is on the left.
That's right.
I see white smoke too.
That's like smoke.
I mean it seems very appropriate weather that we're in the middle of this storm.
There's thunder every now and then.
Look at this building which does look, it's quite an imposing, quite a dark looking
building isn't it?
Right in the middle of the campus.
Should we take a closer look?
You can if you want.
Yeah.
I'll stay here.
Why don't you want to come up?
I just feel that since I live locally and continue to be cited in articles by name that I'll
just stay on the side of the street.
You don't want to come up there and knock on the door?
Oh no no no.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
It's Sunday when the 15 members of Scullum Bones normally meet and it's their last
chance before the university breaks up for the summer.
We waited for the chance to see the Bonesmen and ask them what actually goes on inside
and there was an added attraction.
Pop Bonesmen was in town.
Another and George W. Bush here for his daughter's graduation the next day.
Okay well I'm just going to go inside.
Well close like hand to the two.
Just coming up these steps and there are these huge double black doors that must be
about 15 feet high surrounded by concrete pillars and then there's two big padlocks.
obviously saying.
Have a check.
They are definitely not.
There's no way of getting in here.
I'm not going to do anything.
The building is hard to miss, a 50 foot high windowless mausoleum of grey stones squatting
in the middle of Yale's campus.
The rules of the club forbid any non-member from ever going inside, but Peggy's come pretty
close. She was part of a team that successfully recorded part of the initiation ceremony that
takes place in the tombs courtyard.
Okay, you have the doorway here. Then to the right you have a hedge and then you have an
evergreen tree. If you follow that line straight back, courtyard's in there.
So that's where they have the ceremonies in the courtyard.
The outdoor part of it, part of it was indoor. So we only got to see the outdoor part.
We only got to listen to the outdoor part. God only knows what went on indoors.
And what did you hear? What was it? You know you managed to
forget this unique access. Oh, it was disgusting. It was rough. I mean, they were pretending
to murder people. What was the tone of it though? Was it, was it joky or is this one?
It was just, no. It wasn't joky at all. It was, it was sick. But they only could describe
it, it was sick.
What you're hearing is the first recording ever made of the Scullum Bones initiation ceremony.
It has never been broadcast before.
15 new members of the club.
Okay, I'm going to stop this bit here.
So, fascinating stuff to listen to.
Although, I have to be honest.
Well, first of all, isn't it great the way the BBC does this?
You know, it's a beautiful accent.
The Schollenberg Club on the Yale campus.
It's just, oh man, could you read the phone book for me
and just let me listen to it?
That'll be nice. An audio book or the phone book
done in proper English. That'll be very nice.
So, it's a good listen if you can find it.
I'll see if I can find a place to point to it on my web blog, obviously.
And I have to be honest that, you know, to the Brits maybe
or someone who doesn't know what college fraternities are like
and initiation, you know, all that screaming may seem
a little wacky and a little violent and whatever.
But personally, I went to college for, hmm, see, three and a half months.
I was at Salem College in West Virginia.
My roommate Tyree was from Hamilton, New Jersey.
Hamilton was from Newark, New Jersey. His name was Tyree.
Hamilton. The college was about 60% black and since I was from Holland I wasn't white and
I faithfully pledged Kappa which was an interesting initiation, you know, carrying around a brick
and stuff like that. So that doesn't freak me out too much but the whole story is just
interesting to listen to, particularly when you think about how many US presidents in
recent history have been bones men or members of Skull and Bones. And something else that,
well this is a total political statement, not by me by the way, but something I picked
up from MixFreaks.org. Not quite sure who made it, but it's another wonderful montage.
It's kind of an audio version of a Michael Moore. But it's just, it's a, it's a,
it's well done. It's a great mix. It's George Bush and I want you to listen to it. It's
only two and a half minutes and we still have a whole song of the day to come. But
check out the death of democracy. If you think that your kid is not ready for certain
kinds of environmental simulation, I think it's okay to talk about that.
Ladies and gentlemen, the president of the United States
Death of democracy for the American people
This credits their narrow ideology
We will make this an age of war and misery
Progress must end
I've come here tonight to report to all Americans
tolerated such an opportunity death of democracy for the American people discredit their narrow
ideology
of Americans.
their narrow ideology, death of democracy for the American people.
We will make this an age of war.
Killing is necessary.
necessary. Killing to achieve our goals. Killing is necessary. Chaos to ensure our money is
spent wisely and effectively. Killing to achieve our goals. Killing is necessary. Chaos to
achieve our goals. Chaos is necessary. Killing
of democracy.
Progress must end.
Death of democracy.
Dictatorship is a massive undertaking.
will be respected. Thank you all very much.
Okay, you can get that from a link on mixfreaks.org.
Very nice by the way that the metadata was put into this MP3 or the ID3 tags.
So that means that I can look it up right now as I see encoded by Lane.
URL link.
Oh here we go.
www.hz37land.com.
So hz37land.com.
So I guess that's 37 Hertz is the name of the artist and the composer.
Let's see any comment.
Is there a comment in here?
Produced or range engineered, mixed and edited by hence 37 Hertz Zimmerman.
See how cool that is.
Okay, let's see the album export more violence.
God.
Oh man.
Alrighty.
Okay.
Oh I want to do a little techno geek test with you guys.
I'm going to check my phone system here because now I've got Skype all set up where I should
be able to make a phone call directly from my computer and record it.
What I'm going to do here is I'm going to call my wife.
Let's see if she can hear me, if you can hear me, and if we can hear her.
Okay.
Connecting.
be pretty cool if it works.
Still connecting.
Okay.
We need, yeah, we need here.
We need a little dialing music on a second.
A little dynamic music for you while we try out the Skype connection here.
We're gonna try it again.
That's ringing.
Cool.
I can hear it ringing in the other room.
Hello.
Hi, hon.
Hi, babe.
I was just testing my system.
I know.
It works.
Crazy person.
Thank you, hon.
You're such a crazy person.
Yes, all right.
Bye bye.
Love you.
Okay.
It works.
So that means that I can call out and talk to people on the phone.
And it means that if I have someone else on Skype call, we can talk to each other for free.
Excellent.
I posted a screenshot of my harvest on my weblog yesterday.
You remember we talked about that.
I'm pretty pleased.
This is the first time I've ever harvested.
I've got...
I should weigh this actually to find out how much it is, but it's now laying out to dry.
I'm trying to get some advice on that.
I've heard some people say, smoke it now,
but I don't think it's gonna burn very well.
So everything's on paper towels
to get up some of the moisture,
and then I'm gonna hang them upside down in a dry place
to see how, yeah, see if we can get that done.
I don't know how long it's gonna take,
but I promise once we've harvested,
once everything's dry,
we're gonna do a little tasting on the show here.
I failed to point out yesterday, by the way,
that in many countries in Europe,
certainly in the Netherlands and in Belgium,
you are allowed to have five marijuana plants
for personal use,
and you're also allowed to have marijuana
for personal use and to smoke it.
The only problem is you gotta get it from somebody,
and that's, you know, you're allowed to buy it,
but you're not allowed to sell it.
So it's kind of a funky law we got going on here.
It doesn't matter, I'm not fighting the system,
I'm happy the way it is.
Shout out to Drew Domkis,
who listens to the Daily Source Code
every single day in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
And...
Let's see, he says, interesting broadcast from Belgium and Amsterdam.
My wife and I took a vacation in Amsterdam this past February.
I enjoyed it very much and plan to return soon.
Good luck with your harvest.
I love the photo you posted of it.
Yes, well, indeed.
And so this one's going out for you.
I figured I'm going to play a song of the day today.
I'll play something out that is classical Dutch.
This is a Dutchman who's had minor success in the stakes.
His name is Herman Berenier.
I'm jumping down the line, and I'm high
I wonder why it's so hard to feel fine
But all I need, is plastic teeth
And pocket full of speed and I'm full of energy
Never be clever
Never ever
Some say I'm suicidal with the sounds of humor
Some say I'm breaking the past drug rumors
Mom, let's love
Thanks for watching!
I'm so happy to find you
you'll notice
Herman Broth in his wild romance, never be clever and in the states you call him Herman
Brood known from the song Saturday Nights. Probably heard that one. Actually, I can
let you hear a little bit of that. Sure you've heard Saturday Nights because
that was actually a minor hit in the States.
Wait. Can't even type anymore. Here we go. This is the Saturday night.
Probably heard this one.
Skip ahead.
Okay, shit that's not the version I was looking for.
Anyway, in The Never Be Clever, I just want to tell you, Herman Brod, as we call him here,
or Brood in the States, was truly the rock and roll god in the Netherlands.
When I say was because he passed away, I'll talk about that in a sec.
He's done every drug known to man probably every hour of the day that he was awake.
We all found it amazing that he still walked around.
He became an extremely, extremely popular painter for a while.
He had a very highly publicized affair with Nina Hagen.
Imagine those two.
You've got to look up Herman Brod, so it's Herman, B-R-O-O-D.
I'll look up a picture of him and then this probably pictures of him and Nina Hagen together.
And you heard maybe in the lyrics of Never Be Clever, which was recorded, oh man, it's
maybe 25 years old.
There's a line there that says some people say I'm suicidal with a sense of humor.
Well indeed, because...
That was about three years ago, a hair man who at the time, he was not doing well.
He done drugs all his life, heroin being his favorite.
And the doctor said, look, you know, dude, you got to stop the heroin, you got to stop
the drinking or you're going to die.
And what he did was he stopped the heroin, he stopped the drinking and his body freaked
out.
His body could not live without the drugs and he was just dying and he was, it
was, it was bad.
And what he did is he walked about seven or eight minutes from his house in
the south of Amsterdam to the Hilton Hotel, the same one that John and
Yoko stayed in bed for a week.
He walked up to the rooftop and jumped on.
And thus the end of Hair Man Brode.
Thank God we still have his music to play on the source code.
That's it for today.
With little luck in about an hour, an hour and a half or so, I'm going to
work on taping the new show that we'll do, which I'm sure it won't
be up anywhere for listening until tomorrow or maybe the weekend.
You know, just let you.
that we're working on it. And with that I'm going to finish off the source code for today.
Thank you very much for listening. Of course you can always leave a comment at adamantcurry.com.
Bye bye!