Okay, here we are at Curry Castle.
Well, the second is to make sure I've got everything rolling here.
We are just wrapping up the BBC stuff.
It wasn't really a chance for me to podcast or to record anything earlier,
because we were doing exteriors.
They did a cool show for them arrived by a helicopter.
So we've got quite a crew here.
So now I've got a record for my podcast.
I'll just say anything you say,
kind of we'll be used against you.
In a podcast of law.
I'm recording.
I certainly am.
This is reality.
Oh my god.
So anything you say, Colin.
Hello, everybody in America.
This is the BBC.
So you're talking to my chest.
I'm not very convenient.
Hi.
Yes, it works.
I want to meet my wife.
Okay, here we go.
Well, it's coming up on 620 coming to you from Flanders Belgium from Curie Castle.
Almost live.
It is the daily source code.
And God is Friday, everybody.
I mean, everybody.
Adam Curie here bringing you kind of an interesting daily source code.
It's probably the first time that I'm ever going to edit pieces of the show in.
I've had the BBC visiting here for most of the day for a new program that actually just started
airing the other day on that BBC 2.
The culture show.
And while of course, when you come to interview someone about podcasting,
you basically want to see him podcasting.
So I'm not only going to show some of that,
but also I'll cut in some bits of the whole day that I recorded while they were here.
We had a good time.
We had the Wing Commander William flying me in.
We actually, we look like a real professional, unprofessional proof,
which is kind of what podcasting is all about.
Planks and tunes you've heard before on the source code.
It's no Jones from Holland and Revolution.
So they're going on the side.
And the way it is, my mind.
Or since telling me, I should think about it before I act.
But every time I look at you,
and then you don't leave the word I say on my Jones.
My Jones still do to do an unplug set here at the castle,
but they'd better hurry up because we only have a couple more days before we move and
we're off to the UK ourselves.
Maybe if we move fast enough, we can watch this on TV.
So I figured that we'd to show some of the real power of podcasting,
and what we can do as a demo.
Are you guys still rolling on this?
Beautiful. Beautiful.
Is we'll show you how we have,
even though we're just using PCs, personal computers,
laptops, we have a lot of the stuff that the big guys have.
And I figured what I do is I see these online.
We'll actually bring in a phone call.
We're going to bring in Dave Weiner,
the Mac Daddy of RSS and a weblog.
So I'm going to give them a call right now on Skype.
Hey, Dave, how are you doing, buddy?
Hey, a new drip is going to send you an instant message.
Well, I was just in your instant message,
but I can tell you now.
Well, you know what?
First of all, say hi to the BBC.
Hey, BBC.
I've revolted.
I tried to explain to them about the American radio voices and the
everybody thing.
And I think they kind of get it.
They don't have that horrible fish.
Yeah.
And everybody, let's do some horrible English accents.
That'll make us real popular.
Yeah.
So what you got going on, buddy?
Lots, lots of stuff.
A couple of things.
Like first, I was talking with Drew this morning really early.
And they did a really interesting thing on the Don and Drew show.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The way they recorded it.
She was in Los Althos and he was in Wisconsin.
Yeah.
I heard that show.
And it sounded great.
Yeah.
And they used, they recorded.
Bloodshed band on their end.
Yeah.
He emailed him.
Her side of it.
Yeah.
They were talking on his own.
But.
And then he just like overlaid them.
And it came out fun.
And something that I was thinking that we definitely need to try that.
Because then we could get good quality on both ends when we do that.
Yeah.
It was really good quality.
So now we have a good cell phone connection that kind of makes a difference.
Well, buying an actual cell phone that works Dave helped.
Yeah.
No kidding.
The way they think of next.
Yeah, really.
Anyway.
It was this great story.
I have to go find it about Dick Cheney's penis.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It was really a story about Dick Cheney's penis.
I think this is perfect podcast material to prove what we're on the right track here,
changing the world.
It's the man's head like a horse.
No way.
Yeah.
Apparently.
And.
Boy.
They had a picture of it to prove it.
Oh.
Yes.
Some of that threw instant message.
No.
It's all serious.
It was in the middle.
They had it.
It was really good.
Down to are we recording this?
Yeah.
Of course.
Great.
Let's see.
Hold on a second.
So it's taken gotter.
T.A.
E.G.A.
And.
There it is.
Okay.
Oh.
Boy.
All right.
The article is entitled Big Dick Cheney.
Oh, wow.
It's a new paper.
I created a Dick Cheney editor with Scott Sampane.
It's the top is causing quite a stir.
The long magazine has seen.
Let's just say.
So snugged in the Chinese penis little little to the imagination.
And we're not talking baseline.
Unfortunately, you can't see the picture yourself.
They're not reselling the photo.
But it is at the public library if you live in Wisconsin.
Are we better send on and drew down?
Yeah.
It's a Milwaukee Journal, basically.
And apparently the guy's got a big one.
Yeah.
Okay.
That was that thought pretty interesting.
Whatever.
You're not going to hear about that on BBC.
No.
I doubt you will.
But hopefully they'll pick it up from the podcast and maybe catch on to that.
And they got a humor over there in the UK.
They talk about sex all the time.
And all the TV shows.
Yeah.
They do more than America.
America.
Hold on.
Now they say.
Wait.
You saying they don't talk about sex?
Not a seven o'clock.
We're on the wrong show, Dave.
We clearly got the wrong show.
We wanted the late night show.
Actually, it was baseball dead.
I don't know what.
All right.
I'm going to go into another tune here and show these guys some more.
Actually, I'm going to do a play a tap dancing podcast or news piece.
Is it usually where much still to the BBC people?
Is that usually we much more serious than this?
Well, we're pretty serious right now.
Oh, that's true.
I've been serious all.
For the past five hours, they've been here.
I've been deadly serious.
Why are they taking so long?
Because it's the BBC.
You have no idea.
They've got, I mean, they have producers and lighting people and sound.
They even, Dave, they had tracks.
They laid down tracks to move the camera.
Like in a movie.
I mean, these guys got money.
They know how to produce television, man.
They've got it all down.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
You've been here for so far.
Those nice BBC people.
They need to do it.
Oh, a second.
Yeah.
It's not mentioned this now.
10, we're not here.
And this is us.
We're not even in the room.
They want us to fake it, Dave.
Yeah, we'll be kidding.
I'll do it.
You don't talk about Dick Cheney.
What do you mean we don't talk about Dick Cheney?
I mean, I mean, not the root stuff for me.
I can't use it.
Only I know.
But that was just a, that's funny.
But it's, I can't use it.
They can't use the penis stuff, Dave.
So I, I want as much chat from you in vision because we can see you.
Right.
That I've listened to before.
Yeah.
It's very good.
And you're good at good broadcasting.
So I just want to get some of that.
And it's fun to have input down the phone.
Like banter.
Yeah.
If it's, if it's lots and lots of chat from him, we can't see him.
Gotcha.
It's boring for the viewer.
But we love you forever.
You hear that, Dave?
Yeah.
I don't know what we got to do about this.
This is a clash of the media here.
Totally.
Well, I was talking about your daughter.
And about how, like, you know, did you get a chance to think about,
you know, the whole bit.
Maybe you didn't want to talk about this.
I don't know.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I'll tell you what.
I'm going to, I'm going to play a couple things.
So at least they have what they want.
So hold on a second.
So they're with me.
Bear with me.
Because the one thing that we've been talking about,
uh, on not only trade secrets,
but on the daily source code as well,
is about trying to get this one wonderful podcast
who was out there who was bringing us her daily report.
Well, actually, it's almost a daily report in a complete,
new way of presenting the news.
Do you know what I'm talking about here, Dave?
I do.
It's got to be the tap dance and podcast news.
Check it out.
Dallas, and then later, if that has died,
or he is not of liver failure,
a mysterious blood disease or a poisoning plot,
like, Schrodinger's cat.
He may be half dead and half alive.
Hold on. This is the one where I got to provide the tap dancing for her.
Invisitors fighting to take this place for nine.
Lower the voters and back to our seeking therapy.
Deep hypnosis because they're wearing and staring at walls
when there's nothing to see.
It's called post-delections lecture trauma.
Suckers want to move to Canada or back home with Mama.
And the Scott Peterson trial thing of yours
has been dismissed for doing research on her own.
If she was holding out for not guilty,
there'll be a fewer,
as Scott gets the tear.
And Derek also says to her,
he was blowing up this bulletin just in
aircraft that's condition is worse.
He's in a coma or he's eating
or heading for Palestine in a hurry.
Damn, this is an old one.
He's already dead by now.
We need an update on the podcasting tap dance
or news, don't we?
Am I on the air?
Yeah, you're on the air now.
Sure, absolutely.
Come on in.
I just want to tell this BBC guy is that
I'm going to be on C-Spare.
I don't know.
Maybe it's more letters than BBC,
but I still think there's a big difference.
They know Ariana Huffington.
I don't know.
I'm going to be on with...
Maybe they know her as Ariana status.
I'm not supposed to talk to them.
They're not even there.
No, there's no one here.
There's no camera.
There's no BBC.
I don't see anything.
I don't think.
What?
I'm not objecting.
I'm not about to be someone.
You know what?
I am not a British stud.
I'm not.
I'm sorry.
This is calling by the way Dave.
Hi Dave.
Can you hear me?
You're great.
Good.
I'm going to be borrowing Adam for about five minutes to do another intro to the show.
And I want him to pretend that we're not even here.
He's going to...
Well, he says,
Bumpy's Gums.
I'm going to make that an international expression for talking.
He's going to Bumpy's Gums about stuff.
Nothing through the BBC.
Nothing through the fact that we're here.
That we can use as an introduction to his show and what he does.
So we're going to go for that.
Can I know?
I don't really add him.
So you hear that Dave?
I'm being directed.
It's entirely what you add him.
Yeah.
I feel for you, my brother.
I understand what they want.
Yeah.
But it's exactly what it is.
The thing is that it's no problem at all.
But it's exactly counter to what podcasting is, of course.
Yeah.
But that's OK.
So I'm going to give them a nice little...
A nice little demonstration.
Hold on.
I'm going to get my stuff set up here.
OK.
I'll call you back in five minutes, Dave.
All right.
Let's see.
So I don't want to make this two-stock term.
The bell.
Let's go.
All right.
So how often do you post costs?
I do it five days a week.
I just do it every single day.
But then I got a real trouble with my two girls.
My wife and my daughter.
And I said, well, can we like have no podcasting on the weekend?
So...
But this is it.
This is...
Well, this is actually my office when we bought the castle.
Well, yeah.
It's a bar.
So it's actually...
You know what's so great about it?
The height is perfect.
So you're not that small either.
But the height is perfect to put the laptop right up here.
I've got everything in front of me.
This is the beauty about podcasting.
We basically have all this stuff on our computers.
So here you see a little microphone processor.
No.
You're being from radio.
You recognize some of the things, right?
There's a little meter that's registering.
And really what's fun is it's all being recorded on this little device here.
Okay.
How...
You've got a power book here.
Yeah.
What was the market then?
Okay.
Well, now, of course, I'm a rich podcaster.
So I got a little wireless.
That's my very much like the ones you use.
So here's your microphone.
There's my microphone.
What about pulpy for wadding me?
Oh, well, four people talking to the microphone here.
There's a microphone built in.
Or actually, you know, for like 20, 20 euros,
you can buy one of these microphones, which is just that.
There you go.
How many pounds?
About 12, 15 pounds.
Yeah, something like that.
It's just a USB microphone that you can plug right into into your computer.
Right.
And that's really all you need.
All the recording stuff.
You can record directly onto your computer.
Where for that?
Okay.
Personally, I like, this is all, this is like a 70 pounds external MP3 recorder.
I plug it right into the headphones jack.
Okay.
So you're sitting here and you're just talking about whatever the help
puts into your head.
Well, so what would I do first?
Hold on a second.
I get my monitoring system here.
I get my headphones.
I want to start off the show.
So I've got my opening here.
My opening theme song, which is by Rachmaninoff.
And I cue a sweeper over that.
So I show you how that's done.
So basically, it's all in the fingers now.
Pay attention, Zeener.
This is podcasting 101.
So I hit the space bar.
That starts to play.
Then I hit the sweeper.
And so basically, I welcome everybody here.
So daily source code.
This is for Friday.
And here with the lovely Zeener Warrior Princess.
From the...
That's original.
You've never heard that one.
You don't even spell it the same way.
So basically, when I start off the show,
I'm just using the keyboard for volume controls.
Whereas in a radio studio, you probably have a sliding fader to...
The first that we put costing now.
So you're a podcast.
And you're a podcast.
50,000 more or less.
So what's costing to 50,000?
At least.
Yeah, sure.
And look at how easy it is.
It's completely simple.
So yeah, what I do is...
I usually have a list here of stuff that I want to talk about.
And I talk about other podcasts.
But the great thing about this wireless microphone is that if I want,
you know, this I do this all the time.
We'll just...
Step outside, you know.
And we'll...
Well, now it's dark, of course.
But...
And it takes you outside of the whole idea of a studio.
And sometimes I just come out here and say,
let's just listen to the Belgian air for a moment.
And you hear the fountain in the background.
I can hear the fountain in the background.
And it's really tranquil.
And then it's time to go play something to music.
But that...
But it can really...
Literally be...
Anyway, you like it.
Yeah, whatever you want to do.
I mean, I've done this while flying.
I've done it while in my car.
And see what I do here is...
I remember I was...
I was telling you about music, about music,
that we're allowed to play in our podcasts.
So something that people are playing a lot of right now,
is this guy named Brad Sox.
He's... he calls himself the one...
the one man banned with no fans.
Which, of course, is funny, because he has lots of...
But he makes this all by himself on his computer.
Yeah.
And so, you know, while we screw around here a little bit more,
we'll listen to a dirt bag.
Brad Sox on the special BBC edition of the Daily Source Code.
It's a little bit hard on the stand.
But I don't want to be a part of it.
On the wire.
We're coming out soon.
Just thinking about the one that got away.
Nobody wanted me in my heart away.
You could make your mind up.
We could take a time.
I know this thing.
You must take in me for some of my life.
Here's our news to dirt bag.
Under the weather.
And over a radius scene.
You must take in me for some of my life.
Here's our news to dirt bag.
Under the weather.
And over a radius.
I think she'd run with a buzz and a fly-to-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-owo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
So, there's George Abbott School, which is where we really wanted to go, which is convenient.
Yeah.
I mean, if it comes down to it, private school.
Okay.
But it's on.
It's on the U.K. public school, private school.
Yeah.
It's the other way around, right?
Yeah, I know.
Well, the same thing.
Public school is the same.
It's the perfect school.
Right.
It's Comprehensive.
Comprehensive.
So, what?
So, are we in America or hear a call of public schools?
Public schools.
Comprehensive.
Yeah.
But any of them private schools?
Public schools.
Right.
Okay.
So, a public school, a big, a public schools.
More famous ones are eaten.
Right.
Okay.
So, I guess this would be comprehensive, because...
It's the regular school.
There's three good schools right in the neighborhood.
Right.
Schools.
Yeah.
But getting her in is...
Here in Holland is like, you know, well, we're filled up.
But, oh.
Oh, Mr. Curry, Mr. Ms. Patricia.
Yes.
Well, no problem.
We'll hook you up there.
No one knows me.
No clue.
Zero.
I have no reputation there.
Even if I had it, I don't think I would make any difference.
So, we just got to figure that out.
But there's lots of really good schools in that area.
It's a nice part of the country.
Yeah.
Totally, totally vibrant.
I'm going.
I'm so ready.
Now, I've got to figure out this driving on the left hand side thing.
But...
I can do it.
Yeah.
And...
It's funny money you got.
We've got funny money that I work on.
Funny ways we're talking.
No, I like that.
The danger is...
This is the difference.
If you travel 45 miles...
Oh, yeah.
You can completely change the experience.
Sure.
The danger that I always find, particularly being American...
Lots of English friends, is that before too long you slip into doing kind of like this
fucked up Madonna accent and then...
And I'm...
And you don't do it on purpose.
You know, you just...
It just kind of assumed these...
Hello love.
And you say that.
And I know that the English people are going like,
She should be American shut up.
You know?
She should be saying bullets.
There's Madonna say bullets.
Yes, she does.
Now, she should be kicking the ballics for doing that.
I don't think it's possible.
You know, it should be flatter.
But I know that it irritates.
And so...
And I'm really worried about that because I know what happens.
Yeah, I'm a sponge.
I soak it up and I start...
And it starts with a few words.
Before I come from it, it's the Shina Eastern factor.
Shina Eastern is from Glasgow.
Yeah.
Gold love the woman.
But, you know, where she starts...
That may be the only person who loves her.
Yeah.
But now she's like...
So many Atlantic skin.
Right.
Well, it's like listening to Tina Turner.
From it's conversely.
Tina Turner is any may-ballock from, you know, from the south.
And he or going...
Edward, no.
I would like to do dedicated song, you know.
I know.
Where the hell is this island thing come from, Tina?
Yeah.
She's so kind of like...
She's the Swiss.
Exactly.
Mm-hmm.
Well, she lives with her men, her German husband, her boyfriend.
Yeah.
What's the name of the boy in the guy?
She actually has it.
You know, they all have this little set.
And they all drink sweet and clear.
It's podcasting.
All's live.
Adam Curry.