I'm a Korean, it's Wednesday September 15th 2004.
even be tomorrow.
So this is the place where users and developers party
together.
It's the daily source code.
And I discovered something horrible today.
I was I registered for some, I was looking at different
services, that's what it was, for voiceover IP, still in my
ultimate quest to find a voiceover IP provider that
actually gives me dial-up numbers in multiple countries.
And excuse me, that's a cup of tea there.
And I've learned that when you register for something online,
when they say we'll send you an email, usually the first
place you need to look is your junk mail folder, because
that's probably where that type of email is going to show up,
something in the algorithm that always sends it there.
And so I was looking, I just kind of on a fluke.
Now I'm using Apple's mail program, and I actually have
it running through mac.com.
So if you send an email to curry.com, it's routed
through mac.com.
The reason why is because they have built-in spam filters.
There's still a lot of stuff that
I've just manually wanted to filter out.
And boy, was I surprised when I just did a little quick search
for iPodder and for source code.
I have missed a lot of email, and I apologize
that I haven't checked earlier.
There were some messages that date back to August.
Like, whoops.
So I just wanted to run through a couple of pieces of mail
that I found in my junk mail box, because a lot of them
were responses to the show.
Here's one from Danny.
You see, he said, you asked for a reason as to why Skype
is better than standard SIP protocols.
Now, we talked about that.
So what's the big difference with my question between a lot
of these voice over IP service that you see and Skype?
So Danny says, very roughly, the primary difference
is that SIP, let's just call it SIP,
depends upon a central server to act as the switch
for the voice calls.
Skype has distributed this functionality
across all of its users, decentralizing the switch.
This only provides greater reliability,
not having central choke points.
It also allows Skype folks to operate a huge voice network
with a lot of different features.
having to buy racks and racks of servers to run SIP on. Makes sense. And now I understand,
now that I indeed have been looking at how these providers are put together, indeed they're
all using Cisco boxes or what's the other one, other dialog box, I can't remember
all the names. And they are basically providing that bridge or they're buying that capability.
And the connect point is indeed apparently a centralized service from what I can see.
And maybe there are some decentralized ones, but I'm having good success with Skype.
It really pisses me off that I can't receive phone.
I had a phone call with my secretary today.
She's in Amsterdam.
I'm in Belgium.
I Skyped her.
Notice how that's becoming synonymous to an internet phone
call.
I Skyped her.
And we went through at least about, was it actually?
Look at it here.
19 minutes on the phone.
It was a long distance country to country call.
Normally I'm probably paying because we're calling between
cell phones just out of, just because we're lazy.
I'm probably paying at least a dollar.
And now I think I paid 30 cents for the entire conversation.
And you know what?
There's always room for more money.
So spending less equals the same thing in my book.
Another email from Michael.
Let's see what Michael had to say here.
He says that he discovered daily source code just
yesterday.
Now this was sent almost two weeks ago.
He's become absolutely addicted to audio blogs.
He spent the entire day learning about RSS feeds
and enclosures.
And he says that he'd only seen these terms in passing
when reading about the upcoming Safari RSS iteration.
So he's clearly enjoying it.
And let me see, why did I want to talk about this email?
Oh, he's talking about an audio setup.
Okay, when listening to your recordings, I was struck by the fidelity.
My ask what mic software encoder setup you are using.
I'm working on an Apple platform as well,
but I struggle to determine exactly what mic and software to use to give everybody a good sound.
Appreciate it, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, Michael.
So let me tell you how I'm doing this.
First of all, the key to doing this type of show
is to be able to record any sound
that comes out of your computer speakers.
In this case, I'm on a Mac,
and unless you physically plug something into the line out
and into a recording device,
it's kind of hard to figure out how to do that.
There's a little application called WireTap for OS X.
And when you fire that up,
it will basically record anything
that is sent through the speakers.
So anything you can hear on the speakers,
including when I turn up my volume, listen to this.
So you heard the little blips there of me turning up the volume.
All of that is recorded.
And it's recorded unfortunately to an AIFF file which I then later have to transcode
to MP3.
The reason I do that is so that I can use QuickTime as my media player.
So my opening tune is a QuickTime window.
Then all the bits I want to play, if I want to play an MPEG movie or a QuickTime
In fact, I'm going to do that today. I have a couple of those queued up. Now you still
need to get your mic in. There are different ways to do that. Basically, any program that
will allow your microphone, your internal mic, or your external one, which I'll talk
about in a second, to be played through your speakers will be perfect. Now, in this case,
I'm using GarageBand, since I had the iLife Suite anyway. What's nice about GarageBand
is you can set up filters and compressors. I just actually changed some of the settings.
I had a noise gate in there before. The reason why I use a noise gate is so when
there's a certain level of quiet in the room, then the microphone will just shut
off, so you don't hear any ancillary noise. It's probably most often used
for musical recordings of instruments, but we use it in radio studios all the time.
I'll give you an example of what it sounds like. I've turned the gate on and you
hear that when I breathe, when I stop breathing, if there's not enough
ambient noise, then the gate cuts in and it shuts off the recording.
And so you can set this a little bit looser to the top of it now.
Okay.
So you see that's what a gate is.
Then you have things like a compressor which gives you a little more boost to the sound.
I'm going to turn my compressor on right now.
Now if you're listening to me on an iPod or you're listening through some big speakers,
my voice is probably booming into the room right now.
And that by the way is, oh, you get that big ass radio voice.
Okay, so let's turn that off.
Excuse me.
And for microphone, I'm using a pretty interesting, I'm using a wireless set that we have left over
from our reality TV show that we produced ourselves.
These are, what the hell are these things?
Electro, L-E-C-T-R-O, UHF wireless microphones.
And these are professional.
These are pretty expensive.
This set costs me about, I think, 2,000 euros.
It's about, yeah, about $22 to $2,500.
But you can use all different types of microphones.
And I found that if you go to Radio Shack and you buy one of their metal stick microphones,
which looks very much like a Shure microphone, an old fashioned Shure microphone.
I should actually, well, I'm sorry for the, for the feedback there, but I had to unplug
the headphones.
I walk over to my microphone cabinet.
Pretty sure.
I probably still have one of those laying here.
Got all my good mics.
Shoot.
No. Okay.
Can't find the, unfortunately I can't find it, but I'll look that up.
I'll see if I can find what model number it is.
If you can get that into your Macintosh, then there's all this process in it you can do.
There's also, there's all kinds of different programs.
There are a lot of mixing programs that will let you filter the audio on a particular channel
and play it through so that you can hear it on the speakers.
Again, if you hear it on the speakers, wire tap is.
going to record it. So one thing you're going to get used to is using the mute button on
the program using to get your microphone on to the speakers so that I just turn it off
and turn it back on because when you're playing something you clearly don't want any noise
that you're making to be recorded as well. So you have to learn to shut your mic off.
One more email. Oh the email bag is big today. Hi Adam this is from Julio. Oh this
is cool. Just start listening to the daily source code. Want to tell you it's great.
I listened to it on my commute in the
Caracas.
The subway system here in Caracas, Venezuela.
Hey, we got Caracas on the wireless everybody.
Um, so, and this is another email that was in the junk mail folder and so Julio says
I guess someone must have answered your questions from the September...
and here it goes. This was about the the iPhoto getting in a CD or DVD of iPhoto's
when you put it back in you know the whole thing that that iPhoto actually
boots back up and makes it look just like they're sitting on your hard drive.
So if I'd gotten that earlier then I would have known earlier. Thank you.
And also apparently in iTunes as I said you can select the iPod references and
choose manually manage songs and playlists. After that you can erase
all your files from the computer clearing up space and they will remain on your iPod.
Interesting. Downside you have to move files in manually. Upside you can connect
your iPod to other Macs listed in Music Audit just not just your own Mac.
Okay so that's some iTunes tips from Julio checking us out from Caracas.
Excellent. And today is a very exciting day here at Curry Castle.
It's September and that means it is time to harvest.
Aha! Horticulture on the source code you think. Well indeed.
A couple months ago, I was given by my friendly coffee shop, Purple Rain in Breda, which is
about 25 minutes drive north of here in Holland.
Five wonderful little marijuana plants, of which, well I put them all in our, we have
a little greenhouse, I started growing them a couple months ago.
I didn't know anything about it, you know, just checked a few things on the internet,
didn't really look into how you're supposed to do it, and then figure out after several
months and after these plants were just huge, I figured out, you know, you have to
control their light cycle in order to get them to bloom, because that's the stuff
that you want to cut off.
And so what I did is I set up a little thing down in the basement, brought the
plants down, and these were almost like mini shrubs, they're like trees at this
point, and started cultivating them underneath light, 12 hours on, 12 hours
off, and then bring that cycle down.
Since they were outdoor plants moved indoor, eventually four of them didn't.
make it and they like boom just died overnight which really sucked and I've
had one left and it's pretty humongous we think we're going to be able to cut
quite a lot off of it never done the cutting before and of course we have
to dry everything so that is on this evening schedule we're going to watch
television and we're going to cut all the little buds off the plant and hang
up to dry and I will you know what and I think we should do I think that takes
at least a week maybe even longer to dry him we'll have to celebrate together on
the source code and I'll spark one up for you and pass a virtual doobie let's see
just running through the news man Ivan possibly on its way to Louisiana maybe
by the time you hear this it's already hit that's really intense you know I've
been there a couple times from already brought with MTV broadcasts great
town and probably probably won't be able to withstand a big storm like that
very well and also the geographical location. Topographical location isn't very advantageous
as all the news media is telling us. And I wanted to mention Oprah briefly because her
big Pontiac giveaway did not go unnoticed here either. So just to let you all know that
if you think that maybe giving away, was it 260, $28,000 cars, if that was a bad
idea while I'm telling you, everyone knows about the Pontiac here in Holland and they
probably never even heard of Pontiacs before. So that really worked. Big and
excellent, excellent PR move by Oprah and Pontiac. And yesterday I played some bits
of Fahrenheit 9-11 and got some interesting responses to that. I think most
people seem to agree with me. You know the message is clear but the way it was
all cut up was just almost unnecessary to do it that way. I was really
interested in the historical part of what this documentary is supposed to show.
which definitely was there, but all the hokey bits just didn't seem necessary.
And almost, I think, attracted from the message.
So on source code, we do wanna keep to equal air time.
And I ran across a new documentary, which should be out on DVD very soon,
which is probably just as bad as Fahrenheit 9-11.
This is called Fahrenheit 9-11.
And it has some saluminaries in there who go on record talking about
Michael Moore's documentary, most notably Ed Koch, former mayor of New York City.
I'm just gonna play the trailer so you can enjoy this bit of equal air time
programming Fahrenheit 9-11.
I probably should have queued that out. There's a whole bunch of what you're seeing right
now on the screen is a whole bunch of reviews just like to do in the movies where it says
Michael Moore best film, most important film ever. So it goes through that and here comes
Ed Koch.
man who says that the units have spread misery throughout the world.
Come on.
Michael Moore, I'm a safe shallow.
The terrorist threat is real. It's every day it's real.
I said 3,000 people were murdered!
How the f*** do you say this?
Someone has to explain that nobody took it seriously before George Bush on 9-11.
Iraq was a war for oil. That's just propaganda, but out of the rocket, felt grenades.
And 60 million years.
Somebody's been slipping past the sanctions.
No, fuck that one. They're all the same.
Everybody wanted to defend Sadami, saying they don't like him at all.
That's the first second day of war they wanted to escape.
The biggest thing on their mind was their families, their lives.
That's it. They didn't care about stuff.
I thank God we have the baby on the actual...
What's amazing about this war...
President Bush said, I will do whatever it takes.
You call out war from the get-go, and that really defined the war on terrorism.
The fear for abusive freedom of speech in society is more freedom of speech than a channel.
Somebody can sleep last night by a friend.
Like Ron Reagan and Latchel was good.
Michael Moore's film, in trying to knock our liberty, and trying to say that we don't have it,
is the best illustration of how wrong his film is.
Oh for
Fahrenheit 9 1 1 savage pictures Fahrenheit Fahrenheit 9 1 1
Dot com okay, you can go check that out so much for the equal error
You know what it's only just a matter of time until someone's gonna come up with a perfect final cut pro edit of both the
Documentaries and put a against be and it's gonna be a even
Oh, another video blog post that, actually a video blog post that I wanted to let you
hear because this is Steve Garfield who has a very rye sense of humor.
In fact, at the rate he's going, he could take those places.
He went out as what he calls a citizen journalist for election day.
Now it happened to be in his particular county was election day for sheriff.
And he went to check out on the polling rules if everyone was adhering to a...
that are supposed to be written in stone apparently when it comes to polling.
Well, the post kind of speaks for itself. I'm going to play this as well.
And just imagine Steve Garfield standing in front of buildings with people with signs behind him
and you'll get the video part. It's titled, 150 Feet.
Hi, this is Steve Garfield from SteveGarfield.com.
It's Election Day in Boston and today's big primary race is the Sheriff's Race.
Not many people seem to be voting today so the story that we're going to look at is
if the people who are campaigning for any of the candidates are breaking the Massachusetts law
which says you must stay within 150 feet of a polling place.
Here in Jamaica Plain, the law is being abided by and the candidate supporters are staying well away from the polling place.
Now we're in West Roxbury at the Holy Name Parish voting facility where we can obviously see
that these campaign workers are well within the 150 foot legal limit where they're supposed to be.
be out in the street and not the front steps. Has anyone from the polling place here told
you about the law where campaigners need to be 150 feet away from the polling place?
No, they haven't said that today.
So were you aware of that?
Yes.
So what are we right here? How close are we?
Well, it depends on what you're counting. Where you measure it to, if you're measuring
to where the actual votes are taken, we're outside that 150 feet.
I notice you're pretty close to the...
uh...
law which is supposed to be like a hundred fifty feet away
uh... yes we are right now it's very slow there's nothing going on but as
people start coming in
so where would the polling place actually be like
where does it start
right here at the building?
yes it does right there and i know that's a hundred fifty feet
so if they enforce if they actually enforce that law where we would
Really, that's fire.
Rocksbury Branch Library and it's our third stop today.
So I guess we could say we're two out of three because look at these people.
These campaigners are right in front of the doorstep of the library.
Steven Murphy, Marion Walsh, everybody signs,
posted right up to the lamppost of the library. This is ridiculous.
This law of staying within 150 feet of any polling place is just
not being enforced two out of three times. I'd say if I went to ten more
places, I bet you there'd be people all over the front of these polling places.
So that's something that I think's got to change. I always drive by
and am so upset when I see people swarming right over the front door. This is not right.
You know, I just don't like it. This is Steve Garfield reporting for
SteveGarfield.com. Excellent. Steve Garfield
protecting democracy on the streets of Boston
and very proud of him for doing that because it doesn't matter how trivial the law
is. That's those are the rules. Before you know it, you're debating over
hanging people.
chats. Let's talk about enclosures for a second. There's, oh first of all, good new, well let
me just back up for a second. Enclosures is really part of the technology that we're
using for iPodder. If you haven't used it yet, check out iPodder.org and download one of
these programs either for Mac or for Windows or even for Linux. They're all out there
for iTunes, they're out there for Windows Media Player and if you have an MP3 device
I want to dry them off.
So if you have a MP3 player that works on Windows Media,
then do something about that feedback.
Then you're good to go.
So how this is done is by creating an RSS 2.0 feed,
which is basically just a text file which
has some fairly human readable words in it.
And they represent little bytes of information,
so a blog post typically.
And to each of those postings, you can attach a file.
In this case, for the iPodder and for what
we're doing with the source code and other programs like this,
is we attach a URL to an MP3 file.
And as far as I know, I think really only Radio User Land
has it built into the blogging interface.
If you make a web blog post, for instance,
I say, hey, it's daily source code for September 15, 2004.
MP3, it's going to be a great day.
be about 35 minutes or 30 minutes.
It's this big.
And then I just add the URL to wherever that file is located.
I add that in a little box that says Enclosure URL.
And then it attaches it.
And then my RSS feed goes out without enclosure attached to
it.
Word is that another great weblogs package called Word
Press, which I'm very impressed with.
They're now working.
There are a couple of people working.
I saw some Dutch guys.
It's in fact working on adding enclosure support to Word
Press, which will be great to have.
And there's lots of people supporting this effort.
So I'm sure that's going to show up pretty soon.
Andrew Grumit has also started an audio blog.
Or he started audio blogging.
Let's put it that way.
And I wanted to play an excerpt, which I haven't queued up.
I just realized of Andrew talking about iPod and iTunes
and how that really is going to be, how iTunes is going
to be a killer app.
Let me just skip through this with you for a second.
Let's listen to Andrew's post here.
Good evening.
Andrew Grumit, it's September 14th, 2004, about 945.
Hold on, I'm gonna fast forward you Andrew.
You decide a pub date is for a file that was created.
Okay, so a whole bunch of techy stuff in there
about when, you know, what kind of information
is to be in the RSS 2.0 file.
Users might wanna listen to it,
although you might not understand it,
but this is pretty important stuff,
so we can get these iPodder programs working properly.
Let me see.
So that's probably, I'm gonna probably leave it there
unless I get strong feedback that it's just unworkable.
Okay.
Let's see.
Adam Curry had some nice ideas,
one of which was that the, I think he noted that,
I've putter type scripts on the extraction side, go and use the ID3 tag data to...
This is about publishing using ID3 tags.
Set up playlists and so forth.
That's not the bit I want to...
So should the publishing scripts go dig into the ID3 tags and...
I have to talk about it.
So I went ahead and added some to the script.
Hold on a second.
I have the Perl.
I had to learn a little bit of stuff.
It was...
I sort of generalized...
I really should have queued this up for you.
So it's sort of a mini plug-in architecture.
Okay, now go for it.
Okay, so, oh, and Adam also had an observation about ease of use.
And it's definitely true.
This is kind of a geek script.
I don't expect everybody to set up cron jobs on their server.
It happened to be the easiest thing for me.
And what my idea was to combine it with Radio User Land upstreaming so that what
I can do is drag my audio file to a folder.
It gets upstreamed by FTP.
At some point a cron job...
comes along and sees the new file and regenerates the RSS feed. So that's how I'm going to do it.
But anyone is, the audience or the developer group who might be listening is more than invited to
copy everything I've done and make it work really nicely on the desktop or use the ideas as a basis
for, you know, steel-free-lead basically. Which is exactly what we want to see on the
iPod or dev mailing list. So what Andrew was talking about there was about his DIR2 RSS script,
which creates an RSS 2.0 file. Again, we're getting more and more blog software to support this, so
that's going to get easier for users in the future. Now I think it's the part where he talks
about the media players. Oh, last thing. I wanted to talk about a usability strategy, I guess,
something I did with my iPod that seems kind of useful. I think other people have noted that
iTunes has this thing called the smart playlist and you can tell the smart
playlist. You can tell it you want the last 10 items added to your iPod, you
know, ordered, if I reverse chronological date added, and so that's really a great
way. That for me is the killer app. You know, I just want to go into the iPod,
you know, go to my latest playlist and just sort of, you know, hit play at the top
and have it go down through the last few things added. And one little trick is that
it seems to, the iPod wants to display the list alphabetically. So it seems like,
so I went in and I renamed my latest playlist to 00 latest, which bubbles it up to the top,
so there's even less work. So that seems to be working well and maybe it'll work well for you.
Okay, that's all I have to say and I'm going to go ahead and try publishing this with the latest version of
my script and we'll see how it goes.
Well it worked Andrew.
Take care everybody.
Thank you very much.
So that's interesting there.
Again we spoke about that yesterday where your media player is starting to look a little bit...
a playlist but it's the same thing as rules and you can call it a playlist you
can call it a folder. I mean this nuance is everything in this. And on the list
further I'm seeing a lot of people now talk about hey you know this is so
successful we should start setting ourselves up for other types of
enclosures like video and applications and this is where I want to see like a
back off the developers a little bit because we're gonna get ahead of
ourselves. We still need to get the right installers already I posted today
there's a Windows configuration tool for the Windows iPodder which is great
but on on install I'll just run you through the steps that typical user will
need you know and from a Mac OS X OS 10 perspective obviously and we download
this you know a sit file or whatever it could be a DMG I want it to be a disc
image at a certain point that opens up it says double click here it's probably an
Apple script a double click it sets up my cron job and it pops up a dialogue
and says iPodder will run at these times and make it 3 a.m.
8am, 11pm, whatever, and you could check off or maybe check a few more hours as options.
And that's going to be set up in your cron job, it's going to make it run.
And then it's going to say, you're subscribed to these feeds automatically and you can deselect
any one of them you want to.
And it's also going to tell you how you can add another feed to it, which should
be able to be done after the install.
And really that's it.
The only other thing you'd want perhaps is just a hello world thing to make your user
really happy.
Where you've installed this thing, it should go out, it should download an mp3 from,
you know, just a set mp3 that's always there in an rss file that never changes.
And it'll be, hi, hello world.
You have successfully installed the iPod.
And of course that should transfer onto the iPod or whatever device.
That should be put into a special hello world welcome playlist.
And I think that once we've got all that set up and users are able to just download
this.
thing and their iPod is working then we can move on to other types of enclosures.
And by the time we've got the installation we'll also have other types of devices to
talk to.
Time for the song of the day.
I was rolling through the iTunes playlist and Patricia and my wife was sitting beside
me and she said, oh yeah.
This is, are you searching for a song for the source code?
I said oh yeah.
She said, this has got to be the one then.
She's missing a rock and roll band and the world plays it.
They may not know all the words but it's a classic.
It's a little singing with me and the job.
I can care about him, I saw I kept him there
This one, he was kept him, I worked with two spark-ers
I took all of this money
And I bought it home to Bali
That's with speed and I'm the job
A
M
Taking my mom and the women
This would be a good job
I am with a ball, a chain, a bunch of rain, dammit.
I'm going to wrap it up today with just a brief pointer to the new search engine on the scene.
I was pointed to it by something Dave wrote about it.
Apparently, well, that's something for a different discussion.
But anyway, a9.com, which is certainly less typing to get to than google.com.
Interesting search engine.
I'm pretty sure they use Google's search engine, but they do have some interesting
features.
You know, your history of searches, you can open up multiple frames for different types
of searches next to each other, such as a search based on web pages, a search based on images.
So definitely worth taking a look at, and probably worth having a conversation with Dave Weiner
over.
Now, that's a plan.
And that's it for source code for today.
I'll be back tomorrow with another edition of your daily source code.
If you want to subscribe to the show by RSS check my know with enclosures it's dating source code.com