Hi everybody!
One casting!
All's life!
And a parade!
Well, how do you everybody welcome to the Daily Source Code for Wednesday?
November 10th, 2004, coming to you from Flanders Belgium from Curry Castle.
It is your Daily Source Code.
And I've got something wrong with.
I have a podcast here.
Power!
And maybe saying that so what the hell is podcast here?
I think it's actually going to be my ears by ways.
We can hear both so much in the past.
In the past weeks, one of the ones that I put watch out.
I've got everything here.
Let's see if I can even hear my ears.
It's painful.
I'm going to show me your buds and it sounds crappy.
But it really actually hurts the inner part of my ears.
It's scraping around for the past days.
All right, for the next four minutes,
it's going to be bringing you all the latest in podcast about all three music.
And my day started off recently, Ruff.
All things considered, of course.
I'm back now in the castle, which is pretty empty.
Patricia's packed up.
She's kind of conglomerated areas of stuff.
And she's really taken care of this entire movie, which is so cool.
Because I've been on the road,
blogger con, traveling back and forth.
Now you know, if you read my weblogged,
I had a six hour delay when I got to,
or if you heard just a source code, of course,
that had a six hour delay.
What you didn't hear is that my bag or one bag arrived
when I finally landed in Amsterdam.
The other bag was apparently trapped in London somewhere,
which makes no sense.
I mean, one bag made it.
The other bag didn't shit like that happens.
They found it now.
The bag actually made it to Amsterdam today.
And, you know, I told them that Antwerp Airport was nearest.
And I told them the KLM probably doesn't fly there.
And I said, you should probably just have someone drive from
Skippel Airport or Rotterdam Airport to our house.
Now they flew the back to Brussels.
And that's about as far away from my house as
as Skippel Airport is in Holland.
So whatever.
But, you know, all my shaving stuff and
Christina's good charlatte wall clock that I had all set up.
You know, all of that stuff in that bag.
And, well, a second.
I just want to try a different pair of earphones.
I don't even know if I sound right.
And which leads me to believe that these headphones,
almost a second, shoot.
Okay.
Don't go away.
So, I don't do that very often.
I actually stopped the recording.
But, hold on a second.
I dropped the mic.
But that was really necessary because I couldn't hear anything.
So, all right.
So, these Sony earphones,
I thought would be more comfortable in my ears.
In my tender ears now at this point,
really do not sound good at all.
I'm back to the iPod headset.
The reason I bought a new set of headphones at the airport
because, well, first of all, I had some time to do some shopping.
Second of all, the wires are starting to come undone here.
You know, where the two wires that one leads to your left ear
and one leads to your right ear and there's a little, you know,
kind of like a triangle thing there that's supposed to keep all the wires
to keep them from stripping apart further.
But now the shielding is starting to come apart.
So, I figured I'd be ahead of the game, but I guess, you know,
you've got headphones and headphones.
The Sony little ear buds there are no good.
So, back to the iPods.
Man, my ears just hurt.
All right.
Anyway.
Wow.
Back from, back from BloggerCon.
You know, we're still talking about it here and there on the podcast.
And we'll have some of that coming up on the daily source code later on as well.
Some good comments, some interesting comments.
Got some music on the way by a BloggerCon participant.
And while I did not catch it while I was waiting at the airport,
but you know, a big fan of OpenPodcast.org is always cool.
Just to just a great feed to subscribe to, if someone wants to target you
with kind of like a promo about what's coming up on their podcast
or something's new.
So, I listened to that a lot besides checking out audio.weblogs.com,
which is probably the best place to sample new podcast that come in.
So, audio.weblogs.com with every new podcast that's put up there that's pinged
that server.
You can read everything that was accompanied in the posted notes that goes with it.
You can subscribe to the feed right there.
You can listen to the show.
You can go to the website.
So, it's excellent for sampling out sampling new podcasts.
So, I do check those regularly and loan behold once the model message shows up.
In there, this is Ian McLeod.
Actually, an interesting attempt, at least I think it's interesting.
I've noticed on Adam Curry's live.cray.com that you deleted an airport
for four hours and it's been there with live life.
I second up the podcast.
Here's a shot.
I started a challenge to see if possibly he's checking the OpenPodcast.org
and if so, then Adam you're listening to this.
Trying to get your attention.
Not just your attention.
Can I get everybody's attention?
Specifically, would like to see if I can get a dialogue going with you
at some point.
Check out quest.empowerweb.ca-rss.xml.
That's the feed for you.
We're just going to quest.empowerweb.ca.
I created a podcast.
Put it up.
Late last week, I'm going to be putting together a follow-up
about a whole bunch of really, really cool, very interesting thoughts
that I've had aggregated from a few different sources about where we're going
to go with podcasting.
What tools do you need to create on the aggregators to the site
and on the podcast production site?
I've seen the future.
Yes, my brother.
I wanted to put your hands on the podcast a few of the future coming
down the pipe.
So that's a good way to get something out in the open.
That's what people hear about while you're promoting.
Open podcast.org, love it.
I also listened to Dave's morning coffee notes.
Another one he did on the road.
I was afraid for a second that his recording was going to be skipping again.
I kind of figured that out with him.
It skipped a couple of times in the beginning,
but then it turned out to be a really clean, good recording.
And he cranked some tunes at the beginning on the car stereo.
It's almost impossible to excerpt something from what's on
morning coffee notes.
And I'm pretty sure Dave does that by design because he doesn't really want to
just have the excerpt he wants to go and listen to the whole thing.
And I do encourage you to listen to this one.
Because he had some really good thoughts about what I like
particularly around 35 minutes into his podcast.
How we're going to work with the red states.
He touched on a lot of big things that came out of
bloggercon.
And how should we look at it for bloggercons to come?
I think it was really just a brain dump that he really needed to do.
And it's cool.
So you should check that out from scripting.com.
The morning coffee notes podcast.
And as I was listening around to stuff that came in
through iPod.
I came across, well actually I subscribed to promiscuous bullet.
It was a Thomas and Stephen Bates.
And they had their thoughts about bloggercon.
I just wanted to play a little bit of a commentary.
And they had about the podcast session.
What session did you go to?
What do you think about it?
Well, I went to the podcast to one, of course.
It was kind of interesting.
Adam Curry was not what I expected.
Can't have a rock star on.
The thanks sunglasses were a little bit overboard.
Now that's interesting.
Because I got to tell you that I used to wear contact lenses
until I was flying one time.
And I put on my regular glasses, which you know,
glasses that I had from the 1975 or whatever.
And then I discovered how much I was actually missing viewing
the world through contact lenses.
They're like, this is just as inferior.
So I should go back to wearing glasses.
And so I ordered out the pair of sunglasses,
which remains specifically for flying.
And Patricia suggested I get pink glasses,
rose tinted glasses actually in my prescription.
Because she said, you know, the world looks so beautiful.
And I never really considered it from the other way around.
I haven't really done any public speaking.
I haven't been on television in a long time.
I consider that people would think that that was some kind of rock star
trip, you know, that they're not sunglasses.
They're just rose tinted glasses.
And you know, the world looks nice better
through rose tinted glasses.
I just never really considered the other side.
I guess it could look kind of rock starish.
Wasn't intended that way, certain?
Other than that, he looked like a guy used to know
in Colorado that ran all of the battle bands
shows that I judged on named Biff.
And of course that makes everyone who's hearing
this thing about Biff Henderson from back to the future.
Well, it wasn't his real name.
I'm a Biff, ladies and gentlemen.
But he made everyone call him Biff.
Yeah, I remember Biff.
And I thought that Mkree was a little bit like that too.
He was alright though.
Oh yeah, I liked Biff.
But I'm crazy.
Like we could be.
I never actually got to talk to him.
I see that's a shame.
And they're going to go on and they're going to talk a little bit more about the session.
They went through a whole thing about the microphones.
David and I have discussed that on a trade secrets.
And he's discussed it in morning coffee notes that he's posted on his
on his on his on scripting news.
And you know, there's a lot that we learned from that.
And I think that a lot that can be done.
But let's just continue to listen to the promiscuous bullet conversation.
But he was kind of elite.
See, that hurts.
I certainly didn't want to be elite in any way shape or form.
Yeah, it seemed like when he was doing the podcast thing.
He stood up there and basically went down his list of people that he found and enjoyed
and had decided to elevate.
Oh.
I certainly, of course, the people that I knew.
And I didn't know any of these people.
I didn't.
The only person I knew was Dave.
But certainly now the podcast is not face to face.
It never met them before.
I was happy to point him out.
But I wasn't trying to elevate anyone.
And so one pointed out, you know, rightly, it's a, hey, can't any, you know,
non-famous people get the mic.
And this is a whole problem about using the mics of Blader Khan.
And I think really the only reason we were using them in hindsight was,
so that everything could be recorded properly for a podcast.
And it probably hurt more than it did good because
the blog was supposed to be like screaming and talking through each other and showing
respect that appropriate times and jumping up and having comments.
And, but I think we're past that.
I think we, we understand that that could have been better.
But certainly certainly sucks.
But I like, sounds like I'm trying to elevate people to some certain status.
Because this is a place for everyone to participate.
I was going to do his level and said, okay, is this guy here?
Quick.
Tell us something about your stuff.
And then is this guy?
Well, shit.
I didn't, you know, I'm just waiting for people to raise their hands.
Like, tell us about something about your stuff without actually letting the conversation flow
and I didn't have dynamic way.
Hmm.
Well, I certainly tried to make it flow better in a dynamic way.
And some parts were slower than others.
And it was just a way to get some energy going, I guess.
Yeah.
Yeah, I sort of felt that that session was a little bit tight like that, too.
Now, I agree.
I certainly certainly a lot more I wanted to get out of it.
But it was a blogger call, right?
People are going to jump in and say stuff and then we're going to point around the room.
So have the way it went.
There's Matthew Bischoff calling in.
So we answer.
Kind of busy.
Real quick, then.
Hey, Matthew.
Hey, Adam, what's up?
I'm recording the source code right now.
Awesome.
I was just talking about the microphones of Blogger Khan.
And I was listening to the promiscuous bullet podcast.
And they're saying that I was elite.
And I made it a leadist.
And I'm hurting.
Yeah.
So we're going to do.
What can I do for you, Matthew?
Just want to your opinion on this.
I just started up a cafe pressure up at a cafepress.com.
So I thought I just wanted to take a look at it.
You realize I'm recording this, right?
Yeah.
No problem.
Okay.
If I press dot com slash I potter, what is it?
I potter merchandise?
Yes.
Cool.
Hold on.
Well, right now everyone listening to the source code
is surfing off to it immediately.
So what is it?
Explain what it is.
Well, I saw that if you've seen the Doppler video.
I potter client, they started a cafe pressure up.
And so I figured the I potter limited it.
Do you call it?
Should have a shop as well.
Okay.
I'm going to it now.
Hopefully.
All the stuff won't crash.
Okay.
Here we go.
Cool.
I potter lemon t-shirt.
Excellent.
That looks great.
Very cool.
Okay.
Well, you called it the perfect time.
We got your little plug in there.
Oh, yes.
Matthew Bishop.com.
Okay.
Have you taken it easy, bud?
Thanks, everybody.
Okay.
Take care.
Oh, right on.
And now we're back.
I guess that was enough of a transition.
As you listen to more of a promiscuous bullet.
The guys do go into something that I think is really cool.
They play Brad sucks from Brad sucks.
He said Brad sucks.net.
I think it is.
You'll see it in the production notes on the daily source code site.
I think it was actually Dave Slusher who started playing Brad sucks.
It's, you know, Brad is this guy who does everything.
He's a one man band with no fans.
It's kind of the mantra of what he's doing.
And so we've been picking this guy up and we've been playing parts of his demos
and of his, you know, what I guess they're called albums and stuff that is yet unreleased.
But, you know, here we have an opportunity to make one of our first non-RIA stars.
So I'm going to jump on the bandwagon.
You know, you've got three podcasts playing him.
Please enjoy Brad sucks.
Sounds a little bit like back sometimes a little bit like status quo.
And you don't have to listen.
It's not bad.
It's a dark band.
it's a bright band.
It's a dark band and it's a dark band.
It's a dark band.
And she'll ride with the brothers and the boys
And she'll ride with the boys
And she'll ride with the brothers and boys
And she'll ride with the boys and the boys
And she'll ride with the boys
Right, sucks
Dirt bag on the daily source code for Wednesday November 10th, 2004
It's about 10 minutes to 11pm, so I'm just going to get this one
In under the wire for today
It's going to be busy, I mean we are so close to move date
I'm Monday the movers come in
Tuesday the movers are still here
Then Wednesday Patricia is already in
Actually Tuesday night Patricia flies out with her sister
They're going to receive all the goods on Wednesday
Christina and I stay here in the completely empty castle bar for one bed
And then we fly out Thursday
We're going with a private plane with our dogs
And our cats to get them in at the very last minute
So hopefully all the doors are closed
Because the cats have to stay in doors for six weeks
Or whatever so they get oriented
Then all of a sudden got a nice curveball
Where the re-letters send a new rental agreement
Yeah, because the owner had come up with some stuff
He still wanted to put in there
I've never rented a house with this
There's a lot of shit in there
If I do anything wrong
I'm going to jail for so long
After throw the key away
It's like Christ, I have to review all that
What's just a pain
And then on top of that
Now the BBC has a new show called The Culture Show
Which actually it starts the first episode
It was tomorrow night on BBC 2 at 730
So that's 830 European Central Time
And I guess they have one of these really cute hosts
That host on Saturday or like the other big Saturday show
Or the Sunday morning show on the BBC
And they've got it totally set up
They've got producers, they've got writers, they've got
The crew, they're coming a day early, they're staying overnight
They insist on coming to the castle
They want to see how a podcast is done
Well great, it's going to be a freaking mess
It's going to be as real as you can get it
Because everything's in boxes
Basically everything's going to be torn down around me
Except for me and my laptop and my microphone
And everything else will be gone
So that's coming up
That's on Friday
So Friday, I will just cut a source code and do it with them
But then there's all kinds of other stuff
Banking matters, just coordination
And I missed a last minute guy
So this is usually when I get into my crunch
So if it's the podcasts are coming up a little bit late
And if you're not seeing a lot of posting going on on my site
There you go, it's going to at least take the next week
Until next Thursday
And even then, the whole town we're moving to
It's pretty much wi-fi but
Yeah, we'll have the car there
It's a logistical nightmare late as a gentleman
So anyway, new podcasts that I found
The one minute tip you can find this on audio.weblogs.com
Or also in ipod.org in the directory
And by the way, if you're doing a podcast
And you want to show up
If whatever you're making your RSS 2.0 feed
Whether you're your podcast feed
If it's not automatically pinging audio.weblogs.com
You can go to audio.weblogs.com slash pingform.html
PINGFOR and pingform.html
And then you can just enter into the name of your podcast
Enter the podcast feed
And it'll accept your ping and it'll put you right up on that list
So it's pretty important if you want to get your stuff out there
So this is where I found one minute tip
Today it's the JKL keys and Final Cut Pro
Yeah, it's a short computer tip
Hello and welcome to the one minute tip
A place to pick up quick tips to make you more computer efficient
Today's tip JK and L
In Apple's Final Cut Pro
Oh yeah, it's right there
But sometimes you just don't want to reach down and touch the mouse
When you've got your hands on the keyboard
In Apple's Final Cut Pro
Here is a great tip
The JK and L keys
Clustered right there on your right hand
And what I need like some of these keyboard shortcuts for I chat
For the video conference
When you go to
If you check it out, I chat naked.com
Believe me, that's where you want some short cut keys
The JK and L keys
Excited your keyboard are great for moving around
Inside of clips
The K key will stop the playback head
Okay, so you get the idea that's the one minute tip
Don't just get the URL
Moments?
Email us at tipat1minute.com
Okay one minute tip.com
That's where you can find out about
Well, you can subscribe to the podcast
I don't know if they have separate podcasts for separate applications
Or platforms if there's one for macro windows
Probably this is a Mac one since it's about the Final Cut Pro
But it's kind of cool, you know
Not the JK L keys, but that's probably an exception
More than the rule
Got an email now as we move on to
Concentrating on non-RIA music from Jason
From Hardcore and some of the radio
Of course, the podcast
Been around for almost ever since podcasting started
Hold on, let me just expand the note here
He says you recently proposed listeners
Out here in podcasting
Land, hunt down great music by indie bands
And you would produce the show
However, I'd like to steer you in a different direction
He says he's teamed up with the Chris at indie feed
And true blues that this has major potential for promoted bands
Is already having talks with labels about sending us
The catalogs, things are moving
So that's great, sounds like they're finding
People who want to participate
Participate by giving them the music
And we're giving the permission to play the music
So things are moving quickly in a positive direction
So what better way to recruit help
Then they want to ask for some help
Pretty basically here comes
Need you to ask people why the daily source code
If anyone would be interested in helping to maintain certain indie feeds
Okay, so if you look at the iPodder.org directory
There's a number of, if you go into the music section
There's a number of independent indie feeds
So he's handling the alternative modern rock channel with Chris
But the more moving activity get, of course
The more successful it will be and so he needs more people
Well, I totally agree, you know, I think that we can have all kinds of
Different subcategories at indie feeds
And I love the whole concept of the way indie feeds works
You know, where there's basically a little start-up
Before the song and it says, you know, this is where it's from
This is who these guys are about
And then you hear the song
And then at the end there's another tag that came from
Which indie feed it came and what you can do with it
But I still think that just like I played the Brad sucks, you know
You have to have to build a little bit of a platform
I won't, you know, if you guys get that set up
And please anyone who wants to help contribute
Just go to Hardcore and something to radio.blogspot.com
And Jason, I'm sure we have to have you help out
And, you know, someone wants to maintain
Some of those indie feeds
And we can just use more, you know, all I'll do is subscribe to them
And check it out and if I find something I'll start playing it
But still we got to keep playing attention to each other
And make sure that we can, you know, across the board
If, you know, if we're playing the same songs, you know, that's good
For at least it'll, it'll elevate something
I think. Let's see what happens with Brad sucks, you know,
If you like it, you know, play it on your podcast
Let's see what happens
Um, now, let's see where it was. Oh, yes, this was another
promo that came in on, actually this is very cool
Because we were talking about radio dramas
Um, and the long came, the human dog podcast
And of course, it was promoted on openpodcast.org
And you've got to listen to the drama piece
Well, actually, this is basically a trailer of
Human Dogs work in the podcasting drama sphere
And we've got to listen to the drama
Um, now, let's listen to the drama
of cast-drama anthology that Volgae Odeo, host by yours true.
The series begins this week with the premiere of the casual absurds.
I hope you enjoy your stay within the Volgae Odeo,
and please feel free to produce the rest of the website.
Address again is www.human-dog.com
and please, dear friends, do not forget to add that dish.
They're all of the way to waste those who do not end by warnings.
I look forward to our meeting, but until that time, I am the man named Ryan.
I received it into the darkness.
Okay, so the promo is hokeyer than the shows. Seriously, you should check them out,
but I didn't want to take anything out of contact with the show itself,
but you should definitely check it out.
It's real drama on podcasting, and it's cool that we've got yet another category.
We've got more categories being thought up and created every day
that they're going to start flowing to the directory.
Now, I know that iPodr1.1, the lemon stuff is out.
I guess the new iPodrX is out as well with its directory integration.
So if you want to read about it, just go to iPodr.org and check out the directory
and how you can contribute to building that directory.
So I'm pretty fried. I've got about half an hour down now.
Oh, you know what? I have now officially from the man himself,
from the base player from the band, American Heartbreak.
So I'm going to have already played a couple times on the daily source code.
Actually, going back more than two months ago, I think.
He gave me some of their existing CDs and the new one, which is now yet.
I think it's titled This is Rock and Roll.
From that, the song that I've been playing ever since I heard it on his own podcast,
Rock and Roll to Geek Show. This is the last of the superheroes.
American Heartbreak. I'm a daily source code.
We've seen them on TV our whole life.
Super the friends, we're the Roman stones of the larger life.
I can be like any one I see.
All the record and the drums leave.
This is the whole.
It's the songs of cash never I see me.
We are we are the last of the superheroes.
The last of the superheroes.
We are the 1970s.
Then all the boxes that I've dubbed tonight,
Wond fabulous makes me feel happier.
This life will see back up in me,
Got the stars in the dream release
London, town, heaven, hell, bed sound
Bowie, men, sweet
We are we are
Last of the silver wheel
London, town, heaven, hall
That's the name of the stars in the dream release
The stars in the dream release
London, town, heaven, hall
In the savage song, no one left to call
No no super heroes of the 19th and 19th
The last time I see more heroes
We are We are The last time I see more heroes
We are, we are the last of Superheroes, the last of Superheroes, over the 1970s.
Man, back in hard break, the last of the Superheroes on your daily source code.
Whoops.
Sorry, took off the headphones, forgot the Microsoft attached.
Wednesday, November 10th, 2004.
Can you hear it? Actually, I'm just going to listen to, listen to how hollow it sounds now.
Now I'm walking into, listen to this.
Hello.
One, two, see everything's empty almost in the main room.
And the curtains are all down.
We're moving on out of here, just a reminder that
I'm not quite sure how the source codes are going to be going for the next couple of days.
But I'm pretty sure I'll be able to still be able to get to my packing down this weekend.
And so this is one of the last times you're going to be hearing
the tranquil outdoors of Belgium of Flanders.
So, have a listen.
Because in one week from now, it'll be a different sound.
I mean, it's quiet there as well because we're out in the sticks.
But it's going to be a different kind of quiet.
I bet you we can really tell the difference.
So I'll just shut up for a couple of seconds here so you can hear it.
Right on.
Okay.
Now I got to get to bed because it's past 11.
My body doesn't know what the hell time it is.
To my girlfriend, Dawn, I say, I'm still fighting the man.
She knows what I mean.
And everyone else, who I haven't raised to in a lettuce level.
I'd love for you to tune in tomorrow.
When we bring you another daily source code, live from Flanders, Belgium.
As always, you can leave a comment.
Adam and Cory.com.
I'm catching up on the email by the way.
I had a good 10 hours of computer time on the way back.
So I'm getting better in the directories about the flood with new podcasts that I potter.org.
Sample all the latest podcasts.
Don't forget to check out audio.weblogs.com
And then you can always find the latest source code to then sourcecode.com
And when I got some time to post and check it out on 5.4.com
I'll be back tomorrow.
We're going to another source code.
We're going to use our developers to get one of the ones that party together.
Take care, Adam.
Our door, our door, our door.