The Power of Source Code
Yeah, hi everybody, it's Source Code. It is Saturday, August 21st, 2004. I'm Adam Curry.
Saturday afternoon in Curry Castle in Belgium. It's about 3.36. How's that for an approximate time for you?
Sorry about yesterday. No postings on the blog and no source code. It was just way too crazy.
During the radio show in the morning, as you know, we're winding down.
One more week to go and then two more days to finish up the month and that'll be all over.
We had the Chanuk crew who flew us in Iraq.
They flew us from Camp Smitty to Basra.
a final two or three hour drive from there to Kuwait on our way home.
And we also did some night goggle vision reconnaissance flights.
So anyway, they came by.
They wanted to see where we worked since we'd already seen their area of responsibility.
It was a good time, but tiring nonetheless.
From there, I went straight home.
There was someone who almost arrived immediately for an interview, which was, of course, all
set up.
But I keep forgetting I really don't like doing stuff on Friday afternoons.
And then on top of that, some folks who had seen the house earlier in the week came back,
wanted to see it again.
This time they brought the entire family.
And I got a call earlier this morning that they are coming back again on Monday.
So that looks good.
I don't know if you remember, two days ago I mentioned that Crystal, my assistant, had...
I'm not quite sure where she got it from.
She got one of these Pinnacle Systems Show Center, which is essentially a video device that you hook up to your television.
I have it hooked up to our big Grandmaster View screen here.
It has a Wi-Fi card, so it talks to your Wi-Fi environment.
And it sits there basically listening for a show center server, which I'm not quite sure what protocol it speaks.
It may be Windows Media Server, I'm not sure.
But that has to run on a Windows machine, so I still have an old Sony VAIO laptop with Windows 2000.
Loaded it up, and lo and behold, it's working.
First of all, regarding the...
the setup
the wifi setup
is stupid
you have to fill in
name, a network name, and it comes with a show center as the network name installed
standard, which makes no sense because, of course, that means everyone's going to have
to change that.
Either you have to change your Wi-Fi network name or you have to figure out how to change
it on the show center device, which means you've got to reboot, hold down the B key.
I mean, this is all stuff that is just not easy for people.
I think it should work like my laptop does.
When I walk in range of a new Wi-Fi network, it says, hey, should I add this?
Do you want to connect to it now?
That, of course, is the way this should work as well.
So basically, you create a database in the show center software on the PC.
Of course, just like a share program, like a peer-to-peer program, if you want, it'll
go through your entire disk and pull up all kinds of media files.
So that works pretty straightforward.
And it's basically...
Basically, you have three bins, music, movies, photos.
You can create playlists from them.
is the files that it will accept.
Let me see.
I think I have...
Here, it does tell me which files it'll accept.
Hold on.
mp3 windows media audio wave file jpeg png gif mpeg1 mpeg2 divx avi version 5 plus 4 plus 5
simple profile remember that is x video avi simple profile dv avi windows media video video files
also must all contain audio data well so apparently there's a quite a difference between
avis and avis because some really i had this huge bucket of bit torrent downloads which
are either mpegs or avis and some of the avis do work on the show center if you put it in a
windows media video it converts it to a vcd file you know so it's a little bit disappointing that
you just don't know exactly what is going to work or not and if you should convert prior to
putting it into this database
or if it
will do it by itself. It's very unclear.
Something it does have that's pretty cool is you can
set up a folder to be watched
and the minute you drop
anything into that folder, automatically
it will be added to the database and then
from the control center, the show center
in the living room, which has a remote control,
makes it nice, you can already
a little light pops on saying new media
and you go to the new media menu
it will show up and it will play.
Essentially when you select new media to be played
it's being streamed across
my Wi-Fi network.
So I'm going to play with it a little bit more
and I'm interested to see how
Tricia, my wife, and Christina, our daughter
how they pick it up
and how they use it and I'm putting mounted
volumes on their
computer desktops so they can just
drag and drop stuff in there as well.
So we'll see what happens. It'll be cool.
Right.
I told you that I've been reading
...
That would be big quotation marks.
Michael Crichton's Timeline.
The reason why I say reading
is because I've been listening to it on audiobook.
I actually just finished it yesterday afternoon
on my drive home, sitting in some extra traffic.
So I even was able to finish up
the last 25 minutes I thought
I wouldn't be able to listen to during my drive home.
Great book.
Really enjoyed it.
14 hours worth of audio.
And I got an email from Dave Weiner.
Let me just pick that up here.
FYI, I've become a member of audible.com
and am reading
Timeline now as I drive.
He's driving across country.
It's a very nice, if somewhat paranoid, service.
I guess he's referring to...
He could be referring to the book or to audible.com.
Thanks for the tip in your audio blog post.
Next stop, St. Augustine.
Dave.
Okay.
So there's something interesting.
I was talking about the audiobook.
I think what I even said is...
Gee, wouldn't it be cool if I could attach one of those DRM
protected audio files, because Audible.com uses the AAC, Apple, DRM, can't copy me stuff.
And if you tried to open it in iTunes just by double clicking it, it would then say, hey,
you know, you want to buy this book? Looks like Adam referred it to you. Of course, they have a
number, it's DRM, so they know that I bought it. And maybe they could give me two bucks for selling
another copy, because I think it goes for, I don't know, it goes for at least $10. What I want to do
today, though, is share with you a little piece from that book, a monologue, which I found very
interesting and very applicable to perhaps the reason why we have weblogs today. Now, if you're
reading this book still and don't want to hear any parts of it, then you should probably not listen
to this. It's definitely not a spoiler, doesn't mess you up at all about the plot or the outcome
of the book. But it's a monologue by one of my friends, and I'm going to share with you a little
one of the characters and he's basically doing
a pitch for this vision that he has, which is irrelevant, but listen to the theory behind
the pitch.
Now, of course, since this is an AAC file, I can't open it in any other application but
iTunes.
I tried to open it in QuickTime, didn't work either.
So I can't open it into my recording application, so I'm going to have to put the mic down on
the speaker so that I can start up iTunes and you can listen to this.
This is about three minutes, but it's a very interesting thing.
Hi.
He walked back and forth across the stage.
Today, everybody expects to be entertained, and they expect to be entertained all the time.
Business meetings must be snappy, with bullet lists and animated graphics, so executives aren't bored.
Malls and stores must be engaging, so they amuse as well as sell us.
Politicians must have pleasing video personalities and tell us only what we want to hear.
Schools must be careful not to bore young minds that expect the speed and complexity of television.
Students must be amused, everyone must be amused, or they will switch.
Switch brands, switch channels, switch parties, switch loyalties.
This is the intellectual reality of Western society at the end of the century.
In other centuries, human beings wanted to be saved, or improved, or freed, or educated.
But in our century, they want to be entertained.
The great fear is not of disease or death, but of boredom.
A sense of time on our hands.
a sense of nothing to do, a sense that we are not amused.
But where will this mania for entertainment end?
What will people do when they get tired of television, when they get tired of movies?
We already know the answer.
They go into participatory activities, sports, theme parks, amusement rides, roller coasters,
structured fun, planned thrills.
And what will they do when they tire of theme parks and planned thrills?
Sooner or later, the artifice becomes too noticeable.
They begin to realize that an amusement park is really a kind of jail in which you pay to be an inmate.
This artifice will drive them to seek authenticity.
Authenticity will be the buzzword of the 21st century.
And what is authentic?
Anything.
Anything that is not devised and structured to make a profit.
Anything that is not controlled by control.
corporations, anything that exists for its own sake, that assumes its own shape. But of course,
nothing in the modern world is allowed to assume its own shape. The modern world is the corporate
equivalent of a formal garden, where everything is planted and arranged for effect, where nothing is
untouched, where nothing is authentic. Where, then, will people turn for the rare and desirable
experience of authenticity? They will turn to the past. The past is unarguably authentic.
The past is a world that already existed before Disney and Murdoch and Nissan and Sony and IBM
and Amazon.
All the other shapers of the present day. The past was here before they were. The past rose
and fell without their intrusion and molding and
selling. The past is
real. It's authentic.
And this will
make the past unbelievably
attractive.
Well, that's
probably about enough of that.
And hopefully it sounded okay through my
air-based audio bridge.
So I thought that was just an
interesting bit of monologue.
One about how people were going to look for
reality. And maybe that's what weblogs
bring if you subscribe to that
type of vision. That weblogs
bring a sense of reality. Or
multiple weblogs can triangulate
reality. And the whole
bit about the past, who knows?
Maybe that's what archives are all about.
So what else?
um...
iPodder update, the application that turns your iPod into an audio MP3 aggregator.
So the current status is you fire it up manually.
It sucks in about six different feeds and updates your iTunes.
And if you have it, an iPod automatically.
I'm going to be working on the next release where there will be a separate text file sitting in the iPodder folder.
And that's going to be your subscription file.
So all you do is basically just add a new line with a URL to it to any MP3 enclosure feed with MP3 files.
And it'll automatically run through that file as well.
It'll parse it and download the enclosures when you run the iPodder application.
After that, so that'll probably be about release beta 06,
I hope to just have some form of installer that sets it all up for you and runs the program at a set interval.
with one configuration file
And you never hear from it again.
It just keeps running automatically at the intervals that you set.
And I think I mentioned in the previous show
that it looks like some developers out there
are working on their own versions.
Some Python stuff.
I'm looking forward to that coming out.
Please, make this better than I did.
Let's see.
That's about it.
Let me see.
I've been at this for...
How long are we going to talk?
14 minutes?
Okay, no song of the day.
Besides, enough copyright violation with that bit from the timeline audiobook.
But I'm going to go fill up the server with some more content.
See if I can now connect the bridge on that
so that if a new video comes in as a torrent,
bit torrent file,
it's downloaded and then automatically dropped into this watch folder
on the Windows PC server
so that we can then watch it in the living room.
Wow.
It's kind of like when I was a kid.
The RadioShack 101 projects.
Just need to have a red wire, a blue wire,
and a nice long yellow.
one and it'll all work.
Okay, everybody, that's it.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye.