Well, hi O.D. everybody and thank god it's Friday!
Welcome to the source code!
as the actual name of the place that we inhabited at the time being because we're almost out.
Patricia came back yesterday and she had been on a three-day trip to the UK and she'd been
around looking for houses and she put in an offer on one and looks like we're good to go.
And she completely complied with the only requests I had which were A,
a place that I could stand straight up in. You have no idea how low the houses are
outside of London, the country regions. It's just like, man, people were just small
back in the day I guess. Anything older than 100 years is going to be really really low
when it comes to ceilings. Second request was broadband internet. Well the area that
she's found something is in the county of Surrey, Surrey, which has quite a
number of high tech centers and we're right near a technology park at a
university.
I bet there's plenty of bandwidth there, great infrastructure, great trains, and my third
and final request was about half an hour away from an airport.
Well guess what?
There's an airport about half an hour away.
I'm completely jazzed because it has a flight school, which means I can continue my flight
training.
Of course I have a helicopter pilot's license.
Now I want fixed wing.
I've only done about 10 or 15 hours of regular airplane training.
So I'm going to do a fixed wing.
They have a flight school there that does the FAA certification, so that's the American
license.
perfect and they have a fly higher fly yourself program so if you're a member of
the club you can rent a beautiful plane they had they even have a Saratoga which
is a great single-engine airplane and nice cruising speed so oh yeah and the
house is really nice too that really is it's perfect it's absolutely phenomenal
and I'm not gonna say too much about it because Patricia was so excited about
checking you know out the house and the surroundings in the area that she
we didn't really pay too much attention to her videography skills and we had
last night when she came home we put up the video on the big screen here in the
living room and I almost got seasick just from you know the motions and she
did also inadvertently zoomed in a little bit so actually had to do some
pause and you know step framing back and forth to get a real good idea and
very hard to get a layout of of a of a house if you haven't been in it and
someone's just like whips through it with a video camera but we're really
excited and I'm sure that we're gonna have a good time there. It looks like
somewhere around the middle of November we'll be making our move.
Alright big shout out going to Skipper today on the source code she is so far
the one in the
request this song on the daily source code. So I'm gonna play it for her. Of course she was also my
first employee at OnRamp back in the...
to New York City.
I've been driving all night man's wet on the wheel
Red Allah
Videos, things, I've forgotten song
RERALAAA
Thanks for watching!
Here I go!
And it's common on the stall
And the newsman sang
I want my rain, I love it!
GO!
Red our love
Oh shit, that's what you get for MP3s.
Miss the very ending of it.
Gold nearing radar love on the source code,
going out by request to Skipper in New York City.
And I made a very important discovery yesterday.
I found something, a feature, a hidden feature,
it probably wasn't intentionally hidden,
but it was hard to find, in Audio Hijack Pro.
I discovered that if you go to the effects portion
of the application, now this is a program
that you can record audio from any application
running on your Macintosh.
The effects I thought was really cool
because you can basically plug in reverbs and echoes
and flangers and compressors and whatever you can think of.
You can really process the sound coming from the application
just perfectly, which is all right.
But what you want to do is, I've
played about this many, many times,
I want to be able to mix in a microphone signal.
Well, darn wouldn't you know it.
Right there under effects is a VST plug-in.
Now I'm not sure if it comes with Audio Hijack Pro or
it picked it up for my hard drive somewhere. I've certainly never purchased any
my knowledge. So it's probably a free plugin and it actually says voiceover. Duh! And it
gives you a nice little effects panel. You can select the audio device. So I've selected
built-in audio, selected line-in. That's what my mic's connected to. It does little
crossfade for you. It has an auto ducking threshold if you don't want to click on and
off switch, which I do like to do because otherwise any cough or sudden noise will
interrupt the record and actually lower the volume of the record. And you can
actually set that up so it's mixed in with the signal mixed in as its own source.
So now I have a very stable environment. Well knock on wood and you know there's
my invitation to Murphy. It appears very stable and I can now get the audio from
any application I want. In fact I have a couple other bits queued up for later in
the show which are going to come from QuickTime. I can also perfectly bring in
iChat. I think I've
got it all running.
I'm just going to try this setup for a week or so.
I can't wait to do another trade secret with Dave because that's always the real test.
As it is right now, if someone were to instant message me, I could bring you into the show
immediately.
I could put you on the air.
Let me just see if I'm actually online at all at this moment.
Very dangerous switching applications where I'm doing this stuff.
Yeah, I'm online.
People who have me in their buddy list, you know that if I'm online and I'll actually
put something in my status bar there, let's see, I'll put in a custom thing there.
Oh, actually, no, I have a custom thing.
Have it on the air.
There we go.
On the air.
If I'm on the air and you have something to say, go ahead, just give me an eye chat.
Just check and see.
The settings are all, oops, settings are all.
Okay, there we go.
That's better.
Perfect.
I can close that up.
Right, we're all set.
So should anyone call in?
Probably won't because of the first time I'm mentioning it.
But it's all set up.
And as I said, it's pretty stable.
There's a few quirks to it.
But once I've tried it out for about a week, then I'm going to write it up so that people
can start to emulate the same setup because now I don't even have a breakout box working.
Granted, I can't route the audio yet back to the person on the other end of the call.
And Skype still, I was able to get it working a little bit, but Skype is just not really
happy with what I'm doing.
And until they support multiple sound devices, I guess we just can't use it.
So we'll have to wait until they...
Oh, it's still in beta.
It was a long way to go.
I'll see if there's a Skype mailing list and see if I can get some feature requests
in there.
Another question I had, and I've got a lot of feedback on the past shows and I really
appreciate it, is file size.
Now looking at the bandwidth, I'm pushing out at this point at the top of the hour when
there's a new source code or new trade secrets.
upwards of 12 megabits per second of traffic.
This is an enormous amount.
And so eventually, that's going to cause problems.
And so we know that we're working on bit torrent integration,
and I don't want to talk too much about that today.
But one of the things that certainly can be done
is to lower the file size.
So I've been on a quest.
I don't understand too much about it
about continuous bit rate, variable bit rate.
Yeah, I do understand what it is
and how it's supposed to work.
But in practice, what is the right setting?
What is the perfect setting for voice and music
and for the slowest file size possible?
Well, wouldn't you know it?
We got an audio message from Dr. Dave,
who was more than happy to explain the right way to do it.
And Dr. Dave, it's good to have him online,
because, well, you'll hear immediately,
this is a guy that you want to have some kind of podcast
from on a daily basis.
Check him out.
Hello, I'm Dr. Dave from Las Vegas,
former disc jockey in the Las Vegas, Phoenix,
in San Diego markets.
But that goes way back to this.
I don't even know if you're that old.
Bumper Morgan is a friend of mine,
and he was kind enough to send me a link to your site,
where you archive your mp3 files.
Listening to the one dated today, 9...
before you were talking about file size.
Well, may I suggest a few things?
First, use a lower bit rate.
32 KBS will still give you up to 16 kilohertz
in audio quality, far superior to FM radio,
and really better than most systems
and headphones out there can reproduce.
So by doing that, or if you go down to 22 KBS,
you're still at 11 kilohertz, about equal to FM radio,
and essentially cutting your file size in half.
Two other ways to decrease your file size
are stretch, which actually compresses
maintaining frequency and pitch and delete silence, which allows for all of the intelligible
information to be saved and eliminates the silent portions.
It's an effect that's built into...
For further information drop me a voicemail or email awchetcocks.net.
Again from Las Vegas it's Dr. Dave. Clear.
Oh, clear. Perfect. I'd fly with Dr. Dave any day. I'd love to hear about the radio.
Okay, so I'm going to take his advice and see if I can lower it down to 32 to get to half the file size if not all re-encode.
But, wouldn't it be great to have Dr. Dave, I gotta have Dr. Dave cut some liners, some
jingles for the show, you know, this is perfect for the daily source code, outstanding.
So, I'm gonna work on that.
And I do wanna, I'm almost ready to make an endorsement.
And I'm talking about iPodder.
iPodder, this is the first time you're hearing the show, is a small program that basically
fills up your iPod with anything you subscribe to, with shows, information, audio books,
well, we're still working on the audio books part, but it is just beginning.
Now, I'm using a Mac, but there are currently versions for Mac, Windows,
Linux, and Pocket PC.
And I know there's also a Java version being worked on.
So there's plenty of opportunity for everyone to play with this.
It doesn't also only work with iPod, it works with Windows and
other, with a Windows Media Player and anything that you can sync up to
Windows Media Player, it manages stuff from your playlist.
It's great.
So, go to iPodder.org, check it out.
Now, I feel that it's about.
time to make an endorsement for a product because what I want to get away from is, you know,
all these versions floating out there.
Now already I've seen everything kind of come together and I'm still a bit confused and I'm
not trying to intervene too much.
I'm not quite sure who's working with who and where.
But I think that pretty soon we should be able to say here's iPod for Mac, here's
iPod for Windows and here's iPod for Linux and if we have it here's iPod for, for
a pocket PC but just one version, not multiple versions and already some of the
scripts have been discontinued and work is, you know, as I said is being focused on
certain apps.
I want to point out iPod or X.
This is what I've been using for the past couple of days and iPod or X is based on
I believe the iSpider engine.
It doesn't matter because it's all Python under the hood and the iPod or X part
is really just the interface.
I've also seen some screenshots of a Windows interface which emulates what iPod
I'm really really happy about iPodRx because it has no install.
It's an application. You drop it in your applications folder, you double click it, it opens, it runs.
It immediately shows you your feeds, you can add there, you can delete from there, you can check there,
you can stop the check if you want to, you can make it run automatically, you can put a little slider,
control when it's going to run. And these guys understand now what users are looking for.
When you say that it runs automatically, it tells you right there.
When you run this automatically, even when you quit the application, it's still going to continue to run
and fill up your iPod. Turning it off will obviously turn it off.
And they also understand the marketing. If you look at iPodR.sourceforge.net,
that's what you say, wait a minute, am I saying that correctly?
I'm afraid to surf. Damn.
I'll post a link to iPodRx. See, this is how confusing it is.
Look at that website.
One simple page with beautiful graphics, with very simple language tells you exactly what
it does, exactly what it is, and it's just inviting.
You just want to go and do it.
You want to get this and get your hands on it.
So I'm leaning towards an endorsement there for the Mac version of the iPodder, and I'd
like to look at candidates for Windows.
I have a Windows machine here, a Windows 2000 machine.
I can run something there.
And I'd like to get this out sometime next week, because we need to move on.
We've got to get going, particularly on the publishing side as it comes to BitTorrent,
so that we can start saving ourselves some bandwidth.
I pointed to something else on my weblog today, live.curry.com, a keynote speech held for
the music industry by Andrew Olofsky.
And I urge you to read that, because he said something there that is so beautiful.
He says that in about five years...
There will be an iPod that will fill itself up automatically.
Apple probably won't make that iPod, someone else will.
And I went, yes. Not five years from now, my friend.
It's already been done. And we're all a group of very dedicated people.
And you should read his vision on that because he says, in essence, he says,
music industry now is the time to pounce.
There is no bigger opportunity to make money off of the music business by selling
music and packaging in new and interesting ways than right now.
Now the flawed, I think, his speech, not that it's a flawed idea,
is he says, look, for all the crap you're going to go through,
in addition to what you've gone through already, by switching to digital and download and peer to
And he has some very, very clear ideas on how to make money, regardless of whether peer-to-peer
sharing and just, you know, exchange of music is going on or not.
His bridge finance, if you will, is a taxation.
And oh, my daughter just instant messaged me, don't forget to videotape top of the pub's
BBC one 830p.
You got it, dear.
I have the...
Good Charlotte.
Good Charlotte's going to be on.
Can you close the door for me, hon?
Thank you.
Bye.
Yeah, he says taxation is the way to go.
And of course it would cost next to nothing, but to get that to happen were probably, well,
if the music business, you know, took that idea, they could probably lobby that reasonably
effectively, but I doubt that they'll go for that.
But that did give me a whole bunch of ideas, man.
Just a whole bunch of ideas running around in my head.
And I came across a couple of sound clips that I want to play for you.
Sound pertains to the music business, although it's aimed at George Bush, of course.
stuff that I just pick up on the net from the blog digger media feed and other places.
And I really want to try and start fill the source code up a little bit more with stuff
that's out there.
And hey, if you've got a cool song or just anything, send me a pointer.
I love to play stuff and particularly stuff that you won't hear on commercial radio.
And I think we ought to use this medium as optimally as possible in anticipation
of the record business catching on.
Right, we got a couple of years.
So here's something I picked up off blog digger feed.
This is called scum of the earth.
Scum of the earth.
George W. Bush.
The fat fuck.
Russ Zimbab.
George Liddy.
Pint.
And pensioners of the state.
We ought to be heard.
George W. Bush.
Russ.
Pint.
Terrorism.
Russ.
Scum of the earth.
George W. Bush.
The fat fuck.
Terrible.
Russ Zimbab.
George Liddy.
Pint.
And pensioners of the state.
We ought to be heard.
Spoon!
Tip tip terrace in the
Rock
Gumbelord
Yeah
George W. Bush
The Fast Pop
Tip tip terrace in the
Gumbelord
Last symbol.
Go on, little pimp.
And pimpness of the state, we ought to be...
Ruff.
George W. Bush.
Scum of the Earth.
Well, I'm not quite sure what the message is there, unless you take it at completely
at face value.
Scum of the Earth from the blog digger media feed.
And I should probably say that source code is NSFW and it's always going to be that
way.
You may not get your, you know, the porn you're looking for on each listen of a show,
but you can certainly expect some raunchy stuff to be played once in a while.
And I love mashups and mixes.
In fact, well, maybe I'll do one tomorrow, you never know.
But certainly for Monday's source code, I'll scrunch up a couple of mashups.
That's where you take an old song, a new song, mix them together.
It's cool.
It's kind of a retro techno thing.
But you'll probably dig it.
If not, let me know.
Adam at Curry.com.
This is also your show.
And this, of course, is where users and developers party together.
Gonna take a look in the mailbag.
Hold on.
I got some mailbag music for us here.
Oops, there we go.
Let's see.
Switching to male, so that can always mess up the sound.
What you did there?
Okay.
Got male from...let me see.
This is from Andrew Jaffe.
He actually sent this to Dave Weiner and myself regarding the Daily Source Code.
And he listens to our shows while he's riding the tube in London.
He also says he's looking forward to my arrival.
said something pretty astute. He said, you know, I really love listening to all these
podcasts, but when are people going to stop talking about the podcasting themselves and
actually do some podcasting? And this isn't working too well with my quick time window.
It's definitely not liking this. Okay, let me just turn that off. Again, a little low
on processing speed here. So I totally agree. Andrew, you know, the days of
testing, testing one, two, three, four, you know, that's almost over. We're getting our
At least 600, 700 people subscribed to the daily source code.
That's a lot of people.
Put them all in one room and you'll see.
And he also has a feature request for the iPod, which I asked him to send off to the iPod
development list.
And I don't know if Andrew is...
Let me see.
He's in the Astrophysics Group.
Are you a user or developer in the Astrophysics Group at Imperial College?
His request is for some file management.
I knew that was going to come.
And I think that's something that can be done in the ongoing development of iPodr,
is how your cache is cleaned up, when files are deleted, et cetera.
It's a pretty normal stuff.
And I think that's a great user request.
Let's see.
Oh, Dave and I were talking on the...
On Trade Secrets about Netflix, about the RSS feeds for your queue on Netflix,
and how he wants to aggregate those together.
If you haven't heard his explanation of what he wants to do,
I suggest you listen to Trade Secrets volume number...
So, Miles Weisslater from meetup.com sent me a link and said that the UK version of Netflix
is videoisland.com.
So even though it's not available in Belgium and not in the Netherlands when I get to
the UK, I can also get a Netflix-like subscription.
I don't know if they have RSS feeds though, hopefully by the time I get there.
And Pete Pradol, Raster Web Audio, sent me a little note, a blurb about ESPN.
I guess this is taken from their homepage.
I'm just going to read this quote.
With our last redesign in 2003, ESPN.com
motion. By downloading high quality video transparently to users hard drives we were able to give our
viewers free of charge some of the highest quality video on the web with no waiting no buffering
and no noticeable encoding artifacts. The simple installation of the little ESPN ActiveX control
users could watch freshly cut ESPN video right within our front page. So sounds like these
guys have the right idea you know the thought of bringing in video or bringing in any type of
content using that word overnight when you're basically on downtime you know and it doesn't
have to be overnight with today's bandwidth speed you've got a real fast pipe you can set it for a
couple times a day just like iPodder but you know I doubt that they're using RSS and that's really
a shame you know think about the audience they could have how they could increase their audience
just you know with with one day's worth of development and a little bit of thought and
just the right blink here and there I mean people would go
freaking nuts. And they'd pay for that, I'm sure they would. The infrastructure is already
there. There are so many news readers out there that already support enclosures and people
are working on more every single day. It's a shame. It's absolutely a shame.
And I wanted to talk about Mars Edit. This is a brand new application for Mac OS X and
it's a blogging app. And it can, it basically is a front end for different blogging systems.
And it supports a whole slew of them. You know, every single one that I know and
actually, and then some, including Radio User Land, which is what I use. And so
basically it knows the API of the weblog system you use. And it also works for
Manila sites and for movable type and for blogger. It's beautiful. But it has so
much built in. It is so well thought out. And I think that's probably very much
because it's a, it comes from a Mac, a Mac developers thinking. It's so user
friendly and I've started using it now and it's still, it's in beta.
now. But it's just kick-ass. It really does the job well. It does it fast. It's real simple
because I do a lot of, I have to go back and edit a lot of my posts mainly for spelling
errors that I don't, I check posts, the posts. I don't know why, but I do and people will
point out huge glaring errors. And also it's easier than going to my web log and looking
down the page. I can just look at the last 50 postings that I did and pull out information
that I might want to talk about. It's very whizzy-wig although you basically, the way I
use it is you know I write up the post and then I'll add the links and it does
show those to you in HTML code, but at the same time you can have a preview window
open and it types along with you so you can see whizzy-wig exactly what it's
going to look like. So that's, that's pretty good. And it also, and the
whizzy-wig is really a browser so if you add a picture which it also has a
little special window pane for to help you upload pictures to your server, it's
It's fantastic. It's really what I've been looking for.
I've been using an outliner to do my posts.
I really like using an outliner for writing, but for the
length of the post that I make, you know, if I really have to write something
that's going to be a couple paragraphs or that, you know, lots of thought needs to go into,
then I'll write in an outliner first and then I'll just copy-paste it into
into Mars Edit. And don't even have to do that because Mars Edit
is fully scriptable. So I could pass it off from an outline window
from Radio Userland right into that, into the
into the Mars Edit, you know, the new posting creation window.
I was going to say something else about it. Oh, yeah, it has built in Apple
Scripts. One that I've been, I just started using, which oh man,
it's like diarrhea of the blog. It's a post from Safari. So basically you just
copy a little bit of text on a web page in Safari. You run the script from the
from the Mars Edit menu.
and it posts in a post for you, which is also configurable.
It'll take the title of the page, you know, what's in the menu bar.
It'll do a colon and then a quotation mark.
So it's really, it's removing four steps that I used to do manually in the Outliner.
I should look at the script actually, but it's really cool.
You can set the parameters, how you want the default post to show up when you post from Safari.
So just totally tits as we say in New Jersey.
And only one request, of course, is enclosure support.
You know, and I would fully expect to be able to just drag and drop something on there,
but I'll take a URL that'll be great for me.
And you know, once that's in there, it's, wow, it's great.
I can't wait until the final candidate is released.
I'm a customer for sure.
Okay, what are we doing here?
32 minutes. Time to wrap up.
Ooh, did I get rid of that I had?
Oh shoot, I was going to play like pull it up from iTunes for you now.
It's gonna play another song that I found on the blog digger media feed.
I'm gonna play that as the fight. It's just a little it's just a little ditty. It's from Uncle Neptune. Yeah, here we go
I've got it in it. Oops
be careful when I switch from one application to the next.
It's just a nice little ditty that I think will cheer you up for a Friday.
I hear Robbins...
Or if I never feel blue
Remember that there's always something that you can do
When you see the good in everything
I see sunshine
Or if I'm ever feeling blue
Remember that there's always something that you can do
Where you see the good in everything
When the day is dark and bright and-
Let us see the gift in every day
I feel sweet love in a sad world
is really grand
For if I'm ever feeling blue
Remember that's always something that you can do
When you see the cut in everything
Uncle Neptune when you see the good in everything and that's it for the sor-
September 24th, 2004.
You can always get to the archives of the DailySource code at DailySourceCode.com and of course that's
where you'll find the iPod or Feet.
Subscribe, RSS 2.0 with enclosures.
DailySourceCode.com slash RSS.XML.
Have a great weekend everybody.
Talk to you soon.
Bye bye.
Subscribe, RSS 2.0 with enclosures.