It's the Daily Source Code! Good afternoon from Curry Castle in Belgium!
I discovered yesterday although a little bit too late that I had lowered my mic volume
instead of the opening tune, the Rachmaninoff-Burris remix.
Anyway, today is September, what is it?
September 9th, 2004.
I'm Adam Curry.
This is the source code available at DailySourceCode.com and via subscription with RSS 2.0 enclosures
at DailySourceCode.com slash RSS.XML.
This is the place where users and developers party together and great news, we have a logo.
Yeah.
Thanks to Jaco van at skipintro.nl.
I actually worked with Jaco a couple of years ago when we were doing the jammedy stuff at
Amsterdam and he now has his office right at the backside of the garage where I parked
my car whenever I'm in Amsterdam.
He actually had to walk to the garage to get to their office which I've never been to unfortunately.
I cooked up a daily source code logo, a little animated GIF, and I'm really happy with it,
so thank you very much, Jaco.
And a technical mistake that I made yesterday, I really messed up.
I was talking about Murphy's Law and how Murphy struck on the Genesis probe that went
to collect dust from the sun or dust particles.
So it wasn't two helicopters that had a net struck between them.
By the way, that was the way it was reported here in the press in the Netherlands.
But it was one helicopter, maybe they had a backup helicopter flying around as well.
It was supposed to catch the Genesis, well, let's just call it a disk, by its parachute
and with a grappling hook, which seems like a real tough maneuver to me.
But anyway, they didn't get to try it out for real, unfortunately.
And I do hope that there's something left of the experiments that they did and they'll
be able to use some of the data.
I want to talk briefly today about Skype.
I know I've talked about it before, but this program is so beautiful.
And it's really just boggling my mind, particularly the more I look into voice over IP and what's
available now and what's inevitably coming in the very near future.
So first of all, I don't know if Skype seems to be a pretty closed environment and I don't
know if anyone can let me know if this works the same as SIP, which is what seems to be
a standard that's out there amongst voice over IP providers.
Not really, not, but what are they doing?
What is the peer-to-peer part of Skype that is so important that gives it an advantage
over using the SIP protocol?
I can't see any from a user's perspective and it may not make any difference the way
telephony is working right now in voice over IP.
It could of course change with some of the services, but if you have any idea please
let me know at adamantcurry.com.
And I'm still looking for a voice over IP provider and a lot of people sent me different
links, most of the stuff I'd already...
you've found is one actually in the Netherlands called Rits Taylor-Kolm who almost offer what
I'm looking for but I'll just go through one more time and maybe you can help me out.
I'm looking for a provider.
It doesn't matter where the provider is located, as long as I can get a local dial-up line,
so my own dedicated number in the Netherlands, that could be anywhere, preferably Amsterdam,
in Belgium, which is, that's only optional since we'll only be here for a couple more
months and definitely one or two in the States.
I'd love to have a California number and a New York number.
That way I can call just about anybody I want and they can also call me at the very low
cost of voice over IP because all the pricing seems to be more or less the same.
Interestingly enough, each country has its own specific rates for the mobile telephony in
that country.
So if I want to call Amsterdam via Skype, for instance, it doesn't matter where I'm
calling from, of course, since I'm doing that over the internet, then it winds up costing
me to a landline in Amsterdam I think four cents a minute and if I call a mobile phone
it all of a sudden it bops up to like thirty seven cents a minute.
Then again a mobile phone in Belgium is cheaper.
So there's all different rates going on in the mobile industry for sure.
But again that's all I'm looking for a voice over IP provider that can give me that and
I guess I'd want to have a SIP compatible provider and I'm only presuming that SIP
works just as well as Skype if it doesn't then I'll wait until Skype gets more
of their services together because it blows me away.
Every single time I call someone I'm calling people now from Skype exclusively
because it's just cheaper and actually people comment on the quality they say
it sounds much better I got my headphones on it works and I'm in front of the
computer anyway usually when I'm on the phone looking at stuff for reference
material when I'm talking to someone so it's perfect just would like to see if I
can do even better by getting local over.
local dial-up numbers in the states and in the Netherlands and in Belgium as well, if it all possible.
Now, on to iPodder. First of all, my apologies to Dave Slusher.
I had commented and I'd given some feedback on the Get-Enclosures Perl script iPodder.
You can find all of these different versions of iPodder. They're all designed to do the same
thing to bring in content into your iPodder or other mobile mp3 player.
So I've been using his script instead of my own Apple script and I'd said that I'm getting all
kinds of duplicates and all kinds of crap flying around and the problem was that I had incorrectly
entered my cron job. So I had the hour right and I told you to run it only these hours,
run it on any day and so I thought I'd done all the entries right except at the very beginning
you have to also specify a minute otherwise it's going to run every single minute.
for that entire hour that you specified and that's why I was getting all these duplicates and everything was freaking out.
So it was totally my fault and I apologize for any implications that the script was buggy because it's not. Now it's working perfectly.
But here's another great example. I mean the fact that I even know what a cron job is puts me way ahead of any user that you can think of in the stuff, the people we're making this stuff for.
And we need to hide that and I don't mean hide it as much as we don't want to tell anyone what we're doing but we need to mask and just set it up in a much easier fashion.
So on that very first run it should say, oh okay I'm going to install this and it's going to run every night at 1am and every morning at 6am.
Is this okay? And you can say yes for the defaults or you could specify maybe a couple different hours.
Maybe just with checkboxes. Doesn't have to be anything super big.
Another script that has been released, another iPodder script which is now also on the download directory on ipodder.org is PyPodder.
And I tried this one out. I like it very much.
The best part about it, I guess, is you don't have to download any other additional software.
If you have Python running on your machine, and just about every computer these days,
I think maybe Windows even comes pre-installed with Python.
I believe my Mac came with it pre-installed, but if not, it's very simple.
You can get Mac Python, you download and you install that once.
But again, that's where the install process should check.
Is Python in the environment if not download and install?
Then Pipotter goes on to actually do a little bit of installation for you.
It creates a folder on the Mac that is in your library folder
and puts all of the feeds into a feed file.
That's a little bit hard to find. If you want to adjust the feeds or remove a feed or add one,
you have to kind of go hunting.
for that feed file, so that's something that could be presented a little bit better to
the user.
Additionally, it's kind of a shame that the downloads before they're added to the iTunes
playlist that they're all crammed into one directory called Pipodder in your iTunes music
directory or in the music directory of your hard drive, which is a shame because I really
like folders being created with the name of the channel that the downloads came from.
But otherwise, a great script, really efficient, and it's up on the download directory now as well.
Excellent.
I got some comments on the bit we were talking about yesterday about radio.
How MSN Radio is copying terrestrial radio broadcast stations formats and trying to,
you know, I'm trying to present a clutter free quote unquote radio station with the same music.
mix, well, I saw an email, actually I saw a track back from Peter Rucavina and I posted
to that.
And he says, you know, my main problem is I have no drive time.
He has no commute or very little commute and therefore he feels that he can't catch
up on some of the programs and audio blog posts that he would like to.
But as he astutely points out, you know, there is some television he could spend
little less time watching since it's really just not worth it.
I don't know, you have to make those choices yourself.
That's your own priorities.
But yeah, of course, you know, if we're shooting for drive time people were, you know,
we're going to miss out on other people.
But I'm sure that, you know, if the shows are compelling enough, people will find time
to listen to them.
Admittedly, I'm even having a little more trouble since I don't have that daily commute
an hour and six minutes up and an hour and a half back.
So I'm missing out.
finding it harder to catch stuff on the first day, I definitely have to plan and say, okay,
I'm going to go out and work out and do some exercises, walk around and then I'll listen
to whatever I have queued up.
But also some of the stuff that came down in the past two days wasn't particularly that
interesting.
Two IT conversations that I didn't care to care for that much.
Yeah, that was an interesting legal terminology in there.
But it didn't catch me this time around.
And see Halley Suit had Bob Metcalf inventor of Ethernet on memory lane.
I don't care about that.
I've just been given a glass of orange juice.
Hold on.
It's eight minutes past one Thursday afternoon and I'm not even dressed yet.
Hey, that is the life of a guy without a job.
So yeah, added another feed to the directory on iPodder.org.
It's the mix of the week feed.
It's an MP3 mixed with new and older tunes all together.
So if you're into cool mixes, definitely subscribe to that and that will work with
iPodder, that feed.
And came across another program because you can't call it an audio blog post
through reinvented.net.
It's a program called Live from the Formosa Tea House.
And I'll just let you hear a little bit of it.
It's an interesting format.
I think it's three guys who sat down and had lunch at the Formosa Tea House,
apparently.
And you can hear the kind of the Muse act going in the background.
And they're just discussing all kinds of general topics, politics, their food.
What is a blog post like this supposed to, how is it supposed to work, what's supposed
to sound like?
I'll just let you hear a little bit just to get the feel of what they were putting together
because I think it definitely has potential.
Check this out.
Great, insightful post.
You'll get one comment and I like that idea.
We're no comments whatsoever.
Who knows?
Maybe you post on a Sunday.
You get that post.
People do things.
I find that the replies, like the reader comments, that they're not going to be a comment.
So you probably noticed right off the bat what I noticed the first, when I listened to this,
is it's really hard to hear their voices and so that's a shame but that's just something
that can be solved with maybe two microphones.
That should be possible on most setups and maybe a little bit of sound processing on the
recording end.
It's a lot of stuff that we've got to figure out to make this work but the natural mix
of the environment, I think they had right on with a little bit of background music going
on there.
And it was a...
It was kind of fun to listen into what they were talking about.
So you can check that out through reinvented.net.
Something else I came across.
Oh, this is from one of my favorite feeds, which of course is the Blog Digger Media Feed.
And I heard this, actually I heard it on the radio this morning, bright and early, and
I was like, wow, that's really good, and I had no idea where it came from.
And I was about to go look for it.
When lo and behold, I checked iTunes and it was already sitting right there.
It's a classic, and we'll actually do this as the song of the day for today.
It's a classic from YouTube, although with a new vocalist.
And the editing on this is just simply amazing.
Check out George W with Sunday Bloody Sunday.
There's been a lot of talk about this next song.
I can't believe the news today.
I can't close my eyes and make it go away.
Hello! Hello! Let's taste this sauce! Hello! Too, too, too long! Too long!
We can be as one tonight.
Tonight.
Broken models of your children's feats.
Body stone across the dead end's feats.
But it won't need the battle hall.
It puts my back on the ground.
Sunday, what do you sound?
Sunday, bloody Sunday
Let's roll
And the battle has just begun
This mini lost in him
He has won
The Tracer's War for their hearts
Mother's sh**
Thank you so much.
What's your song, babe?
Hello!
Hello.
Two long.
We can be as one tonight, tonight, tonight.
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, Sunday.
Let's roll this.
If anyone wants more details, I can if you find them online.
The web address is not very easy to remember.
Park, park, don't know.
Walk the tears from your eyes.
Walk your tears away.
Sunday Bloody Sunday
Let's go!
We need a drink while tomorrow at night.
Something like something
Next Sunday.
It's Sunday!
Brilliant. Not too sure who created this, unfortunately. The metadata only states the artist as Rx and it's from the album The Party Party.
It's Sunday Bloody Sunday here on Source Code. Moving along, I got an email in response to my question is where you listen to the source code.
Is it indeed during your commute? Is it at work? Is it at home? Is it while you're working out? Is it in the bathtub?
I got one from Hedzers Hotsmann from the Netherlands. He's studying part-time at the Freit Universiteit, the Free University of Amsterdam.
He says what he always does is he always records lectures on his iPod. I guess he's using a Gryphon i-mic or something like that.
So that he can review them again and go back and listen to pieces later on if he so wishes.
He says a great idea for the iPod would be for either a lecture room or you could do it by course, which would make sense.
RSS feed with all of the lectures so that if you couldn't go, if you're sick or if you
didn't feel like going, or if you just want to keep a record of it, all you have to do
is subscribe once to a certain lecture feed and they'll keep flowing in.
So a great use and an excellent idea.
So it's kind of, yeah, everything's kind of cool around here.
We're starting to wrap things up.
We plan to be out of the country by the first of the year or before.
So house hunting in the UK is going to start seriously in about a week or two.
Patricia has one more show she's going to do.
It's a fashion show and she's designing the makeup and the models.
So she's still pretty busy with that.
But then she'll be off to the UK to find us a house.
And so my quest will be besides working on the iPodder and the daily source code and
whatever other trouble I can get into and trying to make the world a better place.
I'll be working on my fixed wing license as you know I have a.
I'm a helicopter pilot. I plan on hopefully on my way to blogger con in
November I hope to go through Florida, Pasadena, Florida
to do my check ride for my commercial
Pilots license for helicopter and then as I said I want to get my fixed-wing license
The flying bit is you know the navigation everything is pretty much the same
But flying a
Regular airplane versus a helicopter there are some definite differences and I need to really build up
Some hours so I feel confident enough because I plan on definitely flying back and forth between
the mainland and the UK
Pretty regularly certainly for the first year and it's much
It's just much much cheaper to do that with an airplane than with a helicopter helicopter doesn't even go that much slower
But it's still it's using a fixed-wing is just much more efficient for that. So I've been looking into
An interesting category of
Aircraft you know, so what I'm learning on now is it
like a Cessna 172. It's a very standard airplane. It's like all of your typical little plane
that people fly around on the weekends. But there's a whole new category called VLA,
Very Light Aircraft. And these used to be known as the, I guess it came originally
from the ultra lights, which are pretty much like those broomsticks that fly. You just
sit on them one after another. But the very lights are, many of them I believe are
now certified, which means you can land at a regular airport with them, maybe not
just confined to certain hobbyist airfields. And some of them are just
absolutely stunningly beautiful. I think it was the velocity that I saw that has
a canard wing that's a small wing in the front of the nose. Canard meaning
duck, so it has kind of a duck bill, which has all kinds of safety advantages.
You can't, it's almost impossible to pull it into a stall because the first wing
will stall.
all before the main wings. But anyway, I mean gull wing doors, seats, four or five, attractable
landing gear. Now you're supposed to build them yourself because these are kits. But
I'm pretty sure you can work something out where you get it pretty much pre-built. But
they're really efficient, they're very fast and they're just looking really, really
good. Great machines. Tony, if you have any suggestions about excellent
DLAs for going back and forth from the UK to the mainland, let me know. And I want to
wind it up today. Inevitably, we're almost at the eve of 9-11. Today is the
ninth. You may be listening to this on the 10th or the 11th itself. So there's
all kinds of media attention surrounding the anniversary of
this tragic event. And Dave pointed out something on American radio works.
which is a special they did called Witnesses to Terror.
And that's something you should check out. It's available on real audio only as far as I could tell.
What I like about it, and I'll play a little bit for you here. I think I have a bit cued up with some of the real audio footage as it were,
is they do have a lot of the calls between the control centers and, you know, the questions.
Hey, do we need to scramble planes? Well, who's going to make that call?
It's really a fascinating radio documentary. Listen to a little piece of it.
Okay, so immediately we go into buffering mode. This is one problem I've noticed.
It's very hard to get a free feed from them.
Presumably because it's really good and a lot of people are hammering their server,
but they may have a little light load. Oops. Well, that actually just crashed my real player.
Okay, well, you go listen to it for your-
yourself, AmericanRadioWorks.publicRadio.org.
Well worth it.
Excellent document.
Not that it's going to change your mind about anything.
It doesn't go in any conspiracy theories,
but it does give a whole new angle
to the events that unfolded that day
that you probably haven't seen or certainly
haven't heard before.
With that, 23 or 24 minutes almost, time to wrap it up.
So if you have any comments on the source code for today,
just send me an email.
It's adamantcurry.com.
Or leave a comment on the web blog, live.curry.com.
You can always catch the latest source code right here
on dailysourcecode.com.
Subscribable through RSS at dailysourcecode.com.rss.xml.
Slash RSS.xml.
I butchered that.
DailySourceCode.com.rss.xml.
Oh, that's better.
All right, I'll see you tomorrow
for the Thank God It's Friday edition of the Source Code
Bye-bye!
It's time.