Yeah, once again, it's the source code.
Today is the 16th of August, 2004.
Hi everybody, I'm Adam Curry.
Welcome from Curry Castle in lovely Belgium.
And of course, just as I'm about to start,
this looks like everyone's coming home.
Okay, my daughter.
She had some kind of insect sting on her arm
and she went to the doctor's cell and showed me
how it is in just a second.
So I'm back on the radio for the final two weeks
my tenure, my year-long tenure.
Started this morning, got up at 3.30.
Yeah, that was quite a shock after about 10 days off.
Although, you know, even on vacation,
I couldn't really sleep in at all.
Once you get into the rhythm, it's it.
You're just in the rhythm.
I was getting up at 6.30 every morning.
And actually as of September 1st
when there's no more radio show,
I still think I'd like to try and get to bed on time
and get up early.
Yeah, it's just, there's advantages to it.
Let's see what's going on in the world today.
Big news.
Paris Hilton's sister, Nikki, also heres to the Hilton millions, hundred millions,
billions.
God knows what.
Got married in Las Vegas yesterday to a 33-year-old money manager from New York.
uh
coincidence
And I want oh yeah
You may or may not have heard the the fuck the FCC song. I was it who did that Eric idle from
Monty Python
I
Figured I just play that because there are still a lot of people I've noticed in my
Environment who haven't heard it and so brilliant and especially to think that a Brit had to do this
You know this is the great protest song
If there ever was one of what's going on with the with the FCC and I'm just gonna play it for you
Here's a little number. I wrote the other day while out duck hunting with a judge
Fuck you very much the FCC
Fuck you very much for finding me
Five thousand bucks a fuck so I'm really out of luck. That's more than how you deflice was judging me
So fuck you very much the FCC
See you.
For proving that free speech just isn't free
For clear channels a dear channel
So Howard Stern must go
Attorney General Ashcroft doesn't like strong words and so
He's charging twice as much as all the drugs per rush limo
So fuck you all so very much
So fuck you very much dear Mr. Bush
For heroic early sitting on your tush
For Halliburton and Ron all the companies
Hail!
Let's send them a clear signal and stick Martha straight in jail
She's an over dear rich bitch
And at least she isn't male
So fuck you all so very much
You dickhead mister chewy too
Fuck you and fuck everything you do
Your pacemaker must be a fake you haven't got a heart as far as I'm concerned
You're just a pasty face don't fall and I'll spaconda leaves a she's an intellect you taught so fuck you all so very much
So fuck you very much the EPA
Forgiving all the lascas oil away it really is a bummer when I can't fill my hula
The ozone so no-go-zone now that Arnold's here to say the nuclear intergames are going to take place in LA
So fuck you also very much
So what the planet fails let's save the great white males and fuck you also very much
That's just perfect. Oh, hold on a second. I can now actually hear myself on the headphones without
some huge delay. Oh, that's good. Mm. Nice. I wonder why all of a sudden that work now.
Hmm. Alrighty. I also hear my wireless mic set cracking a little bit here. Oops. Almost
dropped the battery, huh? So, a great protest song there. Just love that. What else has
been going on? I've been, oh, listening to an excellent audiobook. Timeline by Michael
Criton. It's the unabridged version, which means in total it's 14 hours worth of spoken
words. Speaker's actually pretty good. He's doing accents because part of it, at least
the part that I'm at now, is situated in France, so he's doing French accents. So,
no, it's actually quite cool. Good book. And I bought it off of Audible.com. Really convenient.
I'm big audiobook so much. And since I didn't catch much on the iPad,
Potter script the other night. So for Dave's audio blog, I figured I'd just
listen to a book I'd already downloaded, so I'm kind of in the middle of that.
And I actually did have a great chat with Dave Weiner. We talked about our audio
blogs and it seems that we're almost doing a radio show together. But there
are people listening, I'm looking at my server logs and there was at least
well, there was over a hundred downloads of a second show that I did. And we're
talking about how much room there is, so much room for improvement in
distributing our audio and video files, the stuff that we make. You know, this is,
we've got all the bits in place and I think a lot of it pertains. You know, a
lot of the blogging stuff we're doing will fit perfectly with audio and video. A
lot of it won't really wasn't intended that way. And it's just interfaces. You
know, all I think all the stuff is there. It's just how do we make it as simple as
possible. And the day that Tricia, my wife,
You know, has an iPod that she just slips into the cradle and it automatically downloads
her favorite music channels from whomever.
Or it could be a cooking show or a new show or an interview show or it could be all kinds
of different audio files without actually having to do anything else but just click
a box to subscribe to something.
That's when we've achieved success in my book.
Let's see, about seven minutes into this now, there's not a lot going on.
It is a Monday.
I guess everyone's just kind of getting back to work now after vacation.
So an opportune day to play a song of the day.
Actually I felt like playing some country in Western.
Don't get a lot of that over here.
In fact, most people over here hate country music and a lot of people in America hate country
music too.
But this is a classic that everyone loves and it is by Mr. Country himself, Johnny Cash.
I like to stay out and help us on some songs play the guitar for the greatest guitar players as well as songwriters
Thanks, my business. Make me shade a little hip on the guitar. All right
Well my daddy left home when I was three and he didn't leave much tomorrow and me just this old guitar an empty bottle of food
I don't blame him because he running here, but the meanest thing that he ever did was before he left
He wouldn't named me Sue
Well, he must have thought that it was quite a joke and it got a lot of laughs from a lot of folks seems
I had to fight my whole life
Some cow would giggle and I'd get rid and some guy'd laugh tonight bust his head. I'll take it life ain't easy for a boy named Sue
Well, I grew up quick and I grew up seeing my fist got hard my wits got keen
Roll from town to town to hide my shame
But I make me about the moon and stars
I search the haunted Thompson bars
And kill that man and give me that awful name
Well it was Captain Burger in mid-July
And I'd just hit town and my throat was dry
I thought I'd stop and held myself a groove
Had an old balloon on a street of mud
There at the table, he'll instead
Set the thirty mange you talk, name me Sue
Well I knew that snake was my own sweet dad
From a worn out picture that my mother had
And I knew that scar on his cheek and his evil eye
He was big and bent and pretty and old
And I looked at him and my blood ran cold
I said, my name is Sue
How do you do?
Now you sit down
Yeah, but I told him
Well I hit him hard right between the eyes and the eyes.
He went down but some nice surprise.
Come up with a knife and cut off a piece of my ear.
Well I busted a chair right across his teeth
and we crashed through the wall into the street
kicking in a gouging and the mud and the blood and the beard.
I told you I bought the Tucker men,
but I really can't remember when.
It kicked like a mule and it bit like a crocodile.
I heard him laughing and I heard him cussing.
He went for his gun to pull mine first.
He said they're looking at me.
I saw him smile.
He said, son, this world is rough.
And if a man's gonna make it, he's gotta be tough.
And I know I wouldn't be there to help you along.
So I give you that name and I said goodbye.
And you'd have to get tough or die.
And it's that name that helped to make you strong.
Yeah. He said, now you just bought one hell of a fight.
And I know you hate me and you got the right to kill me now.
I wouldn't blame you if you do
But you ought to thank me before I die for the gravel and your guts and the spitting eye
But I'm the son of a bitch that named you soon
What could I do I got old chills tough and I flew down my gun
Called him upon he called me a son and I come away with a different point of view
And I think about him not then every time I try every time I win
And if I ever have a son, I think I'm gonna name him bill or George anything but
I'm legendary Johnny Cash boy named suit
On the daily source code
Just want to wind it up with a couple of things whoops
One is the Olympics now we've all noticed that no one has blocked
logging from the Olympic Games.
And I think I know why because the Olympic Games has nothing to do with what you think
the Olympic Games are.
The prices are too expensive for the individual events, at least for common people, just to
spend a few bucks and go to your game.
It's all invited officials and members of the International Olympic Committee and the
National Sport Federation and the National Olympic Committees.
And it's all cronies and it's one big advertising you have to make for television events is
what it is.
And you can even see how the directors are cutting the shots so you don't see, hey baby,
how are you?
My God.
Yeah, but your arm is in a, what is this?
This is an entire...
I'm actually...
I'm gonna grab my arm because I had an allergic reaction to some kind of...
I'm staking that that animal had that...
That bug had some kind of infection?
Shit.
It's completely red associated with this on. I'm actually not allowed to use this
I'm recording this by the way for my show. Okay. Yeah, but I'm not allowed to use it for the week really
but I'm still gonna go when can you ride you can't ride. I'm still gonna go
Wednesday. But you're not allowed to. Yeah, but you're not allowed to. Yeah, but you don't want your arm to get worse.
Witness witness the logic of a 14 year old. Okay, but they don't know what kind of animal it was that
stung in. The stinger. Well, it looks very official. Looks like you're officially wounded. Okay, I'm gonna wrap this up.
One last thing. Just a quick plug here for BloggerCon 3. The date has been chosen. Saturday, November 6, 2004. And it will be held in...
I'm from Palo Alto, California at Stanford Law School.
I definitely plan on attending.
And that's it for the source code for today.
I'll be here tomorrow with more thanks for listening.
If you have any...
Oops.
Yeah, my assistant calling, hold on a second.
Chris Lee, wait till I tell you through.
Yup, bye.
If you have any comments, Adam at Curry.com,
or of course my web log is live.curry.com.
Talk to you tomorrow.