Actor Income
Entertainment
International gek My astronomer
Independence
Entertainment
Everybody down
потреб
Track
It's Adam Quironom
Chey
It is Tuesday December 28
Subscribe
Hey everybody how you doing welcome It's your day Lisa for SKoSp
This is where I used the developer's party together and we're closing on the end of the year
and there's so much inside. So much cool stuff going on. I've got some excellent stuff that I found for you
of course I didn't find that people sent it to me, but some interesting iPod news today.
I've also got some positive tunes going back to the 60s and I'm sitting here and
curry cottage enjoying my own venti. It's the cappuccino venti. It's straight from the
senseo machine. I love it. They have those in the States. They must have the senseo machine
a wonderful Dutch invention I believe. I think it was developed by Phillips. Of course
are mainly known for their light bulbs and not necessarily for their coffee machines, but
wow you slip a pod in one of those coffee pods or pads. Some people call them pods and
some people call them pads, but it's perfect. It's exactly what I need for a source code.
As Mr. Non-Smoker. Okay, the end law is left yesterday. I was really sad. I mean these
these two folks are almost 80 and the airport is really close by so I was no I mean and they
know how to travel with airplanes and no no problem at all for them to just we had a car
to come up take them to the airport. They had a like a five hour delay. The airplane that they were
supposed to go on had technical problems and they just said and the ground staff just left. They just
left the gate and said sorry you know can't help you right now and then the the big board
showed later that the flight was canceled. It's totally horrible so they were supposed to be on a
five fifteen flight. They wound up going on a nine thirty flight and of course it really
made much sense for them to come all the way back. Only to turn around and go back to the airport
again. So that was that was sad and fucked up. So they finally got home around midnight. And today
in fact right now it is ten minutes too noon. Christina and I are about to rush off to Heathrow
to pick up her one of her girlfriends, one of her best friends in the whole world I share,
who is British, who she met at the British School of Amsterdam where they went to school together
for a number of years. I show also has or had or they're still trying to find out a house in
Thailand right in Puket and so maybe we'll get some more information from her or from her parents.
Anyway so we're going to pick up the airport she's flying isn't ummy and on a company minor which
means you got to be literally at the gate to pick her up. So we should be able to fit in 40 minutes
of source code today and the great news came in yesterday after I had already cut the show and was
in fact on my way to Starbucks to upload it we were parking in the garage and I had the girls with
the Christina and Patricia because they wanted to do some shopping of course all the sales are on right.
After boxing day sales that's what you really want and Bob who was um mom's husband called
and he said we just spoke to the doctor they got the results back because what they do is they you know
they take this lung out they don't just discard it in the corner you know like oh just throw it
on the tarp over there no they go in the exam and that and yesterday they gave her an official
cancer-free declaration and that calls for a celebration.
A little bit of foundations for you everybody to make you happy
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
I love you I love who I love, and I I love you fighters
I love you, you love you, everybody I love you
I love you, I love you I love you I love you, I love you I love you I love you
Baby, try to find it, baby, it's time
I'll make you have it, I'll be home
I'll play beside the phone waiting for you
Why do you kill me up there?
For the company, there's the left me down
Unless you're on it and where's the phone?
Never come baby, when you see you will
But I love your skin, I need you
I need you, what a nanny one dog
You know that I have from the sky
So kill me up there, but if I don't bring my heart
If you were my type, and I could be the one you were done
And you just let me know
But I'll do you want to, want my track to do you
Why do I need you, what a nanny one dog
Baby, baby, try to find it, baby
I need you, what a nanny one dog
I'll make you have it, I'll be home
I'll be beside the phone waiting for you
Why do you kill me up there?
For the company, there's the left me down
Unless you're on it and where's the phone?
Unless you're on it and where's the left me down
But I love your skin, I need you, what a nanny one dog
You know that I have from the sky
So kill me up there, but if I don't bring my heart
Take it to the bridge, everybody
I need you, what a nanny one dog
That's probably the shittiest, shittiest encoding I have with that song
And I have it a couple million times
Build me a buttercup foundations
That was from I think 1967, 1968 something like that
This is one of those songs that I'm sure you have if you have a lover of friend
Someone that you share memories of music with together the soundtrack of your lives intersect somewhere
Then you probably have a song that when it comes on the radio
You call that person up and you hold the phone up to the radio
This is one of the songs that Patricia and I always do that with
If that plays on the radio, she'll call me up immediately and I have a whole voicemail full of
Of times where she called me when I was on airplanes or in tunnels or in meetings and I had the phones switched off
But this is one of those happy songs just makes you even though it was the cruddies
I mean, I'll have to remove this from my from my iTunes library and get a new one because it's just just no good
I've been working with Firefox for the past couple of days. I've been
Ever since I got OS 10 and I was pretty much one of the first people to switch to OS 10
And I've been going along with the upgrades every single step of the way. I used
Who can be calling me right now, please?
Okay, whatever. I'll talk to that person later
Isn't that cool with GSM phones? I don't know if you do that but when someone calls and I just look at the number and if it's so
Basically this was a number. It wasn't something was in my dress book because I didn't recognize it so it's someone I don't know
And then
You know, you can just hit you can do two things you can reject the call which sends it directly the voicemail
Which I don't like doing because that pretty much
Gives the call or clue that you rejected them if you know if it doesn't go straight to voicemail because you're phone is off
Bringing one or two times and going to voicemail is a dead giveaway
Which could also be a signal because I do use that with some people and vice versa like okay
He or she is busy they'll call me back. They recognize it was me. They sent it away
What I always do is I hit the silent button. I have it on my Sony Ericsson 700. I
Hit the silent button and so it keeps ringing and goes to voicemail therefore giving the caller who I don't know in this case
No clue that I that I saw the call come in and rejected it. Well, do we use our phones differently than it then we use to or what
Remember the phone was ringing and was a phone's ringing?
You go see now
This person is
Wow that I'm getting like phone calls on every single fucking device here. What is this?
Uh, okay. Well, I don't know don't have to figure it out later
Right back to Firefox. So um when uh always 10 first came out. I was using internet explorer
Which was bundled pretty quickly. I think and
It wasn't long until Safari came out and I immediately started using Safari mainly because it integrated so well with with the macro
And I've been hearing a lot about Firefox. I've been reading about it and I finally decided to bite the bullet and to install it
Got to tell you I'm pretty happy. I'm pretty happy with Firefox a couple of
Things that if I just haven't figured out or aren't in there yet
The most
Obvious is I you know it used to be on Safari if you want to switch between tabs you'd hold down the apple key
And the shift key and then arrow left to right would shift between tabs. That doesn't work anymore
If I want to go all the way page up it used to be apple key and then the up key
That doesn't work either
You have to use like the control key and you can page up
Or down but not all the way to the top or all the way to the bottom haven't figured that one out yet
I don't use any of the RSS stuff
I understand what they're trying to do like it auto discovers an RSS page and you
Click on it and I just I don't know where to find this shit. I just want to regular aggregator that doesn't really do it for me yet
That's just interface stuff I guess
Everything else I like
Except for the fact that when I open something in my OPML application
That calls for a web browser it calls for
Explorer and I don't know how to set that to call Safari the cool thing that I did find out though is if you actually want to set a different browser as you default for all other applications
You do that in the Safari preferences
How great is that you so you put you set that up in your current browser is where you set up the preferences to use a different browser
At really slays me in fact. It's probably the same let me see if it's the same with
Not the same with firebox luckily
So anyway um liking it a lot and I got an email that apparently the version that I'm using is not the real
G4 or G5 optimized version of Firefox I put a link to it in the show notes for today's podcast
The real Mac Firefox client is still lurking out there and hadn't been released for for some
Some reason which is unclear to me
But I guess that if this is you know this is kind of like the the pre release version
I'm liking it very much. It is definitely faster. It's faster when I'm using it on the modem link
Because that's what I still have at home January 4th is when the 4 megabit pipe is supposed to be laid down to the front door and in the front door
I learned a lot about working on slow bandwidth let me tell you and Firefox definitely does quite a good job
There's also all kinds of hacks you can apply you can set it up so that so you can determine how many connections it will open
When it starts rendering after how many seconds of receiving data
And that's the nice stuff about open source you know is that that basically if you don't like the way it performs
You can go in and change it yourself and we'll be talking about that a little bit later in the show because there's some exciting open source news on the way
In fact open source sex coming up in just a second but first George Carlin who we talked about and in fact
I played a whole bit from his audio book yesterday
The auto book titled what is that?
Well, so I'm please bring the pork chops when let me just open up iTunes and get that for you
So here I was playing this awesome bit about George Carlin about two hours or maybe three hours after I post the whole show
I get an email saying hey, do you know the George Carlin check it in the rehab?
No, didn't know that brain droppings. That's the title
Is that it? Yeah brain droppings the title of his new book
His audio book which I suggest you got and buy because drunk stone or not the guy makes some excellent points
And I really like what he says, but apparently good old
Good old George Carlin went in to rehab for addiction to
wine and vicaridin a
lovely combination for the Christmas
You are great
Okay, open source sex new podcast if you impaying attention to the iPod or directory which is updating like a motherfucker of these days
I mean now ever since I built the iPod directory scanner
We've just got podcast after podcast being added categories and of course now the people who are maintaining the category nodes are
Waking it up saying hey wait a minute. There's a lot of life in this thing and I'm gonna start scanning and checking for
Activity on the nodes themselves because at the for instance the
The radio node was given back to me by Todd Matham because he at the or at least temporarily
I'm saving it for him if he wants to take it back
But there's some other nodes that may just not be you know people may not be responsive to the request for links coming in
So I am gonna pay a bit of attention to that
Because now you see that it's really working and if you add something somewhere way down the chain
Say in the indie feeds of the music directory which is being maintained in a whole different country different content from where I am
That will percolate with the iPod or directory scan up to the home page and to the what's new node of the directory
So it does make a lot of sense to to maintain your nodes and keep that going because
What have been adding like 10 15 new podcasts the day with the scanner? It's really awesome and I can see that all the other
Directors are benefiting tremendously from this since all that data is available
Just select the XML icon on the iPod or directory pages and then I'll give you the opml file
Which is the entire tree? It's all the directories all the data that you can flow right into your into your ipodder
Application or into your outline or god knows what you want to do with it. Be my guest
Violet blue you've probably seen her website or maybe heard of her website called tiny nibbles
dot com finally time for podcast
This is filet blue and you're listening to open source sex
To find out more about me visit my website tiny nibbles dot com or simply google my name
To that I'll be reading the first couple of chapters from the BDSM novel the castle by anti-Morley
And there are a few things you should know about the castle and the other two books of morelies that I'll be reading
They're pretty intense and they deal with some sexual themes that some people might think are a bit too much
No, there's no incess
Yeah, yeah boing boing boing
Are sex with underage people or anything? You okay like that. No, no, there are some intense fantasies acted out here
And while it's perfectly clear at every point that these are consensual fantasies
There is a lot playing into non-consent and yes, there are some pretty convincingly staged
For sex scenarios and some night play if this is not for you skip this podcast and resume listening with the next installment
Okay, so I'm gonna pause this here for a second because clear this whole podcast. It's basically a reading of a
Part of a novel about 30 minutes into the whole podcast
What I'm missing here because I like what what violet blue is doing
I
The stories in some cases are total turn on. Oh, um, let's listen to a little bit of the story first and then I'll tell you what I think we need to do with this podcast
Before I slept tonight, I would have been taken in every conceivable way. Okay. You understand what I'm saying right? It's not completely safe or work
What we need is a better quality
Recording with violet and I'm willing to help her anyway necessary if we could get a real close mic sound and it doesn't sound so
You know far off
Distant if we can get a closer mic. It'll be that much more exciting to hear
I'm I'm subscribing to the
Open source sex podcast. I've a feeling that that could be one of the greats because
It really is truly about open source sex and it's you know not
It's not anything like yeast radio
Hello, this has mad winestein once again with another day of yeast radio coming to you live on the
Internet as George Bush would call it. Well, we're not going to talk about her just yet
First we're going to explain why I'm using the
The hand held microphone please do today as opposed to the
As opposed to the lovely of microphone I've been using for the past week or so
The reason is
Lesbians and gentlemen
That's I make it
Another not safe for work podcast clearly nothing to strap on
Strap on yeah, okay. Well listen listen to yeast radio because even though Madge winestein is
The most abusive podcast or imaginable when it comes to language
He she makes some incredibly good political points and
Social political points and it's something that you need to listen to by yourself and make your own decision
If you ever want us to do it again. I personally enjoyed very much and it's on my
It's on my list of podcast that I subscribe to it's in the iPodder usually these are pretty short 10 15 minutes
So, you know, I like the shorter podcast something you definitely need to check check out
yeast radio you can get to all the podcasts and everything you hear on today's show
Obviously through the production show notes and of course through the iPod or directory
I was talking about
the delay
That makes me sound like I'm drunk sometimes here actually I'm gonna I'm gonna reset it here for some okay, so now it's been reset
Paul sent me an email about that
I'm gonna just get Paul's email
What did he say said
Thing by the problem you have with a slight delay in your headphones while recording your podcast can't be sure
But this sounds like a problem faced by all musicians when recording a life performance directly to a computer called latency
Exactly what it is it is exactly what it is generated by the vast amount of processing the computer has to do to the
Audio data before it reaches your headphones got it and it there is quite a bit, you know, it's going through
Excuse me first of all, it's going into the breakout box which really gives it
the least latency
Imagineable and if I plug my headphone directly into the breakout box it would be great because then I'm getting a direct hard-wired connection
the problem is I won't hear the end mix
Which includes the processing so I run the microphone through the
Monomizer through the dynamics compressor through the ten band EQ and through a little bit of reverb
I would miss all that so when you're doing radio or when you're doing a podcast and you do it the way I do it
Which is as performance art in real time we're cutting it straight to a straight to the disk and and I'm not
You know going back and putting songs in and putting bits in and editing out stuff you don't like
You really need everything at your fingertips and you need to be able to hear exactly what the listener is hearing
Which is why in fact
It became a real big problem when digital broadcast came around a via satellite back in the old days back in the old days kids
When we have basically the antenna on the roof
You know we'd be playing records with needles on vinyl you just listen you know we'd have a little like a just a regular old
tuner
Amplifier set up that you might find in any any living room and we plug the headphones into that that because then you'd have or that would be the total air signal
You'd listen to of course you want to be able to pre-fade or listen listen to you know cue stuff up outside of the broadcast
But you wanted to hear exactly what people at home were hearing which is what everyone tries to do
I mean
Have you ever been to a recording studio or maybe you've seen this they have the few manga speakers
But then usually on the console there these little what we call reference speakers little square boxes not cheap by the way, but
Some actually have extremely cheap ones and the reason why is they'll do the mix the way they want to hear it in the studio
That's cranking and pounding and whatever they're looking for but then they're gonna listen to it
Does it listen and to see what it's gonna sound like at home at on someone's portable radio in the car
Which of course is you know that reference is changing every single day
But that's what people do in the in the professional audio industry and that's what I want as well
So I want to hear everything and I want to hear the mix
So when I when I'm mixing and music this is the problem another problem because that mix is only coming through the total signal
I'm not going back into the breakout box where I would then supposedly plug my headphone into
So it just doesn't work if you want to do it in in the fashion that I'm doing it in without
Without eventually getting some delay and to delay it builds up over time
It's like there's some some buffer or some cash or something that's not being flushed out
Often enough because if I basically if I un-high jack
The breakout box that have my mic plugged into that everything runs through and I high jack
Again, which is what I just did a couple minutes ago
Then it's good for at least another five or ten minutes before it starts to slow down and actually
It usually happens when I start pumping other audio around when the when the slow down starts to build up
So there's
There's not really a solution other than to create a complete external mix and use external boxes and I don't think that's necessary
I think it's just a matter of working with
Working with developers
Who make this stuff and I and I think that the audio hijack pro guys
I got to talk to them because they're they are coming very very close to the stuff that I think works for for creating
Podcasts and if we could integrate just a couple of a couple of things and change a couple of bits with the interface
I think we'd actually
Be somewhere very very close to fucking awesome
Hey, you know that Don and Drew and and Pete of course
Raster web all live in Wisconsin
Renek oops, did you hear that that was weird? Let me recapture hold on
Okay, I ran across a podcast that had some wacky news from Wisconsin
Don't listen to the best of distorted you daily
Let's get into the news of the weird right now first things first this happened picture this if you will a man in Wisconsin
Was doing his laundry at a laundry mat when he thought I'll just do my clothes that I'm wearing too
So he gets bug naked buck ass naked
There are other people no there are other people in the laundry mat, right?
So he puts all of his clothes in the washer. He's naked. Uh, well women
Started laughing at him apparently he had a small penis
They were the women started laughing at him. He gets mad and he storms off
The police described the man as being six foot three inches
Six foot three inches, no, I'm not saying that the three inches was how big his penis was although it could have been
He did have a small penis with he did have a muscular build though
May have been wearing a baseball cap, so if anyone in the Wisconsin area sees a naked man running around with a baseball cap in a small cock
Call the laundry mat until then where you saw the man because his laundry is just sitting there waiting for him to pick it up
I just love that
Okay, so in Wisconsin news for everybody a couple of things I wanted to run through
I got an email from Mike Corley all of a sudden. I see all these
Websites pointing to this great
Fantastic new invention called parachutes for private airplanes and I want to talk about that for a second because mainly the
There's a private aircraft manufacturer that makes this serious S a C I R I S and
And I and there's links in the show notes to videos of this particular aircraft basically
Ballistic research is a company that came up with a 16 or 17,000 dollar parachute system with rockets
So if the concept is is if you run into trouble with your airplane
You pull this lever. I need like 30 pounds of of power to you know pull this lever and then
Rockets shoot out the top of your airplane. We're talking like you know like a S S no 172 size airplane
So a four four-seater airplane right and it blows out the top or just you know rips through the canopy whatever
Basically rendering your airplane pretty fucked up, but then it deploys a parachute that lets you float down to earth
Couple things about this first of all this is not new this has been around for quite a while the
Serious aircraft has been sold with this as an option at least for a year. I think so you know why people are catching on to it now
But also what it is it's a bad idea because it gives you a false sense of security
I don't know if you've ever done a parachute jump. I haven't but I can tell you one thing
It's not like you you don't land like a frickin feather, okay? And there's a reason why all the
Demonstration videos are done over the Bahávei desert and not over like a populated area or water or whatever
Because you're gonna come down pretty damn hard your plane you will probably live
Because the seats that you're in can take 30 gs worth of impact so that's gravitational force impact
So you probably will hurt your back, but won't break it, but your aircraft's gonna be destroyed and that's only if you don't land
somewhere where there's other people buildings power lines highways freeways whatever
it also I think it makes for bad pilots because
There would be very few situations other than a fucking wing coming off in a goddamn spiral
Which may not be able to you know be a situation where you can deploy your parachute anyway
I would rather try and land the aircraft that makes a hell of a lot more sense to me
And there was all kinds of limitations, but it's really it's just I think it creates bad pilots like
Oh, you know if I get I forget into a situation that I can't handle add snow problems
I've always got my backup parachute that is not the way to go
Anyway, a lot of people talking about the parachutes and I think it makes
It's just making people feel safer and if $16,000 will make you feel safer
Then that could be worth it to you or to someone who's flying you, but I'm not a big believer in this in the airplane parachutes
And no they're not gonna be installed on 747s, you know
Maybe we should do a little bit more to control alcohol in regular traffic and we'll say more lies than these freaking parachutes
And I'd love for any aviators to weigh in with the audio comments and feedback
Adam and curry dot com time for some music mashups big thing of the day got an email from Niels
I think Niels is from Holland this need look I got a lot of mashup people from
From Holland maybe Niels isn't from Holland. Not sure anyway. He did a live mashup
Which he says it's it's live with errors and all they want to play for you today because a couple songs all strung together
You're gonna dig it. It's the mpm rock mashup here on your daily source code
I'm so happy because today I found my friends
I'm so ugly that's okay
I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I
I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm so happy that I'm out
Back to where you want to go
They ran down
They were standing
They were not standing
They were all standing
Deep inside, deep down the track, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside
deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside
deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside , deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep outside, deep inside, deep inside, deep裡, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside, deep inside
Cowbell.
Yes boy, one.
I got him hib.
He only presents him.
The only person you hit is Martin Capber
He really really really domu
It's a big space.
Cowbell.
Doesn't work in the wood.
I gotta have more cowbell.
Cowbell.
Space, space, space.
Excellent.
That's the big mystery of the sample rate on the daily source code.
That's the sample rate of the mp3.
That's the big mystery of the mp3.