Good afternoon from Curry Castle. It's the Big 4 O birthday show. I'm Adam Curry.
Today is Friday, September 3rd, 2004, and it was 40 years ago today that the nurse said
in the Audentine Hospital, ma'am, if you don't push, we're never going to get this kid out.
And that was me, born on this day in 1964. You listen to the source code. So good morning,
good afternoon, good evening, wherever you happen to be listening to the show. But of course,
it's probably on a commute from point A to point B. This is the only spot on your portable MP3
player device that has a playlist where users and developers party together. So I've just been
saying at home for my birthday today, nothing too special.
Birthdays actually pretty big deal in the Netherlands. Typically the birthday boy or girl,
hold on, we just took this off for a second. The birthday boy or girl will get,
they'll have a special chair for them all decorated in the morning and presents are given
in the morning and breakfast. We're not that Dutch per se, but since I'm home anyway, kind of chilling out.
Yeah, just had a nice easy wake up call for my 40th, which is good, a nice way to ease into the
the park where life apparently starts where everything begins at 40. Excuse me.
My buddy from the radio show, one of my two colleagues, Alexander stopped by
to another typical Dutch tradition and he actually drove for quite a distance to come here and he
just stopped by just to have a cup of coffee and chat and he gave me the most awesome, awesome
birthday gift. When we moved to the Netherlands,
about over four years ago, I already had Curry.com, which I was using quite happily.
And well, Curry.nl had been taken a long time ago by Hines, probably.
And I guess they have as much right to it as I do.
But Adam Curry.nl had been hijacked at the time.
I was like, yeah, whatever, I've got Curry.com.
I was never really planning on doing a Dutch weblog, which by now I've been doing it.
Keeping in touch with a blog.
it just became live.curry.com slash Dutch and you know what people find it anyway, it's no big deal.
But what Alex and I did is he went through the time and the trouble and this is what makes
us such a great gift to reclaim my domain name for me and it already links to my to my Dutch
weblog. So that's and he also promises going to renew every single year. So it's the gift that keeps
on giving really. Adamcurry.nl that's my Dutch weblog and still posting on it though a little
less frequent as I used to and I was really doing the radio show in Holland and you know just
keeping up with everybody. Now I'm focusing a lot more of my time and attention on the
English weblog on curry.com. And I think I mentioned it yesterday just so you know that you can get to
the archive of all of the source code shows by going to dailysourcecode.com that's dailysourcecode.com
all three words written together. And the RSS feed if you want to subscribe to it we are pumping out
So which means we have enclosures and those enclosures can be parsed by different aggregators,
which will pull out the MP3 files for you.
And if you feel like it, you can use the iPodder.
Now available for Windows, for Macintosh, for Linux, also for Pocket PC.
And I just got some really good news that there is a version that works with Windows Media
Player. It hasn't been released yet.
This is done by Erwin.
And he based his code on the iPodder for Windows that works with iTunes.
Now what's great about having a release for Windows, the worst with Windows Media Player
9 is that Windows Media Player 9 already has all kinds of different connections with
different media devices.
So when we talk about the iPod platform, of course, we're only talking about all devices
that are portable to play MP3 files.
So this is a big breakthrough.
And what I had hoped is, remember I told you that someone had...
claimed iPodder on SourceForge.
Now it's going to set up a central resource.
Now if I don't see it appeared this afternoon
or by tomorrow morning, then I am going to start up
a central spot, which will probably be SourceForge.
Just so we can aggregate all of these different scripts
and have it in one spot and then have us
get it probably find out if we get a good URL to point to it.
But we really have to start pulling this together.
Because it wouldn't be amazing if you could
create a little toolkit.
Here's a thought for you.
If we create a little toolkit, let's say
I want to publish a program and I already have the software
to do it.
But what I want is I want to make sure
that my built-in audience who may not have already
been exposed to iPodder, that they can basically just
click on a standardized link, subscribe with iPodder,
whatever.
This link then will, if necessary, download a version
appropriate for your system.
including the feed that you just subscribed that you just looked at.
So they'll have one or however feeds that particular program producer wants to put in there.
And if you already have an iPodder, then of course it would hopefully only
subscribe you to to that feed.
I know it sounds trivial, but these are the things we still haven't gotten working on weblog.
So I think we have quite a way to go on that one.
Lawrence Lee sent me a note.
And he too was interested in the iPod platform and working with iPodder.
And he said, well, you know, there's a couple of different angles we should we could approach this from.
At the rate we're going, we're going to wind up with many, many different scripts for many different devices.
Wouldn't it be simpler to create one centralized aggregating resource?
And that's where that's where I say, I don't know.
I don't think so. You know, I think that this stuff has to be so decentralized, not just because of the load because there is death.
definitely load when you're doing any type of central aggregation.
But also for control, there should be no control, there should be no one in the middle
to grab control or for even to be the possibility of having some kind of control.
I just don't think that's a good idea.
But certainly something that we need to look into before we blow it off entirely or at least
that I think we should look into different ways of approaching this problem.
But as I said, I'm really happy with Erwin's Wendell Media and Windows Media Player Number
9.
Hi Anya.
What is this?
Huh?
From the close to fans.
Oh, I'd play that.
Yeah.
Yeah, nigga.
Okay.
It was off the safe.
Yeah.
Okay, don't kill.
I was on your…
She helps out of here.
And so when I dropped off a nice gift for me, a nice bottle of something.
Okay.
Very nice.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Great.
So this…
the Windows Media Player 9. I think that's a big win right there because it's basically,
you download the script, it brings the stuff in, you have a feeds file, you drop anything
into that feeds file you want, and Windows Media Player 9 can already sync up with a whole bunch
of different portable devices, and probably they have the, it's set up with vendors of MP3 players
so that they can, I guess, get something into an update of Windows Media Player or something
that's downloadable so it syncs up. I mean, that would only make sense that they're working hard
on that, so we can piggyback on all of that work. I also got a request to discuss the legal issues,
specifically of playing music during one of these programs, and I don't think I want to go there,
I don't think I want to get into that discussion on this program, or I don't really want to get
into it at all, because it's, it's, it's,
such a big discussion that will really bog down the work we're doing.
In the case of source code, first of all, the rules are a little bit different in Belgium
and in the Netherlands and in the EU in general.
So, you know, there's, I'm not too worried about the RIAA clamping down on me because quite frankly,
I'm outside of the jurisdiction and reach and there's no partnership agreements whatsoever
on that front.
Or at least as far as I know, there's no agreements on that front.
But also, you know, most of the stuff I'm playing, I've played so many times throughout my radio career.
I've made definite money for people along the way and I don't think that anyone who owns
the copyrights on these pieces of music, which I know most of them personally or I've met
at least once, they'll make a big deal out of it.
And, you know, copyright laws can't be intended so that when we're working on development
and research, that's exactly what we're doing here that we can't...
you stuff that's out there to do this type of research. Now if I was trying to make money on this in some other way,
that might be open for discussion and I think that it's something that should be discussed, not right now.
You know, now we're in R&D mode, we're digging down and trying to get
trying to get everything working. And I think we're having a lot of success. The
the Dutch Telegraph,
as I said yesterday pointed to the inquire article and to the iPod or scripts both the Mac and the Windows version.
And traffic has been amazing. I think a lot of feedback here from people in the Netherlands.
Let me just see
I guess, Lawrence Lee, who had the, I think I messed it up there.
Lawrence Lee had the legal question, and it was Andrew Davy, who had the question of
centralizing the aggregation.
Or perhaps, here he says something interesting here.
He believes the development of community should work together to create an application that
handles the nitty gritty of RSS parsing and provides a simple extensibility model for other
people to plug into.
Okay, so he's saying, why don't we build an aggregator?
And that may make sense, but again, you're going to get into, I think you're going to
get into Holy Wars of what language do we use?
And I think it's relatively simple enough that, hey, if I could create one of these things
to work, then almost anybody can.
And all we need is a couple of good versions that connect with all the right bits, and
I think will be good to go.
So anyway, I sent everyone a note back.
He was going to talk to Peter who created the original iPodder for Windows, who asked
because he used some of his code,
well actually what he did is he removed the Apple script,
or the iTunes code and put in the Windows Media Player 9 code.
So already we're working modular across the board.
Very, very fun to watch.
Something that I watched on my computer yesterday
was the most recent Apple keynote
from the Apple Expo in Paris.
Well, although he can't help it,
it was very disappointing that Phil Schiller did the keynote
because I'm a big Steve Jobs keynote fan.
I love watching the way he presents,
and how he handles the stage.
And it's really a joy to watch him do that.
Phil Schiller actually did a pretty good job.
And it was fun to see how a format of a show like that,
because you know exactly what's gonna happen,
right?
He's gonna talk up some stuff in the beginning
and run through some of the stuff you saw
at the previous developer conference keynote.
It brings three vendors on stage,
one of the internal guys, they'll sit, you know,
stand behind their Mac show off their...
stuff, then you get some other wind up, some stuff in the middle, and then one more thing,
then we need the box to rise out of the stage. It has the new iMac on it, which by the
way does look very sweet. So that format was already there. That was cool, and Phil just
kind of fit right in there. But even though he did a different, amazing job, he still doesn't
have that presence that Steve has. And of course, that's because Steve Jobs was a
operated on, and he was at home recuperating. Phil Schiller said during the keynote that Steve
would be back in September. So I guess he's just about ready to start now. Although the one thing,
and these types of things they say about CEOs who are out of action,
I think hopefully most people care right off. How is Jobs doing? Is he okay? Is he
and your house is health? Unfortunately, the investment community.
meaning Wall Street is paranoid about this type of stuff and they really want to know
how is he doing? Is he coming back? And it's important to them for their investment strategies
and because it will, it's already affecting the content, no matter what.
When when Schiller did is I chat AV demonstration, if it all possible, that's where I would have
said, hey, you know, why don't you I chat Steve at home where he's recuperating? I mean,
if he's going to start in a couple of days or a couple of weeks, then presumably he would
be fit enough to do that. Of course, I didn't choose to do that and that it only makes me
hope that Steve Jobs is recovering very well and either didn't think of it or it was too
late for him or whatever, but that if he really is a fully recovered or almost there, that
would have been great. Just from a show perspective, you know, again, all I want is the best for
anyone certainly when it comes to health. So, let's see.
There was a little more in-depth demonstration of Safari RSS.
And I remember commenting, I think on my web blog about the unveiling of Safari RSS.
I thought jobs, uncharacteristically, didn't do a very good job of explaining what you
can use this for and what Safari RSS will give you, what kind of benefits it will give you.
Phil Schiller did a much, much better job.
And it looks like these guys really put together something excellent.
It's basically, it's a built-in aggregator, but not just an aggregator where you can
subscribe to stuff.
You can easily make up sets of aggregated content.
So you can say, here's all of my feeds that I'm subscribed to.
And they do that with bookmarks, by the way.
I'm going to make a collection, so I want all my computer feeds here.
And I think you can mix and match and slice and dice those collections almost on the fly and create a new one.
So you can just be looking at subsets.
that's of your already pre-aggregated data.
And then when you have that,
you can also search through that aggregated
through those aggregated feeds.
And you keep changing your view.
So not really getting results,
but you're getting different feeds.
And there's even a slider bar
so you can say, okay, how much content do I wanna read
underneath each entry in this aggregator
so it can be one line of text
or the entire text or anything in between.
And it's just, it blew me away.
It looks like a really, really good aggregator.
Now, of course, the questions are,
will it support enclosures?
And here comes the big plea, hey guys,
could you please connect it to iTunes?
Wouldn't that be great?
It would certainly make this,
well, we're trying to achieve a lot more robust
and much easier for people to use.
And it could open up an entire market.
So that's a question that remains to be seen,
but I'm very bullish on Safari.
because they've got to have a database under the hood too.
It's very excited about that.
Of course, that'll be at least another,
probably another seven to eight months before that comes out,
maybe even longer, they're talking about second half of 2005.
So remaining with Apple, oh, here's something I noticed.
It's just kind of cool.
Here's something, you know, if you have an iPod, and I'm sure that most of these earphones
are built in a similar fashion, the iPod actually, I'm going to take one out now because
I'm wearing them, listening to the monitor of the recording.
The two ear plugs are different.
It even has one has an L on a right, indicating L on R, indicating left or right ear to
be inserted into.
But they're not symmetrical.
So they are built in a certain way that you can actually put it in.
It goes underneath, kind of, I'm sure that has a name, I should Google that.
What's that little thing on the inside of you?
The little inner low, I guess.
And then it kind of just hangs behind there and just kind of sticks in there and it's a real
comfortable fit.
I noticed something the other day when I was in a group of different people.
And remember, I'm 40 now, so you may...
not to have the same results with people you know. But I, this is great. I found out that
people who have had a facelift can't wear these earphones because a part of it, and of course
has to be a serious facelift. So what they do is they pull the skin of the face back towards
the ear. You'll see people who had a couple facelift, you'll see their ears are kind of on the
back of their head. But in the process of doing that, it kind of tightens everything in that
that inner load part just becomes straight. It doesn't really have a little piece sticking
out where you can clip an iPod earphone behind. So just thought that was interesting, a
little faxoid. And of course that would open up a market for facelifted earplugs. And one
other thing looking at this entire keynote is that Apple along with...
most other companies that are in the business of MP3 players, all they talk about is music.
That's all they talk about.
The iPod is for music, it's for bouncing, it's for, you know, look at the commercials.
It's, you know, listen to different music, share music between different computers, stream
music, buy music from the IT music store.
I'm like, wow, you know, this is, why are they driving it all towards that?
I haven't heard anything about different uses of audio.
And there are so many different uses.
It seems like we're not only have we forgotten what you can do with audio because we're
so video-minded I presume.
Just like we were rediscovering the written word and web logs and how powerful it can be
and what you can achieve just by writing something, we're going to go, I predict that we're
going to have a kind of reinvention of the wheel with video and audio, of course, will
probably happen a little bit sooner just because it's easier.
You know, we're able to transfer these large audio files and video files, you know, it's,
I think they're still a little bit too big right now for the...
hard to space and processing power well processing power is okay but bandwidth certainly is a problem.
So anyway they're just not talking about it and you know that I find that kind of weird because we're
you know we're going to go through people creating you know the old fashioned radio shows where people
are acting stuff out and and interviews and there's just so much more but not a word everyone's talking
about music as if you know that's the only thing we can do with these devices so go figure.
I had hoped at least somewhere that people would pick up on audio books because you know I've
been talking about audio books Dave Winer has been talking about audio books. A lot of people are
using these I think that there's a definite market here. I fact I saw that a quote by the CEO of
audible.com the other set of the other day saying that you know they're doing fantastic. I'm sure
it's his job to say that but he the quote read pretty sincere. Now I've been
to review an audiobook or two here on Source Code. And I thought I was going to step away from it,
but then I thought, no, it's such a great part of the content of the iPod platform that isn't
being talked about. I think we should do it. And there are lots of people who are listening to
to audiobooks. And I reviewed a couple of them, but here's something cool that happened.
Through Track Back, I received a comment on one of my audiobook reviews from Eric Rice.
I'm going to pull up his page here because what he doesn't have is, hmm, I'll see.
Oh, he has a little spinning beach ball of death. He's giving a second.
So anyway, he's using, I think he's using audio blog.com to post his audio blogs.
And I never used it, but from what I understand with audio blog.com, you best be set it up
and then you dial in with a special phone.
number or use do a select a phone code once you've dialed in. You record your audio blog,
you press star or hang up, and then it automatically posts it onto your web blog. Well, so here's
what happened. Eric is listening to Source Code in the car. He hears something about audio books.
He wants to respond to it. He calls up his audio blog.com account and leaves the following message.
There comes, hold on.
everybody is there from air christ dot com
on a very warm and beautiful when they hear in california
uh... today's audio blog is actually for adam curry i a uh...
like adam i drive a tremendous amount
during the week
and something we probably put similar miles on our cars and i'm looking to a
daily source code mp3
it's a kind of content that i can take with me a little bit different than some
audio blog for audio blog more streaming the more momentary
uh... probably takes more work to go ahead and load it up on your iPods and it
does actually fit it play and
figure out that the amount of the business with me so
uh... he's talking about audio book and he talking about
reviews of audio book and i have to pipe in here because i recently purchased
at another audio book and i'm starting to do to join the audio book bandwagon
primarily because of how much time i spend in the car
uh... like everybody else got an iPod
and i am hopelessly addicted to one book
and i think it's because of the
the reader
the guy who narrates the story
The book is something that probably most technical folks like.
It's a cyberpunk thriller called Snowcrash by Neil Stevenson.
I have the unabridged version and it's 18 hours long.
I'll tell you, there is nothing cooler than listening to Snowcrash, especially if you like the novel.
And driving, especially at night or when it's rainy and nasty.
I've actually video blogged this before.
It's a book that really just draws you in.
Jonathan Davis does a phenomenal job of reading this.
So I actually went on iTunes to search for more audio books that are read by Jonathan Davis.
Now I know Jonathan Davis is a part of our work.
There's just a little snippet from Eric Rice.
So here's what I find phenomenal.
So he wasn't necessarily responding to a book that I was talking about.
But he was responding to audio to my program about audio books.
And he gave me an idea.
Let me tell you, Snowcrash by Neil Stevenson was the inspiration for Metaverse.
which was a domain name that I registered in the 80s.
It was a very early 90s.
And I was right after MTV.com, that's right, Metaverse.com.
And I actually had an agreement with Neil Stevenson
that, you know, he said, you can use the domain name, no problem,
as long as you don't merchandise the name, Metaverse for T-shirts
or books or films, whatever.
We had a little contract and it was perfect.
And he actually thought it was quite an honor that, you know,
he was this place in cyberspace called The Metaverse.
If you've read Snowcrash, then you know that The Metaverse is basically,
it's basically the net.
It's the internet in this book and everyone can jack into it.
But you really jack in 3D.
So Snowcrash has such, you know, I love that book.
I really did.
It gave me a whole different view on where we might be going in the future.
So I thought, hey, you know, if there's an audio book version
and Eric Rice, who apparently really appreciates the speaker,
you know, then this is a book that I want to have.
And yeah, I think I can...
and divvy up 18 or 19 hours worth of listening to Snowcrash. I'm sure, yeah, I mean do it.
So the real interesting thing here is this feedback loop that was created.
Let me talk about what happened first, and I'll get back to the feedback loop.
So check how the flow of money went on this. So Eric says, check out Snowcrash.
I go to audible.com, and I'm like, you know, I hope they have it. Type it in Snowcrash.
You know, Stevenson, yeah, on a bridge version. It's there. And then I see a banner up at the top.
And believe me, I don't think I've ever purchased anything off clicking on a banner.
But it was for John Stewart's new book, which audio book of his book. I guess he has a book,
but this is the audio book version, which he goes through the history of America and democracy.
And see, the Snowcrash book was $34.95. And I thought that was a lot of money for it. But you know,
of course it's 7, 18 hours worth. But still, you know, I think I'm in.
That's a lot of money for one book.
John Stewart's book, on the other hand, was $7.95.
I'm not sure how audible does this, but apparently it's like each time you buy a book, then
you get a book credit, and then it's subtracted from your next purchase.
So I had a book credit from my previous purchase, and what I thought was really nice is that credit
was applied towards the $34.95 and not the $7.95.
So I basically got the John Stewart book and Snow Crash for $7.95, and I feel really good
about myself, and they're both in great quality with great speakers.
And the John Stewart stuff, I haven't finished it all, so I don't want to do a review until
I've heard all of it.
But it is phenomenal.
And it's exactly what I was talking about.
He has different speakers, different voices, he has sound effects, he has, it's a real radio
show almost with people acting out parts, and it's just so well put together.
And he also has a very nice speaking voice for audio.
So if the audiobook business doesn't...
see this and see how simply it goes, you know, than they're crazy. And I think that we can be a part
of that ecosystem one way or the other. See, there was everything else about the John Stewart book.
Oh yeah, I do want to say something about John Stewart book. I want to say that,
unfortunately, still can't seem to get a steady RSS feed of daily shows. But I know John pretty
well because he started out, as many of you may know, at MTV, he had a show called the John Stewart
show. And that was on about six or six or eight months before I left MTV to go and start my company.
And we hung out at the very first MTV V-chows. And he's a really nice guy. And he was just at the
wrong spot at MTV. You know, they were so overprotective because you couldn't piss anybody off,
no record companies. You had to be politically correct. That's what the rock and roll video station was
and still is today. And so Comedy Central of course got a...
over the years because they had the same problem because it's also an MTV network,
so via a common company.
Somehow they were allowed to become the bastard child and of course they've been very successful
with many shows on Comedy Central, think of South Park, think of Daily Show and of course
this new comedian who I just saw on a bit torrent of Jay Leno, was in David Chappelle, America's
funniest man and I'm also going to download the Dave Chappelle shows.
So one thing that I of course I'm just astounded by is that Audible does not have RSS feeds.
Think of the opportunity here, just think of the opportunity if I can create an RSS feed
and say well I'm only interested in these types of books where I'm not interested in this
or I like this particular staff pick so give me his or her recommendations in my feed.
Oh it seems like so incredibly simple to do this stuff.
And you know what? Maybe there's a market right there for someone putting together a feed
of audio books. It doesn't necessarily have to be, you don't have to be selling them.
You could be through an affiliate program. All kinds of opportunities with this stuff.
Okay, so what I did want to say about the feedback loop of audio blog.com, that really connected
to me because what's so great about radio is that you are always involved in a community.
Typically, or at least the way I think radio works best, it's within a city, or within
a certain region so that they're talking about stuff that you are familiar with. And not
just some guy like sitting at Clear Channel pushing buttons, firing off local jingles.
So on Philadelphia, it sounds like he's local and saying, you know, in Iowa. And another
part of that community is that radio stations often use the telephone as the feedback loop.
So you can call in. Yeah, you may not get on the air. In fact, you probably won't get on
the air, but I'll tell you, on morning shows, there are many lists.
who are regulars because they always have something funny to say and some of them eventually
get a hotline numbers they can call in directly.
But most of the time the calls are screened at larger market stations and these people are
professionals they know how to pick someone funny out of the...
to create that feedback with which is a beautiful one if you think about it because here you are
you're listening to the radio you're listening to a talk show you hear someone say something you hear
a phone number you pick up the cell you dial it you talk to a producer if you're lucky you get through
you're on the air boom you know you're on the radio you're in the loop now our system won't work as
immediate as that but of course it doesn't have all the drawbacks of a centralized system as well
mainly that you can't own one and you can't have one but we can use this audio blog system
now I thought about it just briefly last night before I went to sleep and we have to have some
kind of way of trying to tie in you know maybe if this is the source code for for September 3rd
when you dial into a special number you're going to say okay I'm responding to the source code
September 3rd and maybe you you type in oh nine oh three oh four and then it knows that wherever it
sends this
your message to it knows to attach it to that audio blog post or to that particular show in
the ART program and the archive, which could be here we go I'm thinking now I know developers
out there help me out here. In theory I think it should be possible to make use of the comments element
in RSS 2.0 and I think that if I'm mistaken the comments can also have their own RSS 2.0 feed
and then those would include enclosure attachments of the audio blog responses.
Now the first thing I thought in this structure is okay that's great but we're going to get lots and
lots of spam of people calling up and I said well you know what? No we won't because we're going to
charge him. If you want to comment then you know you're going to have to pay a little bit so that
the service is paid for and so
that the feedback loop is completed and also to combat spam.
If people had to spend money on email spam, there would be a hell of a lot less spam.
So that should be fairly easy to set up.
And maybe a way to make money.
If you haven't got enough people who are compelled to drop 50 cents or a dollar or God knows how
much, maybe 20 cents or 9 cents, I don't know.
If you have enough or calling up, that could be interesting.
But anyway, the feedback loop is the main thing.
And I'm going to look into audio blog.com and see what kind of API, the application programming interface.
See what we can do if we can talk to it, if we can tie it into existing programs and
then in an archive using the current weblog technologies.
And they sound a little bit discombobulated, but it is because I'm still trying to figure it all out.
Okay, we are damn 34 minutes into this.
It's my birth.
day today so I get to select the song of the day and I chose for a classic by Jackie
DeShire. What the world needs now is love, sweet love, people are thinking.
What the world needs now is love, sweet love, it's the only thing that there's just too
much love, what the world needs now is love, sweet love, no not just for some but for
oh oh oh Lord we don't need another mountain
there are mountains ready, and you're tired, we need enough to climb
there are us
As two in the time
What the world
We are
With her
Sweet love
It's the only thing
It's just...
Do you know what the world is?
Not...
It's not...
Sweet love...
No, not just for some...
But for everyone...
So
What's up
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm living out
Let it cry
Sweet and heart
It's the only thing
That there's a chance
Do it in love
Oh, I'm, PAYS NOOOO
Sweet and heart
I'm, OH, IT'S LAST
No, not just for some
Oh, but just
Now you know
Here Add另外
Everyone
Please
Is that?
Is that
The
Is it?
I must remember to turn off other applications next time.
I play a song on the day because someone came online and my eye chat definitely let me
know about that in the middle of Jackie D'Shanan's what the world needs now, which is really my
only true birthday wish. And that's it for source code for today. We'll be back to,
no, promise myself we're going to do anything on weekend. So tomorrow, I'm at the air show
and Lailie start all day. I'm being picked up at 10. We're flying in. I'll be there until
about 5. And I will be updating. What I'll do is I'll see if I can keep the computer running
here so I can do some GSM phone updates and also take the big camera for some really high
quality pictures because there's going to be some classic planes there and if you're
into aviation, it should be exciting. So look for that tomorrow on live dot curry dot
If you want to respond just leave a comment there on the post for this program for today
Or of course you can also send an email at atom at curry dot com and I will see you on Monday
Have a good one everybody bye bye
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm not sure I can win here.
But I'm not sure I can win.
I'm not sure I can win.