podcasting live from the
Tata Tata Tata Tata Tata
podcasting
this is daily so
Adam Curry.
How are you.
Hey, well good afternoon everybody a brand new opening for the show this listener supported show where users and developers part
Thanks to Howard Greenstein, Howard, from New York, who's also requested that I play some
very choral on the show, which I'll certainly do once I can find my exclusive live recording
over.
So, welcome to the source code for Monday.
Today is the 27th of September 2004.
It's quarter to four in the afternoon, coming to you from Flanders, Belgium, from Curry
Castle and we have a lot to talk about today.
So much has happened over the weekend and it was several times I was just itching to
jump behind the machine and come on in, huh?
It's okay, I'm recording.
All right?
Yeah.
I just wanted to jump behind the machine and cut a source code but I really, you know,
there was just so much else going on and Christina who just walked into the bar slash
studio area who has the day off today from school.
She won bronze medal with her, that was the national championships with her dressage, horse
riding.
Congratulations, Christina. She's very talkative today. Thank you. So I did have a couple chats
with different people over the weekend. Let's see, with Steve Gilmore, that was a Skype chat.
I've spoke to Dave Weiner a couple of times. And I've had lots of email conversations.
And the first thing I wanted to play for you today was, and I don't think I played this
on Friday, if I did I apologize.
But remember Dr. Dave from Las Vegas gave me all the tips and pointers on how to record
the daily source code at the equal or close to equal quality of sound but with half the
file size.
And as you probably noticed from Friday's source code, the file was indeed about half
And I think the audio was still reasonably good.
So props go out to Dr. Dave.
There did, there was a, well there were a couple of discrepancies and I thought I
caught it and I thought that I also thought, well maybe he's confusing bits with
Hertz and whatever.
But Doug Kay, who is the producer of ITConversations.com, it's his, the
whole outfit is his as far as I know.
By the way, Mia Culpa during the first or second trade secrets, I said that I
didn't think that Doug Kay was a streaming guy and that he sent me a very
friendly email.
explaining exactly how much of a streaming guy he is.
So I stand corrected big time.
And of course he's hosting all the IT conversations and is also...
He's in with us here on the loop on the iPod platform and he's a content producer.
It's great. And he has a lot of experience with file sizes and recordings
and he came back with a response which is an audio.
That's very nice. To Dr. Dave.
So without further ado, here's Doug Kay with more tips on how to reduce your file size.
Hello Adam and listeners to the Daily Source Code.
This is Doug Kay, the host and producer of IT Conversations.
And I just wanted to respond to something you broadcast in your show on Friday.
It was a clip from Dr. Dave of Las Vegas and Dr. Dave was trying to answer the question about what bit rates to use.
And unfortunately he made a fairly significant error.
He said for example that a 32k bit rate was totally adequate for voice
that it reproduced 16kHz audio that it was as good as FM.
that's not the case. Dr. Dave is confusing a couple of different technological issues.
He's confusing the bit rate of the MP3 audio with the sample rate. The sample rate is controlled
by something called the subnyquist theorem. The subnyquist theorem says that if you want
to sample analog data, you can use the sample rate to measure the sample rate.
that you must sample at twice the highest frequency you want to reproduce.
So for example, if you want to reproduce 16 kHz audio, you need to have 32,000 samples per second.
Now in wave file format, which is a lossless format, those are typically 16-bit samples or 2-byte samples.
So sampling at 32,000 samples per second is actually 64,000 bytes per second,
which is in fact 512,000 bits per second.
So that's the sample rate, but it has relatively little to do with the bit rate of the MP3 encoder.
MP3 is a lossy compression technique similar to JPEG.
We're going to throw away a lot of data when we get these compression ratios of 20, 30, 40 to 1 and so forth.
A 64k bit per second MP3 is generally considered the equivalent of FM.
It's arguable, I think that a 64k MP3 doesn't sound quite as good as good FM.
I think a 96k bit per second MP3 is closer to a...
good FM signal, but that depends on the program material.
Here's a brief history of the MP3 encoding rates we've used here at IT Conversations.
When I started a year and a half ago, I encoded everything at 32 k bits per second.
The quality wasn't good, but I still got a number of complaints that the files were
too big.
The reason was that the MP3 players in those days could not take very large files.
Over time things have changed quite quickly.
Until recently we encoded everything at 48 k bits per second.
We got very few complaints.
But now people who have MP3 players that have quite a bit more storage, such as a 40
gigabyte iPod, are asking us to use higher quality bit rates.
They don't mind the larger files.
So just within the past week I've started encoding our files at 64 k bits per second.
That results in about 30 megabytes for one hour of audio.
And that's my current recommendation for what people should be using for audio blogs,
daily source code, and the like.
By the way, it's also not true.
that you need a higher bit rate for music than for voice. The waveform of human
voice is very, very complex and in fact you will hear distortion in the human
voice before you can detect it in most music, the reason being that you may not
know how to predict the waveform in music. Whereas with voice if you know the
person you have certain expectations of what their voice will sound like. Another
question that comes up is stereo versus mono and you need double the bit rate
for stereo or are stereo files twice as large as mono files. In wave files they
are twice as large because it is a lossless format but in MP3 one of the
things that you're encoding is the difference between the left and right
channels. So for example if you're recording voice from a single microphone
it really doesn't matter whether you use a stereo MP3 at 64k or a mono MP3 at
64k bits per second because they'll be essentially the same. The only time
that it really matters is when you have program material where the left and
right channels are substituted.
different. As to the question of VBR or variable bitrate, this is a technique that does allow
the MP3 to vary the bitrate from one frame to the next, but it's not supported by certain
players so I do not recommend recording VBR for audio blogs and the like. There's really
nothing to gain. Anyway, if you have any questions, send me email Doug at ITConversations.com
or you might want to check out a wiki page that I just posted to deal with this topic.
Go to www.ITConversations.com slash wiki w-i-k-i and somewhere there you'll find a link to the
page that deals with MP3 encoders and file formats and things like that. Hope this has been helpful.
Keep up your great work on the daily source code. So far I haven't missed a single show
and I hope not to. Thanks.
Alright Eve, thank you very much Doug Kay from ITConversations.com. Wow, that was
some excellent, excellent source code you dumped on us. Indeed, after listening to Dr. Day from
Vegas and
and the response from Doug Kay, I did get my file size down to about half,
and I am running also about 15 megs per half hour, so about 30 megs for an hour.
And there was some mail that came in, hold on a second,
I'm going to switch applications here,
now we've had bad luck with that in the past, it's working out.
From Eric Elliott, I just want to share that with you.
He said they had a chance to catch up, listen to this past week's Daily Source Code,
also trade secret show with Dave.
Want to address one topic you mentioned both in one of your Daily Source Codes
and on trade secrets is about the AAC audio format.
He says, now I certainly don't have any arguments against using MP3,
and that would be my choice too, since it's the most widely universally accepted format right now.
But I wanted to clear up a misconception about AAC.
AAC is not Apple's proprietary format.
It's a standard that was basically developed by the MPEG group as the successor to MP3.
It is actually the audio component to MPEG 4 video.
However, what is proprietary is the fair play DRM, that's digital rights management,
Apple is put on top of AAC in the iTunes music store. The reason that the
tunes purchased from iTunes music store only work on iTunes and the iPod is
because of the DRM, not AAC. But a non-fair play AAC will play on a variety of
players. Just wanted to clear that up. That's Eric Elliott. Thank you very much,
Eric. And he also posts a link, apple.com, slash mpeg4, slash AAC for some
more information on that. Excellent. So I still think we should stick with mp3,
but I'd like to hear a little bit more if people have more information. You know,
this is a format that is just as, I don't know if it's just, if it can be just as
open as mp3. Who controls mp3? No one. Is there a standards body or something? I
don't think so. Well, there probably is. And I'm sure by now people will already
be hacking away the email to set me straight. What I'm going to do right now
is probably inviting Murphy in, but I just wanted to take a screenshot of my
setup so you can see how I've
got the show lined up for today because I don't have notes. I used to keep an
outliner handy with notes and now I just have all of my my different sound clips.
I have quite quite a few all set up and ready to fire and they're in a
chronological order. So it may screw up the recording but I'm just gonna try
this. Hold on.
It's thinking about it.
Okay. Let me just see.
Yup. Took a picture. Okay. Great.
So we've got that and I'll post that because
great excitement for me over the weekend.
Just as I was, you know, about to give up on the Rubik's Cube
of how we can route audio back and forth, particularly
like a radio station does where you call into a show,
in this case the call in is through iChat or
AOL into Messenger or Skype or a SIP phone.
And we hear you on the air and we can control your volume,
turn you on and off, but you also hear everything we're doing
on the air minus your voice. So you can't be sending back
a total signal because then you get this feedback loop.
And to me that was a Rubik's Cube I've been struggling with
for two weeks now. And I ran across, actually
through my referral log, Hugo Schochmann.
He's from, you see, he lives in Zurich and you can
check out his weblog at log.
and that's h-u-g-o-s-c-o-t-m-a-n dot com.
And Hugo had been listening, he posted his whole bit on his blog about how he had been
listening.
out the trade secrets and he came up with a proof of concept and he actually recorded both
sides of the conversation.
I thought for a second there that he had also run into the echo problem but it turns out
he didn't and he had indeed found the perfect setup and posted a diagram that was beautiful.
I had downloaded the Soundflower virtual audio device a while ago in the beginning of
my quest to figure out the perfect setup and just around when he's doing this setup
all of a sudden things start to click in my head.
Maybe it was just from listening to his MP3 because he hadn't posted it to his site yet but I was
I think he might be, you know, maybe he did it this way.
And even though we came up with a different way of doing it,
I'm using Audio Hijack Pro, he's using a different, see what.
record. And he's also using GarageBand which I used to use and now longer he's just posted
a whole bunch of updates with great screenshots. Let me just see, what is he's using Soundtrack
thing? Yeah, Soundtrack to record. And you know what? You need no external gear. And
the Soundflower virtual device is open source, it's freely available so please check out
Hugo's weblog. It is phenomenal. I'm so pleased that we have someone who's you know
who's all over this and is helping us set it up. Now granted this is all still on a
Mac and actually when I did a test call with Dave he was crying saying you know
I want to play music too. I was jamming tunes down the pipe too. It was great.
So we will keep working at it. Let me see. Actually I just got back from a
quick trip up to Breda. It's about 30 minutes from our house by car. That's in
the Netherlands where coffee shops are legal. I had to go get a new supply.
I have actually the harvest that I had here at home for those of you following. I have tried it
It's it's okay, but it's saying because it's all totally organic and I didn't really you know use any
Anything special on it. You got to smoke an awful lot before it has the desired effect
So anyways, I went up to get a little supply these guys that run the coffee shop from Morocco. So they're all
They're all Arabs. I know I'm really well and we hang out and we drink
Chinese tea Moroccan Moroccan tea which is basically Chinese tea with mint leaves and a ton of sugar in there and
So I just chilling out and we're talking and he was reading a Moroccan newspaper
And I and was a picture of Bush and Perry on the front page and we got to talking and
It was just you know, I think what we concluded and it would have really made for a good a good podcast
Although it was in like four different languages. It was you know, Morocco and Morocco that besides Arabic
They also speak French so it was French. It was Dutch. It was English. It was
some Arabic words, some general high Arabic, which is generally understood.
And so I think what we concluded was that all politicians, everyone in government,
they're all in it for the money. Most of them are in it for the money.
All the big guys are. What was he telling me? He's saying the new president of Palestine,
so there's a new guy. He apparently owns a huge factory in Israel.
Everyone's just in the game for a lot of their own interests.
And certainly we know Bush is. And he said, yeah, maybe if we get Kerry,
then we have a chance at figuring out what he's about before he can really get his hoax in.
But Kerry's the same. There's big money there. There's his wife with Heinz.
There's all kinds of cronyism and nepotism and everything going on in government at all different levels.
And what I think what we base...
What basically concluded is, in 30 years there will be a new generation, there will be our
kids and they'll hopefully have grown up a little bit differently and they'll have different
values and will think about religion differently and won't hate each other.
Kind of like the Germans now.
Germany completely flattened the Netherlands, occupied it outright, just killed people,
kicked off a million Jews, flattened Rotterdam.
The Germans still come to Holland on vacation, they sit on our beaches and we get along fine
and all the young Germans or...
generation, 30 to 40 years old, we don't give a fuck about what happened then.
We hope we can learn from it and we get along and there's no animosity.
And that eventually will probably happen in other parts of the world where huge conflict
is abound at this time.
There was a couple other points that we came up with.
Well I said that clearly this is where the internet probably will speed up that cycle.
I'm hoping 10 years maybe because we're just not buying it anymore.
We're not buying what's in the media.
We're not buying what's in what's being shown on television, the speeches.
We're being lied to.
You know you're being lied to.
within a millisecond that you're supposed to read that disclaimer and know that your actual
results will vary due to road and weather condition.
But anyway, it was always fun to have a political conversation in four different languages while
drinking some Moroccan tea and smoking some wonderful plant of Mother Earth.
But when I got back I checked my iPod or inbox, better known as my iPod, and I saw a whole
bunch of interesting new bush clips that had come up.
And I figured I might as well just do a little bush block here, including a political poem.
So first let me get to this first one.
This has probably been circulating around the internet.
That's why it shows up on the blog.
This is Bush, basically fucking up whatever he's saying.
He's trying to say peace, but it comes out a little bit differently.
Listen to this little clip.
It's in the interest of a long-term peace in the world that we work for a free and secure and peaceful Iraq.
A peon's free and secure Iraq in the midst of the Middle East will have enormous historical impact.
A peon's free and secure Iraq.
So that was one guffaw that I don't know where that came from.
Another one. This is my favorite one and I'm sure this is going to come back to haunt George W. during his many years as ex-president.
And they want us to leave. That's what they want us to do.
And I think the world would be better off if we did leave.
If we didn't, if we left, the world would be worse.
The world is better off if it's not leaving.
How am I gonna have that death? What?
Okay, as the source code continues for Monday the 27th,
I've got a political poem for you.
And it just showed up in my iPod. It's pretty good.
Listen to it.
It's like we were relaxing, sit around talking.
I'm not saying
I'm not saying anything anymore.
Man, I'm sorry, this is nice music and I don't want to spoil it with another political
tirade because I don't even like political poetry because most of it sucks and most
of the political stuff that comes out of it.
Intimence glia die with pain slowly
slowly, painfully. You are all criminals. You will never go to jail. So just die as soon
as possible with great pain slowly. I would die the slowest who was painful death of all
of you. If it meant that just half of you would die now. Come in, liberal. Come in,
I'm not interested in sick. I don't care. I hate you all and I hope you all die.
you
Another political poem that was King Missile 3, I'm reading this from the ID3 tags, from
the album Royal Lunch.
And oh man, that's exercising your free speech there, isn't it?
Damn.
But I think that just listening to that, the point is maybe just like we had Hitler, we
had Stalin, we had Mussolini, and they're all gone and new ones come and they're dictating
coffee. And then they'll go, eventually we all go and then new ones pop up and let's
just hope that we can steer some of our leaders. And I think that that's a lot about what
blogs are about and podcasting. It's exactly the same. It's all freedom of speech. It's
really, really important.
Okay. Let me just go back to the mail bag because I had a lot of mail that came in.
Jonathan Green sent me a note about Mars Edit. I was raving about that the other day,
hoping that they'll build in enclosure support pretty soon. I mean, I've been using it now
for the past, well, since whenever I started talking about it, it feels like about a week.
I like it very, very much. It's really, I have a central place for all of my web
blog publishing. It's easy to edit. There's just no waiting involved, no waiting for
browsers to render. It's just, it probably stores a local copy of stuff in its own
cache. It's great. It's really good stuff. And he suggested installing the book
market.
Because I said there was a script that you can post from Safari.
It's called the script.
It's called post from Safari in the Mars Edit Scripts menu.
And the bookmark is cool because it does the same thing,
only it also gives you a routing tag like via,
and then you put in whoever it came from.
And just more good stuff, smart user stuff
that I'm really enjoying using.
Let me see.
What is this here?
This is just a shout out from Kurt Wendelkern,
IT pro working for the US Navy.
It says, in case you've been noticing the .navy.mil hits
in your logs.
Yeah, didn't go unnoticed.
I try every day to move tech users in my giant organization
forward.
Your stuff certainly helps me to keep thinking.
Happy to hear it.
And that's a lot about what the source code is for.
Let's try to get users and developers to party together.
Hold on.
Let me just see.
I had a couple other comments that came in.
through the weblog. Oh yeah, there have been some comments about, I posted that I'm pushing
about 9 gigs a day out through my servers for the daily source code and trade secrets.
And I call that a bump in the road. And I mean that, you know, it is a bump in the
road. We're going to fix this. And I think the first and most important thing we can
do before we get to the ISP level is getting BitTorrent fully integrated. I played with
that. I finally subscribed to my first BitTorrent feed. It's the, what is it? It's
the Air America archives. They have an archive, an RSS 2.0 podcast feed for
you to subscribe to. And it brings in recent shows through BitTorrent as
OGG files, which is another compression standard, which I think it's a pretty
geeky standard. It really compresses stuff incredibly. I think it compresses
about twice as much as MP3, at least it seems that way from the file size.
I tune.
Torrance doesn't support it out of the box, you have to download a plug-in.
But anyway, so if that's the way it's coming, then I still want to listen to it.
And iPod or X successfully got the BitTorrents, downloaded the show, it created the folder.
I didn't quite put the files into the folder and renamed them as mp.mp3 instead of it's
originally...
But the iPod are concepts there and it's working.
And what we need to do now is make the publishing of MP3s a little more easier.
So that you don't have to go through the process of,
I've done it myself just in local bench testing of,
okay, here we go.
You know, got to first create the MP3 tags,
then I'm going to make a bit torrent out of it,
then I have to upload the torrent and I have to upload the file.
You know, that's just a lot of steps to go through.
And then just briefly at the ISP level,
I also did a test, I threw up the latest trade secrets on my .mac account
where I bought a gigabyte of disk space.
You know, if you want to publish, there's going to be pain somewhere.
Even if you have a web blog, if you get slash.com,
Now, bandwidth is being commoditized, so you'll find that there are deals out there that can
really help you.
But we want to make sure that we're not victims of our own success here, and shouldn't be
that every single time your show takes off and people are listening to you and you've
got a popular show, that your bandwidth bill goes up.
That's not the economy of scale that traditional radio or television have.
And I think that's where BitTorrent is going to help us.
And that's mainly because this is not streaming, it's time shifting, it's downloading.
I think that we can effectively distribute the load.
And I think we're doing a pretty good job so far with the integration of BitTorrent from
what I've seen in iPod or X.
Also Danny Gregor, Gregor, Gregory, we've been emailing back and forth and I mentioned
him before on the source code.
He is submitting a proposal with our buddy Dave Slusher from Evil Genius Chronicles.
for the O'Reilly e-Tech conference.
And they're going to do it about podcasting and the iPod platform.
See, they actually have a, I guess they're calling it podcasting.
Yeah.
And they invited me to go along with them.
Now that's not going to work schedule-wise with the move and everything.
Excuse me.
Hold on, let me just get rid of this.
That's better.
So I said, but no, please, you guys go have a ball and let's see, you know, apparently
that's the conference to be at.
I don't know, I don't really do a lot of conferences, certainly not conference conferences, but
they're submitting your proposal and I guess they're going to get out there and we're
keeping an eye on them and they'll be reporting to us, of course.
So, I'm going to be doing conferences, BloggerCon 3 coming up the 6th of November in
Palo Alto, bloggercon.org is where you want to check it out and I'll be leading a
discussion on podcasting myself.
And I wrote up a description today, you can check it out, it's on the web blog at
bloggercon.com.
And if anyone listening to this podcast, you know, can come or is planning on coming,
let me know, you know, let's get some stuff set up.
I really hope we can have a massive jam parties.
We're all bringing our mobile studios and we need to talk about setups and how
it works.
and all the stuff that we're talking about on the iPod or dev list.
You can hear by the way that our good buddy Luke is blowing the leaves outside the castle at the moment,
outside of the bar door where we are.
Alright, let's play some more fun stuff.
I got an email from Tony.
And now my email, there we go.
Tony Khan.
He was another fan of the source code.
He's in Boston and he's working at Public Radio at WGBH.
And he does, let me see if he, yeah, I think he produces, I don't know if he hosts it,
but he produces a series of short stories called Morning Stories.
And he pointed me to them and you can get them in streaming.
There's also a download MP3 archive and they're really good.
And so I suggested, well, you know, dude, why don't you get an RSS 2.0 podcasting feed together.
And I'll point to it and then everyone can enjoy this.
It won't be that much.
better. And so he said, well, yeah, certainly, what was this quote here? Hi, Adam, wish there
was an RSS feed your way ahead of us that makes you such a force in changing the face
of radio. I'll see if I can make it happen. You know how hard it is to make an elephant
sized operation like WGBH remember it can still dance. Tony, I'm sure you are teaching
it new steps as we speak. And I want to play this bit, which is one of the from the morning
story series. Meanwhile, hopefully by the time we get back the leaf blowing will
have diminished a little bit. Check this one out. It's titled 1-800-YOUR-DAB.
Hello?
Cold?
Heathunt?
Door?
De-
tied up at work right now.
A scene can't have a meaningful relationship.
Press 1 if you call to chat.
Press 2 if you call to apologize for not having phoned in months.
Press 3 if you really called for money.
One.
If you call to shoot the breeze.
Press 1 if you want to hear about my problems.
Press 2 if you want us to hear about your problems.
Press 3 at any time if what you really called about was money.
One.
If you want to hear about my problems.
How far is one to hear what you think about.
Huh?
Press 2 to hear what we think about your planet.
Cycle.
World with your barbarian friends.
What's wrong with them?
Press 3.
You put really cool out with money.
Great.
You finally pressed 3.
Please enter now with the dollar amount you are requesting.
Followed by the pound sign.
Bottom of the dial.
Eh.
The heck I won't get it anyway.
Hm.
And pound sign.
5,000.
Who are you on?
Press 1 to hear my lecture.
I am not for nuts.
Press 2 to hear mother.
You, of course.
Or press 3 if you're willing to sell for $100 cash.
Question set by the turn name.
Hmm.
Please hold your request as being a set of songs.
You're fine.
Dad, it's a-
It's a-
Oh, a lot of guys gotta do 500 bucks.
Yes.
Mom.
Your request has just been electronically-
Thanks for calling.
Miss you
It's two to hear Duke bark.
Bye.
Press three to hear your little sister Judy tell you we don't understand her either.
Some choice.
Go with the dog.
Hi Duke.
Dog got a G.E.O.
Yeah, there you go.
1-800- Your dad from WGBH and as soon as they get a feed together I will most definitely
point to it.
Okay, so there's still a little bit of leaf blowing going on but you know what, maybe we'll
make this a double shot source code today.
Playing a full hours worth of all the best that I've tripped across on the net.
Let's listen to the Isles right now.
Yeah.
It's pretty much a full hour.
It's a full hour, there we go.
That's the end of the video.
That's it.
Bye.
I'd like to take a home for last, cause me this tongue got cheap on keeping on if I don't shield you.
Europe, European Union where it is end of October because then I can download and happily
pay for a good version of the Isley Brothers who's that lady that's had a dropout somewhere
in the middle there. Come on people. Yeah, so I wonder how many of you skipped ahead
to this part and didn't listen to the Isley Brothers? Does everyone always listen to
all the songs? Let me know at adamantcurry.com. So yeah, we're going to make this a double
shot of the source code for today because just so much to talk about and what
what is what's the worst is when great stuff happens on Friday and then I sit
there you know all weekend thing I gotta talk about this stuff gotta remember
to talk about I'm writing stuff down
I've got bits and notes.
I mean, I've never, I haven't been this active since the first time I hosted the morning
show on Z100 in New York.
You know, I'm just totally, everything is show prep mode, which is great.
I love it because I have so much to talk about.
And it's my version of web logging.
On Friday, there was new Gilmore Gang that was put up.
You know how much I love this show?
It's ITConversations.com, the Gilmore Gang, Steve Gilmore, John Udell, Doc Searles,
and they always have some guests on there.
And I have to say, a lot of this show was about iPodder.
And I mentioned this on Trade Secrets because Dave called up and so we might have said, well,
shoot, we're talking and we want to talk about this Gilmore Gang thing.
And so we recorded a show out of it and put it up.
If you haven't heard it, secrets.scripting.com.
And it was, you know, they kept wandering away to talk about suns, you know, buy
computer cycles, buy the hour offering.
I actually posted a link to that on my web log.
And they kept coming back to iPodder.
It was great to hear.
They were clearly excited about it and it was wonderful to hear it.
But there were some errors in there that now I was listening.
You have to understand that if you read a newspaper and you read an interview or an article
about yourself and there's something wrong, I am like, oh, man, shit.
And then you see it on TV.
Sometimes you feel like throwing the remote.
And you hear stuff on radio or your iPod and I'm like, ah, jump up and down.
Like, no, that's not right.
That's not right.
So I did get some interesting points wrong.
And I was thinking about playing back the show, stopping it and talking about exactly what they
said.
But I didn't have to because Saturday morning on my iPod waiting for me was a new evil genius
chronicle.
Exactly that.
He did it in post-production and edit, but I figured I'll just play you a little bit
a clip and then the response that Dave gives to that clip because his response is just
excellent.
It just really cracked me up.
So this is a bit of the evil genius chronicles from September 25th, 2004, regarding the
Gilmore gang of the same date.
Well, there's an optional portion effectively of RSS called enclosures that bear the
greatest similarity to email attached.
Hold on a second.
You know what I should do?
I should probably rewind this just a little bit, just so that you can hear Dave's
intro and who's talking here.
Hold on a second.
And rewind this.
Okay, you know, if you want to do a big set, you can probably call your
RSS and show them.
There's a...
Here's what he had to say about it.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
We're almost there.
Okay.
Hold on.
It's also actually important.
I hope I'm not...
Okay, I'll play... Z also does a Mia call to hear which is important for context.
You and I are hearing this at different times.
I wrote down everything I wanted to say so hopefully I'm not
misremembering as I do this.
So we're going to hear the first piece and this is Scott Rafer from...
who's the CEO of Feedster. Here's what he had to say about it.
There's an optional portion effectively of RSS called enclosures
that bear the greatest similarity to email attachment than anything else.
And with the restriction you can only have one per RSS speed,
with per RSS entry.
And they've been gaining popularity recently and Adam Curry,
the former BH1 VJ who's now sort of done a lot with RSS
from the Netherlands,
put together a piece of software called iPodder,
i-p-o-d-d-e-r.org.
where you can go straight from RSS enclosures onto your iPod.
And he's got his little daily radio show,
similar to a certain extent.
To this one, it goes up digital files on the web and whatever.
It's a soliloquy, mainly.
But he put it out there and started
distributing his radio show this way.
And then listenership took off.
And so they put out the piece of software
as a come one, come all kind of little attachment
to drop onto your Mac.
I don't believe there's a Windows version yet.
And what Scott Johnson did was he reacted to this
in the growing popularity of enclosures,
putting together some master feeds up on Feaster's site
so that you can have an RSS feed of all the MP3s that
come through the system, all the JPEGs, all the video files,
all the calendar events even.
So his advocacy and his company obviously is
supporting things to help this platform out.
I had a couple annoying little errors in there,
which as I posted about this earlier in the weblog,
I ascribed him as working for Technorati,
so I make the annoying little errors myself too.
I don't think Adam ever worked for VH1.
It was, I think, only MTV.
That's not a biggie.
No, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on, hold on.
To me, that is a biggie.
I used to host Headbangers Ball, dude.
I mean, it's like, oh man, that's so rough.
The only real VJ that was ever on VH1,
besides Rosie O'Donnell, by the way,
and I did her audition,
and she got hired because of me,
was Tim Bird the Birdman.
You're probably still here to see him
somewhere around your...
So no, that's actually quite, so I'll say that I was from VH1 and I was jumping up and down
when I heard that, like, come on man, that's unfair.
But of course maybe that's because MTV no longer actually plays music videos and VH1
does, so it may just be a very honest mistake.
Let's continue now with the Dave Slush's analysis of the statement.
It isn't really an error, but something about the way he said stuff kind of rubbed
me the wrong way.
You notice that he uses the word little like three times.
Adam's little radio show and this little program that you put on there and it runs
on its little subscription.
To me that, I don't know, that just sounds like derogation and kind of
diminution of what we're doing here.
I mean, it's not something to get your, you know, be so thin skin that that
bothers you about, but I don't know why he's using that adjective.
Oh, Dave, I think I can tell you why.
Because people who talk like that, and I listen, I caught that as
well. I was like, whoa, I see saying a little this and a little that.
And usually people who say that have a psychological thing.
And of course everything you say is always based upon your own
psyche and your own frustration.
So he probably has a small penis.
That seems kind of out of place.
As does soliloquy, because it sounds almost, I don't know,
accusatory.
Like, Adam's show is a soliloquy.
And guess what?
This shows a soliloquy too.
Is that, I mean, any one person talk radio show
is like that.
And I replayed that bit four times.
What does he say?
Well, I couldn't understand it.
And it wasn't until I heard Dave's analysis that I heard it
was soliloquy.
And I had to look it up.
I had to look it up on dictionary.com.
Hold on a second.
Let me bring up the definition of soliloquy.
I think I posted to my web log about that as well.
No, hold on a second.
Let's just get soliloquy.
It's even hard to say.
Soliloquy.
Damn, it's the word of the day.
a day. So lilikwy. Let me see. Where is it? Here, so lilikwy. A dramatic or literary form
of discourse in which a character talks to himself.
his or her thoughts without addressing a listener.
That's not true.
That's just not true.
I'm totally 100% addressing listeners here.
And the only reason I'm stopping by, I'm just making light of the situation.
I'm tickled to death that these guys talked about it.
Really am.
And I'm so happy that Feaster is supporting us.
But shit, I got a whole hour to fill here.
You know what I'm saying?
Let's just see if Dave has anything left here.
When he talked radio show in the period between they're taking calls, that's a salute.
That's just the way it goes.
But it is interesting that Feaster is behind this.
I don't know that I would ever use a Feaster feed to aggregate for the same reason when
we were going around.
Alright, so that's a whole different conversation.
You should listen to Dave's show if you want to check out all of that.
But anyway, it's a hilarious analysis of that conversation on the Gilmore Gang, which
is still one of my favorite shows.
So just saying howdy guys, we're listening to you.
I don't miss one of your shows either.
In fact, I'm really upset when I miss one of your shows.
Let me see, what else do we have left?
Oh, I ran across an interesting podcast.
Let me just see and look at the metadata here.
This is from Peter Overbaker.
It's called Ghost in the Machine.
And well, you should just listen to it for yourself
and you'll understand what he's doing immediately.
I've taken off the first bit of the theme song
and it almost goes straight into the actual start
of the podcast.
Ghost and the Machine Audio Blog for Sunday September 26, 2004.
Hi, all welcome to my very first audio blog, read to you by ReadPlease 2003.
Because my own voice sucks, I thought this might be a fun solution.
Well, it might not be as successful as Adam's or Dave's show.
Well, anyway, shoot, there's Luke again with the leaf blower.
So, clearly, you're not going to listen to a voice like that for very long.
But I have to say, and this can't be Apple's speech synthesis that's built into OS X,
because it doesn't sound that good, I don't think.
Maybe it is, but Peter should let us know.
But it does seem like it could be appropriate.
If I have a playlist of stuff that I want to listen to in the morning,
which includes a local weather report, it includes a sports update,
and I say it's unlikely, right?
Okay, so let's take a political update.
Then I want to listen to a show that plays two new songs for the day.
And then maybe there's something else that's totally...
automated that someone doesn't feel like setting up a voice track every single day.
You could automate that with tech.
Maybe the weather report is like that.
I think it'd be pretty boring, but I think it's certainly useful.
I think there's a spot for it in everything that we're doing.
Again, this could be used for so many things.
Just look at the telephone.
Look at a web log and say, what can this be used to make money?
How can I use this to make money?
I forget the web log.
Look at a telephone.
It's the same thing.
Just think about what we're doing with radio.
We're doing two radio.
The spot where radio makes its money is during drive time in the morning and the afternoon.
It's a very different way of consuming information because you're not going anywhere physically.
You're sure you're moving along the road.
Hopefully, maybe you're in traffic.
You're moving along slowly, but you're not getting out of your car.
Besides the cell phone, there's not much else to do in the way of entertainment.
You're stuck there in the most.
00:51:57,000 --