How are you all doing?
Good afternoon, everybody. Welcome.
Friends, family, global dominating world leaders. Welcome to the daily source code. I'm Adam Curry.
Coming to you from Amsterdam, the Netherlands today, from the bunker on the canal.
Oh, thank God, it's Monday, huh?
Because Monday always reminds you that there's a whole new week of fascinating stuff up ahead.
There's so much that can be happening, that will be happening.
And there's a lot to talk about that did happen.
Or maybe a little more specifically, some stuff that didn't happen.
If you were somewhat annoyed or disappointed that there was no source code Friday or Friday night,
or there's nothing sitting there waiting for you on Saturday.
You were probably waiting for the helicopter flight addition of the daily source code.
Well, I'll guess what, it didn't happen. I'll explain why.
Because the root of the theme song here for a second, I'm tired of that.
First of all, so yeah, Patricia and I are in Amsterdam today.
She's at the dentist, finally finishing up all the rather nasty dental works.
She's had in the past couple of years. So everything's great, and she's happy to be done.
And so I had time here to finish up a couple things.
And we're still winding down just about everything we can here, so that when we leave,
which would be around the end of November when we moved to the UK, everything will be pretty much done.
Unfortunately, I still have this humongous house in Amsterdam, which, well, the housing market right now is just not good.
People who live in the Netherlands are not really buying houses, so clearly a lot aren't selling,
and it's hard to find the right people folks coming over from other countries looking for something like this.
This is a big place.
Anyway, thinking of things to do with that.
But back to Friday and Saturday, what the plan was,
I've been asked to be a celebrity waiter at a special benefit dinner for war child.
Feast for peace is what it was called.
And there were several other Dutch celebrities there, and it actually was a lot of hard work,
about 200 people that had to be served.
Part of them were on a buffet, some others on a set menu,
but I used to waiter in a rather classy restaurant in Audeca,
called The Old Prince, The Out of Prince.
And I wore the three-piece suit and the bow tie, and really worked my ass off when I was like 17.
And even a little bit younger than even 16 is when I started there.
I did that for about three years, so I definitely know how to do it,
and I know how it works, and know how it restaurant runs.
It was a little on handy as they had two floors, and the kitchen was on the top floor,
so anything that was delivered downstairs had to be taken down by the stairs,
and the dirty plates had to be taken up, so that was kind of a bummer.
But I'd promised to do this.
It was about 200 kilometers, so let's say about 110 miles from my house,
each way.
I knew it was going to be really late by the time we were done.
So I said to the organizers, who I knew to friends of mine, I said,
I'll tell you what, I'm going to fly to your house,
which is nearby.
It's their restaurant nearby the restaurant.
Then I'll pick you up.
We'll fly to the restaurant.
Then we'll do our thing.
We'll leave the helicopter there, and then the next morning,
you just take me over to the restaurant, and I'll fly back home.
And the plan was, since I was going to be up on myself,
was to hook up the recording equipment.
I've done this before.
It works perfectly.
I have the wireless mic set, and I just put the little lovelier mic
inside my headphone, because when I talk through the microphone
on the headset, you'll hear me through the inner-com system,
and you'll also hear what's going on with air traffic control.
Now, on, I left late, so Friday afternoon,
this is funny.
All the air bases, all the air force bases in the Netherlands,
they're always closed.
Or they'd closed early on Fridays.
They're closed all weekend.
It's a perfect time to attack Holland if you're planning
a stealth attack, because they just closed.
There's no one there.
Literally, no one there.
So there's also no air traffic control,
and around each of these, the basically airports,
so these bases, there's a control zone that can reach
several miles wide, and you have to request a crossing.
Usually, you ask them, the air traffic control
around the ground, and these control zones.
So, they've not being there.
You have to talk to Dutch military info.
And Dutch military info is kind of the default
that you go back to, if you can't reach somebody,
or if you want to know something about a certain area,
that's their flight information service.
And it was so beautiful.
The weather was just so phenomenal that everybody
and their freaking dog was in the air.
I swear to God, excuse me.
You're right, math.
There are days that go by when I don't hear a single soul
on the radio.
There's no one in the air, but me and KLM basically,
and they're 30,000 feet higher than I am.
And today, everybody was up.
There were gliders.
There were ultra lides.
There were lots of fixed wing aircraft.
There were some helicopters.
Everything was flying around.
And since I couldn't just listen to the specific frequency
that I needed in a new one of these air bases,
I had to listen to Dutch mil info.
And it was so busy.
And I really wanted to pay attention because,
you got people zooming around at a thousand feet,
which is about my height.
That's where I usually fly.
Sometimes a bit lower.
700 feet is what helicopters like to fly.
But there's people all over the place.
Especially gliders.
And there's only one air traffic controller
controlling all of these areas.
And so either I would have to turn the sound down,
which would be unsafe to say the least,
because you definitely want to hear what's going on.
And just where everybody is,
as you can get a little global picture of what's happening.
Or you would be distracted by it because,
and I would be distracted by it and couldn't talk.
So Friday was bad.
Of course, the weather Saturday was even better.
All the control zones were closed.
Everybody was out again.
So I just decided not to do it,
because it would either be unsafe,
or just I don't think it would be that entertaining.
So I owe you that one,
and we'll definitely do it,
because I think it's cool.
I think you'll enjoy flying along,
and just listening what's happening,
and I'll talk you through some of the stuff I'm doing,
and we can just talk about stuff.
So for today,
I figured I'd try and make a little bit good,
and kick it off with a nice song for this Monday,
which is a promise for the future.
Oh, blue eyes on the daily source code.
It's about aviation.
To blue.
In Lama Land,
there's a one-man band,
and it'll tutt his flute for you.
Come fly with me,
let's take off in the blue.
Once I get you up there,
where the air is where I find,
we'll just fly.
Star.
Once I get you up there,
I'll be holding you a song.
Yeah.
You made it.
Angels tear,
cause we're together.
Where the wise,
it's such a lovely day.
Just say the words,
and we'll beat the birds down to act.
A book obey.
It's perfect for flying.
Honeymoon,
they sell.
Come fly with me,
let's fly, let's fly away.
Once I get you up there,
where the air is where I find,
we'll just fly.
Star.
Once I get you up there,
I'll be holding you a song.
Yeah.
You made it.
Angels tear,
cause we're together.
Where the wise,
it's such a lovely day.
You just say the words,
and we'll beat the birds down to act.
A book obey.
It's perfect for flying.
Honeymoon,
they sell.
Come fly with me,
let's fly, let's fly.
Pack up, let's fly away.
I believe with Nelson Riddle.
Frank Sinatra,
come fly with me.
We're just kind of how I feel about what we're doing with iPod.
We're all just flying along here,
and everyone's allowed to jump on and fly along.
It's extremely nice.
So we were talking,
I don't know how long ago it was,
but we've been talking often on about
the genre setting in these podcasts.
If you have an MP3 player,
you look at it,
there's different categories that you can put your
music into,
and of course there's all kinds of music genres,
and there's a speech genre,
and a talk genre I believe,
and maybe there's,
I don't even think there's an audiobook genre.
This is according to ID3 tags,
1.3 or 2.1,
or I'm not quite sure.
But I've been able to force a podcasting genre
into the daily source code,
so that it's encoding,
and I guess everyone else can see that in their MP3 players,
and their iPods,
that it's coming across as a podcast.
And I've been doing this after an audio comment that came in
from Michael Gogan,
I've already been pronouncing his name.
Thank God he doesn't for us.
Hey Adam, it's Michael Gogan.
There we go.
Go Hagen.
Okay, here's some feedback from Michael Gogan.
As a follow-up to my suggestion yesterday that everybody
begins setting genre as podcast,
as they're sending out their podcast,
it appears that there is absolutely no rules about
what should or should not be listed as a genre.
So I say let's make the platform ours,
and start listening to everybody's genre as podcast.
You know, the side benefit of that is
that if you were to pass along one of these recordings to a friend,
or somebody that's not even familiar with this entire format yet,
just by pulling up the name and title in genre,
they'd see what they've got and go out in the internet
and find out all about it.
You know, as we begin aggregating more and more of these things,
for those of us that are interested in keeping it,
you know, that metadata is going to become important.
I know it really helps me to have a consistent setting
in iTunes because I've just got thousands of songs,
and this helps to segregate it from actual speech recordings
or audiobooks and that sort of thing.
So I was really pleased to see that you had implemented
podcast yesterday.
I know that Matthew Bischoff did so as well,
and so it's kind of neat to see some hair-brained idea
I had implemented just a day later.
On the window side it appears that sometimes genre
is referred to as content.
It should be easy enough to change if you're a particular
editor, a recorder doesn't allow you to do it on the window side.
There are plenty of ID3 tag editors you can download
or worst case scenario.
Just pull down iTunes that's free anyways,
and it makes it really easy to change.
You know, just on a side note,
right after my email yesterday,
you played a little recording from Dave Slescher's
Evil Genius Chronicles.
It was actually a recording I had sent in to Dave
a day or two prior, so you made my Wednesday.
I felt like I hit a home run.
I ended up both on Dave's show and on your show.
So maybe I've invented the first subset of podcasting,
which is just recording a two or three comment,
two or three minute comment, submitting it,
and seeing who plays it,
almost like a correspondence.
So anyways, keep up the good work,
and I look forward to listening to your show.
Alright, thank you very much, Michael.
That was well worth listening to.
When I do encourage that,
please send in your audio comp.
It's good, it's a nice way to communicate in these podcasts.
Certainly for the Daily Source Code,
coming to you today, as said, from Amsterdam,
and the iPod or hype seems to be at just climbing to higher peaks
every single day.
I've been doing interviews more over the weekend,
wired magazine, wired came out with a real nice article.
Haven't seen the L.A. Times yet, but that's on the way.
I've been doing interviews more over the weekend,
wired magazine, wired came out with a real nice article.
Haven't seen the L.A. Times yet, but that's on the way.
Last night, the BBC interviewed me.
I was so cool to, I'm still looking for a recording.
They promised they would email me the piece when it was broadcast.
Because the BBC has so much good content,
so we got a little bit into that.
I hope it was pre-recorded, so I hope they left it
in the actual interview that aired.
Also, I was on with Leo L.A.
The beginning of the weekend,
tech guy on KFI, Leo now has two podcasts going.
So check them out at LeoVille.com.
You can hear the part to the interview there,
but he's also doing a news podcast,
which is a little more regular.
So be sure to check out LeoVille.com.
I've been working on the directory at ipotter.org.
The traffic that we're getting is just,
it's unbelievable. I'm really happy we moved this to,
a new server before all this started to just
unleash itself upon this server running ipotter.org.
The concept behind the directory,
and I'm really starting to understand the beauty
of decentralized directories right now.
A directory is just like Yahoo has,
where you can look at businesses by region,
by town, type of business.
In this case, looking at podcasts,
it's exactly the same thing.
Only, of course, this is going so fast.
I already have so many entries in the directory tree
that it's impossible for one person just to maintain.
Nor do I want to do that.
Nor should there be any central person
that has that type of power.
That's a concern,
because we want to make it as open as possible for everybody.
So this concept of the open directory,
really eliminates that.
Here's how it works.
Basically, you create the directory in an outliner.
That makes sense, right?
You've seen an outliner.
You can expand a node, so you might have music
underneath there.
It would be blues and rock,
and then maybe world music.
You expand that.
There may be some more subcategories,
like for blues.
It could be rhythm and blues and delta blues.
And underneath that, you eventually find the links
that you're looking for.
Now, you translate that to the web,
and you get a directory structure where you have
a breadcrum trail of basically directories that you
jump into until you get where you want to be,
and then you can trace your way back.
So you create these in OPML, which stands for Outline
Process or Markup Language.
It's like HTML for Outliners.
And I've linked on us as iPodder as well as
Curry.com.
I've linked to OPML or Outline program
programs that export OPML.
So I basically have created a number of top categories.
It's just a start, right?
Because we can have any number we want,
and any way we want to categorize it.
But the way this works is other people
should own trees and branches or, you know,
and nodes of this directory.
So already I'm working with two people.
One is already taken hold of the music directory.
And that means that anything,
when the minute you, in an iPodder or the minute
you click on the music folder,
it looks like it's still staying on iPodder.org,
but it's actually bringing in the OPML
from a public web server and it's giving you a seamless
overview of and breadcrum trail
through the directory structure.
And in addition to that,
if you want to suggest add a link,
it goes to the owner of that branch
and to that owner's email.
So that's all automatic.
It's really cool.
It's far from done because I'd love to have
or there's so many more, so many things I could go for a whole show
that's what I'd like to have in the directory.
But what's cool is already the music directory
is now being maintained by someone else.
And once I get another person ready,
who's already got everything good to go,
but his OPML is still a little funky.
So we're working on that.
Then there's going to be a sub division,
specifically for mixes,
that'll be made by someone else.
So you can see how this directory can build
very, very quickly.
So I'm looking for people who want to help.
If you can figure out how to create an OPML document,
which in essence, you can create it just like RSS.
You could probably write it by hand.
You know, it's not that hard.
But it's a little bit easier.
And it's more visual if you do it in an outliner.
Personally, I use radio user land.
It supports all of the bits we need out of the box.
It is fully OPML compliant.
And well, there's a drawback,
if you call it that it does cost money.
You do have to pay for it.
You can use it for up to 30 days to test it out.
And then you have to pay 40 bucks and you get some hosting
and a weblog and all that.
But I think the outliner is at this point,
the most important thing to talk about in radio user land.
A lot of people who have started helping out using
Omni Outliner, small drawback,
the minute you export to OPML in Omni Outliner,
it does not send the owner name element.
Or it doesn't create the owner name element or the owner email element,
both which you need in order to work with the directory.
It also doesn't have a created element
and a modified date stamp element.
And some other things like node states,
but that's less important.
But hopefully we can get some of those
incompatibility squared away.
I'm getting a delay on headphones here.
It sounds like I'm talking with a big rubber ball on my mouth.
Which could have been true, but not today.
Okay, let's see.
What do we do?
Oh man, 20 minutes into the show.
Talk about the directory.
Now I want to talk a little bit about the election.
As I've been cruising through the internet,
just finding all the cool bits,
subscribing to new podcasts.
I'm using iPod RX.
It has an option to download the files,
other than MP3s.
And I've subscribed to the blog digger,
media feed and feedsters, AVI feed.
So I get all these cool little video mixes of stuff,
which is usually all anti-bush,
or very pro-carry.
Certainly those are just the two categories.
You could put everything into.
And there's some, it looks like there's some movies
or documentaries coming out and there's lots of trailers.
And I did a little test and I listened to each of these
without looking at the video,
just listening on the headphones.
And I thought they were good enough to put on the source code,
because there's just some,
well, there's interesting angles and interesting takes.
And this is the time to display this art before the election.
After the election,
it won't make any,
it really that much sense.
So I think it's important that we,
that we get the stuff out there,
so you can hear it.
I'm going to start with a bit,
which is about Fox News Channel.
Often, of course,
if you're into conspiracy theories,
you're going to love this.
Fox News Channel is said to be,
a supporter of Bush,
totally hammering Kerry,
but also just any Democrat versus Republican.
And Roger Ailes is the guy,
I think, still runs Fox News Channel.
And the question that was asked in this,
I believe trailer for documentaries,
who is the guy that runs Fox News Channel?
Who runs Fox News Channel?
In 1967, Roger Ailes works as media manager
for a public and presidential candidate, Richard Nixon.
In 1984, Roger Ailes is hired as a media advisor
for the Reagan campaign.
In 1988, Roger Ailes works as the media manager
for a public and candidate, George H. W. Bush.
It is accused of master-minding
a DuCoccus race-bading campaign
using convicted murder of Willie Horton.
After a career of running cutthroat conservative media campaigns,
for three Republican presidents,
Roger Ailes launches the Fox News Channel in 1996.
We'd like to restore objectivity,
where we find it lacking,
and I left politics a number of years ago
and run on whose organization for the last two years.
So we just expect to do fine,
balanced journalist.
On election night of 2000,
Roger Ailes Fox News Channel prematurely announced
to the world that George W. Bush
had won the state of Florida.
President Bush's days of absorbing John Kerry's attacks
were without counterattack or over.
John Kerry has been lashing out at President Bush
and by extension Republicans for a long time.
But the president is a gentleman.
You know, he set a different tone for his campaign.
John Kerry was scaring old people as usual.
The guy who says what he means of means what he says.
North Korea loves John Kerry.
Really? Yeah.
It's John Kerry's Jane Farnder with the Burmary Stark.
Dr. Rodgersman.
He wanted to do this Kerry plan.
We'll do his punished, successful companies.
Elias worked well for Democrats in the past.
I think the market is down on John Kerry.
The economy is very, very strong right now.
I think it's going to get stronger.
It's picking up.
Day by day.
Killing more jobs.
I'm going to suggest to the budgetary for John Kerry.
In 2004, Roger Ailes is running yet another Republican media campaign.
This time, he's got an entire table
that worked to help him re-elect George W. Bush.
Move on.org.
That's who put that out there.
Definitely an interesting site worth checking out.
Although I had to say, I'm on the mailing list and I rarely ever read it.
But I like what they produce.
I think they produce really wonderful stuff.
Very powerful stuff.
Good video.
Okay.
Now onto something about the...
What was an SMS coming in?
About the Patriot Act.
Another trailer for unconstitutional...
The film was called Unconstitutional.
And you can find more information at unconstitutionalthemovie.org.
Let me just see if I have the right one here.
Pretty sure I do.
Now, this is coming off another media play.
This is coming off of the VLC client.
So hopefully it'll play and you'll be able to hear it.
Here's the trailer for Unconstitutional.
This legislation is essential not only to pursuing and punishing tourists.
But also preventing more atrocities.
For about 20 second, I've got a phone call about 7 o'clock in the morning.
For my uncle saying that by 12 to 15 federal agents
just came into my pants house, picked up my mom, my dad, and my sister.
I go sat down next to me and I said,
George Bush is out of control.
I would gasp probably 30 minutes later.
Over my shoulder and there were four Santa Fe police officers standing behind me.
We have to ask ourselves, is this the most effective use of law enforcement?
Power.
Nearly 1,000 individuals.
He swept broadly, he swept blindly.
Until the number was over 1,000,
and people started asking questions.
They said, how many of these 1,000 people have been charged with
the crimes of September 11th and the answer was zero.
I know my dad was so hard to come to the country for freedom.
And then you know, 10 years later, we find out that the country that we came here to save us
is actually doing the Santas.
You had the Justice Department itself criticizing the actions and the policies.
These are critical issues.
This is what we're fighting for.
These are our civil liberties.
Well, I mean, I'm the was we'd say.
And have that drink open, I know.
I'm talking sex, I'm living real for.
I'm moving.
Okay, this is here.
It's sponsored by ACLU, unconstitutional, unconstitutional,
the movie.org.
You can probably tell by now that this, if you're a Republican,
this may not be a good podcast to listen to today.
And there's more where that came from.
I got an interesting audio feedback from Alan Pine,
Alan's from Paris, and he has a very cool podcast.
Well, I'll let him explain exactly what it is and where you can find it.
Hey Adam, this is Alan Pine calling from Paris and France.
I just wanted to let you know about a great site called truthout.org.
And in particular, there are nightly truthout overview, MP3 bulletin,
which is presented by William Rivers Pit.
It's basically a five to six minute news,
style bulletin of credible journalistic coverage of the US
and US foreign policy, the political situation, et cetera, et cetera.
The only downside is that at the moment,
they don't have any RSS feed, nor any enclosures.
So what I've done in the meantime is to handle the feed,
and pointing to their archives.
And it's available on my blog, which is at
Perso.1ado.fr-72% water.
That's P-R-S-O-Person.1ado.fr-72% water.
Hope this is useful for you.
Keep up the great work, your seven-dave, and
Viva La Revolucione.
Take care, bye.
Right home, Viva La Revolucione!
I love it, thank you very much, Alan,
and I have subscribed to the show,
and I got to say it is very good.
I wonder if this actually airs anywhere.
It sounds very much like a podcast.
It's very well written and well read,
but it doesn't sound like it's,
it doesn't have quite that professional radio quality.
So please let us know exactly what,
where this is being broadcast or,
is it always at web only?
And since you already publicly announced it
in the feedback, I will place a link
to the podcast feed for truth out.
It's definitely some good stuff.
Okay, another trailer, this is a funny trailer,
about the weird speech that our current president
often produces.
Also included in this at the end,
is an entire song by the George W. Burst Singers.
Ladies and gentlemen, I present for you
on the source code, Bushisms.
Africa is a nation of suffers from incredible disease.
Yeah, I think it might have been better to say
that there are a lot of people in Africa
who suffer from terrible diseases,
as opposed to making it sound like
the whole continent.
She's got to be cut off and sunk.
I think war is a dangerous place.
War, what is it good for?
A three day weekend.
It'll take time to restore chaos.
I think that they brought chaos to Iraq promptly,
and he thought it would be a challenge in fact
that proved to be very simple.
I kept you imagine something like
someone been more than ever saying
the George W. Burst Singers.
We're knowing the simple pleasure
finding an egg on Easter Sunday.
Oh, someone been law night filled the same way.
He misses out on Hanukkah,
Yom Kippur,
Russia-China,
and the United States.
He misses out on Hanukkah,
the John Kippur,
Russia-China.
He just doesn't appreciate the joy
of the George Holidays.
I can't imagine Osama in
Joing Spring Break.
It can come.
It's almost like this Osama
bin Laden, Pella,
is from somewhere else,
from some other culture.
It's weird.
And interact.
We entered the rule of one of
the worst tyrants.
And in so doing,
we'd not only freed the American people,
we made our own people more secure.
And there's no doubt in my mind.
Not one doubt in my mind
that we will fail.
No!
Most people are very unsure about
failure.
Is that who we want as president?
No, we don't.
We want someone absolutely positive
that we're going to fail.
That's leadership.
Ladies and gentlemen,
once again,
the George W. Bush Singers.
Woohoo!
And so,
am I straight of them?
My state of the Union.
My State of the Union
Our State of my State,
Master their name.
My State to Knock.
Nice.
We want to go in.
You want to call it.
Speech.
Speech, pleasure.
To the.
The.
Action.
I asked the Americans.
I asked to give.
I'm married to give.
For a thousand years.
For a thousand hours.
For.
Thousand.
I was.
Over the next.
The rest you're.
Of your life.
Of service to a mercy.
Of.
There we go.
Tonight.
That's.
Two.
Four thousand hours.
Oh man.
The bush.
The.
Bushism dot net is where you can find more on that.
It's just silly.
But you.
You should really see the video of the George W. Bush.
Singers is just so hokey.
It's.
It's awesome.
Oh, by the way.
And when I was listening to another podcast and actually played it on the source code the other day.
I could hear from the other podcast.
I could hear the volume control on the Mac here.
If I turn my volume up on my headphones.
Let me see.
I don't know.
Of course, it's not going to do that for me.
You just give a little blip.
If you're using a Mac or power book.
Then you can hold down the shift key.
And then turn up the volume.
I would probably on a desktop Mac as well.
You.
That blipping noise.
That aside.
I had one more video to play for you about the draft.
But yeah, I like the George W. Bush singer so much.
I'm going to skip it because I'm just depressed.
Look.
I think you should vote for John Kerry.
George Bush is in the.
Kuhuts with a whole bunch of guys who got a whole lot of agendas.
The only way we can make sure that.
There's a clean slate that we've got something to work with.
If we get them out, get a new guy in and keep sharp, sharp look out for what's happening.
And let's not this happen to us again.
We've got all the tools.
We've got our voices.
We've got our web logs.
The time from weblog to CNN is Dave would say is getting shorter.
It's dropped down to hours.
So we do have the power.
And I believe that.
That we should elect John Kerry as our next president.
Okay.
So no, let's not talk about that anymore.
Let's talk about some cool stuff.
I was talking to Dave on trade secrets the other day.
I think it was on trade secrets.
Maybe it was just.
It all runs together.
I don't know who I told what anymore.
We were talking about William Shattner.
And I said, you know, William Shattner actually is.
You know, he's got his stuff together.
He's got a he's got a web log.
There's daughter maintains.
Oh, we were talking about.
The Peter sellers.
I played Peter sellers did a Beatles song.
She loves you.
And he said, didn't Bill Shattner do that.
So he did loosing the sky with diamonds.
So we were talking about the musical career of Bill Shattner.
I had no idea why.
And it turns out loan below loan behold.
He is just released a new album.
It's titled William Shattner has been.
And it's got photos, news, videos, press appearances.
Got all kinds of stuff.
It's a DVD to go with it.
But the album, check this out.
It includes guest appearances by Joe Jackson, lemon jelly,
Amy Mann, Henry Rollins, and Brad Paisley.
And he's got a couple samples on his website promoting this.
Shattner has been.com.
And I would love to play a little bit of it for you.
Okay, I'm going to play.
You have time.
And I'm playing this from the flash interface and the browser.
So who knows what can happen.
I'll be a bit of an experiment.
Here it comes.
Now.
Maybe you won't suffer.
Maybe it's quick.
But you'll have time to think.
Why did I waste it?
Why didn't I taste it?
You'll have time.
Because you're...
Gonna die.
Yes, it's gonna happen because it's happened to a lot of people I know.
My mother, my father, my loves.
The president, the kings of the pope.
They all had a hole.
And they muttered just before they went.
Maybe I won't go.
Live life like you're gonna die.
Because you are.
Maybe you won't suffer.
Maybe it's quick.
But you'll have time to think.
Why did I waste it?
Why didn't I taste it?
You'll have time.
Because you're...
Gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
I tell you else left us.
Best I've gone to heaven along the rules.
Johnny Cash!
Yeah!
JFK, that guy in the stones.
Luke Garic, Einstein, and...
Joey Ramon.
Johnny Ramon.
Have I convinced you that you're replying lips?
This may come as news, but it's time.
Okay.
So unfortunately, that's all there is.
It's all in China.
Let me...
Well...
Stop that.
It goes into the interview.
Wise words for a man in his 70s,
who's been around and seems to be enjoying life every single day.
You'll have time.
Bill Shattner from his album has been...
Can't wait to get my hands on a copy to play the fool song for.
Yeah.
Just a word or two about some new podcast feeds that are really exciting.
I told you before that I've been working with Tony Khan of...
WGBH embossed in public radio.
And he is the writer and producer of a show called Morning Stories.
And there's short stories.
They're read by a normal people who he coaches through the whole process.
He produces these wonderful, you know, two to three minute stories.
I've played some of them here on the source code.
And he finally...
He got it done.
Somehow he got MPR to, you know, to figure out all the rights issues.
And they've put up a feed, a podcast feed.
You can find it in the directory under public radio.
And I think this is just the start of many more MPR shows to come to...
to a podcast thing.
And we welcome them all, of course.
And I'm very excited about it.
Also, KOMO news from Seattle, KOMO 1000, I think it is.
They have also put up a podcast feed.
I've got this delay again.
It sounds like it got the rubber ball back.
One of those red, what rubber balls, you know,
the one with the leather strap that goes around at the back of your head like the GIMP.
Okay.
So KOMO 1000 news is doing it exactly the way I think it should be done.
They produce these, you know, little news bulletins.
These 40 to 40 is a 60 second news stories.
Which is fun, you know, because now for the first time I play this,
I can actually see how long these stories are.
And I'll get like three or four one after another.
And they sit there in the playlist.
And the reason that it's so cool that each individual podcast is a news story.
If you don't like the topic of the story, just hit the next button, boom,
you're on into the next story.
So it's fantastic and so happy that they're supporting podcasting this way.
Again, also one I think of many still to come.
And of course in the past couple of days,
there's once again been many different opinions about just what podcasting is
and what it's worth.
And well, I want to share some of that with you.
I wish to do some podcasting.
No, you cannot afford to.
Why not?
Oh, you have me in.
When does 95?
No, I'm podcasting.
What?
The term itself is bullshit.
Oh, fantastic.
And it's funny how you can see the game of telephone working with these podcasts.
I heard a podcast from who was at Northwest noise.
I think it was.
And he was referring to my podcast from the car where I said,
you know, I really love my A8, my Audi OA8.
It's got everything I need, all the technical bits,
but it's kind of boring and unsexy.
And he was talking about me saying that, you know,
I wasn't too hot on the car.
I was like, no, no, no, no, don't get me wrong.
So the history of podcasting also is,
you know, it gets its twist here and there.
And of course, you can leave it up to Raster Web Audio,
our buddy Pete to bring you the complete
and correct history of podcasting.
Welcome to Raster Web Audio,
441008.
Raster Web Audio is proud to bring you this audio biography,
the history of podcasting.
Adam Carey was born in New York, New Jersey,
the younger brother of Jim Carey.
Adam always had an interest in the law and lawyoring,
but soon found himself involved with pirates
who would steal transistoradios from Dr. Cyril's medical office,
and sell them on e-bates,
the lives of David Winner,
a man obsessed with digging and digging and still digging.
Soon Adam met up with another Dave,
Dave Slushie, the founder of 711,
and together they came up with a way to make
a video images of Tim Conway,
appear on your giant flat screen TV,
even if you lived in Conroy, South Dakota,
or anywhere a hurricane was likely to hit.
Later, Adam and Dave teamed up with the Gilmour Girls
and tried something called poo casting,
but found that the audience for people who wanted poo
auto-magically delivered to their front porch morning
with extremely small,
even among people who listened to NPR,
or were on NPR,
or used to have a radio show,
or even if they lived in Conroy, South Dakota.
Eventually pod casting was invented,
and we had a way to deliver iPods
to every boy and girl in the New Zealand.
But the only problem was that all of the files
on the iPods were stolen from Steve Gapes,
the creator of Microsoftware,
and this made him mad,
so a guy named Stephen Jobs kicked his ass quite hard,
and the flow of free iPods continued.
And that's how pod casting came to be,
and the fact that you're listening to this right now,
is proof that it works.
This has been audio biography.
Thank you, and good night.
Just had great visions of poo casting
with the Gilmour Girls.
Excellent.
Another podcast that popped up
is a professional radio feed from CBC,
Canada, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation,
which operates very much like a pod cast.
People can contribute to CBC,
the listeners do actively contribute,
and a story showed up on CBC,
and of course it was copied over to their pod cast,
all about pod casting.
This is much less humorous,
but very well put together,
and I think just an excellent overview of pod casting.
In a coffee shop in Charlotte Town,
Stephen Garrity is sitting down with a friend,
a cup of lemonade tea,
and a laptop computer,
a few key strokes later,
and he's on the air.
Live from the poor most of the time.
We're back to the poor most of the time.
This is Stephen Garrity here I'm here with.
This is the new face of radio,
at least if people like Garrity have their way.
It's called pod casting.
It works like this.
Ordinary people record their own show of sorts
into their computer,
then they post that show online
for others to download and listen to.
But don't expect high production values yet.
This is a trend just emerging.
Garrity show is interrupted by commercials.
It's interrupted by the waiter.
Interesting, in five or five.
Thank you.
Indeed, most pod cast shows so far sound,
a little bit campy.
Hi, welcome to the Don and Drew Show.
I'm Don and Sally.
Take this example.
Broadcast from Wayne was constant.
And it's cold.
It's very cold.
We started fire today.
Yeah.
Well, like on the wood in the wood burner.
In the wood burner.
So Drew starts opening up with what you're wearing.
Okay, I'm wearing some hammy downhill figurines.
But others sound downright professional.
From the Silicon Valley,
Dan Finsett and the rest of California.
I'm Eric Grace.
And this is my show.
This guy created a show by literally wandering around
a technology conference with his laptop
and doing impromptu interviews with industry
potted tea bumped into.
I'm sending her with Sam Tesla who started.
And this is very deja vu,
especially for those of you familiar with the Apple
Store user group.
You started a user group.
Podcasting is evolving out of the blog trend.
Short for web blog.
Sort of an online diary.
And like the beginnings of the blogging trend.
Today's podcastures are mostly extreme computer users.
The early adopters for whom the word nerd is a badge of honor.
But increasingly, their content is going mainstream.
Well, good afternoon, friends, family, world leaders.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code for Wednesday October.
This guy Adam Curry used to be a VJMTV.
Now, he produces a daily podcast out of his castle in the Netherlands.
Actually, we got a lot of cool things lined up for today's show.
I've got a couple of songs to play for you.
Lots of examples of new podcasts.
One of the reasons podcasting is taking off is the way it's distributed.
Listeners can download the show and play it on their computer,
but there's an easier way.
Using special software,
listeners who own iPods, those portable music devices from Apple,
can have their iPod automatically store the latest episode of their favorite show.
It's sort of like a VCR that takes your favorite programs overnight while you sleep.
Except in this case, it's taping radio shows.
For now, if you want to catch a podcast, you'll have to hunt around.
The main website that lists available shows, podcaster.net,
only has about 35 shows listed.
But that number is growing daily.
As more people become self-made talk show hosts.
And that is getting some radio executives nervous.
Think about it.
With enough of an audience of iPod listeners,
it's entirely possible some of the better podcasters could actually attract advertisers.
Advertisers who want to reach tech savvy and niche market listeners.
In that scenario, radio stations, as we traditionally know them,
would become irrelevant.
Who needs to tune to a particular station,
or even bookmark a specific website.
If every morning, your listening device is already filtered out the shows you don't like,
and left the few you do.
You might argue it's already happening to television,
where fewer viewers stick with a single channel through a whole evening,
but rather pick and choose based on the show brand.
Either way, today's podcasters are onto something,
with that they realize it or not.
Can I internet for a CDC radio?
I'm Todd Maffin.
Excellent piece, absolutely phenomenal.
And actually, I'm considering adding that to the default feed
that iPoders are now using.
You know, you have the welcome, the kind of like hello world it worked
and installed.
I'm considering adding that one.
It's not too big in file size,
and I think it'll be just cool if that all sudden started playing.
You'd really get a good idea of what's already out there.
It mentions iPodor.net, which they have more than 35 feeds now.
They have about 64 feeds.
I'm considering asking those guys if they would like to become a node
of the directory of iPodor.org,
they have some different, they travel in different circles.
So let's connect this together.
Let's make this as big as possible.
Okay, so you've set through all of that.
It's about 48 minutes into your hour that we're here on the source code.
Gonna play you a song that'll pick up your spirits for a Monday.
It's Grand Funk Railroad.
I don't need a whole lots of money.
I don't need a big fine car.
I got everything that I made before.
I got more than I could ask for.
I don't have to burn around.
I don't have to stay out all night.
Cause I got me a sweet, a sweet living woman.
Cause you know just how to treat me right.
But my baby, she's all right.
But my baby, she's clean outside.
Don't you know that she's just some kind of wonderful.
She's some kind of wonderful, yes she is.
She's some kind of wonderful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
When I hold all in my arm, you know she sets my soul on fire.
Ooh, when the baby kisses me.
My heart becomes still with desire.
When she raps the Lord and all around me.
About to rise me out of my mind.
Yeah, I'll give my baby kiss to me.
She's been up and down my spine.
My baby, she's all right.
But my baby, she's clean outside.
Don't you know that she's just some kind of wonderful.
She's some kind of wonderful, yes she is.
She's some kind of wonderful, yes, yes, yes.
That is the end of my day.
Got a sweet little woman like mine.
It got to be somebody.
Yeah, I can't I can't I can't I'm with you.
Can I can I'm with you?
I can't I can't I'm with you.
Get again, done.
Yeah, I can't I can't you.
Yeah, I can't I can't I can't you.
The world of all talking about my baby.
She's so kind of wonderful,
author, you know how that baby of each moment.
She's so kind of wonderful, Tonking about my baby.
She's so kind of wonderful, tonking about the baby.
She's so kind and I wonder,
I'm talking about my baby, I'm saying that I'm playing around.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Grandfog Railroad, some kind of wonderful, on the source code.
My name's Adam Curry.
The show came to you from the bunker, the canal house in Amsterdam.
Looking forward to another show tomorrow.
Keep all the good stuff coming, all the bits, all the short clips.
Everything you find, send it to me, I love it, point me to URLs, whatever.
Just about anything that can play audio, I can record.
So, love to see more of that.
Keep the podcasts coming as well.
I'm subscribed to just about everything that comes in.
I've unsubscribe from a few, just because, well, you know what,
the big problem, the reason why is because hard drive size.
Looks like we're finally in an industry where size really does matter.
And that'll be it for me for today.
Have you ever heard of this show?
As always, comments are welcome through my email at amercurry.com
or through my weblogger to post a comment on live.curry.com.
And all the archives of the show and the podcast RSS feed are available at dailysourcecode.com.
Hey, I'm going to have lunch. I'm out of here. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.