Before we get started, let me remind you of the following results or events predicted in these things,
the name of our materialism, from actual results.
The factors that could cause actual events results to differ from expectations include
lack of growth, intense competition in our industry,
integration failures, changes in government regulations,
operational failures, or looking to take them from success.
Alright, some of the volumes of today should not be relied upon as representing our
future. While we may delight something more than we say, it's a complete future.
We need to not give it so even for us to change.
Augustine, all's life, and a curry.
Power of glory to all of us.
Hi everybody and welcome to your daily source code. It is Monday. It is November 1, 2004.
Bunny Bunny, or is it rabbit rabbit? I'm just supposed to say that at the start of each new month,
and then money and good fortune will come your way. Let it be yours, my friends.
Once again, welcome to source code.
Got a lot of good stuff lined up on the show today and I got to talk about this new production
system that I'm using. I feel so incredibly organized. I could actually almost do my nails
while recording the podcast today. Some tunes and of course some politically oriented
stuff because we are just about a day away from the elections. And we'll be looking at both sides
and we'll be letting Republicans speak on the show as well. Yeah, new concepts.
I'm not going to show a long one. I'm going to run but I don't know if we're going to make it
40 minutes man, there's too much to do. So I'm coming to you today from Flanders, Belgium,
from Curie Castle where there is less and less of our stuff to be found. It's all packed away in boxes.
Today our brand new bed, I just decided we needed a new bed, didn't really like the one we had here,
in Belgium. We just got a shitty bed and kind of lived with it. A good bed still an Amsterdam.
So we bought a new bed and they brought it over. We can't sleep on it right now because it's
going to be moved to the house in the UK. And man, that's what is that? It's only a little under
two and a half weeks away. Oops, hold on. I forgot to silence the old telephone there during
the show. So for the next 45 minutes you are in mind here on the daily source code as I said
some political stuff here as well. Might as well kick it off with the tune from the billionaires for
Bush. They say, you know what? Don't bother, don't vote. And now an important election day announcement
from the billionaires for Bush. I keep flashing back on why it's okay. When the billionaires
took your voting rights away, you can think that the felons got personal lift. A lot of innocent
people's names were dismissed. We said our road blocked on Baton November day, it caused full
of black people got turned away. So many felons were tossed out in the back of a dipwood or a hanging
chat. Down in Florida we struck a mortar blow. Cause George's brother James was running the show
and the Secretary of State who inflicted the fame was the chair of the Florida Bush campaign. And
a commentator recorded for George E. B. Was his cousin who been working for Fox TV. A new election
day this coming that was kind of wedding. If the billionaires keep you forgetting, maybe it's
got a better place to be. You can stay at home and watch TV. You can be kicking it with your crew.
Just let the billionaires choose for you.
We found a better way to make it in the same clean. We put it electronic voting machine
and then we sold these suckers nationwide. But with the only ones who know what's on the inside,
you push the buttons and a voting machine keeps track. You made it so was very easy to hack.
Quite for a recap of what probably felt when machines don't leave no hate to travel.
The billionaires don't want you to vote this year but send your message that's loud and clear
that the votes can't be counted in your community. Why revenge to don't waste your energy?
Don't go to the polls on election day because we bought the election in the federal
girl all the way. And on election night we'll sit back and go. The billionaires don't want you to vote.
If you're happy with George Bush in charge, if you want to keep us living long. Do you really
want to rock the boat? Hey, the billionaires don't want you to vote. When other countries go and
have an election day, people walk across mountains that have their stay. What in life are days
until the vote begins? They sit and watch the votes are counted. They see who wins.
Here in America we put obstacles in your way. Really hoping you stay home on election day.
If you're all voting each one of you just off and wet, there'd be a very different government.
If you really want to fight in the world, if you like the way we're treating the poor,
if you don't care about education, keep the billionaires controlling the nation.
If you want to help you see, no. If you like the way the money flow, do you really want to rock the boat?
Hey, the billionaires don't want you to vote. Billionaires, for Bush, don't vote on your daily
source code. I don't know where that came from. I supposed to pick that up on the blog digger feed,
but it's been floating out there. I'm seeing more and more of this, these surprises pop along,
that's just like the John Stewart interview on Crossfire on CNN. You didn't really have to
subscribe to any particular feed to receive that digger. That popped up just about everybody everywhere.
I've got some more John Stewart on the way today on the show on the source code.
The weekend was a little bit messed up. No Gilmore gang. You know, my weekend just doesn't feel
right. If I don't have a Gilmore gang to listen to on Saturday or Sunday. And as I've said before,
you know, when I don't get a Gilmore gang, I used to go and immediately start debugging my iPod or
scripts. Now I know better and I know to go and check out the IT Conversations.com website. So
nothing there unfortunately. I did just see just before I started the show. I see that the behind
the mic series with Dave Weiner came out. So I can't wait to listen to that. I'll have comments and
hopefully some expert excerpts from that tomorrow on the show. And during the The Billionaires
for Bush clip that I played, like everyone that I wanted to talk to today started calling,
so I've just put the phone on silent and have to make the calls when I get back or when I've
done and I'm back on the phones. See, I was also talking to Dave Weiner. He also has a real problem
with the Gilmore gang not showing up. And I said, wait, this is a big part of what differentiates
a audio blog post from a podcast. You know, podcast, you're making a commitment. You're saying
to your audience and even if that's one person or if that's, you know, 10,000 people or 100,000
doesn't matter, you're making a commitment that you're going to do something. And people will
become dependent upon that. So if you want to do a podcast and you're going to have to pretty
much, you know, make the effort to have something up every single time, you know, that it's
supposed to be up. So if it's a Friday show, like the Gilmore gang, you know, even if it's just a
one minute piece of audio, the show that my aggregator kicks in, you know, my iPod or picks it up
and I can hear, you know, hey guys, sorry, you know, Gilmore gang today. In lieu of that, here's
his one, you know, from the archives. Here's the best of. And so I've been coaching Dave a bit
because he's been basically doing audio blog posts and I said, you know, one chip really
call it a podcast and let's work on a tune and get some stuff going. And when I'm out in
in San Francisco, I want to help him set up some software and show him how I do these things
live and on the fly because it's a lot easier to do him live than it is to go back and edit
stuff in, which I know a lot of people are doing. They will make that a part of the session at
blogger con. So looking forward to the more coffee notes more regularly, we love being regular with
morning coffee notes. Stroke in time. Yes, a message from Todd. Listen to this.
Hey, they're Adam. This is Todd. I just wanted to drop a note and say how great the interplay
between your show and the Don and Drew show has been. In fact, I can't really think of any
other shows or mediums where we get this kind of interplay or I might be kind of unique to podcasting
at the moment. At any rate, you guys are amazing. I don't know what I do without your
wit and cynicism every day. I keep up the great, great work. Wait, listen.
Yeah, Todd, got one back for you, buddy. Here it comes. I've been receiving so many
boring sounds from so many people is just awesome. And what do you think of that new opener, huh?
Of the show? I found a new podcast, the earningscast at earningscast.com and that was actually
a part of, I think, the double click disclaimer that you have to do in front of every earnings conference
call forward looking statements, et cetera. I just kind of messed around with it and garage band
and mixed in some music and cutting my opening sweeper and the rock money off power of pure
intellect stuff. But the Buying's, man, that's just been too many of them. They had them.
I still rise to Bill Rice.org. I just wanted to give a quick shout and make a request. I'm sure
several of your faithful listeners like the self-reface and the lengthy flight of the water
time. I wonder if the youth through the daily source code or maybe you and Dave through trade
seekers could give us a special travel addition to these programs. Help us pass the time and maybe
we could even pass it along to others as we evangelize along our pillar of the doubt to
the call. I also wanted to quickly express my concern, prayers and hope to your mother and your
family. It sounds like things are progressing positively and I hope that I continue blessing.
And finally, I know your mantra has been what programmers and users parted together but I thought
to consider an important part on the immediately after the president's election. It might also
be appropriate to consider the possibility that maybe celebrating conservative,
so-called liberals do also part together. Anyway, thanks for all the great things. We're doing
as a blog at Podcasts and Space. I look forward to meeting you and blog at Podcasts on my friend.
All right, Bill. Thank you very much, man. And I agree. And as you'll hear later on in this podcast,
Republicans and Democrats definitely can party together and we've been partying together without
really even knowing it or maybe only half of us were knowing it but the party still continues.
That is what makes America great for sure. Now, you were talking about a blogger con
trample edition, something that's a little bit longer. I wouldn't mind that myself. I'm stalking
up now on podcast and forcing myself not to listen because I sit on a plane for about 14 hours
from Amsterdam to San Francisco. So, you know, well, shit, my iPod won't even last that long but,
yeah, we'll give it, maybe I'll keep the volume down low and I won't use the buttons too much.
Maybe I can eat out 10 hours of listening pleasure. There's something you might want to take
along though and I, they put a link to this on scripting news is the piece that Australian
Broadcast Corporation did about podcasting. It's a very detailed piece, so I liked it a lot.
I basically hijacked the real stream and created an MP3 of it and so that again, that's linked
today. I think we're maybe from yesterday on scripting.com. Just a couple pieces I wanted to play
from this because it was so detailed and what I liked the most is they had a lot of radio industry
executives talking about what iPods and MP3 players and ultimately also podcasting will mean to their
business and, you know, how it's snuck up on them. Can you outside and going, what could we do here
to protect radio? I may be even grow out of it so we can either work a little less or for the
same amount of effort keep even more radio listening. Nick Pete.
You have all your favorite music living happily together in one place. Introducing the Apple iPod
from HP. Your PC will never be the same again. HP. In that. Downloading audio from the internet,
copying it to CDs, the rip and burn mentality has been around for a few years. What's really
new is podcasting. Adam Curry, internet millionaire and one of the first DJs of the music TV
station. Oh, man. Internet millionaire. Right. MTV has taken it up fast. Hi, I'm Adam Curry.
Welcome to the iPod platform. I didn't want you to hear that. That's the first piece of the
download feed. I should have prep this better. I'm sorry. Early this year,
Carrie wanted to find a way. I want to look for them. I'm looking for the guy who says that they're
really worried in the industry. Here it is. Our phone is expensive and as the audio downloading
and podcasting is easy and cheap, advertisers and commercial broadcasters are worried about loss
of revenue. And of course, heavyweight industry groups like the Recording Industry Association
have a thing or two to say as well. Adam Curry. The reason why I can absolutely survive is
nobody owns this. I was very specific in making iPod or org it's home. Nobody owns the way that
this stuff is traveling. I think we'll have much less of a fight with the RIA as people, of course,
we're going to start distributing music this way, whether in mixed form or radio form, but this
is going to be some issues there. I don't think anywhere near as big as what the NAB, the National
Association of Broadcasters could do if they totally misunderstand the result of putting these
technological bits together. Most people, particularly broadcasters, understand that there is now
a new antenna. There's a new channel. You can broadcast down and we don't know what the limits
of it are yet. So far, we haven't hit any major walls. And one of the reasons it hasn't hit major walls
is that it's relatively easy and cheap to have a little radio studio in your closet, record the
audio and distribute it over the internet. We really have two important things. I want to listen
to that guy a little bit. I wrote down the time codes. Maybe something should be done in the
team. I never seem to sleep. They're tinkering away with computer code.
There's this podcast being people who are here today. They never seem to sleep. They're
tinkering away with computer codes, playing around with the new technology and they
organize blogger conferences, like blogger con, which is on a day. And you don't have to be there
because all the proceedings will be podcast. I believe this will be the first conference where
podcasting is going to be up front and center. Yeah. Okay. Well, somewhere in this piece and it's about
15 minutes long. I'm not going to look for it anymore. I don't understand why how I lost that.
There's a piece about a radio executive saying, we were too busy paying attention to kicking
the others guy. The other guys asked on the FM frequencies and all these iPod and MP3 players and
people doing stuff with them kind of snuck up on us. I think what happened is I wrote down the
time codes when it was an AIFF and probably when I compressed it down to an MP3 something went wrong.
Let's just see because I wrote down a very specific time code where they were talking about
about John Stuart. Let's see if I can find this reactionary talk. Well, I thought you were going to be funny. Come on.
He thought, no, I'm not going to be your monkey. What? What? Within minutes, perhaps seconds of the
show being broadcast, it was copied, distributed and downloaded via the web. You could watch the
video on your computer. Cliffs of the audio were inserted into podcasts and re broadcast.
More people got it via the web than watched on television. No one asked CNN for permission to
re broadcast. The point is we got it out there and the traditional media in this case Australian
broadcast corporation noticed that we got it out there and we got it out there fast and that was
blogging. That was just blogs passing this around and along with that some podcasters wrote
on that and we're getting pretty powerful here. I wanted to make a bridge between
that bit about John Stuart and an appearance that John did made on C-SPAN, which I was also sent
a number of pointers to. First of all, in this and this is about an hour, it's a bit more than
an hour's worth of show. The quality is pretty low. I'm just going to play a little bit about it because
this was actually recorded or broadcast before the CNN crossfire interview. It's interesting
the language that John Stuart uses is I don't know how that works, how that can air on C-SPAN.
He said mother fucker and shit and fuck a couple of times and act, you know, I didn't really notice
it because I'm so used to podcast and it didn't phase me at all. But I was like, whoa, you know,
hold on a second. How does that work? How come the FCC allows that to happen on C-SPAN
and yet stops so much more, you know, Janet Jackson's nipple for instance. So anyway,
since everyone enjoyed that piece of John Stuart so much on crossfire, here's a little bit more
of the source code to his thoughts as he talks about this interview recently on C-SPAN.
You know, you should have done at that point, you said,
did he allow you to bring up no vacuuming? No, it's not a good good.
My editor said, don't trade jokes. I'm not sure. But your chapter is called the
Microsy's valiant Voguearians about the press. That is correct. What do you mean?
Voguearians? I mean that the lowering of the discourse is done with tenacity.
The press has bravely and nobly eroded the public trust. And I celebrate that.
You, you also said, I Charlie Rose recently. It's the wrong room for this, by the way.
No, it's great. I've done this at a union meeting.
C-SPAN 11. All right. You told Charlie Rose about politicians who you said,
seek above all else to retain power, quote, when you go to a zoo and see a monkey throwing poop,
you go, that's what monkeys do. What are you going to do? But then you went on to say,
what I wish the media would do more frequently is say, bad monkey. It's a brilliant metaphor.
What I meant to say was when you see a monkey masturbating at the zoo.
Listen, the room is dark and he's looking at you and it's very comfortable and you throw out
the monkey metaphor. You know, they're not all gems, can? I'm riffing, baby. I'm spritzing.
I'm working the room and it's dark and he loads you into sleeping thing and you've been
listening to the minister of Singapore for half hour and you know, you get out there and you don't
know where you are. Shit happens. What would happen if Hitler were interviewed by Larry King? What?
More coffee? Let me go back to the bad monkeys.
The gist. The essence to distill that is that we require what I'm advocating is that the
media come work for us again, that that remove themselves from the symbiotic relationship that they
have developed with the power structures of corporations and of the politics. And
we as Americans can we shall fight? Never give in. I'm sorry. I don't know what happened there.
No, it is all together too comfortable. We're busy in the world. We have things to do.
And the corporate mentality and the political mentality is to create layers of
obfuscation that make it difficult to penetrate what's going on. And the print media, by the way,
is very different. Most of what I'm talking about is television. And the print media is much better
providing context, but you're providing it a week later and by then everybody's moved on.
I mean, that's the sad truth about it. It's the world moves much more quickly now. And
the real responsibility now lies where the people set the agenda. And the agenda is set on the
24-hour networks. And unless you're keeping up with them and unless they are held to a certain
level of accountability, that's where the death is lost. Let me just say with that John last night
in the debate, you wish the media had said, what about the monkeys?
Well, again, it's not about a process. It's not about a moment. And so it's not about one debate
and it's not about one issue. It's about holding to account this idea that debate is to advocates
for two corrupt organizations that to have a democratic strategist and a Republican strategist
is not a debate that's Coke and Pepsi discussing beverage supremacy. And it's not, it's not real
and just suggests that it is what I'm suggesting is that the person mediating that has to have
some expertise and has to have a job and their job can't be, what do you think Donna Brazil?
Okay, what do you think babe, you can and we'll be right back. That's not a job. That's doing nothing.
And it's allowing two people to dominate a debate that are strategists and understand
the television press is getting their asses kicked and they're doing it willingly. And that's the
thing that I think is so frustrating to watch at home because they have a role and they have a job
and they're not doing it and that drives you insane when you watch. Go back to my, I should
end it with a joke. We'll give you another opportunity, thank you. Larry King, you're right about
so that's John Stewart on C-Spat. I like it when he gets really serious and even said that I should
have ended with a joke. I don't think so. I thought I think it was really right on the money. Perfect.
And I've spoken about this before, but I have a request in for an interview with John Stewart.
His people know about it and it's obvious that podcasting still won't
take the forefront when it comes to elections. So it won't have a chance to talk to John
until after the elections. But then again, it may be just as important and just as exciting
depending on how the elections go. You're listening to the Daily Source Code today is the first
of November, 2004 time for the tap dancing podcast or news.
What's most with cameras to form a documentary crew? A guy trying to stab his girlfriend
for voting for Terry? Another guy ran down Florida's former secretary. The red socks won the first
world series. It's not much less than a hundred years. But the headlines didn't waste much
space on theories. Drugs replaced the website with new terrorists fears. Now Gibson called Arnold's
a neighbor to say he won't support public funding for stem cell research. He said Arnold
couldn't be short, but Arnold claims he called no right. Not to attack. Or even to brag.
Mills, we saw well though we'd be moments with mental neck. Stay tuned for late breaking.
Okay. That's the tap dancing podcast for news. I love that. Tap dance and podcast
news, which comes through on the openpodcast.org feed. This is number 65 on the open podcast.org
RSS feed. I figured out who this is and I sent her an email hoping that we could get her set up
with her own feed because I'd like to subscribe to that separately. And I'd also like to point
to because I think that's this is perfect. That's one minute 15 seconds of pure joy. Great
creativity. A longer comment now. I want to say longer. I'm talking more than five minutes. But
well worth listening to Ken Gans from Louisville, Kentucky. He starts off talking a little bit about
podcasting. But kind of halfway through the conversation it turns a little bit. But not bad. Interesting.
I want you to listen. I think you'll enjoy this. Hello there. Adam Curry. My name is Ken Gans.
And I live in Louisville, Kentucky. I've been the avid podcaster actually a receiver of podcast
for about the last three weeks. Guess I got started just about the time this whole technology was
just starting to break loose. And I have to admit I'm addicted to the daily source code
and also the trade secrets podcast. So I guess for that, do you get a hearty
boi? If you prefer the more machine-based boi around we have. I love that.
Well anyway, I never recorded anything on my Mac before. So I bought a microphone today and then
little did I know I also needed a preamp because I couldn't hear a thing when I hooked a mic up.
But I got this goofy radio shack mic and I'd be curious to hear what other people are using.
Especially I'm curious what you use because it sounds very good. Yeah, let me tell you.
First of all, I love radio shack. Radio shack rules. It is the store that bloggers
survive on. I have a couple radio shack mics. I like them very much. What I'm using is a wireless
set and it's made by... where these guys. Electrosonics, LEC, TROS, O and ICS, Electrosonics.
This is a really expensive set. This is a main of because it's a professional television
wireless microphone. But you might be able to use a little bit of filtering because it sounds
just a little bit muddled, but not bad. I support radio shack especially for their microphones.
What you want to get is you want to get the metal one that looks just like a sure. There's
something like 39 bucks and really those those will work fine. But this one sounds pretty good.
And I've seen to remember you mentioned that it was like a clip on mic. So I'd like to find out
what that is. You know, we've got a couple things in gallon and then there's a couple things that
are just total opposites. I'm a Jersey boy. Born in Jersey grew up there. I spent 20
some of my years there before I struck out of my own. I'm an aircraft mechanic and a pilot.
Though I'm not a current pilot. I haven't flown a long time. But I do have that love of aviation.
And of course, I'm also a computer geek. No training in that field. I just seem to have that
extra chromosome that allows people to understand unix and shell scripts and stuff like that.
On a little more serious note, I remember listening to the daily source code when you told
everyone about your mom's condition. And I've ever since that day I've prayed for each day
a junior family. When I was three years old, my dad died of lung cancer. That was back in 1962.
And then just five years later, my mom died also of lung disease. So I'm very familiar with
how those things work and they were both heavy smokers and probably living in the old garden
state wasn't helping too much either. But anyway, best of luck to your mom, best of luck to you and
your family and I hope everything goes okay. So that's the end of the love vest. Now let's get down
to some of the differences. Oh, here it goes. From time to time, I hear you and Dave Weiner talking
about someday maybe podcasting video as if that's the next step or whatever. But as a user,
that's the last thing I want to see. I think what makes podcasting great is that when you are
passively listening to it with headphones or earbuds or whatever, you can do stuff like
driving or riding a bike. I frequently listen while walking around a park and doing other kinds of
activities like that. Also, there's something kind of cool about having you and Dave right between
my ears, although from time to time it's a little scary too. It's like the shows kind of originating
right from within my own head. Now what would really be cool and what I would like. Have you ever
seen how a Griffin I trip works with iPod? You get your iPod to play these tones that Griffin has
and you plan through the iPod and the I trip interprets these sounds and tunes itself to
the certain FM radio frequencies so it can broadcast over the air to your radio so you can
connect your iPod wirelessly. The tone sound something like this. Well now that's how I want
my iPod and podcast or I don't want a video. I want the iPod interface directly to my cerebral
cortex and I want the podcast like the Griffin I trip tones. Those because video to appear directly
in my brain. That will be a cool application. I do like Dave's idea of having like a two-way
interface where the podcast center the iPod and the user can also create things. I want to
wait for the computer on the iPod to upload to the web and then go to other people's iPods as podcast.
Now I guess the last criticism that I have. There's my dog pixel. Probably isn't going to exist.
Oh, you're a dog pixel? You are a computer game dude. I'm going to respond to all the things
that Ken said by the way because I have some responses but first we got to get through his final beef.
The past two's day once the elections are done but what the heck is it with you and Dave supporting
Kerry? I cannot for the life of me understand that. I guess I know you don't live in the country so
maybe all you have to go buy is the BBC or something so you've got totally distorted view of the situation
and I know that Dave lives out there and the people's Republic and Seattle but as I mentioned
I live in Kentucky. I live in the heartland. I live in a big cluster of red states. In the heartland
you learn how to take the measure of a man. When you look at John Kerry you don't see anything worthwhile.
That guy's not fit to pick the cheese out from between George Bush's toes. Okay, hold on one second.
I got a respond to that one. When I look at John Kerry and I see him testifying in the Senate
during Vietnam right after he got out of Vietnam looking at what he went through at Vietnam
he is a man. He definitely is fit to at least pick out the cheese between George Bush's toes
which is a horrible visual Ken. What's Dave talking about a civil war?
Good freaking guy. That is so over the top. I could not believe it when he said that
in fact if there were any kind of trouble at all the only reason there would be is because
Democrats are like a bunch of spoiled little kids. Even before the election or over here shoot
up campaign headquarters, robbing campaign headquarters, assaulting Republican campaign workers
are they telling you any of that stuff on a BBC over there? Right next door here in Tennessee
they shot up Republican campaign headquarters. It's almost like you got the adults, the
Republicans running against the kids, the Democrats and they seem to exist for no other reason
than to spread fear and certainty and doubt. I think even if Bush wasn't president, they'd find
some reason just to raise hell. This is not the Democratic Party of 20 years ago. This is a bunch of
I guess what they remind me of is just spoiled little rich kids. You know, you got Jennifer Lopez
over here saying stuff like if you vote for George Bush, rape is going to be legal. I mean these
people are just so over the top is ridiculous. And I think even you mentioned that a
not letting what happened in Florida happen again, nothing happened in Florida. The only thing
to happen in Florida is you had a bunch of Democrats misdesign the ballot so that the idiots
down there can figure out how to vote straight. And then when people looked at all the votes,
you know, several independent new services, night ridder, a bunch of them looked at the
tally's months and months after the election. Well, it came up the same. Even if the election
wasn't decided in the Supreme Court, George Bush went to one. Case closed. They've been living
with this for four years like it was going to kill them if they didn't get George Bush out of the
White House. And what are they going to replace them with? I've got who when the gun gets stuff
looks for the nearest person to stick a knife in their back and twist it. He did it in 1971 and
too. And he's doing it right now to the third infantry division blaming him for some small amount
of explosives that are missing over in Iraq. I mean, the guy is just, I think Mrs. Cheney said
it best. He's not a good man. He doesn't deserve to be president. In fact, I don't even deserve
thinking he deserves to be a senator, but the good people of Massachusetts will have to fix that.
Anyway, I don't want to leave on a sour note, but can imagine how, how if you want to listen to
you and Dave talking and I'm sitting there in my car. Y'all in my head off. You guys seem like
pretty intelligent people. I don't really understand how you could be so swayed in the wrong direction
on this election. But like I said, I really enjoy your podcast. I think what you guys are working on
here is a really fantastic thing. I wish you all the best. And like I said, I'll keep your
you and your family and my prayers and I hope everything goes well with your mom. Thanks a lot
for everything. Take it easy. Yeah, that's what I like so much about the community that we have.
We can differ of opinion and boy do Dave and I differ from of opinion, from Ken Gansson, Louisville.
I wouldn't know where to start, because I just wouldn't make any sense to go into each point
individually, but I felt it was good to let the source code listeners hear. It's an equal time
from the other side. And also how we can still party together, regardless of our viewpoints.
And we clearly both love America a lot. So a couple of the things I wanted to touch on,
if there was so much in that audio comment. And I don't know if you have a podcast Ken,
but I would really look forward to subscribing to it. Let me know so I can get in the iPod or
or directory. Because it's refreshing to hear something else once the while. Even if I don't
agree with it at all. And I picked up a couple clips that I wanted to play for you as a relate
to your podcast. The first one, well, of course, is about the elections and the voting booth.
And he says in our hands, heading to my voting booth. I am the old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old
old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old, old
I vote, it makes things right
Out of my house, or rush to the bus stop
I found the way to make the worst out
It into my ethical culture
The truth, Kalello Hona Coppena
Isn't the beat for about to go down
They come every day well
I pick a wooden drop
And these big children real justice
Learn the life from the father
And my mother, big kids and chemo
I like to tell you, hold me and I'm holding you
I'm real close
I'm here in whispers
We need a peace rhythm
Oh yeah
To be right
Everyone's got love with, oh yeah
I'll be your voice
I'll be your love
Oh yeah
Hurry into my voting group
I am the end
You're not here
But like that's why I'm thinking
I'm choosing one minute to vote for her
Which makes things that I want
My vote then makes things right
It's fire, it's burning to my voting goes to the end
I am the end
Oh no, you're back
I can't hear about like that's why I'm saying
It's losing one leader to vote for you
Which be sensitive for you
My vote makes things right
Well that's right
Unfortunately, done enough metadata
Pass along with that MP3 file
Through blog digger their MP3, the blog digger media feed
To let you know who that is
All know is it's called voting booth
And there's also a karaoke version out there
But I don't know who it's by too bad
Excuse me
Going back to a little bit more of
Ken's audio comment there
He mentioned that he had a new microphone
And he's not the only one
There was another podcast that I bumped into
That also had a new microphone
We didn't have any complaints about the audio before
Aside from my own
Welcome to blogosphere news
My name is Mack and I'll do a host
We take a look at what's happening in around the blogosphere
For Friday, October 29th, 2004
Quite a few items to get to today
But first off, the big news here at blogosphere
Radio is that we got a new microphone
We didn't have any complaints about the audio before
Aside from my own dissatisfaction with the quality of our voice
But in any case, audio quality should be much better
At the very least, I'm excited to have a new toy
I love hearing that
That's blogosphere news
And they got a new microphone over there
And you can subscribe to the podcast
At blogosphereradio.com
That's BLO-G-O-S-P-H-E-R-E-R-E-R-D-O.com
And there's always some good stuff in there
There was always some nice little nougat
A tip for the microphone there
Maybe you want to try and move it away from the computer's fan
And maybe move your face in a little bit
Close to the microphone
Close to the micang is what we call that in professional terms
And that'll give you a better result
And what I've done in the past
Sometimes when either there was a wall that didn't give me
The right acoustics or if there was fan noise
You can also kind of position two couch pillows
Next to each other in a V form
That close behind the microphone
That has been known to work pretty well
So yeah, I'll be listening to the blogosphere news
And see if anything changes in the acoustics
Now here's the one thing that really blew me away
about Ken's audio comment
If you have this griffin eye trip
If you have an eye pod, you might have seen this or heard about it
The eye trip is a little plastic accessory
That plugs into the top, I'm doing it here
I'm doing it here, just to plug to the top of your eye pod
And it enables you to broadcast the signal
From your eye pod onto your car radio
Or any FM radio for that matter
I found that the signal was pretty good
And many times I'm sure if you have this
Then you've probably set it to a popular station
And turn it on and see if people around you
And traffic if they look down at the radios
If they're trying to figure out what's going on
So the way that you use this thing
Is you basically just once you start playing
It uses the headphone jack and it uses the little connector jack
It recognizes that audio is coming through
It fires up, it starts broadcasting
And it broadcasts at whatever signal you set it to
Now the way you set it is, and that's what you heard in the audio comment
Is you have to play a series, actually it's just a little MP3 file
Of a couple of short blips
And that then changes the frequency
To whatever those blips are associated with
So I'd like to try something out here
If you're on an eye trip, if you're listening
Right now, hopefully you're somewhere in traffic
Because what we're going to do is I'm going to switch all the iPods
That are using eye trip at this very moment
To 100.3 FM, which is a very popular frequency
For top 40 stations
And it should automatically change by me sending out the tones
So I'm going to send out the tones
That will program everyone's eye trip
To start broadcasting on 100.3 FM
And of course I'm going to try this myself to see if it works
I'm just presuming it does
So let's switch all those iPods to 100.3 FM
Okay everybody
Look around, look at the traffic
How you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code on 100.3 FM
Long ago in days of your
It'll begin with a god named Thor
There were bikers and boats and some plans for a furniture store
Not a bodega, it's not a mall
And this is a thankful apartment smaller
The mine is if there were a part
My smaller than mine
Ikea
Everyone has a home
If you don't have a home
You can buy one there
I ran a car, take the bus
Lay our cash down
And put your trust in the land
Where the furniture pulls you a much smaller size
Feeling the book is his hello
So does the table, his name is Ingo
And the chair is a ladder back
Where his butt is friends calling Carl
Ikea
Just a morning to find a handful of noise men
Everyone has a home
If you don't have a home
You can buy one there
Ikea
Flyward
Brush
Feel
Ikea
Meatballs
Taste
Ikea
I'll end
RENCHES
All the back free
Sorry I said Ikea
Sucks
I just bought a table for 60 bucks
And a chair
And a lamp
And a shelf
That's the candles for you
I was a doubt of just like you
Till I saw the American dream come true
In the journey
They got a goddamn Swedish parade
Ikea
Just a morning to find a handful of noise men
Everyone has a home
If you don't have a home
You can buy one there
Here's from Chester, Connecticut
His name is Jonathan Coolton
The album is smoking monkey
That's his O2 Ikea
And now that we're moving
Even we are loving the joy
That Ikea can bring
When you need that book
You just don't can't get the right size
And you don't want to chop up
Something antique
Ikea's got it all for you
I want to talk one second about this
Great new podcast production system
I'm working on
It's kind of a podcast production console
I'm using radio user land
If you've never seen this program
You can download a 30 day trial
It's a weblogging client
But it does so much more
And a lot of it is based around
It's internal scripting language
It's object oriented database
Or object database
And everything is done in outliners
And ever since
I was introduced to Frontier
Which they win or conceived
And created and built so many years
I've loved outliners
Outliners make so much sense
To the way my brain works
And I love
I've been using outliners to
To line up radio shows
And basically if you look at
That the line up of today's show
And I will post a screenshot
You'll see that everything is neatly in a row
From top to bottom
And as I go down my list
I can expand each node
And that might have an email message in there
But now it also has special nodes
And with a little music note next to it
So I know that that's an audio clip
And if you double click on it
It opens up the file
In quick time
Ready to play
So it's a great way for me to organize
All the things I need
I used to have 20 quick time windows open
And moving stuff around
And that's really expensive
For desktop real estate
Excuse me
Oh boy
So now all I have to do
Is basically when I get an MP3
I want to add I just drop it into a folder
If there's an email that I want
I forward it to a special email address
It all gets sucked into one central place
All of the MP3's been scanned
For metadata
And put into a general playlist
And then everything that's new
We put into the new playlist
So I can select from those
And because it's an outline
You can just move stuff around
If you want this part of the show to come earlier
You can move it up or you could even cut and paste
And it's really fantastic
And what's nice about it
And I haven't done that part yet
Because I'm slow but I'm getting there
Is I want to be able to just save that outline
And it should go with
The podcast for that day
It should be a part of the post
And you'll get all the metadata
That's relevant to what I played
You'll get all the links to webpages
That I reference everything I'll be in one spot
And even better than that
Because it's OPML
And we've been talking about OPML on the source code
You'll be able to hook in to different pieces of it
So we could basically have this huge
Interconnected decentralized
Podcast production suite
This network
If I hear something cool on your podcast
Is going to your podcast console
And look for that file
And I could actually bring it in
And then use that in my podcast
I mean the thoughts are just mind-boggling
But how this outline or expands
And I'm learning about something really important
And outline is called node types
So what happens when you click on a node
It can contain a link to a website
It opens up your web browser
It can contain a link to another OPML file
It can contain RSS file
It can contain an MP3
That opens up in the quick time player
It's mind-boggling
It really is
So we are going to run about an hour
Probably a little bit over
But it's well worth it because we got some more audio
Comments on the way and some bush
And carry cut-ups
And if you're feeling down
Have you been in a rut lately
Then listen to the latest podcast
From career opportunities
Anyone no matter what their age
Confine themselves in the depths of a rut
It can start out slowly
Going to the same restaurants
Using the same software
Listening to the same music
The next thing you know
There you are in a rut
As I'm finding getting older
Can make it even easier to get into a rut
There are days when I simply don't want to face
The trials and tribulations of daily life
I just want to do something familiar
Of course
A few days later
I wake up feeling bored
And not really knowing why
Even though I know the importance of finding new challenges, new passions and new input
I have to actively reach out and engage the world in order to find them
Imagine my rut-ridden joy
When I discovered something new to engage my intention this last week
Due to an odd set of circumstances
I found myself with a week without much consulting work
As I headed into the week
I was dreading it
How was I going to make productive use of this time?
In scanning my daily list of RSS feeds
Yet another way I try to find new, interesting tidbits
I came across ipotter.org
Adam Curry, a former VJ and current DJ
Put together an Apple script to automatically collect MP3 files posted to the net
Download them
And push them into iTunes
And then to the iPod
This immediately caught my attention
I don't have an iPod, but the new shows I discovered
Engaged me immediately
They also gave me a way to randomly sample new music as it came across the wire
Much that I would have never sought out on my own
Wow
Here was a whole new world opening up
With very little effort
I immediately grabbed the software and began to closely follow the iPod or world
Including a group that quickly collapsed to expand development on the software side
Suddenly I was energized
I didn't want to go to bed at night and couldn't wait to get up in the morning
Here was this little piece of the internet that was making me excited about technology again
I was looking to break the rut and podcasting appeared to help
These good feelings spread to other aspects of my life
I found a few more topic ideas for this column
Posted some good stuff on my weblog
And had a great time at the free computer class I give it the library every month
Don't discount how one small thing can wake you up and shake you out of your rut
Even in some small way
If you can reach out and find one small toe hold
It can help to raise you up
If you're stuck in a rut you have to force yourself to look at one new webpage
One new piece of art read one new magazine or listen to one new song anything to get your mind working again
When you're languishing
You have to keep listening for the knock of opportunity at the door
While this discovery of podcasting helped me to get my thinking moving in other ways
It also got me started on a project I thought about for years
Producing audio versions of my columns
So the people could listen to them on the bus on their bike or while doing their daily walk
In the past the technology just wasn't there to support my idea
Now with podcasting
I could see a reason to drag out the mic and mixing console and get to work
So starting with my column of September 24
I'm producing a weekly show of each new column
Released each Friday when the magazine is published
Additionally, I'm releasing a column from the archives each week
You can use the iPodter software available from ipodter.org
To download the shows automatically as they're released
I think that's nice that we got a whole new podcast started
So that's career opportunities
And you can find career opportunities in the iPodter.org directory
Which is located of course at ipodter.org
If you just want to sample some new podcast stuff that's fresh
Just then release go to audio.weblogs.com
And you can find links to the sites
You can if you mouse over the the name of the podcast
It'll give you the description of what was happening
What's happening in the podcast
There's a link to the direct link to the MP3 files
You can download sample it right there as it comes in
And of course the RSS 2.0 feed that's the XML icon
You copy that link and use that to subscribe to that feed in any iPodter software
And there's so much cool stuff happening in iPodter world
Now everyone's looking at how a new and novel way is to integrate the
The directory and thank you'll see now at ipodter.org
In the podcast directory under what's new
You'll see some new data which is the iPodter X guys data
They basically if you use iPodter X
They're keeping track of what podcast you're subscribed to
So they have the iPodter X favorites and top picks
Which is based upon user data which is extremely cool
So make sure you check that out
And of course the what's new is automatically generated
If something is added to a node somewhere down the line
That's even maintained and someone else's opml file
It still shows up
It's neatly categorized by a year month and by the day
Thank you very much Dave for getting that in
We also a Dave released a feed checker
So you can see if your podcast feed works
And it will work with the with audio.weblogs.com
Which you can ping and there's all kinds of information about that on ipodter.org
Another comment and another podcast that started
Well, thanks to the podcasting
But in part thanks to the to the daily source code to
Another podcast that I introduced you to
And it looks like we've got our American Indian brothers
On the podcast
Hi Adam my name is David Newberger
And I work for the Quarterling Tribe in beautiful plumber
I've been following podcasting since later
I guess when it first showed up on my radar
When I heard about it I thought wow
This is exactly what I've been looking for
A quick and easy way for our tribal members as well as employees
To get out information to the public
I started to think of ways to convince the tribal government of this
Which is where the daily source code comes in a play
On October 21st
You had an example podcast from Texas A and I'm the university called
The Agricultural News Weekly
This was a final piece of evidence I needed to convince the rest of tribe of
Podcasting's practical uses
So with that firmly cemented in their minds
We are now working on a rather large list of programs to air through podcasting
We plan on using it as a way to get information that our tribal members
As well as non-Indians
Would like to know about the tribe and Indian country in general
So thank you very much for helping me convince the tribe to use this new technology
Here's just one small example of what we will be using it for
Hello and welcome to the Court of Land Tribes
Smoke Management Report for Thursday, October 28th, 2004
Agricultural Burning is authorized for the following areas
I'm a Court of Land Indian Reservation
Zone 1, Cootney County, Zone 2 and 3, Benua County
Burn Times RS follows
12 noon to 4pm
This message has been produced by the Court of Land Tribes
Thank you very much David Newberger for that comment
That's extremely cool, please let me know
When the tribal podcasts are up so we can point to them and add them to our directory
Hey, that's cool. We could have a whole new maybe you want to maintain a directory
Node with the tribal podcasts
Excellent stuff
Okay, winding it up for today with a couple of emails and responses
The first one from Brendan Creasy
I'm just expanding the node here for my email
Oh, I remember this was about
You might have heard the source code early last week and I started off
and was a young child saying, you know, I listened to daily source code
Adam Curry all day and I got an email from Brendan Creasy
who sent me that clip and he said, you know, I loved hearing the clip
of my friend's daughter talking on the source code overjoyed
But bum that I failed to give him credit, I apologize
But it was kind of hard to give credit at the beginning in a montage
But, you know, it's something to think about because
You send me stuff right and I use it and I presume that it's okay to use it
If you send that to me
But does this mean that we should start a credit to the end of each show?
I'm not against it by the way, just a little more work
But then that's something that I'll program into the podcast production console
So anyway, thank you very much to your friend's daughter
I we loved it enormously here on the show
And Wilson Roberto Afonso says, hey, Adam, great to hear you playing Brazilian music
even better when it's RIA free music, by the way
Did you know that the singer and composer of the song that I played
Remember that Latino song I played?
Do you have Betto Jiu?
Currently, he's the Brazilian Minister of Culture
No, I did not know that
Excellent, so the Brazilian Minister of Culture is into RIA free music
Gotta keep our eye on that guy
Now we're going to leave you with some cool two cool mix ups
Political mix ups, of course
It's always easy to get some George Bush stuff
Chris Molotesta sent me a George Bush mix of clips
But right after that, I'll play some interesting clip montage
By John Kerry
I'm so doing, we don't only free the American people
We made our own people more secure
I didn't realize I had to black do
The minute I got elected
The storm clouds on the horizon
We're getting nearly directly overhead
But they underestimated what our campaign is about
Well, thank you, Ashana, to witness that
The courageous stage of our careers
That's the chapter of the last chapter of the 2020 documentary
That's our 21st century that most of us would rather forget
The last chapter of the 20th century is the 1st chapter of the 21st century
I'm afraid that the union in our state must be the nation
We're every one called it
I asked the Americans to give 4,000 years
of 4,000 hours over the next of the last few lives
I'll serve as your mother
But I am a student 4,000 hours
This will dictate our ship in the heck a lot easier
Just for long time to dictate
I think war is the dangerous place
It'll take time to restore chaos
The tariffs and barriers everywhere are torn down
Our economy will be strong
That's our gas is the hemispheric
I like to call it hemispheric in nature
Because it is a product that we can find in our own neighborhood
Responses have got to end
In order for us to get this framework
The groundwork, the groundwork to discuss a framework for peace
All right
Know what I believe
We'll continue to articulate what I believe
And what I believe and I believe what I believe is right
Welcome to the People's Home
I'm sure you can imagine that there's an unimaginable honor to live here
I see it all the time when people come up to me and say
I don't want you to let me down again
San is whether they west that's this girl
Just like me there's an old saying in Tennessee
I know it's the best it's probably gonna say this
There's a fool me once
Same on
Same on you
The fool me can't get fool again
I am here to make an announcement
That this girl is me
It can count as airplanes
We'll fly out along the way you know
I ain't even know what you believe
Make a lot easier than I have to question
Hi
Hello
Podcasting
All's live
Adam
My first is to America
I have a plan
Every plan
My health care plan
My plan for education
My plan for kids to be able to get better college loans
That my health care plan
But I got a better plan
I have a plan
I have a better plan for homeland security
I have a better plan to be able to fight the war on terror
Grab a plan
I have a plan
I've laid out a plan
I think my plan is better
And my plan
I have a plan in my plan
I have a plan
I also have a plan
I have laid out a different plan
and I have a better plan
I proposed a plan
My plan
I have a plan
I've a plan
and I have a plan
and I want to talk about my plan somewhere
I hope we can
I have a plan
That's why I have a plan
But I'll also have a better plan
I have a plan
You choose your plan
If you don't want to
take the offer
Of the plan that I'd want to put forward
I have a better plan. I have a plan. But I got a better plan. I have a plan to put America back to work
I have a plan. I have a plan. My plan does a better job and that's why I'll be a better commander in chief
Okay, so I promise you that if you vote for John Kerry, we're gonna make him stick to every single plan
He has promised
Well, I'm sorry
I got busted
So I used my one phone call to dedicate a song to you all the radio
Yeah, I got busted
In custody, I imagine our melody being played on the grand piano
I saw your face if run of me
It was perfect, where we are
I saw light in the end of the tunnel
And it was you
Because you're like my rich son
Travelling to you
Because I'm not you, I'm like
You're like my rich son
Travelling to you
Yeah, I got busted
I paid it a dirty word on your old man's Mercedes Benz because he told me to do us
But soon it released me because the cops were sad
And they didn't know how to prove it
Oh, I saw your face in front of me
It was perfect, where we are
I saw light in the end of the tunnel
And it was you
Because you're like my rich son
Travelling to you
Because I'm not you, I'm like
You're like my rich son
Travelling to you
Because I'm not you
It's also obvious
So obvious
That's the point
Because you're like my rich son
Travelling to you
Because I'm not you, I'm like
You're like my rich son
You're not in my mind from the album when I said I wanted to be your dorm.
You are the light, you're just like my not the baby source code.
For October, no shit.
November 1st, 2004.
And that's it for your source code, time to run it down for today.
As always, you can leave all your comments and suggestions on my weblog live.curry.com
or through email at www.curry.com
I'm getting through a lot of emails and getting some stuff done, please.
And of course, all the archives of the new shows at dailysourcecode.com
And that's it for Monday's show.
I'll be back tomorrow as we continue to pack up all of our stuff.
Get ready to remove and on Wednesday, I get ready to get out of here.
I take it to San Francisco for BlenderCon, November 6.
Take it easy, everybody.
I'll see you.
I'll be back tomorrow as we continue to pack up all of our stuff.