Well, howdy everybody.
Your source code coming to you from Curry Castle in Belgium.
My name's Adam Carr...
I'll say Thursday the 23rd because it's 14th.
A PAID SPEAKING
of the radio show, the morning radio show stopping.
I knew that I wanted to get out of the house.
And also, you know, that's for the best.
Any regular stuff is for gas or should I say for a one jet fuel to be precise
So that was at the World Trade Center in Rotterdam and
If you've ever been to Rotterdam, it is such a beautiful city, a city that was completely
utterly destroyed and flattened in the Second World War.
There was just nothing left over and they rebuilt the entire city and they actually called it
And they call it Manhattan on the mass.
So Manhattan of the mass.
And it does look very much like, a bit like Manhattan with the big beautiful buildings
and any of the harbor in the distance.
They've got the Europe.
and seeing that, because I don't get to Rotterdam very often.
So it was a speaking engagement for,
this was for insurance agents of Stuttel-Tedon-Persakeningen,
so that's the name of the insurance company,
and it's about 400 people there,
and they split off into individual parallel sessions
around 230, and that's where I did a session.
there and do your thing and talk and I rarely use a projector or slides although I try to
put some multimedia stuff into it. If I use a slide on the screen it'll be like a home
movie or
to accentuate a point. It's never text. I can't stand it when you've got someone speaking
to you and then you're being distracted by text. And of course, this is quite the opposite
from what BloggerCon will be, which is November 6th in Palo Alto. This is the third BloggerCon
and you can hear more about that on Trade Secrets, which is the brand new show on the podcasting
platform that I do with Dave Weiner, Dave from Scripting News, Scripting.com.
And we did another show today. We had agreed to do one at 8am his time and somehow, and it's
probably my fault. You just get so confused after a while with time zones and getting up early and
then my whole rhythm is still out of whack from getting up at 3.30 every single morning for a year.
Somehow I'd messed it up and David had been waiting for me to dial into him 24 hours ago.
Luckily he didn't wait for the full 24 hours, he did find something else to do.
So we finally hooked up and we recorded a show today.
I was much happier with the quality of the sound.
Now in fact, even Dave sounds a little bit too loud.
I'd listen back to the show, I'd check that out after we recorded it.
And his levels may be a little bit too hot compared to mine now.
But it worked pretty well and I was able to route audio back to him.
Although I think I mis-routed something and sent something back so hard through an audio loop
that it probably made the song of the day on Trade Secrets sound like it was tripled or quadrupled.
Oh well, luckily it was a remix of Sting's Russians anyway.
So no real harm done probably.
Oh boy, I'm just totally wrecked. I'm so tired from doing all that
because I didn't get back until QoRt-ed.
6 and I you know so that was 9 a.m Seattle time so I quickly through the laptop to get
I got everything ready and set it all up.
Oh what am I getting here a warning?
Oh no.
Oh this is nice.
Folder actions alert.
One new item has been placed in folder iPodrx download.
Would you like to view the added items?
No not now.
Oh boy, there's more items coming in.
That is the iPod or X running in the background.
Running happily, I have to say.
That's good news.
So we had to get the call set up.
Now remember we're doing this voiceover IP, which means that I'm doing it on iChat, which
is Apple's instant message client.
And it's the iChat AV so you can do audio and video.
And Dave's using AOL, he's using AIM, he's using the Windows client.
And you know that was all right because certainly if you compare it to the first show we
did where we literally had to stop and retape sometimes just minutes worth but
at one point almost half an hour's worth of it.
it kills your energy. So the energy was much better now. We didn't have to really do anything.
His sound was clipping once in a while, but all things considered, I think it's pretty
damn good and you can't beat the price. Now, let's be honest, you just can't beat that.
So it's a long show. It's about an hour and 20 minutes and you can see that you can
listen to it. It's secrets.scripting.com. It's trade secrets and maybe in the next
week show, we'll explain to you what that title really means and where it came from.
I was thinking maybe we'd just take a, since it's such a, you know, it's so late and I
haven't done a source code. I don't think I've done a source code at this hour.
We'll just take a quick step outside. Hold on a second. We go. Just to get a little vibe.
Hold on a second. It is raining. Let me just get the umbrella. Just take a quick evening stroll.
around the back courtyard.
Now actually it's harvest time.
Oh, there's a little froggy.
Hello frog.
I almost stepped on him.
It's harvest time.
And particularly now that all the rains are coming,
the farmers that have the lands all surrounding our grounds
are harvesting.
And they do this almost 24 hours a day non-stop.
It's really time is money kind of deal.
And I heard him, up until about half an hour ago,
I heard him buzz and buy with the tractor
so we may hear him.
Now I'm about, let's see,
I say I'm about 50 yards from the receiving end of this.
So I presume that that's still working.
Sorry, I'm taking a sip of my drink there.
I got a humongous flame of comment on DailySourceCode.com.
Someone was unsubscribing from my feed.
He couldn't stand listening to me slurping on my drink as I did these shows.
Unsubscribed forever, he said.
Well, that's your right.
That's what it's all about.
You know, it's not like a mailing list where you can't get off.
You know, that's what RSS does so beautifully.
If you're sick and tired.
arrangement you just unsubscribe okay nothing going on much tonight oh I also
got a note from Pete Prodell oh god I hope I pronounce it right now I can't I'm
too afraid to open up my email client while I'm recording stuff I thought it
was Prodell Prodell right Prodell raster web audio you know the guy who who I
mentioned yesterday when I was talking we were talking about short content and
comedy bits check out his latest offering this is raster web audio for
September 22nd 2004 slightly after mid-autopathy could be the weather in
Montclair New Jersey the current conditions for Montclair New Jersey it's
currently fair with a temperature of 58 degrees the dew point is 56 humidity is
93 visibility is around 10 miles and the winds are calm thank you and good
night thank you Pete wonderful I'm telling you
I would subscribe to a feed that does that.
I absolutely would.
We've actually been discussing him doing some other kind of feed,
like maybe a joke of the day, which is great.
And I will promote it and I'll certainly play his joke of the day a couple times.
But then the whole point is you subscribe to it, you know,
and then in the morning as you're listening to the latest shows
that came down the pike or whenever you have a chance to listen to it
on your walk or while you're jogging or you're down time, you're uptown,
you're in your sleep time, whatever,
and you'll just automatically hit it.
And it'll be in between shows, you know,
maybe morning coffee notes or trade secrets or evil genius chronicles
and then a joke of the day and then a source code
and that way you really start to tivoize your experience.
Oh man, this iPod or X is just going nuts.
It's giving me all kinds of content.
I subscribed to the...
Oh, that was so beautiful.
We got a couple of feeds from Feedster,
Scott Johnson had set that up for us,
even set up a whole webpage saying, you know, here's my gift to you.
And I just said, well, give me some picture enclosures.
I want to see how many come in, which apparently is quite a lot.
And I did see noise, or not noise, I saw signal to noise
on the iPod or developer list that were, you know,
there's talk of putting in either a, you know,
do not download more than X items or, yeah,
or enclosures for each feed,
especially when you subscribe to a new one
because that can really screw up your machine,
your processing, your power.
And for any newbie who's just installing it,
it's kind of daunting, you know, like you.
The fan is worrying, I've got files popping up all over the place.
It can be kind of scary.
Let me see, I'm just fried.
I apologize, normally I've got my energy up.
You know what, maybe this will help.
Let's play a song of the day.
This is something that...
It's not safe or worse put it that way, but it's it's music to walk in
The dark clouded sky, silt with rain, with turdward dew.
Everybody's fucking but me.
I just can't sing.
Some girls even bought you
And they just seem to trade
I can't
A dazzling urban eyes like me
My pussy's useful only when I eat
But he's fucking...
But...
dying of terminalized.
so depressing to see
my flum and cuss
That's it.
My secular is the blooming
Even my door
I guess I just don't have a plan.
Last four guys behind every tree
It's just a pain in the ass
The man just sings a dark free
I will stay like a stupid
And fuck me
Everybody's fucking
Honey
Everybody
I'll tell you, I'll say for work.
Isn't it beautiful though?
Got a whole album.
If you'd like it, let me know.
I'll certainly play more.
I wanted to wrap up today's source code too
with a little bit of feedback for the Audio Hijack Pro guys
from Amoeba Software.
And I know that some of them listen to the source code
and actually got an email saying,
you know, we also, we're trying to build this application
into something that works for audio blogging
and give us some feedback.
And I'll tell you, I love this application.
I love this program.
It works extremely well for what I'm trying to make it do.
If it were possible to improve anything,
what would make it the most ultimate,
fabulous, fantastic tool?
Would be, you know how on the effects pane,
so basically for, you know, you can hijack the audio
from any application.
the effects page, what I'd love, you know, because you can set in all kinds of effects
and filters and you can route audio through from one filter to another. Wouldn't it be
beautiful if I could either A, route the audio from the effects pane to another recording,
right? Or if I could select several applications that I want to record at the same time and
then have them all record into one file, because currently I can record four out of
four or five, you know, as many applications theoretically as I want at the
same time, except I can only record them to separate files. So if there's any way to
integrate, primarily the microphone, that's the most important part is being
able to mix in the microphone with the general signal coming off of off of the
the main, the core audio driver. Just being able to do that would be absolutely
phenomenal. I don't even know if it's possible. I've been getting a lot of
emails that in the next version of the Mac OS, what is that, Tiger or whatever.
Yeah, it's Tiger.
that there will be a lot more, there will be many improvements to the core audio drivers and
ways to mix the signals and all kinds of APIs and stuff that developers can get into.
So hopefully, Dave and I also talked a bit about this on trade secrets and the Apple guys,
I love them man, they're always right there when I need something.
you can. They're just not quite thinking about this yet, but hopefully they'll catch this
on the source code and if anyone wants to give me a call and pick my brain about it,
I'll be happy to let you know because if we can get this to work reliably, then it's great.
Then anyone can have a full blown audio or radio production studio on your desktop. No need for
breakout boxes and external devices or
Maybe not all the hardware we need to make it work perfectly, but something more should
be possible than the results I'm achieving right now.
Okay, oh, I almost forgot to tell you the really good news.
Patricia called.
She and her sister have been in London or England for the past couple of days.
And we have a house.
She found a house.
She cut a deal.
Or at least I think she made an offer.
And I think that'll be accepted.
Which means we'll be moving somewhere I guess before Christmas.
So I'm very pumped about that.
And I've actually only really seen a picture of the house on the internet.
And Patricia took the video camera.
So by tomorrow afternoon, I'll have seen it.
And maybe I'll be able to let you know a little bit more about the new digs.
Okay, I'd say that's about all I can muster up today.
Still have to get this up to the server.
And since I'm still Mr. Mom, I've got to close down.
Also got to clean up some of the kitchen, get the dishwasher going, make sure all the animals
The animals are secure, the house is secure, you know, make sure Jim Bob, Mario and Sue
Elnor all in bed.
And that's it for Shows Code for today.
It's dailysourcecon.com.rss.xml.
I'll see you tomorrow for another video.