Before we get started, let me remind you of the following results or events predicted
on these things.
The name of the material is from actual results.
The factors that could cause actual events or results to differ from expectations include
lack of growth, intense competition in our interest rate, integration failures, changes
in government regulation, operational failures, or looking at things like that.
All right, some of the volumes of today should not be applied upon as representing
our internet at the beginning of the 20th of the 20th, while we make a light update for
what we say is that something's a future we need to not to do it, so even if we're not
interested in it.
A casting, all's like Adam Curry, howdy everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code for Wednesday,
December 8, 2004, coming to you from Curry College.
I'm Adam Curry, it is quarter past 11 in the evening, big day today, went to London, took
a train, it's been a couple of years.
I don't know, man, I got to talk about these English trains.
I only hear English people complain about the trains.
I thought it was a pretty fucking great experience.
Seriously, I had a really nice ass train.
I'm not a train guy, maybe I've just been missing out on trains.
Good matters, is your Daily Source Code, will we try to bring you 40 minutes of 40 minutes of
well-party?
40 minutes of users and developers partying together, or maybe there are no secrets, only
information you don't yet have.
And while we're on the power of pure intellect, let's start off with an audio comment that
is influential for the entire show.
Hello Adam and have everybody.
This is Chris Penard from Streetport, Louisiana, and you're listening to the Daily Source Code
with Adam Curry.
Adam, I wanted to tell you I enjoy the non-reverbs sound of your cottage.
I hope you get broadband soon and best wishes from the States.
You've inspired me to create a podcast on my own.
Now only have to think of a subject.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Subject enough right there.
Okay, so after yesterday's source code where I basically asked everybody, no, I'm sorry,
I asked everybody, you know, what you thought about the reverb, I'd say 75% of all comments
were predominantly negative.
In other words, get rid of the goddamn reverb.
We were just getting used to the sound of the cottage.
So the reverb is off, you can still hear a little bit of the room because I don't have
anything up on the wall yet.
You've got my gold records.
Gold records on the wall?
My picture of me and many celebrities.
So actually, I think that if I'm lucky this weekend, it's finally time for my office.
Then we've done just about everything else in the house and then my office is last.
And the reason it's last because I have the most shit that has to be sorted through.
So anyway, back to the reverbs, the reverb is basically off.
However, I have added some more cowbell.
I think that makes the show much better.
Don't you?
Can never have too much cowbell, you know, basically.
So anyway, I had an appointment with my senior private banker, her name is Kherty.
She works for Mace Pearson.
She's been our banker for, that's enough fucking cowbell.
She's been our banker for, should I know, five years, I guess, and she really takes care
of a whole bunch of shit.
And I have a complicated life, or I'm trying to get away from her very complicated life
with all kinds of companies and structures and crap in the Netherlands and Belgium.
And here, I just want to have a simple, and I have it, a simple bank account, an internet
bank account that I can look at, I can pay my bills, I've got a direct debit card, you know,
we've got everything is online within my world, within my universe.
And all the other shit is basically being sorted out.
But anyway, so Kherty is, besides being beautiful, is an excellent banker.
And it's always fun to, she came over from Amsterdam for some meetings and so she said,
you know, why don't we hook up for lunch and I'm like, yeah, yeah, I'll meet you in the city.
No problem.
You know, having never been to the city from, in fact, we've been here for two weeks.
I haven't ventured in the London.
I've just been here sitting in the, at the cottage in in Guilford, having a good old
time exploring Starbucks, which I still visit every single day.
I haven't done a podcast from there because it's just the vibe, it's kind of worked out
where I've been doing stuff in the cottage, then uploading from Starbucks.
And this will actually have to upload during the night anyway.
So I mean, my big mouth said, okay, lunch, I'll meet you at the, was it the Great Eastern hotel,
which is Liverpool Street Station at noon.
And I figured, well, you know, I'll have a, a car picking me up and take me to the station at 1030.
And yeah, radio cars here are pretty normal.
Just cost, you know, like a pound at a half or something and take me from, from the, from the cottage
to the station because it's not all that far.
And it was one of those perfect days, you know, when you walk into the station,
you walk up to the window, you say, I got to go, you know, to Waterloo Station.
I was thinking I'd take a cab from Waterloo Station to Liverpool Street Station.
I mean, you can take the, the tube, which is the, the subway.
I really wanted to go above ground, so I could, you know, get a little vibe of the city.
And, you know, walk up to the window, got my, got my ticket.
I chose for a first class ticket because I want to see what that was like first, of course.
Being a stop that I am, the elite fucking stop that I am, and it was really nice.
I mean, it was kind of like a luxury airliner, you know, what used to be economy class,
and I'm talking about 25 years ago, only now the seats, you know, still go back further than those days.
You have your own little power supply, so you have 220 volts there for your laptop and door for your cell phone.
And it's really nice and quiet. And what I noticed was,
the suspension of the train is unfucking believable. I don't know if it's just the first class train.
Maybe the first class car has, has extra suspension, but I mean, it was like riding on air.
It was just nothing at all what I remembered about a train ride. And it was only like 35 minutes.
I'm at Waterloo Station, hop in the cab, 12 minutes later I'm there, door to door,
less than an hour. Unfucking real. And I thought, you know, I was in for at least an hour and a half
ordeal, but the train is almost nonstop. And on the way back, almost exactly the same thing,
you know, after a great lunch and a little bit of war driving in the cab, I picked up.
I must have picked up 15 different, uh, open Wi-Fi signals on the way back, um,
actually trying to connect, uh, but we weren't sitting in traffic long enough to, uh,
to actually, you know, have any luck of, uh, of, of down or uploading anything on some open Wi-Fi.
There were a couple of open Wi-Fi's according to, uh, I stumble or which I use.
Um, and again, on the way back, it was, I was backed by, uh, by four o'clock. It was awesome, you know,
off the Starbucks on the way home, uh, sucked down some, uh, podcasts, the Gilmore gang, specifically,
which I haven't listened to yet. And also it was great on the train. I had a commute, you know,
after a long time, and there I was, um, chuckley, about on and droop. Uh, with, you know,
the suits around me looking going like, what the, what's the sad weird guy with those weird
shoes and, and he's kind of weird hair. I got my eggs. If you don't know what they are,
eggs, they're basically Australian, ugly ass Australian boots, which are kind of furry and they're
made from, uh, sheep skin, but the sheep was killed humanly or some crap marketing story like that.
Which, of course, is probably completely true, um, but, yeah, nonetheless. So anyway,
had a great day in London. Uh, really, uh, happy about the, the connections. I had no idea what's
going to be, um, yeah, really so incredibly easy to get back and forth. In fact, if I had one
Christina's in school, Patricia and I could literally just decide to say, hey, let's go have lunch in
the city and we could, you know, hop off, drive down to the station and go. It would be awesome.
Oh, and Patricia had her first drive today. I mean, I've been doing all the driving since you,
you know, we have to drive on the left hand side and we have a right hand drive car, which means
you sit on the left hand side. So it's still a bit confusing. And, um, so the other day I came home
around 530 from Starbucks and it was dark and I said, come on, let's go. We're going to go to
Sainsbury's going to go to the, and which is, that's a good, uh, three, four, about four, five
kilometers, lots of roundabouts that you have to go around. Um, and producer to great, you know,
it was, uh, yeah, especially for the first time and in the dark, which I specifically made or do.
I, I noticed that I picked up a couple of instructional, um, habits from, uh, Wing Commander
William, my, um, helicopter instructor and all my, I should, my flight instructor period. I got
a call, I'm missing. It's like my wing, wingman, you know, my flying buddy and miss those guys,
him and Nick the stick. I got to catch up with him soon. I got to catch up with him. I got to get
flying and hold on a sec. Do you want to go out, Chess? I'm going to go out, girl. Okay, hold on. I'll
tell you what, why don't you listen to this promo. I'm going to let the dog out of the, uh, out of my
office here. Uh, uh, uh, uh, it's almost like the old days, isn't it?
Hitting you right between the years with the message of hope, love and good news. This is light spring.
And I'm Steve Webb, you're host. Here at Life Spring, we want to tell you about the one who loves
you unconditionally and who gave his life for you, Jesus Christ. Here you'll find music,
conversation, and reasons to believe. Our website is calpm1.org slash podcast.htm.
Hey Adam, thanks for this brand new avenue communication. We all call podcasting and thanks
everybody for listening. I'm out of here.
Thanks everybody. The Lord says everybody give me a bowing. Oh, man, perfect. I'm telling you,
I love religious podcasts. There's broadcasters of all sorts. I, I get a kick out of it.
And sometimes I actually get a real positive boost. You know, I love people who are just
positive and up and got energy. It works. It really does work. And we just said again,
everybody, can you give me a bowing? Hold on. He went, buddy, for listening. I'm out of here.
Excellent. Speaking of everybody, being out of here, big news here in the UK about the BBC.
3000 people got fired or displaced before Christmas and expected another thousand after Christmas.
As, you know, this is like, the BBC is public broadcasting and you pay a license. And actually,
just, this is whack. You go to tvlicensing.co.uk. And maybe it's even tvlicensing.com. And there you
register whether you have a black and white television, which costs I think, you know, 65 pounds.
Or if you have at least a color television, you can have multiple sets, but you have to pay for the
first one. And that's like a hundred and I think a hundred and twenty-one pounds. And if you don't,
you can get fined up to a thousand pounds, which is, well, these days, almost $2,000, like $1,900.
If you don't have your license. And I think maybe the, like, the mailman checks you or some shit like
that. And as was in the train on the way to London, there were huge posters of tvlicensing.com.
We said, we have a database. And we know every single home that doesn't have a TV license.
Just thought we'd let you know. It's like, fuck that shit. I got my TV license immediately.
But there's so anyway, so you pay for it, you know. And then took the people have a right to say,
hey, what the fuck? We want, you know, we want value from money. And with over 27,000 employees
at the BBC, there was a general feeling that, hey, you know, there's a lot of people here who
think they got a job for life. We got to keep them on their toes and keep it competitive.
And there's a lot to be said for that. There certainly is. And you know, we witnessed how the BBC
worked, and although extremely professional, you know, even I was amazed at the, the amount of money
that was basically being spent. And not to attract anything from the BBC, because I'd love the
programs they made. But there's a lot of inefficiencies. Even when they needed me to be on BBC
World, they called me at 9 o'clock 9 a.m. And I said, you know, can you be here at noon to be on the
on the BBC World Service? And I sent a cab from a town 10 miles away, you know, it's like,
because they had an account with them, which is totally ridiculous where they could have called
a cab. Shit, they could have re-enversed me, you know. There's so many different ways they could have
done that. And the, of course, the cab didn't wait. They had another one come from a different company.
It was a, it was whack. It was totally whack. Anyway, so this has been going on. And I think most
public broadcasts are being paid out of community funds are under a lot of pressure these days
for this very same reason. And a lot of the pressure, of course, comes from the commercial
broadcasters. What's really happening is everyone's eating each other up, you know.
They're all just fucking eating each other up. And we have, what I think is great about podcasting
is, and I was talking to the, uh, to charity and, uh, another, um, someone who works for, you know,
the Anglo-Saxon into a trust division. It's great, man. Women bankers, they freak me out. I love it.
They're so fucking smart. Um, we were talking about, uh, uh, I was thinking about women for a second
then I lost my, my train of thought. Oh, shit. Oh, I don't remember. Uh, oh, yeah, about, uh,
about podcasting. Um, you know, that we basically don't have to deal with 24 hours in a day.
You know, we have to deal with how many minutes the podcast listener has to consume in a day,
which is why I'm always advocating short podcast, right? Um, so because we can broadcast 5,000
hours a day if we want of a simultaneous audio programing because it's completely three
dimensional. You can listen to it whenever you want, wherever you want, however you want, um,
and you can be behind a, you could, you could catch up. You could list skip bits. You can do all of that.
So we basically, as podcasts, there's have to figure out how to grab people's attention and keep it,
which probably means they should move on from this conversation. But I will say that our next or next
or next or neighbors down the way. Um, I think her, she, uh, she's a school teacher. She brought her
daughter over to meet Christina, uh, both the same age. Her husband works for BBC interactive.
And, uh, I think they might have to move to Manchester. It sucks because the whole interactive
division is being moved. Uh, they fact thousands of employees are being moved to Manchester
because, um, the BBC also feels. And this is a big thing that, uh, that the, the general, uh,
listening and viewing audience feels is that it's too London based. It's too based around
what's going on at London and not about basically the heart land. So that's why a lot of the, uh,
programming staff, including interactive is going to Manchester. And I'm sure there's some financial
reasons for that as well. And another big piece of news today is that there also be, um,
and haven't confirmed this. I heard this from the cab driver that there were several, uh,
I don't, I think he's a thousand, uh, job cuts at, uh, uh, Colgate Palm Olive headquarters,
ladies and gentlemen of, uh, Colgate Palm Olive is in Gilford in the United Kingdom,
which means there's going to be thousands of people, uh, being kicked out. Some of them, of course,
must be some kind of at least mid-level executives, which means some ports are likely to free up
at the Gilford Exchange, making DSL capable and probable. And BT, don't call me. Okay. I got
my boys at EZNet on the case. We're going to use their gear at the Gilford Exchange. And you can
go out and solicit more people. You could have had a real good customer on your hands.
That's a, uh, that, uh, that, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
I haven't actually, listen to this next, uh, audio comment that came in. It's from Lee Wilkins and Jenny Patton,
um, of course we know about them from the Alphi and Benson fund, there are two little doggies. Uh, and they sent a,
thank you MP3, uh, which is intended for you listening to the daily source code right now.
Hey, what's up everybody? This is Lee Wilkins from the Jenny and Lesha. This is just a
special message for Adam Curry's daily source code and just to say a big thank you
for me and Jenny to all those that have donated so far as of six o'clock
Greenwich meantime on Monday we had raised up near our $1,200. I just wanted to say a
big thank you to all of the daily source code listeners and also all those that
done listen to today's source code and yet have donated it's just amazing knowing
and seeing how community like the blogger's fair and podger's fair can come together
at a time in need to help bring back Alfie and Benson. Alfie and Benson will hopefully be
returning this weekend and will Alfie and Benson will have their own number of podcasts
which we will launch and then we'll also have around blog which they'll be posting to as
well when they get back and there's nothing left else for me to say apart from a big thank you
to everybody and we would of course give you a date of progress at Alfie and Benson.com
but I just yet there's nothing left to say apart from thank you Adam to forgive me the
chance to tell our story and thank you again to everybody and I do mean everybody you will
begin personally now especially now from both me Jane and Alfie and Benson when they return.
Thank you very much. All righty I say mission accomplished everybody good job.
Now imagine what we could do if we really fucking got together and really pulled our resources
for something really big. It could happen you know I want to think about that and I'm sure there's
lots of people out there who see the power now I mean we have just proven once again that you can
create revenue and cash flow in in podcasting and man it was quick and you know it was realistic
and we set a goal and we and I feel good about it you know and we could do the same for like
people dying all over the world. Oh my god I'm about to break out into we are the world I should
stop immediately. Thank you very much Lee and Jenny for sending in that audio comment.
A comment on the weblog from let me see this was from Michael Martelli. Michael says hey Adam
love the show rather new to podcasting got into him about three weeks ago while listening to
and gadgets like that so of course I had to start listening to the god father's cast. Uh huh
the pod father you mean. Uh actually don't list the podcast on MP3 player actually downloaded
it to my computer at work. Listen while I write software. I'm very excited to be finally
getting an iPod for Christmas so still probably listen by my computer. Oddly enough here comes
I actually work at your old place of employment good old MTV networks software developer in the
time square office 1515 Broadway and you show really helps that they go by special on five o'clock.
Shocked listen to the days cast you mentioned my hometown of Wayne New Jersey. I did not know
audible was located there neat thing to hear. You know there's all isn't it there's a isn't there a
great roller rink in Wayne New Jersey. Maybe that's one town over from Wayne and I think the
willabric mall is in Wayne New Jersey and when I think about 1515 Broadway actually was at 1515
was the main office we also at one point had 1775 Broadway that actually part of that burned down
um the some god I should ask Kenster J he should he'll probably do that on the next Ken and
Squip show um and it was like someone's fucking extension it was Dave Kendall's god damn extension
core that burned down a whole floor of the MTV offices remember Dave Kendall he did 120 minutes
and we always used to tease him we said in the day where that fucking dead cat on his hat which
was very mean to say of course some of the hair god should have actually punished me for that but
they've been pretty pretty nice to me so anyway cool to hear that you're haunted and I wondered if you
work for MTV if MTV's I guess it's still the biocomb building 1515 Broadway which of course
we're also their live studios are all right well thanks for uh checkin in um and there was also
I don't know if you saw this this new story um actually it finally got sent to me uh by email uh Gary
why is who um we're scary from he's the IBV Greece transmitting station the station manager
the hell is in Greece okay uh is that the same I guess so uh I Adam enjoy the source code yeah
Boeing blah blah good luck with your uh with your van with sure Denver Post reports that the
ours people spend listening to radio are in steep decline as younger audiences switch to iPods
CDs mix at home and subscription satellite signals newspaper reports several local stations
are taking steps to address this by cutting ads per hour jumping back into internet streaming
no no no no no no an emphasizing live local shows to restore the companionship factor
in commercial radio thank you this is exactly what is going on with podcasting and of course the
BBC were you know they're talking about the value of what they're doing as well and I heard
even though it was a pompous ass today uh who's on radio two or whatever it was uh and it was
course radio BBC radio London whatever it was a call-in show and he was saying radio is also about
the relationship between the listener and the person the presenter on the show and I think that
the big companies like clear channel who own most of the radio stations have kind of overlooked that
fact that you can't you know it's an art form it may be the lowest rung of the show is
ladder to be in radio but that's okay you know it is an art form and uh and you can't just
it's like you know disco eventually was doomed to fail for the same reason you can't automate
music you know which is what the big excitement of disco was it was hey no more musicians you know
fuck that shit we don't need those motherfuckers anymore well guess what you know it doesn't work
that way you do need musicians um so uh and then he also points to a actually included a
scan of an article from what was that uh radio world um and he yeah it's very cool sent me a
PDF which of course I haven't attached to the production show notes everything else is an
production show notes um that talks about podcasting um as it relates to radio broadcasting and that's
it's an interesting it's a good read I'll see if we can get an online version he couldn't find one
oh here it is Gary says he's writing from northern Greece where he manages a large short-way radio
station for the for the man for the government I've moved internationally many times so I could relate
to your comments on the transition from castle to cottage yeah right on okay oh by the way it's
has my girlfriend is joining me here in Greece this weekend coming from Germany if you have any tips
I'm making a multicultural relationship work in this case the American guy in a German girl please let
me know hmm well that's an interesting question I think about that I don't have I'll have
never gone out with I mean I don't even know German women I don't think the only German women
I know are the ones that uh that make my Audi that's the only German women I know
that are usually named Helga but somehow I doubt your girlfriend's name is Helga or nor does she
look like she should be working in an Audi factory I don't think it makes any difference man
whatever you're from it really doesn't as long as there's love as long as there's love and
you might want to consider some you might want to consider some cowbell
is it hey baby I want you to come over here and take off your dress and I'll put my cowbell
okay all right Gary thank you very much Merry Christmas to you and uh into your girlfriend
let's see about 25 minutes into the show so we're gonna be perfectly on time the way I have
it plan at this point actually I was gonna talk the day today and we were emailing back and forth
and yeah and I had half of an idea maybe we could do a trade secrets although I'm a little
bit concerned still about his setup because when he's recording and there's something funky with
his new computer and we have to get this fucking fix because if it's skipping while he's recording
that's just not gonna work because then we can't do the the dawn and drew double ender trick
because we won't be in sync and I'll have to now that's gonna be a fucking nightmare so
and then he sent me a link to the latest morning coffee notes which now of course is on scripting news
and I figured out maybe today would not be the day a great day for even just a social chat on the
hell hello hello um this is a uh I feel better but my voice doesn't sound much better
it's really interesting way of speaking because once they start getting going you know no when
it's gonna just jump up normally I have a fairly deep voice but when it's in this mode
just never know um when it's gonna jump up about it you know this reminds me of do you remember
that episode of the um the cartridge family when Peter was going through puberty and he would sing
and then his voice would crack and then you know it was like a real big problem because he had to
do this solo during a really big concert and then what they did is they eventually changed the song
or they did a special song for him to sing which was about changing let's go
hey Dave you're going through your second puberty it's at 49
anyway I just was reading a thing that said that Elliot Spitzer is running for a governor
of New York State I just thought I could die with me like that run for a governor anything
what if he wins people say governor Spitzer you'll be able to kids love a great time
or sorry I have a fine mood that's right oh man that's frightening when Dave talks you know what
we should bug him home on a second he's been posting eyes aware blog he wants someone to call him
he has like one of these 206 free numbers let's see if you can do this I think what would be
kind of let's give it a try I'm gonna try to do it on Skype with Skype out even though I'm on
the dial-up modem here at the at the cottage I bet you I could get it done so while that's loading
I have some great news for you um my mom called today and she has a date for operation um and this
so the operation where they go in and remove either half a lung or a whole lung and I just said
this off the cuff like she's going in for a fucking tune up but it's going to be on the 22nd
that's when she should be admitted 23rd is when the actual operation takes place and we're
really excited about it and it's great for her you know she now she has a date she can work
towards it she knows when it's gonna happen and everything is really you know right on track
and looking great so we just could not be could not be happier about it all okay hold on I've got
my Skype here I hope this works hold on so I'll be going over I guess yeah I may spend
yeah I may spend a good part of the holiday perhaps even Christmas in Holland so we'll have to
see okay I'm gonna try this Skype out now let's see if this works see if we can call Dave's voice
a 206 338 3143 so now there you go Skype just crashed fuck piece of shit
fuck the application Skype is unexpectedly quit because it's a piece of shit on the Mac
okay you know what we'll do I'll just call this boy
hold on I'll just call him on the speaker phone here that's what I'll do okay so it's
one country code 206 is the area code 338 3143 feel free to participate and and call Dave right now
if you're in the car have yourself owned by anyone here let's call him hold on if I can get the
oh that's lame there's like no message it just goes beep oh okay hey Dave it's Adam and friends
here at the source code just partying is users and developers everybody and we want to say hi
hope you feel better I hope your voice gets better so you can do another lovely morning coffee notes
bye okay no to care of that okay moodlong Scott Phillips says fuck thanks for ruining my
morning cigarette man first second hand smoked guilt now the shame of the love the dare not
speak its name next I'll be supporting the terrorist I can just see it now stop sucking off the
malbro mula I know maybe it's time to try the patch again I admire you for sticking with it still
love you and Don both actually um as this is from Scott from Texas and Scott we hope you definitely
definitely will consider quitting and you know Don's voice still rings true in my head the what she
says and it keeps me off the evil the evil devil weed um and we'd like you to be around for
why as well so anything we can do to help just listen I gotta get that excerpt from Don you know what
maybe I should just try and find that right now excuse me for sniffing so disgustingly where's
there was Don Andrew where's fucking Don Andrew show I have the Don Andrew show here somewhere
let me just maybe just go and find oh where's Don Andrew show hold on I don't know if I can find
it that quickly hold on a second let me put this into the right sound channel here we go
all right you were gonna tell me something when we're driving home yeah like I think I'm gonna save it for
when we're on the air what was it what was it I told you to remember because I knew you were gonna forget
what's that it the field yeah it was that close find us some shit I'll kill that up tomorrow
I just I gotta I need that as a jingle I need to play that over and over and over again whenever Don
said whenever I want to smoke whenever you want to smoke I should play that and man it's the scariest thing
so Scott also sent along a was it Scott who sent this tune I think it was we just see
yeah attached
a pod save song which means non RIA from garage band dot com it says thought you might get a kick out of
it stick with it till the end okay oh yeah right well it's it's a different kind of song
roll it's into it since since you sent it in and since you like it I don't like to brush my teeth
is the title you can find the link to this song in the production show notes
was this the point where I go yeah everybody
it's kind of like Mr. Rogers and I ask I don't like to brush my teeth go up and down and on around and underneath
I don't like to brush my teeth don't like to brush my teeth
but I know that there are things I have to do so if I got a brush my teeth then I want to brush my teeth
I don't like to wash my face my eyes my mouth I know that every place I don't like to wash my face
but I know that there are things I have to do so if I got a brush my face then I want to wash my face with you
I don't like to be a down word about things to get done and it drives me insane but I just can't explain
why with you they almost seem to be fun
I don't like to go to bed for much prefer to watch to be instant I don't like to go to bed
but I know that there are things I have to do so if I got a good bed then I want to go to bed
and I want to go to bed
oh if I got a good bed then I want to go to bed with you
and that's sweet it starts off with brushing his teeth and before you know it you didn't let it
be as
welcome to the ripen read blogger podcast I'm Charlie Quidnung reporting I read the blogosphere so you
don't have to miss a day of posts no worries just listen to my ripen read blogger podcast and you'll hear
what everyone is saying maybe about you 10 minutes a day to hear the top three or four political
topics from a conservative perspective to get the details and read the original sources you'll find
all the links on ripen read.logspot.com that's ripn r e a d dot blogspot.com all right that'll do it for
your source code for today for Wednesday December 8, 2004 save perfect time just about 40 minutes
such as others looking for so always the best of the use of developers where we party together
to figure this shit out makes the work if we can and of course all the best of podcasts and
the promos and keep them coming Adam and Curry dot com attached to file
that's really working quite well for me if you keep it on the keep between keep it on
the three mags or five mags doesn't really matter if you send me seven mp three files
absolutely perfect because I just leave the mail client running dirty during the night
in the caches everything that comes in along with my my iPod or so I'm actually doing okay
yeah wouldn't mind having a little bit of bandwidth with him in the next oh fucking century or so
you can leave comments on the weblog of Curry dot com and of course I can get the all the archives
in the latest show on daily source code dot com we back tomorrow with the source code from the
cottage in the UK talk to you there and bye bye I remember all that