Well, good morning everybody. I mean, everybody. It's just a little bit past nine o'clock and I am on my way from Castle,
back Māori on the highway to Breda. That's where I'm going to pick up one of my instructors in the
evening and Nick has invited me today. It is a beautiful day. I must say, the sun is shining. There's
hardly a cloud in the sky. Beautiful sunrise. Oh, full, full. Just burning hot. Beautiful. Although it's
not really going to be hot, it's going to be about 16 degrees centigrade today, so not particularly warm.
But you might have made to comply with him. I mean, fly with him for Rotterdam Airport, which is a small
but commercially used airport in Rotterdam, obviously. And Rotterdam Airport has flights from
your KLM and the city hopper, so you can get there. From modern time, you can get to Spain, to France,
to Portugal, to the UK, so it's really a nice little airport. Just one, one terminal with extremely
modern and there's a flying club that's also part of the airport, because of course that was probably
there before for some of these commercial guys came in. It was very small airfield. And I'm not
quite sure who's playing, we're going to be using today. But I have the idea that, you know,
that there's a maintenance that was done on the plane and it needs a good test run, right? And
that's when I usually get invited, which is cool. So it's a mooney. I'm not sure which mooney it is that
we're flying today. Nickel be able to tell us all about it. I haven't discussed the fact that
I'd like to do a podcast with him. And actually, I have my wireless mics that and everything
with me, so I can hook up the inner cons system. So we're going to have some good quality right
now. I'm just yapping into the yep, right into the microphone. This is that eight kilohertz wave
file that you're hearing. So I'm not going to show this is going to be a daily source code, or we're
just going to do this as an additional fund segment. I'm sure that I'm going to have to edit all
kinds of stuff together, because there's a certain point, you know, we may just not be talking
at all, it may not be interesting to listen to. So I'm just going to record a whole bunch of stuff
today, see what pops up, see if it turns out cool. I think that you'll probably enjoy hearing
me getting instructions on how to find this plane. And the mooney is, I don't have to say it's
kind of a Ferrari single engine piston airplane. It has a light calming engine, which is used in many
types of single engine airplanes. But this particular model, because I've flown, I think it's
the same one. I've flown this one before, has, well, mooney has retractable landing gear, it has a
low wing, not a high wing. So you're kind of sitting on the wing, as it were, which I think is
a little less like sporty for you. It's kind of, it's more like a professional airplane with an
underwear. And it has auto pilot and all kinds of cool stuff in there. You can fly this plane
completely IFR, instrument flight rules, which means that you can fly to the dark or bad weather,
and you can land it on the ILS of any ILS equipped airport. So it's a beautiful machine, and I'm
not quite sure where we're going to go today. We might go up to the very top of the Netherlands,
which is almost the very bottom of Scandinavia. It's also possible that we might just fly across
the North Sea or across the channel to BlackBush, which will be my new airport. So we're just
going to kind of see what happens where it takes us. Almost at Nick's house, and the next time I check
in, we'll probably be on startup checklist. So stay tuned everybody.
Come to Peru. In Lama Land, there's a one-man band, and it'll tutt his flute for you.
Come fly with me, let's take off in the blue. Once I get you up there, where the air is where
you are. We'll just fly, start. Once I get you up there, I'll be holding you a sword.
You made angels cheer cause we're together. Where the wise it's such a lovely day.
Just say the words and we'll beat the birds down to a book obey. It's perfect for flying
and they move and they say, come fly with me, let's fly, let's fly away.
Once I get you up there, where the air is where you are,
fly, we'll just fly, start. Once I get you up there, I'll be holding you a sword.
You made angels cheer cause we're together. Where the wise it's such a lovely day.
You just say the words and we'll beat the birds down to a book obey. It's perfect for flying
and they move and they say, come fly with me, let's fly, let's fly.
Back up, let's fly away.
You're going to mix them down to the earth once they're full.
Okay Nick, there's him, hey, hey, well, we're on the hill, dude.
I think I was hearing like, Chris the boat, Chris the boat, Chris the boat,
The Resonals at Pforce is still hot there.
And they say, sir, please.
We're right behind time now, but we're ready to go up in that park from K-10?
Yeah, that blows.
Yeah, excuse me.
You take air miles?
Oh fuck.
Yeah, the mooney is definitely not for big deal.
Not for big guys.
Okay.
Actually, well, Nick is getting all that set up.
Just check and make sure that we're recording here.
Listen to my monitor system on the headphones.
Hello? Yeah?
Let me see. Yep.
Check one, two, one, two. Yeah, beautiful. Okay.
So I've got the recording unit, the yep, with the receiver of my wireless mic,
in my bag on the back seat.
And I've got microphone clipped on.
I'm nibble to the both of them.
Right on.
Okay. On the side.
So I'll have to do some translation here, you know, Nick speaks.
Excellent English.
Building up the left wing tank.
So what do you tell us about the mooney 201, Nick?
It's a good plane.
This reliable one is fast.
Isn't the Ferrari of the single engine piston?
Yes, it is. Rob small on the side, but it's very comfortable in the plane.
It's sporty. That's not small. It's sporty.
It's a very clean AC off the aerodynamic wise.
Yeah.
It's flying pretty fast.
32 liters, you can gain the speed of 150 knots.
150 knots, so that's 140 miles an hour.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
Oh, they have a field gauge here.
Cool.
It's a mechanical one.
You have an electronics one on the side.
Yeah.
So many gallons total, 60, 70 gallons total.
You can fill it up.
One hand, 70 gallons total.
70 gallons total.
Hello.
What's up here?
No, we have nothing to think about.
No, it doesn't matter.
That's not what I'm talking about.
That's somebody else.
No, that is not us, my dear.
Okay. I love you.
Okay.
I love you too.
Bye.
I was Patricia.
I wanted to know if we were already in the air,
because someone had been flying over the house,
doing some lazy eights.
Nope, wasn't us.
And I've told everybody else.
Don't do that.
Just doesn't like the lazy eights.
She doesn't mind if you come out of the sky,
drop down with a helicopter and land and have some coffee.
That's okay.
She just doesn't like the lazy eights.
Just standing here on the apron.
There's a huge, lots of swipes are actually coming up.
Telecopter, three person.
Looks like they're coming in for some deal.
That's actually kind of jet engine in that swipes.
It's mounted upside down in backwards.
Really, it's like a little coffee.
I'm like a tadpole.
Not a pretty machine, that look at them.
Doesn't job.
The entry and exit of the moon is...
I can't forget it indeed.
I can't forget it.
It's the women with the short skirts that have the problems with that.
I like them in the summer.
Yeah, aha.
Okay.
I have one last one.
Here goes the landing Michealду…
MEXRAPAIN
I'm going to do a wee more, and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and then I'm
going to put my camera on and then I'm going to put the camera on and my camera on and then I'm going to put my camera on and if it hurts, it is going to hurt.
It's a bit of a nice to hold.
It's a bit too far.
I've never been on level 5 started this before.
It's 2-4-1-18-0-8-9-9-8.
It's a time in 08.
I'm a 9-8 set to start a pro for the mid-to-4.
And go even though it's a sexy hold.
I've never been on level 9.
If it takes you to throw it, I'll only do it.
I don't know if it's sexy.
This is a clear and start a pro.
I wouldn't really like anything.
I look tired.
I think I'm behind you端
What's going on on top?
Excellent.
Thecription?
What are you doing out of there?
I don't know who's on level 9.
It's an empty box.
Follow me or be the pirate or pirate Oscar?
Or dem Oscar?
The micro-clamming one thousand feet, stay 500 meters right outside of the roadway.
This is a few longs, here up your old car, so if you can open it, it's okay.
And then the button.
Yeah.
So what are we going to do now?
Okay.
We're going to come over here to come and go.
Can we do it here?
We're going to do it again.
We're going to go to the right field station.
We're going to line taxi and do nothing to do.
So what are we going to do?
We're going to do it.
Okay.
Are you going to put your boots on?
Yeah.
Okay.
Make sure to stay alive.
Yeah.
Okay.
We're going to take the other direction.
That's just days and days about conditions.
Okay.
We're going to go down.
We want to be prepared.
Okay.
No stay out of here alive.
Yeah.
We want to go to the right field.
Okay.
Take my gear.
I want to rotate and speed up this back.
We're about to flip it.
Okay.
I'm going to make one.
I'm on the way to the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the
Under the bottom of the bottom of the lower, up the bottom of the top of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the top of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the top of the bottom of the top of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom and bottom of the bottom of the bottom, and bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom of the bottom.
ㅋㅋㅋㅋit
Well i've been pushing it over it down for a couple of days
yeah, that sounds like you got under the bar nub.
yeah
damn
you out
its backlog
I know i think i saw a car
what did i film with?
Where?
The vehicle is right there.
It's a place to take off.
I might not know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I might not know what you're talking about.
I don't know what you're talking about, I don't know what you're talking about.
The wind is so weird, I think.
Okay, shall I have a list of them?
Yeah, ready?
Can I go to the barrel and you can go to the station?
Yeah, I must have a bike right over there.
Okay, that's more than sufficient.
That's okay.
Make sure to don't get the roll.
The first minute case is alive is alive.
That's alive.
Another minute.
You better know it's number eight.
Everything is similar to my demo rules.
Okay, if you're alive, you're not.
There are six minutes to go.
That's five.
Seven zero.
If it nine, don't send nine.
Okay, bro.
Okay, that's the base.
Be careful.
Here's your tactic.
There's all the right to fly.
If it's up there, it's zero.
Yeah, if it's okay.
Okay, that's all the right.
If it's up there, it's five.
Yeah, see a minute, I'll do it.
Yeah.
Let's go, look at this one.
Okay, if you're five up here, turn left now.
Off drive the grids.
This is sufficient.
No much.
Okay.
There we go.
Five to five.
There's seven hundred.
The level of a drop now.
Okay.
On to the power.
You do the.
It's okay.
Okay.
Here it is.
Okay, power.
Yeah.
Okay.
Four.
One, two, one.
Five.
Four.
Two.
Three.
Four.
One.
Two.
Four.
Okay, that's left.
One.
There's a railway track down there, and this is an highway up there, which is so built in the front of us.
Yeah, it's about 10 o'clock.
You picked that one about that.
That's it.
I'll see you for the fun.
You can see the fun.
Yeah.
It's limited.
That's it.
Walk this with it to green.
There's a lot of fuel.
Yeah.
It's very long.
We're on the internet.
We're here.
We're going to take my car.
Can we get this car?
a
system
I think it's a nose up, it's an over at the zone, it's a name of Leck and I'm on, okay, it's free to suppose it's a thing.
No, we have the brakes, but you have the brakes.
Die, you give us a different brakes, yeah.
Brakes with gear down, yeah, with the brakes on, got it, I was saying.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, through.
What do we have next?
In the case?
Yes, yeah.
Move it.
Yeah.
We have a front.
That's what?
One, two, three.
Three, two, three.
We have fuel.
That's a bit, okay, turning left.
Now we're heading south.
We're in this name of the car.
Up at secret.
That is this base.
It's a pressure that the engine starts.
So you can say it's a lot faster.
I'm going to use the hazard.
Okay, the valve is not too hot, yeah.
Open the exhaust pressure on it.
That's right, right at factory control, yeah.
So lift it.
No, that was right, no problem.
That would be more direct.
If the clutch energy is on, then it doesn't hit tomorrow,
so it's like we alone do.
What's the bar on that?
I don't think we're gonna roll.
Yeah.
Move it.
Do you want to play me in the name again?
Yeah, I'll play you up.
Uh, okay.
No, I'm glad we should actually see this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, we call that traveler.
Uh, Yeah, yes, yes, not working that way yet.
Nice to meet you, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes , yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Uh, yeah.
Let's go!
The light is a little nervous too.
Okay.
The noise is a little less nervous.
Oh, that's it. That's it.
Now we have an attitude.
Yeah, how do we get rid of it?
That's all for now.
All you have to do is hit the corner.
That's it.
Hey, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
Open the window.
You'll break eventually, right?
Yeah.
I think we should be close to the camera.
Wow, I was killed.
Yeah.