Well, hi everybody!
Welcome to Amsterdam where the show is originating from today.
I am at what we call the bunker bringing you your daily source code.
Got a lot of stuff lined up for you today.
First of all, the reason I'm in Amsterdam is because I have a meeting tonight at 8 o'clock
with a couple of friends.
We've been working on a TV show that we've been testing out on the net.
We've been just using Final Cut Pro and all the typical weblogger type material and tools
to make this television show.
We're discussing making a pilot and we're doing that tonight.
So it was easier for me to come up here and stay overnight and then go back tomorrow.
And tomorrow I have an interesting meeting with a publisher here in the Netherlands.
the iPod platform and audiobooks which is there's no audiobook culture here at all
no one has really ever ever successfully gotten that to fly here so that's the
reason I'm here but so you also hear some some of the sounds of the Street of
Amsterdam I'm in our canal house which is right overlooking the canal and so
there's all kinds of traffic boats and you know by the time the music dies
off you might be able to hear some stuff. Got CNN going on here on the
on the left I see testimonial on Capitol Hill about the Afghan election
okay so we've got all the multimedia stuff rocking and rolling and then let's see
on the health side not too good the news today
personal with the family, although the extended family, first of all, tomorrow we
have to put one of our dogs down, Chrissy, who is a Maltese. We've had her for
15 years. Life expectancy of the Maltese is usually no more than 12 or 13, yeah,
at the max 12 or 13 years. And in the past year she's really, yeah, she's
really deteriorating. Her health is deteriorating and she's now deaf and
blind and when she's awake she cries a lot and so it's just time. It's just
time. So that's sad. So I had to say goodbye to her today when I left. And
Patricia called me. She called me earlier. One of the six black baby swans that we
have was either attacked or did
but she had to fish it out of the water and it was still breathing and still alive but
not doing too much.
And so she'll give me a status report on that, I haven't heard anything yet.
But that's a bummer.
And quite honestly, this is the first year that we've actually had all six live to
this stage.
Usually, it's a bummer.
get just eaten up when they're small, you know, either by fish in the water, believe it or
not, or other prey that's just roaming the premises.
Yeah, it's nature.
And nature is so hard, man, because what Patricia did is she then got the mom and the dad,
who we call Fred and Ginger, and she, because they walk with her and they hang out with
her all the time.
So she lured him over to the baby and she...
walk right past totally ignoring it. So that's the tough, tough way that nature is. And then finally
on the on the health on the health topic, my mac is sick. It really is. And I don't think it's good.
And it's giving me all the signals that it's really just not feeling well.
And I wanted to blog about this, but it's so difficult really to explain, you know,
when just little minute things are going wrong. And it all started, of course, when we started doing
this this audio recording and podcasting and downloading gigabytes of files or somewhere
something something's hosed. I'm just not sure what it is. Now I've looked around at the
Mac health forums. I've Googled this, of course. Here are the symptoms. Every once in a while,
the machine may freeze up for just a second or two. That happens. But that doesn't seem to be
that related, although I'm sure it is somewhere deep down. But that
That's not when the problems start.
But eventually after I've been using my Mac, no matter what
I'm doing, then it seems like the Finder will become useless.
In fact, you can't launch any application sometimes, or ones
that are clearly on your screen.
You can't activate.
And then, for instance, I can't activate Safari, but I
will be able to log out or request a log out or request
a restart.
But then I can't actually activate the restart
window and have to wait in 120 seconds before it
does it automatically.
So there's something with the Finder.
I also thought something with the Dock maybe.
So I trashed Plist files.
I got Cache Cleaner and deleted all the files.
Even though I'm sure I deselected delete browser caches, virtual memory, swap files, everything's
gone so that's all cool.
I ran several set permissions programs, that's not it.
Now here's another one of the symptoms.
Software update has been trying to install the Java 1.4.2 and I know there's been issues
with that.
Whenever I say install, it pops up once every other day to install this update and I'll
click the install button.
It'll go gray for a couple of seconds.
It'll come back blue and then whenever I click it, it goes gray and comes blue.
problem. And I've gone through just about everything I could find every tip on that.
Even though I can download an application and drag it into my applications folder and fire
it up from there, unless of course that finder problem kicks in, I can't install packages.
They just, I get all the way to the install part and then the same thing happens. So
there's something with some, that's why I thought it was the permissions, but that's
not it. And then eventually just to have the machine function even though it's
not, and I must say that it's running much better now. I ran cache cleaner.
It's running, I mean, so much smoother and the secondary fan isn't kicking in.
Upon some recommendations that I read I deleted some key files in the library preferences folder
For finder for doc for a couple other things
So I'm kind of out of loss here one other thing
When I I have the console log open and
Earlier I'm not seeing it now
check
I do have the jack server from the jack tools it's saying it can't connect to the default jack server
But that shouldn't be a problem that it's logical because I don't have the server running so
It does try that every every other you know a couple of minutes
No, it's not saying it before
It was giving me a PA a power management
Error of course, I didn't capture it. Oh, is there a history to this? Maybe there is a history. Hold on
Caesar console history quickly
I guess not
Ah, damn, okay.
Then maybe somewhere.
And lo and behold, and I've had this happen a couple of times, I put my Mac to sleep before I drove up to Amsterdam, and then it won't wake up.
It'll wake up, and you can hear the drive cranking up, you can see your mouse, but the screen really stays black, and then you never get the login screen, it just goes back to sleep.
Try it a couple of times, and then eventually wind up having to do a hard...
So those are the symptoms and then after you do one of those hard resets, then of course it's coming up with the famous
orphaned indirect node
warning and the
I should have written that one down
Well anyway, there's some file that is, I guess not right, it takes a long time for it to scan the disk.
more of the same happens. I've also done the boot in single user mode, done the
Fisk the disk, all of that. So I don't know, you know, it's it just happens after
every once in a while. And of course I'm sure if I reformat everything and
reinstall the OS, I'll probably have a perfectly good machine back. But damn,
what a lot of work is invested in. How much time will it really take for me
to, you know, to restore all those little things I have running. So it's sad.
It's sad when your Mac gets sick. If anyone can help, please let me know.
Alrighty, this is your daily source code where users and developers party
together, also known in some circles as a soliloquy. So I figured we play the
ultimate soliloquy song for today. Can't even pronounce the damn word
soliloquy.
So when it comes to being a lot is to be myself and I
Be myself and I
We must open up
Now, use your plug one style
Wear my plug one style
Because you're the one that you are
Hit these luggages
What's the matter?
You shouldn't have to be forthin'
And you're fast no more
So why don't you really come to
Let's go
I'm not sure if you can hear me.
And from me myself and I
Glory, Hallelujah, Glory, Wokla, One, Two
I know this so I point at Q-Tip and he stays black as black
You're a mirror on the wall, chup
Rima Shottuna
Lady Miskir and the gang of De La Soul, me, myself and I on your daily source code for
Wednesday, the 29th of September 2004, coming to you from the city of Amsterdam.
Oh man, we got so much to talk about today.
So many bits, so many clips.
Let me see, what do I have next?
In my refer log, from my weblog, I came across a link from something called The Linux
Show.
I think I've heard The Linux Show before.
Once I went to the website, which is a little bit confusing, I remembered that indeed Doc
Searle's is one of the co-hosts or kind of like the Gilmore gang.
the past. It's something that I can listen to occasionally, certainly. And I saw that
on the lineup for the show, or maybe it was the evening before, I think it was Tuesday,
so when did I catch this? Maybe I caught this this morning, I don't know. This podcasting
in time shifted mode and I don't know what I said to who or when. Or who's on first
days. So I decided to check out the Linux show and about 46 minutes into it I was
rewarded. It's interesting because what I like listening to is how
people of all walks of life perceive iPodder and what we're doing with
podcasting. And so these are some hardcore geeks. It's a mixture. I don't know how
hardcore docksurls is when it comes to Linux. I mean I have to say I have built
a Red Hat kernel many times myself so I think that's reasonably hard.
hardcore, putting in video device drivers, etc.
And he comes into something really nice, which I have a follow-up to.
So check out this little bit from The Linux Show, and Doc Searles is going to talk about
his story of the week.
Yeah, the story is actually, as it's so often is with me about radio, I'm here in
this hotel, in this hotel, and I was just bored by NPR, and then I got bored by Howard Stern,
and I got bored by several other things.
And there's a lot of interesting stuff I haven't been paying some attention to, but not enough
that Adam Curry has been working on for what he and some others have been calling the iPod
platform in a generic way in the sense that there's a personal player that can be filled
with files that the user can listen to with their discretion.
And actually, I asked Kevin several weeks ago what percentage, how many more people
download The Listen Live to the Linux show.
And he said quite a few more do listen to the downloads and do listen live.
This is a very interesting point.
And this is the one thing I noticed immediately when I went to the Linux show website,
which I think is the Linux show or linuxshow.com or .NET.
I'm sorry, I don't remember what it was.
And I'm afraid to fire up Safari at this point in the podcast.
But you know...
you could download like M3U files to get the streaming version or you could listen to it
live and really, see there's no benefit listening to it live, although yeah, maybe I guess if
you have a call.
make some sense. But it was actually kind of hard to find the downloads, the MP3s.
And once I did find them, lo and behold, I couldn't find an RSS feed of these archive shows.
And I thought, wow, what an opportunity. And here they are. They're talking about just
that. Yeah, well, maybe we should do that. Well, yeah. More people seem to be listening
to the download. Man, this is, you guys are so right for iPod. Just let me know.
I'll be happy to help you out.
And that's true with almost everybody who broadcast live and also archives it.
There's this other show I do called the Gilmore Gang with Steve Gilmore and several
other people. And that's also archived. And once again, many more people
listen to it on their own time. And Adam's show, Adam, you might remember
his name. He was an MPV VJ, many, many.
Okay, I just want to say thank you. Doc, thank you very much. Thank you very
much for setting that straight. I want to mention that Doc is
a radio guy. He knows a hell of a lot about radio, particularly in the United States.
And we're going to get into that, some of that. He's going to start talking about that
in a minute, but first he's going to say something about the work that Dave and I have been doing
and stuff.
years ago. He's quite a figure in Holland in the Netherlands where he makes his home.
Like me and a lot of other people in radio, he remains a base of thinking for him as we
keep coming back to it.
Exactly. And I've said this to many different people. In fact, when I met Dave Weiner and
saw that his, I don't even know if we called it a web logging tool at the time, well actually
I met him when it was Frontier 4.2 or 4.7. I think 4.2 before it became RadioUserland.
I said what a great name. I totally understand this. Web logging is like radio. You just
open your big blabbermouth, you throw some shit out there. Your jingles are pictures and
bits and stuff. That's what we call packaging. That's what it is. It's packaging.
So, you use the HTML for packaging and you have different feedback loops, you know, with
comments, with sending email, with trackbacks.
So this is something that radio people totally understand.
And you're also performing the act of soliloquy.
The first thing that he's been doing is basically his ramblings in the morning on
the net.
And the one this morning, several things kind of coincided.
One is that he's been working with Dave Weiner on using the enclosures capacity of the RSS
Duplino standard to create an open source product for OS X.
Now, what's funny about this is that Dave and I have been working on enclosures for RSS
for five years and been preaching this stuff for a long time.
Now the downside is what...
What Docs about to say is that we've created something for OS X and my question has been
answered about the Windows versions and by either tonight or tomorrow.
to the, so the Windows users when they come to iPod.org they understand immediately yes,
there is a Windows client.
But at this point, Doc believes it may still only be OS X, which means Mac only, which
is not a good thing from an iPod or development standpoint.
But let's continue.
I'm called iPod or I think.
All the nouns get, I'm not looking at the computer right now and get confused if I do.
But there's a, but the idea is that you, you know, you get the RSS feed, like it's
a, you subscribe to an RSS feed for this show.
It doesn't stop in your computer just goes straight to your iPod.
Now conceptually, the standards are there.
Any, any Linux hacker listening to this can make it happen for Linux and
use AUG or whatever, you know, I mean, that's not a, that's not a problem.
It's a, it's a real opportunity and that, and coincidentally in the middle of all
this, finally, Dave Weiner open sourced with the GPL, the code base to
the frontier, which is the, the scripting and development system with which he
developed Manila, which is what's used to, it was my blog run time.
It's a really big project and it's a really...
I want to salute Dave for doing that.
Andy, I mean, he's been meaning to do it for some time.
But for using the GPL as well, that was a cool move.
So that was tied in with it as well.
Okay, so that's interesting that Doc says that was tied in with it.
And the question is, of course, is there any such thing really as coincidence?
I don't believe in coincidence. I really don't believe in coincidence.
I've had too many coincidences take place.
I just can't believe in coincidence anymore.
I also knew that Frontier was going open source.
I've known it for a long time.
I think there was actually a point several years ago
where Dave was seriously thinking about doing this.
And I learned to script, if you can call it that,
just look at the iPod or Apple script and that's my work.
But I learned to do this. I actually did it in radio.
I started looking at it a little bit when...
before radio was born and it was Frontier.
And Frontier is essentially, what interested me about it
was that it was cross-platform.
So anything you scripted out in this development
environment would work on a Mac and on a Windows machine,
on a PC.
And at the time I was starting to get interested in P2P
and sharing and also web logging, although I didn't know
what it was at the time.
And although Dave Weiner was beating my head with,
you know, look this company you've got that's listed
on NASDAQ, the way you're creating things is highly
inefficient and you need to do it this way.
And perhaps we had a bit of not invented here syndrome.
But I think I just didn't really understand really.
Yeah, I just didn't understand what he was saying.
I couldn't quite grasp the concept.
It took me several years.
But what was wonderful about this, it wasn't really
something you installed.
You kind of like down.
loaded this application and you just double clicked on it and it was running and then
anything you did with that environment would just work.
And it also talked to the file system.
It talked to Apple Script.
You could run Apple Scripts within it.
And so I was introduced to the concept of upstream folders.
So basically a magic folder that's checked by some thread that's running every couple
seconds or every minute.
So I really started to understand a bit about scripting and saw that it's just a language
you have to learn and what, as I continued and did more and more, I've created so many
radio user land hacked up things that, you know, it's one thing I really covet is my
radio dot root file.
I backed that up all over the place all the time because there's so many patches and
bridges and stuff that I've built in there.
I'm afraid if I ever lose that then my life will be destroyed.
You know, there's just one ball of string.
because there's an object database in there.
And that's really nice because you can access that directly.
Frontier developers will know that I understand what
pta means, page table access.
Anyway, so as I started to look more and more and as I actually got closer to doing iPod,
Dave was going to do an open source release of Frontier.
I was really looking at this saying, man, this would be so perfect because think about all
the things that are already in there that we need for iPod.
I think the aggregator code is maybe even a part of the open source release I have
to check.
the one that you access through Manila is put it that way because Manila of course
I believe will remain a commercial product from user land.
It's awesome, you know, it's at least it has all the stuff there. I use it, I like it.
It has all these, you know, these whacked out TCP calls you need to make an XML RPC
and it parses RSS and OPML and just all this all the web stuff that
that we use and that we develop for every single day is in there and I believe that
you know if I can
than any user can and and it's of course it's the way the future.
Doc Searles actually has a website about this, the Deweyers.
But Google it, Doc Searles, I do it yourself, DIY garage.
And that's how I created iPodder.
And thank God we got a whole bunch of smart people into a group to continue this work and
improve upon it and come up with new ideas and have a much faster development cycle,
that's for sure.
But I needed something that I could get out there that wouldn't cost anything for
anyone to just try out.
And the frontier release just wasn't there at the time.
And to do it on radio would mean you'd have to download a copy of radio and
you have to register and
wasn't the right way to do it. So that's why I chose the Apple script. Of course, severely
limiting myself to the Mac platform while doing so. And that's been solved by Pearl
and predominantly Python. I see that as... And I think isn't Python... Wasn't that invented
in Holland? Isn't the...
I thought he was at least and I've looked at Python and I haven't actually developed anything in it
But I think I could learn that and it seems like a great language
one of the things that
that I've always liked about
Frontier and radio is that you know is that you could incorporate?
the not only just Apple script but also the
OS X shell so in fact in the iPod or script I believe the way I download the files is by
Using a command line. I forget what did I use for that? It's it not get Earl
Whatever the improvement is of
Links remember links minus D that would download your file
Actually, I use the the minus there's some other switch in there that I use curl like that's what I use curl
Some other switch that checks to see if it's downloaded a partial portion of the file and will actually resume the download
Those I think that was actually a thread on the iPod or develop developers list
the other day. So I've been looking forward to delving into frontier. I don't know if
I'm going to have time to really focus on it before the end of the year because we've
got the move, we've got blogger con, there's all kinds of stuff happening and I have so
many fricking podcasts I have to listen to every single day and I love it by the way.
I just don't know if I'm going to have time because essentially what I've been
invited to do now that this is open source and you can check it out at
kernel.scripting.com and everyone's invited is you can actually bake some of this
cool stuff right into the kernel which was just apparently is supposed to be
megatons faster than doing it in the scripted way but of
course you have to program C I think. There's a couple of different and
everything's explained and it's just a huge huge code base and it really is I
think at least for as long as I've known him Dave Winer's life work.
And I don't know what he expected it to become,
but I think he's doing the right thing by putting his baby out there to the rest of the...
Actually, a lot of emotional stories from people about how much they lived with this code base.
I think we probably had a very similar, very similar to the iPod or Dev group,
where people just getting along and hanging out and having a good time and creating something that was groovy and worked well.
where. And I think that this, that that community is still there. I certainly want to join
it. I want to learn how. And I was listening to Dave's morning coffee notes for, it was
actually two days ago, the 27th is when it's dated. You can check it on his web log. If
you haven't subscribed, you should subscribe to his.
with your iPodder. And he told the story about releasing this and it's a very personal, very...
It points even, I think, emotional tale and what he really wants to come of this.
And I wanted to play a little excerpt from it. In all, it's about 30 or 40 minutes and it's really
worth listening to because it really sets you up to understand what the culture is behind this
code base. And he does talk about a couple of things that I think any developer that is
working on iPodder and even some users who may just be interested in checking out...
And I think that this may be something that we should look at particularly because of
some of the integration capabilities that it has or will have and the cross-platformity
of it.
We might want to look at this for developing the podcasting side of iPodder.
I just want to drop an mp3 file.
I think I should do is create the mp3 file set the metadata you know the id3 tags and the rest should happen by itself
Right now I spend so much more time doing other things getting it up there that you know
There's just a lot of
time to be to be one doing that and and hey fuck it time is money, okay?
So I want you to listen to a bit of Dave
Talking about the frontier open source release this software just wants
Two things it wants to be preserved and it wants to have a chance so
It doesn't want to take anything away fact one of the projects that I've listed on great things to have would be
to have Python run inside of the frontier environment and
Believe me if you look closely it makes a ton of sense
Python is a wonderful language. It's very philosophically compatible with
The approach the frontier takes
I
Think frontier goes a little further
Python says that white space is significant which I think is a very good idea
Frontier agrees, so much so that there are no curly braces and semicolons in the language,
although there actually are.
But don't tell anyone.
And I mean, you can enter them if you want to.
You don't have to though.
It will generate them for you.
And other languages like Perl and Java and C-Sharp and so forth, all would make sense
in this environment.
It is that, an environment.
So all are welcome.
What else?
So what other ideas are there?
A Linux port would be great.
And how about baking in a BitTorrent server inside of Frontier?
That would be something I'd love to see.
In other words, let's make BitTorrent as easy, setting up a BitTorrent server as easy as we possibly can make it.
So that they'll...
See where I'm going?
There'll be lots of BitTorrent.
server. So when I want to publish something and release it under bit.torn, I shouldn't have to do
anything other than just drop something into a folder and have it immediately be recognized and
then have the proper .tor file be generated or is it .tor? I never really remember. Be generated
and published and you know make it so that it's absolutely effortless to do that. Would be wonderful.
Just some ideas. I'm sure there are plenty of others. In terms of forks.
Okay. Before we get to this, to the cutlery, I encourage you to listen to that
morning coffee notes that Dave did. I heard it this morning and I was like,
wow, you know, this
emotional stuff but it's cool because it sets you up and it gets you really in the mood to
go and do something with it.
And I like that idea of a bit torrent being baked in.
I thought actually, I don't know if it's true.
Oh, hold on a second.
I had a feeling that there was some kind of P2P hooks in there already.
I don't know.
Definitely worth taking a look at.
Pernell.scripting.com.
Okay, I want to bob back for a second to the Linux show just briefly.
Remember, Doc Searle's Radio Guy, so he has the same senses that I do about...
It's an industry.
You grow up in the radio industry and they're just like any of the music business.
There's our version of the Amit Ardagan from Atlantic Records.
We've got the big program directors, the big music directors.
Although that's diminishing now that everything is becoming clear channel basically.
And we have that.
We've got Clear Channel, we have the NAB and lots of Radio Guys.
I'll talk about it later.
And especially the morning show guys. Hey, man. I had doing as you know, what's going on in Margaret Matt?
So that's kind of like the radio jargon.
And Doc and I both understand that very, very well.
And he's going to go into some interesting points that I think that I've not in the same
words, but I've certainly touched on in the past couple of podcasts of the Daily Source
Code.
And it probably pertains to your life as well.
We're thinking this.
And I suddenly realized what it was that had happened to radio,
that I...and what this represents.
I stopped listening to music radio for the most part about 20 years ago.
And now I'm stopping listening to pretty much all of it, except when I'm sitting in the car and I have no choice.
Well, exactly. Except when you're sitting in the car and have no choice.
Actually, you do have choice when you're in the car.
You can talk to someone else.
You can soliloquy. You can ask for more cowbell.
You can talk to someone on the phone or you could listen to the radio.
And of course, in direct competition with that is podcasting.
And partly it's because the net has spoiled us for looking at what we want and reading what we want and referring to whom we want.
Why don't I have choices here?
Yeah, exactly. And it is, as Eric knows better than the rest of us,
it's a libertarian playground. I mean, we are all at liberty to do...
with the fuck we please and pointed when we please and listen to what we please and on
our own time, on our own ways and much as we might criticize the iPod, it's such a ubiquitous
prototype in the world for the new transistor radio.
The transistor radio made rock and roll.
I mean, rock and roll happened because of the transistor radio.
This is so cool.
Listen to what he's saying.
This is great stuff.
I think I agree with him.
It's absolutely true.
So what is the iPod?
And we may have to worship this device pretty soon.
In most markets, the rock and roll station was not the biggest AM station.
It was often the smallest one or one of the smallest ones.
They were always the secondary stations in the markets.
Or when they were very powerful in a weird place like XTRQ.
Oh yeah.
Or they had a directional panel.
I used to listen in the 1960s, they used to listen to XTRQ.
Detroit. Yeah okay so these guys go on for a little while about you know what
stations they remember and and how far away they were when they could actually
receive them and hey I'm getting I'm getting mail from from as far away as
Australia
I got an email back here for a second.
Hold on, I didn't want to do that one last actually.
I got an email here from Guy Dickinson and he said something funny.
He's actually been following my weblog for a while.
They say, where the bloody hell is the BBC and all this?
To get the Beves radio output on my iPod, I have to stand on one leg,
stealth record real audio, ick, streams, etc.
I pay a license fee and that content is quote, mine,
can't timeshift.
How long until your podcast model is adopted over there?
Well, you know, I'm moving by the end of the year,
you know, give me a couple of weeks to convince him.
And he also points out another great idea for a podcast.
Then he's actually pointing to, it's a commercial venture,
it's a commercial venture, a company called skinkers.com.
S-K-I-N-K-E.
skinkers only with 2K skinkers.
And he's talking about, oh this is the walk around.
That's what it was. Yeah, the...
So I'm trying to find, yeah, soundwalk.com.
That's what he was talking about.
Audio tours of New York and they have an audio tour of Paris.
And wouldn't it be great to just have walking tours, go out on your city, I mean, check
this out.
But here's, you want to make some cool technology.
You integrate, oh God, I remember this one before, you integrate your iPod or your
iPod with a GPS.
And the GPS has waypoints that you download and are pre-configured.
And as you walk around town, just like in the Wax Museum where you stand close to an
exhibit, then all of a sudden it's going to trigger a file on your iPod.
You know, if you're within proximity of this bridge or this museum or this monument,
boom, it fires off and then all of a sudden you get some.
So a guide, definitely thinking about what we can do with this stuff.
Mail from Ed from Pendengo.com.
And he pointed out Nicecast, which is also a Rogue Amoeba product.
Rogue Amoeba are the makers of Audio Hijack Pro.
And I'd looked at it before and I thought it was just some quick
down and dirty streaming app, which is exactly what it is.
Although if you look a little bit deeper,
at Audio Hijack Pro Lite and they actually it's much easier to understand how to get
your microphone voice over to work and I could record
players that I have with that software. There's really no difference except it
just focused on capturing one application sound and then you can
mix in anything you want you can put the filters in. So definitely check out a
nice cast. Let me see, I had a lot of things here. Who is this? I'm sorry.
Where's my producer? Damn it. Okay, Brandon Fuller, yeah this is something that
pertains to Audio Hijack Pro as well as to nice cast. Brandon Fuller said, you know, I
got Audio Hijack Pro but it will only actually record something when an
application is outputting an audio signal. So for example, if you just want to
record your voice by using the voiceover, you know, iTunes if you're, if
you're hijacking iTunes as it sounds.
source has to be running in order for the channel to open up.
Now I ran into the same problem and you can solve it in a number of ways.
What I've done is I have this mix program called DJ1800 and I just have a track of,
I took a little bit of just ambient noise, just recorded about 20 seconds of that, just
room noise, you can barely hear it.
It's just very, very low decibel level and I copied-paced that about 50 times into
a quick time document. Save that and so now I have this silence track and I just
have that looping in that player and it's enough bits even though inaudible to the
human ear that it keeps the channel open. That's one way to do it. Another way is to
it's to hijack an application that does stay open. A couple of them do that.
In fact it's funny the X10 SIP phone that Dave and I have been trying out.
If I dial one digit then it opens up its audio channel and it stays open for as
long as you want so I hope that was of some help.
Let's see, man we're gonna run along, we're already running long today and there's a
couple things I want you to hear.
and I also have a bit of comedy, actually two bits of comedy.
Around the net, I've been, around the web, I've been reading about John Stewart's appearance
on The No Spin Zone, that's a O'Reilly show on Fox News, and I've read transcripts, you
know, I hadn't actually seen a pointer, couldn't find a bit torrent to it either.
Finally I did today, and as I watched this, I thought, you know, the transcript doesn't
know justice, because you don't hear the nuance and the context that these guys are
talking to each other, and I think the audio, listening to that, will give you a
lot more of the context. Of course without the, without seeing the video,
you're kind of missing the smirky way these guys are looking at.
It was only about five or six minutes, but I'd like you to listen to this because I think
John Stewart did a great job and I think O'Reilly, I think he was left with some egg on his face
because John just hammered him at a couple of points and he was funny about it.
John Stewart for fucking president, I say.
Oops, hold on a second.
I don't think that was recording.
Hold on.
Or actually that it wasn't outputting properly.
Let me just, here we go.
Gotta put that onto, what is it?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
How come I only have the two channel thing?
Let's see if this works.
Hold on, I'm gonna try it again.
Really?
The host of The Daily Show on Comedy Central.
And now, has a book called America,
Citizens Guide to Democracy in Action.
In Action One Word.
Welcome, John.
This of course, I'm sorry.
He's here to promote the audio book
that we reviewed on Source Code before.
Stuart to the nose, spins on everyone.
How are you, sir?
Okay, you know what's really frightening?
Uh-oh.
You know what's really frightening?
You've been reading my diary.
You actually have an influence
on this presidential election.
Oh, that is, that is.
If that were so, that would be frightening.
It is, it's true.
I mean, you got Stone Slacker's,
watching your dopey show every night.
Yeah.
Okay, and they can vote.
You can't stop them.
I just don't know how motivated they would be if these stones flackered.
Yeah, it just depends if they have to go out there.
You did the research, you know the research on your program.
No, we don't.
87% are intoxicated when they watch it?
Oh, no, see, no, I didn't realize that.
Yeah, we have that there.
We come on right after, I believe, the puppets that make crank calls.
Yeah.
So we are, I think, the appropriate follow-up.
Yeah, and it's a great lead-in for you.
I have to put your vote.
You can't vote, but these dopey kids who watch it, can't?
Actually can.
In Florida they can.
You can't vote.
vote Republican and they haven't committed a felony and they haven't
committed a mess attack. But you do have some influence. Now how do you see that?
You have influence. John Kerry bypassed me and went right over to you. You're only
four blocks away. He said, O'Reilly, I don't think so. Stewart.
Again, I mean, no disrespect. The snack selection backstage, quite frankly.
You know, listen to O'Reilly, how fucking jealous he is. I mean, he can't fucking
stand that this is happening. I don't want to say Guantanamo Bay, but it's a
little fair back there. It's close. We want people to be hungry when they come out. I
think that's why. We have what I like to call a snack size, three musketeers,
some snickers, some Milky Ways. If I were presidential candidate and I had to
choose, I think a place that had an energy pick me up might be the place I
would go. Do you think that Kerry does himself any good talking to you? Because I
think most of your audience can vote for him anyway. If I thought,
Lackers, if I thought honestly that their strategy hinged upon his coming and
talking to me.
I would suggest that they are in some deep trouble.
I don't know, I feel like if, you know,
we're not, we don't have an agenda of influence.
We, if we have influence, it is peripheral.
And I don't imagine that people who watch the show
are watching it to make up their minds in terms of
who they think would best prosecute the war on terror.
I think they watch to see who would maybe
have the best jokes on the war.
No, here's what I think they would.
I've been on a show a couple of times.
I mean, you obviously make fun of everybody.
You're, you're, you know, I'll make it fun of your show now.
But you are a show that your target audience is younger,
left leaning, so you have to play to the choir sometimes.
Well, the real estate is younger just because it's company-
And it's at 11 o'clock at night.
I don't know if it's left leaning.
Foxworthy and all that, you consider that a red state show.
You know that it's Foxworthy and Bill Angle.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
There are lead-in on Monday nights and there's really no difference between.
Okay, but even so, younger people tend to be a little bit more, you know.
When you say younger, you're talking nine times.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I'm talking 18 to 25.
Excellent question.
Excellent.
This is the shit you got to watch out for on television is people just throw
stuff out there, throw, I mean, what the fuck does he know?
Did he really look at the demographics of John Stuart's show?
I have some doubts.
Why do you have such unicycle?
Yeah, some French, we're boycotting French so I couldn't answer.
By the way, I think I couldn't agree with you more about the French thing.
They are such an important country and I think really deserve a boycott.
This is classic John Stuart and he's going to grill O'Reilly about, you know, hey,
why are we making, well listen to what he says, this is fabulous, fabulous television.
The influence they wield in the world.
Well, you know, I know you don't do a variety of cheeses.
I know you have to have your breed before you go on.
Honestly, I do really believe France is in any way worthy of a boycott.
I do.
I think France has really hurt the USA to be well-sealed.
Really?
Yes, I do.
More than Saudi Arabia.
You would advocate a boycott.
I'm not going to say more than Saudi Arabia, but I'm
we're a question for revolution they haven't been our friend okay
right on the right on the other side of the area
yet again he bypassed me so i took it personal yet when i would talk to you
and i are not competitors but but well i'm a lot of our second rerun on the
factors i don't mean it in terms of we're not competitors in terms of
content your new show that we are a competition but what do you want the
audience to get out of your discussion with terry just yuck's or anything else
uh fuck you first of all i so rarely refer to it as yeah
yeah and i think you should be content okay i'm sorry about that arcane term
uh schnicks we call it schnick schnicks and giggles
thank you all right uh i am very uncomfortable
going more than a couple of minutes without a laugh
because uh the same weakness that drove me into comedy
also informs my show so that same what we call neediness
neurosis if you're not hearing the audience laugh you get a little nervous
that that that would be exactly correct now because it is
heart, a comedy show, but it's a comedy show about things we care about. So naturally it's
informed by relevant issues and important information. What do you think Kerry wants to get out of
coming on your show? Like what he wants to get what any politician does. Access to a
new constituency. He wants to get what any black marketer. That's exactly right because
the stone slacker's this election is going to rely on the undecided. Who is more undecided?
Right now they're thinking of themselves ice cream or pretzels.
Don't you think that these guys want to be hip when McCain goes on with you?
Bush hasn't been on with you, right?
You would have remembered that.
Well, George Bush?
Yeah.
I don't recall the...
But McCain's been on. Yes. Okay. Kerry's been on as we mentioned. Yes. I've been on. So you've had the three most powerful people beside him on
That's probably right. What do you think Kerry wanted to get out of it?
Hug?
Just a sweet hug. I'm sure what he wants out of it is again that access to it's the same thing that Budweiser wants out of it
Oh, there you go. That's exactly right
That is the point that he was so good that he made that the same point that the same thing Budweiser wants out of it
Exactly, John. Good at Dell computers. No, it's access to this market that may be untapped
An untapped potential a reserve and an Anwar if you will he wants to drill in an area that has previously been
Undrilled and don't make a dirty remark about that because I see it coming. All right, you're welcome
What do you think he wants out of it? I think he wants to be hip. I
Do I think going on your show is a cashier and he's considered to hip or candidate this
And he probably wants to get hair tips from you.
Look at the hair.
All right, John's doing by his book.
Here he is.
And I'll see you on your show in a couple of weeks.
You will see me on my show.
Right back with Dan Rather.
I'm not watching.
So this O'Reilly guy, man, he looked like a total dick in that interview and rightly
so.
And what the fuck does that mean?
John Kerry wants to look hip.
I mean, damn, he's out there selling.
That's what he's doing.
He's marketing.
If he doesn't get that, then what the hell does he understand?
Shit.
OK, source code continues.
Want to make an announcement?
A new show?
Actually, I'll let them introduce the show themselves.
This is GeekSpeak.
All right.
Well, welcome to GeekSpeak.
This is our first show.
This is Scott Alden and Dirk Solco from Solco, from Board Game
Game.
Geek.com and Dirk and I got together and we wanted to do a radio show.
Radio show, cool.
And this is...
Broadcast it over the internet.
And basically what I've been kind of inspired by...
Okay, right.
So it's GeekSpeak.
It is at BoardGameGeek.com and they're podcasting now.
It's low quality.
That's like 16...
What was that?
Is that 16 kilohertz?
Yeah, 16 kilohertz.
So it's a very low quality stream but they have guests on.
And if you're into gaming, I think that these guys really have it down.
I listened to a part of the show and I was like...
I just have no idea what they're talking about.
But it's a great show and they are kind of like the beavisome butt head of gaming.
So give them a try at BoardGameGeek.com.
And as our final bit for today, a comedy bit which came to me...
This is something...
I'm Douglas from Tom from Australia.
He maintains a lot of my archives, my radio shows that I've done throughout the past 20
years.
I don't know where I got this from, but it's some sound advice for sure.
Every time you go drinking in order not to get sick, you have to remember your stomach
is just like the bouncer, right?
And you're having a party.
The party's in your stomach.
The stomach's the bouncer.
Now, when you have a party, you invite your friends, you invite your family because
you know everyone gets along.
Same thing with inviting alcohol into the stomach.
Now you can mix up all the beer you want because they all know one another and they get along.
Beer comes to the stomach though.
Hey, how you doing stomach?
Listen, man, it's just us beer here.
You know, we figured we hang out and stuff.
I mean, you know, you know, Core's Light and Sam Adams and Budweiser and Heineken
and Zelo.
He's crazy, man.
He's crazy.
You are crazy, man.
He's stomach.
It's usually cool with that.
Alright, come on in, but keep it down.
Beer goes in there to have a good time at playing darts, singing songs, but just like
any party, people find out about it.
And they try to, same thing with alcohol.
Next thing you know, couple shots are coming along, you know, loose scotch sometimes.
It's stomach hurts you having a great party on there.
Get in by it, that's just a corner browser out here, see?
Stomach goes what?
What is he talking about?
This is when they come here on your great party, when they come in by a
show in the bank.
All right go in there, but now whenever you mix up crowds next thing you know scotch is walking around
like
Right here your journey one
Your foot looks so lovely
And you can feel the tension your stomach's like all right guys everyone chill out
All right, but now everyone's showing up Yeagermeister
Fuzzy navels and they're partying here tonight
We're a party sometimes sake. Oh, huh that big party here
So your stomach lets them in and now it's getting pretty packed in there and you can feel what's going on
There's some warning signs, but the end of the night
That's when you know who always shows up the most dangerous shot to kill
The tequila never shows up long
There's always eight or nine of them.
Come on man, we won't start no trouble man.
We just came here to have a good time man.
We let them work back in the van.
He was bother nobody.
They're like an idiot.
You let in one shot and then he sneaks in all his friends.
Come on man, ain't nobody looking.
Soon as they get in they're like, hey man, there's everybody.
Na na na na na na
fights and flying next thing your stomach goes all right that's it everyone get
off wait away you came in let's go hot shot there's always like an old hot dog
I've been here for nine years this is ridiculous I didn't do nothing I'll
stomp a mud hole in here behind went out even the air
You alright man? Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Let's go to another party! This one sucks man!
I really wish I knew who that was by.
Let me see if there's now,
there's nothing in the ID3 tags.
And that'll do it for the source code for today.
I hope I'm not keeping you too long.
if you got a comment send it to me adamantcurry.com
uh... my mac account is working again by the way it was
Or you can leave a comment on my weblog, live.curry.com, and check out the archives of this show at
DailySourceCode.com.
And of course you can subscribe to the RSS podcast feed.
It's 2.0 with enclosures.
It's DailySourceCode.com.
So I'll talk to you sometime tomorrow on Thursday.
Take care everybody.
Bye-bye.