Koji is folks wide. It's so time.
That is curry.
The power of the door.
Yeah.
How did everybody welcome to the Daily Source code?
It's Wednesday.
November 24th, 2004.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage in the United Kingdom.
This is the Daily Source code.
It's hard to say that.
Good morning. Good evening. Good afternoon.
Good evening.
I've got a grit, you know.
Someone called me the It's all going to podcast me out of the day.
So I guess it's fair for me to say.
We've got a really great shoe for everybody.
It's all going to ever say it ever.
I wonder if it's the ever.
Oh man.
Still no bandwidth to speak of.
Looks like that's going to be another seven days from this moment on.
Although my phone line now has officially been verified.
So we're no longer on the professional thing.
We're official, which means.
Eventually we're going to get build for having a
A diet of connection open for 23 hours of the day.
Now we're on the door.
We've got a couple of things lined up for you today,
which I think are kind of cool.
We've got some non-RIA music for you.
Which actually comes from the cottage itself.
So talk about that later on.
Got a couple of comments.
Come on, the net.
Oh, and tonight.
At least it's tonight here.
It's 1026 p.m.
We're going to get Patricia in here to talk about.
Well, another one of Patricia's hippie stories.
Actually, I don't think it's a hippie story.
Actually, we were even married.
I think when this particular instance occurred.
Which should be talking about on today's source code.
Something that I've teased before.
It is a her story about Stevie Nix.
So, I'm going to break the rules for just a second here,
while we get into the mood.
A lot of little bit of feet would make.
Did you learn so bad?
Yeah.
You need someone's help.
To lead me through the night.
I need someone's arms.
So let's squeeze midnight.
Don't want the night begins.
I'm out of hand.
Because I need.
Your love so bad.
I need some lips.
To feel next to mine.
I need someone to stand up.
Tell me what I have.
I wear the lights alone.
And it's time to go.
That's what I need.
I love so bad.
So why don't you get it up.
And bring it all to me.
All right, and on a piece of paper baby.
So we can't be left to me.
There will be that you love me.
And bring it all to me.
And stop by the blue fire.
I need someone's help.
To feel next to mine.
To feel next to me.
And bring it all to me.
I need someone's help.
To feel next to mine.
Because I need someone's help.
Yeah, that's a bummer.
I thought there's going to be the full version.
It's like the single version, three minutes, forty-six seconds.
Damn.
Did you love so bad?
Fleetwood Mac on your daily source code for Wednesday, November 24th, 2004.
Oh man, so much stuff happening today.
There were some actually a friend of ours, was in the neighborhood you called up
today.
I'm visiting someone else in the neighborhood, had some tea with them, Patricia and I went
out.
Oh man.
What do we do?
We got all kinds of trash, waste baskets, dog food bowls, we had some grocery shopping
and I'm still totally tripping from the flueberg, although it's much better, I had a sweaty
ass night, literally a sweaty ass night, not good and Patricia just put a clean sheets on
the bed too.
Okay, so let me get Patricia, I'm going to turn on the roving mic here, I'll know
what to say.
On?
It's a big advantage of smaller dwellings, there's even here each other when you call
on.
Huh?
Are you there?
Showtime baby.
Come on, we're on the air.
Yeah, come on up.
I have a mic just for you, it's like really professional.
We should take a picture of this right now, that's horrible.
Yes, of course, he is sitting chair, this is like the guest chair, so it's like the
tonight's show.
Can I just put the microphone on you?
Yep.
Who do I say tonight?
Show.
Let's make sure I can hear you.
Hello?
Hello.
Okay, let me turn you up just a little bit there, let's say.
Okay, so I actually just played the flueberg mic, you do your love so bad.
First of all, what do you think about the United Kingdom, but living here?
Well, so far, I think if I compare it to Holland, I think a lot of Americans think
that Dutch people are so nice, don't you think so and so friendly and we always look like
yeah?
Well, that's because they're confused with Scandinavians.
I think so.
Yeah, or German.
Well, actually, it's the higher up you go the nicer they get when I think they say.
Yeah, Swedes are really nice, and we're dealing with you talking.
Well, it's Dutch.
Oh, he said Dutch now.
No, it's Dutch.
Oh, Holland days.
Oh, yeah.
That's probably confused.
It's the Holland days sauce from Holland?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is it?
But it's so far because we haven't been out a lot.
No, no.
No, because we're unpacking.
Yeah, we've been out.
Between boxes and boxes, we dream of boxes and everybody who moved knows that it's a pain
in the air.
Yeah.
Well, especially international moves.
It's time you're unaware.
You don't know which box it is.
Yeah.
You can't read the things as on it, you know, written by the movers.
See, people just don't understand how horrible that is, particularly for you.
Yeah.
Well, particularly, I think for you.
Yeah, but that's your, you're, you're, you're working very, very organized.
Yeah.
I'm organized.
I am a perfectionist.
I have to say.
And you look lovely in that outfit.
Thank you.
And so it's so hard to sit between all those boxes and, and, can't, it's just not, it doesn't look good.
I, on the other hand, feel right at home.
And we have to say, and they know that we're coming from a castle.
Yeah.
And we try to put the castle in the house.
In the house.
Very difficult.
That's hard.
You know, you can do that.
To say the least.
So what we're going to do is sort of a charity.
We're going to look it up in the yellow pages.
Yeah.
And see if we can, you know, we have to give things away.
Because I was just talking to a friend.
I said, isn't it strange that if you go, say, on vacation or you go in for a weekend, you take one bag.
You have your, you know, your stuff in there.
Your t-shirts and your jeans and, and sort of, and a toilet bag.
And that's it.
And again, and all those days, you never miss anything.
No, you know, well, maybe some clothes, but other stuff.
No, but she don't miss anything.
No.
And look, you know, you're schlepping all this stuff with you.
And find nothing.
Yeah.
Why?
You know, we, we are ants.
Yeah.
Yep.
Money can buy me love.
Exactly.
Okay.
That too.
We brought you here tonight on the daily source code.
And the last time we spoke, we had a hippie story.
The early seven days David Bowie.
And man, thank you again for letting the world know that I am, um, better endowed than,
than David Bowie.
Let me tell you that that has been an incredible go boost.
Yes.
It's very important for me.
And I know there are lots of guys out there who understand exactly what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
And tonight, we have another story from Patricia's archives.
Uh, and this is a nice one.
Which one too?
This is, well, thank you.
We have many more, right?
Yeah.
We have plenty.
Right.
So when I run out of shit to say on this show, then I could just bring you in.
Uh, Stevie Nix was, uh, a store.
It's a short one.
Oh.
Okay.
A shorty but goody.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
It's very short action.
It's, it's, it's not, not really, uh, something, uh, really important.
Am I better endowed than Stevie Nix?
Oh, that's, yeah.
Well, no.
So you have to, this is also about, about size.
Um, I, how long has to go?
We were in LA.
Mm-hmm.
And you had to tape a show for MTV.
Remember that?
We were not married yet.
Oh, we weren't.
Also, this was 1987, 88.
I think it was in the beginning.
Oh, yes.
We just moved to, uh, to New York.
Okay.
So that was 87.
Yeah.
And you had to go out to LA and you took me with you.
Because it was better weather there.
So it was very nice.
And we went out to a lovely restaurant that was one of the famous hot spots that we needed to see.
Which one was that?
The dome?
The dome.
Right.
Oh, it wasn't Lionel Richie there that night as well.
Yeah.
I was so proud of this.
They always said, like, you have to go there because lots, lots and lots.
Yeah.
I don't think it's like that anymore.
I think it's completely, it may not even be there anymore.
Right.
But in these days, you know, it was that day with the sheep.
She hot spot.
Right.
And there we were.
So we were there.
We were in the restaurant.
And who do we with?
Do you remember?
Was it just MTV people Charlie Midnight?
Maybe.
No, no, no, no, no.
I wasn't Charlie Midnight.
I think it was only.
Scott Shannon, maybe.
Dana Miller.
Now, I probably Scott Shannon.
I don't know.
Scott Shannon, everybody.
If I would have.
Back and see you.
Well, maybe it was only the two of us because I told you right away.
You mean just the two of us.
Just the two of us.
Now, so we said there.
And while you ordered, I said have to go to the bathroom quickly.
Ladies, really.
So I have to go to the ladies room.
And while I'm in the ladies room, there were, I think, three doors.
And there were all locked.
One of the doors went open.
And out came Stephen X.
Okay, let me just reset this.
So you walk into the ladies room.
There's three stalls.
All three are busy.
This is it.
Up here.
Did you look underneath to see the fee?
No, no, no, no.
I don't think the doors like that.
No, we don't do that.
Oh, guys do that.
No, no, no, no.
Who the hell?
No, but when you walk in, you want to make sure there's no one in there.
So you look underneath.
No, no, no, no.
They were closed.
So Stephen X.
Stephen X.
I'm like, oh, Stephen X.
I'm just going to do like.
What was she wearing?
No, I don't remember.
It's something black.
I remember that.
Okay.
Was it like her flowing clothes?
Of course.
And so she came out of there.
The door went out.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, she taller than you.
She taller than you.
No, she's tiny.
She's not that big.
Really?
Well, I can't remember.
She's not not a very tall name.
Really?
I thought you were.
No.
Okay.
So she came out.
And actually behind her came sort of a roofed.
So the way terrible smell.
She was like, yeah, she was coming out of the straw.
I was coming out of the straw.
That's the way she came out.
But I had no choice because the other door was.
Stinky Nicks.
So.
Why are you going?
I had to, you know, go into that door.
You know, in that bathroom.
Because the other one, the other one,
They'll do.
And who was the other one?
Like Oprah.
I don't know if I'm a waltz or something.
So I went into that one and the seat was still hot.
I don't know if I felt very warm.
But we have to say, before I sat down,
I thought you were a...
I saw that it hadn't, she flushed, but it was still there.
So that was a big...
It was a hair.
Turling, probably too heavy
to flunk.
And then I said, I'm like, Jesus, you know, you're flushed in these turds.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So every time I see her, I have to think, too.
Turd.
Excellent.
Hold on a second.
That was excellent.
Thank you.
That was an excellent story.
Aren't you proud of yourself?
Well, you know.
OK, we have some other exciting news that happened today.
Today, we bought the masters of Mamboitulliano, the song that you recorded.
Just two months ago, three months ago.
So I was thinking, first time I'm going to play it on the show.
I was thinking, why don't we make it available for anyone to play on a podcast?
Yeah.
It's a good idea.
So it's a big band.
It's one of the different bands.
Yeah, it's up to tell me about the song.
Tell me about how you got it all set up and...
Well, actually, it is from Mamboitulliano's thing.
That was Dutch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do you want to say?
It's so clear.
Rose made a clue.
Yeah, it's late.
Yeah, I also have Frank Sinatra did it, too.
I don't think, I don't know.
No, Dean Martin.
I have Frank Sinatra.
It's a very famous song.
Yeah.
And it's...
I think I have that.
I think a 50's song.
It's always a great.
It's a wonderful, wonderful song.
It's a...
It's a Mambo, which is, of course, more Spanish.
But it's an Italian Mambo.
It's Italian Mambo.
It's an Italian Mambo, yeah.
Okay.
And it's called Mambo.
Well, that...
First of all, this isn't just like some little thing you did here.
You had like everything that all the instruments are real.
Played by the music.
Yeah, it's not like...
It's not like...
It was in real time.
You guys are overdubs.
I thought you recorded that whole thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Life.
I sang it live with it.
Yeah.
And afterwards, I did some backing vocals with Ivan, my sister.
Right.
But I sang it right away with the band.
Like, Frank Sinatra used to do first studio.
That was the band.
That was me.
And...
You did some pickups here.
You must have done some pickups.
Just some insert.
No, no.
I don't know.
No, I don't need some.
That's right, baby.
That's right.
And you're a turd's flush.
All right.
See you.
So we'll be sure to put this up for download.
Mambo, if you don't know.
I just shot.
Thanks, honey.
Thanks.
Mambo, if you don't know.
We're gonna go here on the daily source code.
You know, you should do something with your voice, huh?
Oh, I don't know that.
That's awesome.
Oh, my mic.
It's okay, here's another one.
So we'll at least that under the Creative Commons license,
which means anyone can use it non-commercialy.
We'll choose for that one, not no.
Oh, we're gonna have a DVD out soon.
You know what I'm just saying?
Anyone can use this song in their podcast
that can use it non-commercial as long as they create it.
It's ours, so we can do whatever you want to do.
Isn't that fun?
Yeah, I love that.
That's cool.
No.
We cannot do that.
That's cool.
No.
That's cool, baby.
Anything else?
No.
Okay.
It's nice here in your studio.
Yeah, it's nice.
It's very nice.
Why don't you take off your dress?
Oh.
Okay.
Oops.
I'm gonna have a nice cup of tea.
Yes.
Okay.
All right, see?
You take off.
Let's speak something English here.
Oh, but...
Crazy American.
Yeah.
I have to learn some English here.
Well, sweetie, darling.
Go downstairs.
Okay, yeah.
Could you make me a cup or two?
A cup or two?
All right.
All right, then.
Patricia Pi, everybody.
Alrighty.
Source code continues.
Let's see.
More comedy.
Hello, and welcome to Adam Curry's One Minute Moving Tip.
Things you need to know when you're moving.
First of all, put all of your worldly belongings into cardboard boxes.
Now be sure to tape them up a nice and tight and the way all the way.
What was that?
Look at the...
Well, it looks like that box needs just a little bit more tailor.
Hmm.
More you're gonna have problems getting that through customs.
Just a little something for you, Adam, to help you get through through this crazy move
to the UK.
Good luck.
Boy on.
When you walked in the door and you changed your shoes, you switched to a sweater
and said, how do you do neighbor?
How do you do?
I remember the look in your sparkle eyes that said clearly.
I love you.
Don't do the nice neighbor.
You saw me looking at you.
I'll picture picture up on the wall of the old street standing tall and I'll
maybe go round, spin it away, Charlie.
Oh, Charlie.
Where did you go today?
Well, we played with Santa Wemper walks in the park, you were a gentleman.
We were home in front of the neighbor.
It's pretty slippery, make me feel free.
Chef Brock gets showed and has to bake a pie.
Well, let it elame, give him the evil and neighbor.
You never acted that way.
In the whole world, you said there's only one need and in your world.
I was happy to be your neighbor.
Oh, with the wood with lady Aberlin, lady Aberlin, she was so pretty.
I came home today with a way on my mind, life isn't simple anymore.
But I know where I can find you, you said there's only one need and in your world.
I was happy to be your neighbor.
Oh, with the wood with lady Aberlin, you said there's only one need and in your world.
Oh, with the wood with lady Aberlin, lady Aberlin, she was so pretty.
Thank you, friend.
She was so pretty.
Hey, Adam, I just want to give you the quote unquote shout out from Nashville, Tennessee.
Love your show, love what you're doing, love this whole podcast thing.
Keep up the good work.
Oh, I am boy online.
Yeah, before that, you heard Lassipia's Bitties.
Yeah, my favorite.
I had their whole new album and I'm allowed to play every single track.
So my does all work through them, digging it that was neighbor.
And you know, you should do that.
You go over and say, how do your neighbor once in a while?
We've got new neighbors now.
We've met the neighbors on the left.
Hope to meet the neighbors on the right pretty soon.
Neighbors are a good thing.
Neighbors are important.
Quick plug for those of you that are new subscribers or, well, actually, the reason I'm doing this
is because, you know, you may only be hearing this on Thursday by the time it gets uploaded.
The BBC's Culture Show will be on BBC 2 Thursday night.
So that's tomorrow night at 7 p.m.
UK time.
So 8 p.m.
You're central European time.
And if you go to bbc.co.uk slash culture, I think that's the link.
I'll make sure I put the correct link in the production notes for today's show.
Then you can probably see a reasonable online archive.
What they do with the BBC is they're kind of in the middle of trying to figure out what
they want to do with download.
So they make a download of a show available for about seven days and they take it off,
which is, I guess, is, you know, some kind of loophole in their own policy.
There's also a couple of people who'll be recording a high quality digital version.
And as soon as I get some links, we'll be sure to put that up so you can see it.
I'm pumped.
I'm hoping that it's going to be good.
You never know.
And I talked yesterday about extending RSS and how I was working with August and
Ray of iPod Rex and of course with Dave on coming up with some, you know, some interesting
ways of, you know, adding stuff that we really need for our podcast.
One of them is, of course, what I'm working on is these OPML production notes.
And how do we include that and how can we make iPoders aware that there's a show notes
included with the show.
And I haven't been able to respond yet because of my bandwidth woes.
By the way, tomorrow, right after the trash guy comes and I help him load up all the
ship we were accumulated, I'm going to go into town and, and really hop on the, on the
high speed, high Wi-Fi because I'm, I really need to catch up with my podcast.
So we now have, yeah, we're working on and I'm looking at it right now, the podcast RSS
module, which will be a name space, which I think is going to be really great.
It's really going to give us a lot of the tools that we've been looking for on the
development side of, of ease of use and ease of production and connecting more bits
together in podcasting.
And I guess we'll be releasing this to the iPod of developers list pretty soon.
At first, I, even I had to like, you know, look at this.
Hey, is this right?
Is it really that simple?
This is giving us, if it's giving us everything we want, then it must be wrong.
No, but it was right.
So I'm, I'm way excited about that.
And I just need to get some more bandwidth so I can concentrate a little bit more on this
stuff instead of watching, you know, shit download.
Oh, it's horrible.
Okay.
Boy, we've gone through almost everything I want to do.
Oh, no, there's one thing I wanted to play for you.
And we're currently, what are we at, almost 30 minutes into the show, perfect timing for
today.
And I'll have to look up who sent this to me.
This is like a new, in your face, hard edge kind of poetry.
It's called disillusioned filibuster.
And it's a, I'm pretty sure it's a live performance piece.
It's totally, you know, performance poetry art.
So it's a little bit distorted, so I'll have to work on the levels.
But listen to it and then, you'll catch on pretty quick.
It's, there's no real title to it, but the whole theme of this disillusioned filibuster
is America, your panties are showing.
They're the night outside, we'll be talking about the life in times of really
cars, where one friend checked another friend and said, yo, you're slick of saying
you're saying, well, I'm telling my friend, my country, America, I can't, I can't, I can't
see.
Your slip is hanging.
Somebody is looking at your ass, nation building in Iraq, regime changing in Africa,
closing your eyes to genocide in the far, you are showing, you're ass, you showed it, you
showed it, you showed your ass in territory of war, as when you let refugees from
Cuba come to Miami, but you repatriate the Haitians, what they want to come here, you
said, no, back home, told them they couldn't stay, your slip is hanging America, your
slip is hanging right, you ain't got no problems with Mexicans crossing the barrel
because they can work for you for less than minimum wage, they can get involved in rights
labor, they can get involved in being slaves and indentured servants and that's in
your best interest and number one, they can vote for you, the Mexican vote can get you
elected, so you don't have no problem with them crossing the borders and coming over to
Arizona, no, you don't have no problem with that, America, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't see,
your slip is hanging.
And you think you think I'm the only one that sees your ass, America, look out the window,
I know this is your house in that, you think you can walk around naked and think you can walk around
disrespecting people, think you can act like you want to, do what you want to because you
in your own house, but America, I can, I can, I can't, I can see, your slip is hanging
and America, I'm not the only one who sees your ass, world of news tonight, so I'll show
you, show your ass in front of the morgue, when you commit a war crimes, breaking the Geneva
contract, show your independence of war on TV, show your independence of war on naked, show
your independence of war being disrespected, show your independence of war, maximize your
slip, your slip is showing America, your slip is showing women, when you capture the president of
Iraq and and show them all TV being interrogated, show them all TV appearing weak and
right, right, when he showed us all TV, when they show us all TV, it becomes a
world crime, from America, America, America, I can, I can, I can, I can see, your slip
is hanging, you are showing your ass to the world, and you are showing your ass to the
black caucus too, every time you will meet with you, you are to wrap up, dial up,
take it up in your whole empire, they're lost to it, service can come to the king unless
they are selling, they're showing them respect, instead of showing them kindness, America,
I show them the black caucus, they are ass, and still we are still so vulnerable
to believe that America is the leading authority of morality, do people of morality go
around stripping in front of people, no, no, people of morality go around showing
their ass to everybody they don't like, hey, no, somebody somewhere needs to say
something, somebody somewhere needs to do something, America, America, your slip is
hanging, America, you are showing your ass like you didn't hate it, when a
democratically elected president of Haiti was told he had to leave a coup d'tat
maxi, you want to speak this to this, he was told he had to leave, they, America,
got together with guy for leap and committed a coup d'tat and took the
credit of Haiti out to him and his wife, Milquid, you got to leave or die,
or die, or die, or die, America, America, America, America, I can see, I can see,
your slip is hanging, you have a fight another country for democracy and yet
when we have democracy, a democratically elected president in another country, you
don't support him, you would join your truth because he's not doing what you
want him to, he's not being manipulated, he want him to, and because of that,
because of that, you commit a coup d'tat, America, America, America,
man, man, can see, I can see your slip, your slip, your slip is hanging,
and I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, peace, peace.
Man, that's some powerful stuff, now that is exactly what Paul
Boutin, Boutin, Boutin, Boutin, meant when he was talking about why doesn't
Bano use his incredible voice and power through podcasting to start to change
the world.
Yeah, sure it's great that we can sell a black eye pod with all the YouTube
songs on it, but why don't we add a little something else there, Bano?
Shoot dude, you've got your own freaking eye pod.
Is it just a thought maybe to put something on there?
You know, like, hey, feed the world or something, just put a couple MP3,
I'll do good with you Bano, put an AAC file on there, you know, so it's bookmarkable
and it's D-R-M, perfect, go for it, dude, that would be awesome.
That just blew me away, I mean it's more about Haiti at the end there, but just the whole,
yeah, you know, disillusioned filibuster, pretty interesting stuff.
And that's it for today's source code.
More bandwidth tomorrow as we slipper away the Wi-Fi.
I want to thank you very much for tuning in and subscribing.
I want to thank our guest for today, the Trish and Pie.
By the way, we are married and she does sometimes use my last name, but, yeah, she's a modern woman.
As always, comments are welcome at the Prairie.com.
You know, don't send it to me, you know, just send a link that's probably better,
until I get some real bandwidth.
And again, I'll be downloading lots of stuff.
Tomorrow's, we'll play on the show.
Comments.
You can also leave them on the weblog at Prairie.com.
And of course, the latest source code on the archives or data source code.com.
We can also find out about cast-feed data source code.mums-carSS.com.
We'll check out tomorrow on the source code.
Bye-bye.