Everybody, thank God, it's Friday!
Welcome to the Daily Source Code for Friday October 15th, 2004.
My name is Adam Curry.
Coming to you from Flander's Belgium from Curry Castle
as the girls are starting to tear everything down around me.
The echo is getting larger every day.
We're in the middle of packing up for our move to the United Kingdom
and the drapes are down.
As you walk through the hallways here, you can now hear your footsteps again
as the paintings are coming off the wall.
Gold records, awards, newspaper articles, all that kind of stuff
is all getting put into boxes.
And actually the girls joke at me, my wife and my daughter are saying,
you know, what's going to happen is in about five weeks time.
Everything's going to be done.
The only thing to be left standing when the moopers are done is me standing
over my laptop with my microphone and my iPod and its charging stand.
It gets worse.
So I look towards the weekend and which is nice.
Although the weather here isn't too nice in fact,
this is a kind of dreary day.
And we're entering what I call the tunnel here in the lowlands.
It's kind of like a big car wash.
And you go in, it's just all wet and slimy.
And somewhere near March or April, you start to see the light at the end of the tunnel
and it comes on out.
Anyway, the good news, despite the weather today,
is that we're back with bandwidth.
Yes, welcome to the show that teaches you how to cruise around
Europe on one gig a day.
Because that's apparently what I get.
If you average out the month, having 30 days,
it's 30 gigs per month, one gig a day.
And of course yesterday was a very low bandwidth day.
And today I'm up to 95% of my total quota.
So, hey baby.
Sorry.
You told Mr. Who about the iPod?
Mr. What is he?
Oh, the guy, that's the dude who was burning CDs.
Okay, Christina just came home.
He runs at school with bandwidth.
He was?
His neighbors don't have secured bandwidth, so he never uses his own.
Oh, so he steals their Wi-Fi.
Cool.
And was he going to try iPod or?
Yes.
Now it's iPod.org.
Okay.
Do you want to do a video for my answer, please?
Thank you.
Okay. Well, that was well-timed.
That was Christina.
Cool.
As I was just introing the show,
and apparently her one of her teachers is checking out iPod.
Okay.
Speaking of the move for the house,
and for everything over there,
and also for moving to the UK,
I have to get a couple of references,
obviously you need bank references and stuff like that,
but you also need a personal reference.
And a buddy of mine, actually the first guy who taught me,
or who gave me my first helicopter lessons,
I won't say he taught me how to fly,
but he certainly gave me my first three hours worth of training,
was Stu mold pilot that we'd hired when we had the helicopter company.
Retired RAF pilot,
he denies it, but I'm pretty sure he was SIS,
you know, secret air services and all that shit.
And very nice guy, Brett,
and just to give you a little example of British humor.
So I sent him off an email and I said,
you know, dude, would you,
right now he's flying for the Yorkshire police.
He flies their MD 902 or 900 helicopter.
And I said, you know, would you be a reference for me?
And I said, cousin, you know, we're moving.
And he says, hey, I'm good to hear from you again.
Must say I'm a little shocked,
you're moving to the UK.
Everyone here is looking for a way out.
You do realize the country's full of Arab terrorists running
drug and prostitution rings, the health services failed.
Nurses are killing old folks and hospital beds
to make way for others.
The transport system, any of it, doesn't work.
The police have lost the plot,
taxation has never been higher,
and just when we thought things couldn't get worse,
they are forecasting the coldest winter in the UK for years.
And you want to move here.
Please don't tell me you're going to sell the lovely house in Belgium
or is this another pad you're just thinking of buying.
Anyway, we want to go is really nice.
It's at least it was last time I was there.
Very English and far too expensive for asylum seekers,
I suspect.
We would only be too happy to provide a reference for you.
So long as I don't have to vouch for your sanity.
Give a regards to Patricia who I expect is really delighted
about the idea indeed.
So that's the ride British humor for you.
We got lots of cool stuff to talk about in the play.
In today's edition, we'll probably run about 45 minutes.
And I was looking for the perfect song to play today,
because of course I want to try and find tracks that you remember
you really like, but just don't hear on the radio anymore.
And you don't hear enough super-trap.
Goodbye Stranger on the Friday Edition of your daily source code.
Was it early morning yesterday?
I was up before the dawn.
And I really haven't enjoyed my stay.
But it must be moving on.
Like I came without a castle.
Like I came without a drop.
I'm a dream on another.
And it must be moving on.
Now I believe in what you say.
Is that undisputed?
But I have to have things my own way.
To keep it in mind.
Like I came without an echo.
Like I came without a jeep.
Because I thought I was completely different.
And it seemed after my beginning.
And now I'm going to enjoy.
Like I came without a drop.
And I really haven't enjoyed my stay.
Goodbye Stranger on the Friday Edition of your daily source code.
But it must be moving on.
Now I believe in what you say.
Is that undisputed?
But I have to have things my own way.
To keep it in mind.
And I really haven't enjoyed my stay.
Is that undisputed?
But I have to have things my own way.
To keep it in mind.
And I really haven't enjoyed my stay.
But it must be moving on.
Now I believe in what you say.
Is that undisputed?
But I really haven't enjoyed my stay.
Oh, come true, come here, let's party, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win
let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win,
let's win, let's win, let's win
let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win,
let's win and let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let's win, let
find a Wi-Fi hot spot living in where we live here out in the sticks. Well, unless I had
we'd go war driving I might find something but I'd never really done that in the city nearby
or in the town nearby I should say. So I took advice from a hot spot locator and I was supposed
to be a commercial hot spot at a total gas station on the E19 Highway which runs from France
all the way up north to the Netherlands. That's about 15 minutes from my house so I went over there
of course no hot spot at all and you know go and ask the gas station attendant right.
So I remember that I had installed a couple of EMAX at Christina's old school two or three years ago
and drove over and sure enough popped up the network now the school was closed so I had to
sit in my car because it was raining and the only way to get the signal and I posted a picture on
Curried.com. The only way to get a signal was to roll down the window, have the the butt of the
laptop sticking out of the window about two inches and because it was raining I had my laptop
case on top of it and I had to hold everything you know kind of just so for about 47 minutes.
So it was interesting because I was also downloading ran a run eye part and I was downloading
the latest shows and listening to them at the same time and I was just about you know 20 minutes
to spare on the battery with the upload and the download so glad it made it up finally.
And when I talked a day a little bit about NPR National Public Radio in the United States
and podcasting. Now I've been talking to Tony Khan who has arranged for a podcast feed
of morning stories and you can find that in the podcast directory under radio and public radio.
And the more I think about it the more I realize how perfect this is for public radio because
public radio is although listener supported you know they've got money they've got lots and
lots of money now like any big organization an NPR is huge you know there's agendas and and people
have you know there's nepotism and friends and links and all kinds of stuff so this stuff is not
going to go extremely fast but from the programmers the people who are making the programs
they see this opportunity and they're jumping at it at least you know the early adopters are like
Tony Khan who by the way please I've pointed to his biography before check them out this guy's
a pioneer, a legend, a legend in public radio and I hope it doesn't mind me saying he's been around
forever but he's and we're going to do some podcasting together when I try to do an interview
do a show and he's getting a lot of public radio program makers radio program makers very
interested in podcasting and I think it's a perfect avenue for all the stuff that NPR just
doesn't have time for you know just doesn't have time for and in fact knowing a little bit
about a public radio and having work for several pubcasters the world over the largest problem
public well certainly public radio has is the commercial competition you know because they have
more money bigger budgets and they create lower quality crap so this is the way to you know jump in
jump in early jump in now and expand your audience just so infinitesimally you know you
would expand it so there's such a degree um I really just you know all the all the possibilities
are just completely mind boggling and people are already we're already doing this they're already
and I'm finding these and people sending me pointers to them there are so many different
applications that will record your favorite NPR show you know in in MP3 so you can put on your
MP3 players some of them might even put it on your MP3 player I mean there's a whole service a company that
you know VC and venture cap was invested in um what is it called sound I can't remember the name of
that company I'll look it up I've pointed to it before they let you subscribe so they give you a
proprietary iPodder and probably do some encoding on the files so you can't you know steal them
and they charge you a subscription like well but we're already paying I mean I've I've contributed
to NPR why should I have to pay to subscribe to get NPR when I can you know record it myself and do
that time shift really why don't we as the finance years of NPR demand you know hey this is great
this is where we want our money to go we want it to be on the air absolutely we also want to be on
iPods so so I'm looking forward to doing more with Tony and supporting him and what he's doing
because I'm sure because of his background he has some good connection of his own and it's really
pushing this stuff and there's some technical people on the inside of NPR at least at WGBH
who really understand this and are pushing from from the bottom up as it were and Dave did a Dave
whiner did a an interview with public radio and Minnesota on Future Tense show hosted by John Gordon
and I'll play this for you it's about five five minutes and well Dave of course is playing the
same the same flute you know Pied Piper's here and inviting NPR in again in this piece now they
only have a real stream available and I'm just realizing now I probably could have hijacked that
and turn it into into an MD3 but that may be more fun if if we try to you know go through the
trials and tribulations of playing a real stream together so let's see if it's four minutes and 58
seconds if you want to skip ahead but I think you want to listen to every single word so I'm going to hit
it now it's contacting host let's see if yet loading listening to the internet this is future
tense from American public media on John Gordon it's called podcasting and it might be the hottest new
thing on the internet a podcast is a talk or music radio show that sent directly to an iPod or
other digital music player through your computer it's a new take on the growing technology called
RSS that pushes text-based web content to computers but with podcasting listener subscribes to audio
feeds podcasting derives its name from the popular iPod player so far it seems to be an outlet
mostly for unpolished sounding bloggers and pirate radio enthusiasts hello again it's Brian
support of a podcast and it's October 13th 2004 that opening clip was private life by
Oingo going go go out and look for it. This isn't going to be a standard sort of rant I don't think
I have a point to make don't know whether I will do that successfully or not
some of you probably will want to tune out main stream broadcasters like new station
KOMO in Seattle and Boston Public Radio Station WGBH are beginning to offer podcasts and observers
see great commercial potential in podcasting technology industry veteran Dave Weiner is a
blogging pioneer and a podcasting advocate he says you can think of podcasts as a sort of
Tivo for radio it's like broadcasting the two in iPod and then take it with you wherever you want
and you listen to the shows that you want to listen to when you want to listen to them so you get
you know geographical choice so you can listen to the for example you listen to a radio show on
which is something that you wouldn't be able to do before or you could listen to a radio show
that was local to by for example San Francisco radio station KGO has a talk show that I like to listen to
and if I wasn't Seattle so you know but now I can listen to it because I can just move it over to my
iPod and then take it with me when I go for a walk or when I write on the train or drive somewhere
so it's giving me choice that's the that's the big deal that podcast and we're in a radio
listen to sort of like well I'll take my chances of what's available on the air being like
after the time listening with podcasting I get the control I get the power 10 days ago I'd never
heard of podcasting and in those 10 days I've had several people say you got to do a story on podcast
and you got up your show has to be podcasted now what happened this amazing all this
amazing and it's the first time I've been in the tech industry now for about 25 years and
this is the first time I've ever seen adoption happen this quickly part of the reason it's been
possible is because of the increased communication that we have through these of weblobs
news can travel much more quickly now and so when something new comes along it sort of sparks
everywhere in the imagination like this as or obviously everyone but so many people's imagination
that that it just you know it's a very efficient we have a very efficient communication system now
the reason why everyone's telling you about it is because it's you know RSS which is the technology
that this is built on top of has been something that has been slowly growing through all you know
forms of journalism amateur professional but it's been print because you know it's what it's been
about reading text on a computer screen what's new here is is that now there's a way for a
radio programming to participate in the RSS revolution and so that's why everybody's telling you
that it's time to do it because we want your contact we want your show available this format and
and it's you know and I don't doubt that we're going to get what we want. I wonder if this will be like
other internet applications where yes lots of people will sort of self publish or do their own
radio shows but it will still be the big guys who have the most audience or the most listeners.
Maybe so but at least it'll be a little playing field so that the barrier's entry will be
that substantial. Dave Winner writes the popular weblog scripting news. He also hosts a podcast
with blogger Adam Curry who you may remember from the early days of MTV. Hey Vanessa news
good morning or good evening depending on where you are welcome to trade secrets on that I'm
curry in Belgium. Dave Haskell. Dave Winner at five a.m. in Seattle. You're such a trooper Dave.
This is a speech I'm John Gordon. Okay future cast John Gordon pretty good piece there although
the choice of audio clips of course makes me chuckle you know if you choose all the bits where
people are saying I don't know if anyone's listening I don't know if you care what I'm about to say
so maybe a little bit slanted there for the to accentuate the point but totally understood.
Then I was listening to that a couple of things that pumped in the mind one is on traditional
radio you can train to formats and that's just the way it works you know you have a top 40
station old station classical station talk news news sports all sports you know these are formats
and you don't necessarily and the reason why you have formats let me explain that is because when
people are cruising around the dial that's how they cruise or that's what the belief is is
I just you know I want I want to hear some news now boom you got to hear some news got to be news
immediately and you know when people are going to switch because all the stations in one market
know exactly when the commercials are running on one station the top 40 stations used to have
lights that would pop up that I worked at when the when the competitor was in the commercials
so that we could hit some music so that when people got bored around three minutes in the
commercials that read it to switch stations boom we played the biggest hit we have I mean this
is very competitive environment but so it's always going to be music you know so you're not
going to have a station that when you when you when people are switching looking for a music
station that there's something there that you know they're not expecting or they're not looking for
with the podcast you know you can put everything together make you're on a little specialized
station where it's much more about you know about the personality granted you're probably
going to get less of a wide audience but the audience will be very dedicated to that topic so
that's how radio works this is the beauty of all this I've been waiting this for this to happen
for 10 years since the first day I saw a modem and someone pushing PCM encoded audio through a
56k modem I said this is broadcasting I know how to do this we got to make the broadcast part work
and it turned out completely different I had no idea that it would I thought it was going to be
streaming and then I saw them revenue modeled and work on that and this is clearly the way to go
and and I guarantee you that people with iPods will listen to the radio shows on iPods
through whatever means they get on if it's iPod or something it looks like it as long as
I don't have to pay for it I guarantee they're also going to listen to the commercials just
make them entertaining they can fun again you know you don't you're not constrained to your
22nd or 32nd or 22nd or 22nd with a 10 second tag somewhere else it's you can do all kinds of
new things create be creative every ball that also I just want to say again that the big O wow
factor here is that we as and I'll just call us consumers for a moment here have been marketed that
this you know just the way playlists are set up in in MP3 players you're conditioned to think of them as
tracks as music as you know you can download music and put it on it's yeah maybe the exception
is an audio book but pretty much I think still the whole mass market is focused and has been
conditioned to focus on music as being what you put on these MP3 players and no one really ever thought
about it and then we came along with with his iPod idea and then you know we kind of forced the
issue where once you subscribe then you're going to find out that hey we can put other things
on these iPods and it function is at a whole different device and I think that's what the real
magic is here is people are saying oh wow you know this also and I have something that's even
more valuable than I thought it was and again I think people are just very bored with with the
choice that they have on radio not that radio is boring far be it for me to say that but
certainly certainly needs some more choice let's talk about the cost of podcasting for second
my cost these days is about $10 a show and that's because I use this fancy wireless mic
setup that takes two nine volt batteries and I was buying my regular pair of batteries the other
day I always have four on hand and I looked at the price and I said actually it's more expensive
this five euros per nine volt battery five euros that's like six bucks and I said you know
excuse me why is this so you know why does this so expensive and lady in the store said oh that's
all taxes I said oh really what kind of taxes oh it's it's taxes for the environment
this is legislation that wants to convince you to use rechargeable batteries you know what I am
fucking convinced so tomorrow I go out and buy me some rechargeable batteries because this is just
this is could get an out of hand let's see um right I got so talk about the iPodder.org
directory this is also something very exciting just like the iPodder developers were were you know
developing iPodders now we have other people who maybe not is technically inclined but really
want to help out was what we're doing and they're helping out by building this open directory
through a format called OPML outline process or markup language and Aldo Castaneda had been emailing
me back and forth and he's interested in business and finance and I think he might still be at school
university let me see if I can um oh anyway he did I remember he did ask about making money on
the trade secrets we played an audio clip from him and he's now managing the law uh node as well as
business and finance and he sent me a node here he says uh actually he says am I missing something
technology wise that makes this idea suck and I'll tell you what the idea was of the answer is no
he says he wants an audio update of new stuff in the category and I think that's a great idea so
if you go down to uh if you go into a category and in this case Aldo is hosting that category himself
so if there's something new you could provide a podcast so just another podcast feed which is an RSS
2.0 feed with enclosures pointing to an MP3 file where you can update people on new shows coming
into your directory they'll receive it automatically through their iPod or right uh and you can play
a snippet or something that they will give people a good idea of what um what that's about what that
shows about and then help them uh go uh to your node and subscribe so I think it's a great idea oh
I was speaking of uh the OPML directory um I got an audio comment about that
hello Adam this is Justin Walgreens from Lost Cruces New Mexico
I had a comment on the feedback you played on Thursday's Daily Source Code regarding the fact that the
OPML directory does not have descriptions for the feeds uh I think the directory itself the OPML code should
stay the way it is uh just a list of uh XML RSS feeds displaying the title and the description for the RSS
feed should be the job of the viewer and should not be encoded into the XML itself because people
could change the description on their feed I'm working on my own version of iPod or written in
Coco for uh macOS 10 Panther uh which supports this feature and certainly the web interface that is
parsing the OPML and displaying it at ipod.org could be modified to do the same thing uh so that's
my two cents thanks for listening uh love the source code keep it up. Excellent okay thank you very
much so a couple things there first of all is developing a Coco iPod which is great news and he's
apparently already incorporating the iPod directory OPML into that so what he's saying is that we should
let some of that stuff like pulling in the information from the channel from the RSS feeds uh that
should be handled by uh by the iPod or client and I don't know but I sure hope you're uh posting to the
iPod or developer list uh you can uh just go to the iPod.org home page and you can see uh on the
on the links there's the link to the mailing list so please join that the more the merrier and uh
I've seen a couple other people uh looking at integrating this and uh remember I told you about
the servers that Dave and I purchased oh by the way I'm still not verified now I've uh I'm trying
to get a hold of them to get a fax number to send off my credit card and uh and my passport
being the European that I am um uh Dave is set his up uh uh for podcast pings now if you've ever
been to weblogs.com you know that that's the place that you go to see if a weblog is updated uh
there's an HTML interface so you just go to weblogs.com and it tells you what weblogs have been updated in the
past a few hours and you can step through it to go back more hours if you wish the way this works is
just about all blogging software these days either does it automatically your provides a place
for you to enter a URL to issue this ping now the reason why this is important is because at the
at the back end of weblogs.com is an XML file called changes.xml I think there's also a
recently change or small changes.xml to lower you know the bandwidth on people requesting this file
but with this file that's something that we could integrate into the iPodders so you could do all
kinds of stuff with that you could fire off emails when a podcast you subscribed to was updated
you could make it bold in a window you could just provide a channel guide and say here here's
something new that popped up if it's not in the subscriptions list so a whole bunch of things we
can do and I'm really excited about that and I think I'm pretty sure Dave is going to do some
bootstrapping to get some data in there and this particular source code will of course ping
the URL so you'll at least see my my my podcast show up in the changes.xml so that's kind of for
the developers there also funny Dave recorded actually he I think he even called it is very first
official podcast it was so excited about Google desktop search that he installed it and while it was
running and indexing he he recorded a podcast and he did it on his older machine which I'll have to
say is probably not the most stable thing around or it's it's been known to do some funky stuff
and he's got a lot of shit running on his aggregator and stuff so you know this is why I always
recorded a iFF before and then compressed the MP3 later is because if your machine gets a CPU glitch
you can skip and it'll actually skip in the encoding and most software packages will even tell you
so I'm not gonna play it because it's so hurtful but it was I'm sure Dave was telling a great
story and he was talking about fractional HTTP servers and whoops and how oh no second now I'm
getting the funky stuff here from from my setup okay he was talking about how radio had that in the
beginning with using port 5335 and it was great but it was just skipping through the whole thing
you could barely hear a word he was saying so as far as I can insert so far Google desktop search
which of course doesn't run in the Mac totally blows because it screwed up my life and I think I just
thought Dave posted he'd actually he was able to successfully uninstall it and now his machine is
back to normal but the whole concept I think is good and it's definitely a daring move of Google to
do that unfortunately it doesn't work for the Mac and it's not gonna you know even if it did run
on the Mac it wouldn't track any of my files because it you know it looks for outlook messages and
stuff like that okay we're about 32 minutes into the source codes podcast for today by the way
a lot of people talking about the name podcast where that came from I can't remember who it was
that that that registered podcast dot com so that's the the guy that probably came with it first
Dave slushle remember because he saw it in his refer logs but I'm not actually doing a podcast here
you know I'm doing a podcast you you you must have misunderstood me all right so I said hi to a
dawn of the dawn of drew shade the show yesterday on the source code because he's talking about me
and well they played the clip on their own show and here's a dawn's response
he told me put on this sexy voice the directory yeah he got a quiet because he doesn't want
his wife to hear Adam Curry you're so busted you're right if my wife actually what I was
doing now yeah quite honestly her sister listens and then calls her up and tells her what I said
wait so I'm in love with Adam Curry that's what he says he's out at me he doesn't know if that's
gonna cause me to get divorced then I'll have to move with him we could get divorced on the show
because of that tune in next time to find out what happens in the continuing saga of dawn to
an Adam whoa something's really funky about my setup today home on a second there we go
is it still recording uh that's hard to tell yeah it is oh man this is just not my day okay let's
move along now so that was a bit from dawn and drew here's something really cool that came in on
the portalette podcast now it's a Brian who who does the show he told me that he had to work
as office and he was using a Mac G4Q I have one of those at the office in Amsterdam I love the
machine but indeed it's a lot sorely lacking internal microphone or even a lining put so he'd
have to use a griffin eye mic or some other USB device but he came up with a whole different concept
and I'd never and I don't know if he was doing this on a Mac or if he was using the natural
voices from AT&T I mean I gotta have this whoever put this out I hope it works on a Mac
listen to the quality of this text to speech in the recent portalette podcast
it's October 14th 2004 and this is the portalette podcast Brian had to work late tonight so
he has asked me his computer to fill in for him you'll have to forgive me this is my first time
so I'm not exactly sure what to do now do you hear this I mean I've heard a lot of text to
speech synthesis but this is really good I mean this is like an actual voice yeah it's a little
burpy here in there but it's not hard to parse at all why don't I just start off with a little news
and updates the podcast seems to be going well he has been getting a lot of email from people all
over the place he asked me to respond to the guy who asked about the mixer he's using
it's a six channel and it's made by Samsung now here's what's cool is he has other voices
even with accents and he puts those in and then when they talk together it's it's crazy
hey everybody look who's here it's Mark Stingpet Alfonso don't any chicks right in
unfortunately no what are you doing I'm podcasting what's that it's like blogging
but only with audio that's sad real sad I know I like to better when he was down here late
doing what it's word or what you got in your browser cash just a bunch of mp3 files now
man this pop casting sounds like bush it
then I got a woman in there and an English guy and it's great I really love it and I
I wouldn't mind listening to an audio book that way if you could put if you have if you have a
novel and you put in uh different voices with different characters I think it would work so I
got to find out what that is that's excellent stuff I hope it's not windows only because I really like
it and then another uh whacked out idea that I that I received from Andrew Woolridge
um see uh I'll just read his email to you so if you listen to your podcast on my laptop while
writing home on the train here at San Francisco very cool had a minor brainstorm regarding regarding
podcasting wanted to relate to you what if you combine podcasting with geocaching mean imagine if
you were going to a certain location in your geocache say to the top of a hill overlooking a nice ocean
before you left you went to podcasting.org or something and downloaded all the comments stories or
whatever you have about the location then when you got there you could listen to all the stories or
impressions of all the people who had visited that location so I think what he's saying here and this
sounds really cool is to create a podcast feed based on geographic location so indeed you could have
a database and these already exist it look into geocaching people are way into handheld GPS devices
and doing treasure hunts and uh and uh even walking tours you know so you can get uh points of interest
and where to walk and little pop up and tell you you know what's interesting about that particular
particular point imagine leaving you know like comments in midair so if if you are on a certain
bridge in Amsterdam um that well let's just really imagine fast forward right and there would be a
feed for that particular geographic location or anything within uh you know within a 20 meter radius
and you could download that and and it would put on your iPod or maybe it would you download an
entire walking tour and once you hit a certain location it would give you the files I mean I just like
the idea of having space being trackable where you are and I always love the the museum tours
remember those are kids and you put in the earphones the Smithsonian probably still has it
or they have updated versions shit they had one at the uh uh uh and Pompeii they had an audio
walking tour um you know just think of all the the possibilities of that I think it's uh pretty
outrageous okay one more bit that I want to play from the Engaget podcast uh these guys are really
on fire they're already at a you know fantastic community with uh Engaget.com and they do a uh
I guess mom maybe a twice a week podcast now and Len it's Lenin Phil who are on the show is
doing something pretty exciting and upcoming a Riley conference. So speaking of a Riley and good
folks over there um something cool came up the other day through you and I um where they're looking
for some cool sessions to do at their macOS 10 conference that's happening um the week of the 20
year fifth I think it's the 25th through the 28th and um turns out they were looking to do a session
on podcasting and they came to the good current and gadget and um I'm gonna do the sessions.
Yep so it's pretty cool I'm gonna do a session about podcasting everything about it how to
consume how to create and how to distribute podcasts and uh we're gonna talk about how to do it on
the mac we're gonna talk a little bit about how to do it on the PC so um should be pretty cool if
anyone's listening it's going to the conference pop up and tell us how we're doing. Yeah I uh I
think it'll be interesting I can't make it because it's my anniversary and the last year I was in
China and I got forgiven for that because I was literally China um yeah dude dude dude it's okay
it's okay we understand you don't have to go anniversary totally get it rocked the situation
so um look forward to that and I think only appropriate now to say of course that November 6
will have a huge um podcasting session session I should say uh get together I'm just leading the
session everyone's gonna be hanging out podcasting recording god knows what bring your boombox bring
your speakers your amplifiers your microphones November 6 in Palo Alto uh it's gonna be
you blast and that's it for the source code for today I'm ready for the weekend how about you guys
huh that's it for October 15 Friday 2004 thank you very much for listening
we might get a trade secret cut over the weekend uh like and uh get Dave up at a reasonable
hour to do that he's got his new computer installed um and of course Monday we'll back with another
source code as you want to respond send me an email add them at curie.com leave me a comment
on my weblog live dot curie dot com force the archives and the current shows of the source code
find them on daily source code dot com subscribe to the RSS feed the podcast feed me the daily
source code dot com slash RSS dot XML all right we out of here see you Monday everybody