I guess it's a very curry.
And hello everybody!
Once again coming to you from Curry Cottage in the UK,
this is your daily source code.
Today is Tuesday, November 23, 2004.
Long night!
How y'all doing?
Well, that was our story.
Oh, it's our first day!
Friends, I am not well today.
I see it.
Not well.
It's…
I guess it's typical that I get sick right after,
you know, all the heavy bits start to fall into place such as
the movie.
But we finally got all the stuff fed away with our animals,
I woke up this morning at 5 o'clock,
I was mass.
And it literally have…
Like some kind of one thing, like almost like pneumonia, I think it is.
You know, pneumonia kind of feels like a truck hit your back.
That's what I got.
I've been just from that bike ride that I took on Saturday down to Starbucks.
And remember when I was kind of an hour,
Fudging around trying to find my way back, that's probably when that all happened.
So I've been pretty much immobilized for most of the day.
It's my bag.
It's my shoulders.
It's my chest.
It's my stomach.
It's completely messed up.
Not that you want any details on that.
So I kind of hung around a little bit today.
I was up really early this morning.
Notice that my upload of the daily source code had not worked the way I intended it to.
I'm still on the narrow band line, by the way, on the phone line, which is actually.
I'm still amazed at how fast and how optimized the web is.
For instance, for, you know, these, when am I getting like 40, 44k per second speed here.
You know, it's, I'm amazed at that.
It really am amazed at that speed.
And it takes, was it to upload 21 megs.
It takes about an hour and 40 minutes, now and 45, maybe a little bit, two hours.
So it's not all that bad, really.
But of course, that's not true because in the other hand,
life is just, it comes to a crawling halt if you don't have the speed.
I mean, email alone.
You spend so much more time dealing with, you're information when you're on a slow,
low link that it's, yeah, it's really, it sucks.
And still the provisional line status.
So we're looking at next week, Tuesday at the earliest that I'll be able to get my broad
band in here, which means, of course, tomorrow, come hell or high water.
I'm going to make a, uh, a stop at the Starbucks.
I got a, a weeklong pass for the team mobile hotspot.
Uh, it's like 30 pounds.
So, yeah, it was, it was better than, if I able to go there two days and just get two hours
worth each time, then it would be the same amount or more.
Um, and I'm Jones and man, I'm so Jones and for podcasts, because that's the one thing that
just does not work on the dial-up line.
No way.
So it's, yeah, it sucks.
Really, really, really sucks.
And then you add to that, they're not feeling well.
Anyway, so what do we do today?
Um, oh, we, uh, we opened up a bank account.
Or at least we started.
And you can't do anything here, as, you know, as probably is the same almost everywhere.
Um, unless you, uh, unless you have some kind of credit history, you have something built up,
uh, something you can point to that says, yeah, you know, I'm, I'm a, I'm a guy that you
want to, uh, rent a cell phone to give a cell phone contract, you know, stuff like that.
It's just a minor stuff.
So we're really, you know, uh, enjoying the pioneering of it.
Um, it's, uh, uh, you know, just figuring out new stuff, um, the whole new culture, a whole new country.
It's exactly what we wanted.
This is exactly what we wanted.
Um, and you know what?
It's fucking tired, exactly what we expected.
It's tiring to go through this right now.
But it's going to be great.
And we're, uh, we're really enjoying ourselves.
And we're just enjoying the culture, totally.
Um, part of that culture, of course, is driving on the left hand side of the road.
Now I have a, uh, left hand drive.
So I'm sitting on the left hand side of the car.
It's an Audi, uh, that I've, you know, that I had in, uh, in Holland and in Belgium.
And there's another year left on the lease.
So I figured just, you know, drive around in it here until it's, uh,
into like, and bring it back.
Um, thank goodness.
It has a great GPS system built into it.
I mean, really, uh, detail DVD.
So it, you know, if you fuck up and you, uh, or as we say, if you cock up and you, uh,
uh, and you miss your turn, which is very, uh, possible.
I hold on, uh, what did my software update just said?
You should update airport software, bluetooth module, firmware, iCal.
iPod update or uh-oh, what's in the iPod update or?
Let's see, compatibility with iTunes 4.7, iTunes music store,
shuffle and play song library with one click.
The hell does that mean?
Create multiple on the go play lists.
To lead songs from the on the go play list.
Okay.
Select reading playback speed for audiobooks.
Hey, check that out.
I wonder if it's fast and slow.
Here, click wheel, clicker through the headphones.
Ooh, I love that, baby.
Sync and go with improved disconnect performance.
Sync and go.
Now with improved disconnect iTunes.
Oh, wait.
Here we go.
iPod update or 2004.
Now, Sync and go with improved disconnect performance.
You need it.
Now.
I don't think so.
Not for 20 megs.
I kind of do that on my phone line.
Boeys.
Morning.
Um, so back to driving left.
Baron, uh, has a theory about why they drive on the left hand side of the road in the UK.
Um, he says during revolutionary war, the colonists move their channel markers,
markers from marking the entrances to harbors, ports.
So that it was safe to stay on the right side of the marker, the British and previously
the colonists, the colonists, rode their boats on the left side of the marker to stay safe.
Thus, when the British tried to attack by ships coming through the channel, they grounded
their boats by going left.
So chock it up to a sneaky Americans.
Oh, that's an interesting theory there, actually.
Yeah, I still like the one where, you know, if you're riding along and there's a rival
that might come up on horseback that, you know, you want to be able to chop his head off
or at least jost him off his horse and you do that with your right hand.
So it's easier to be driving left or riding left.
Um, Martin, uh, from green dragon online.co.uk has a different take quite simple while we're driving
the left.
All our cars are right hand drive.
If we drove on the right, we wouldn't be able to see the traffic lights and directional signpost.
Oh, hold on.
I had an audio comment about left hand driving.
Let me just open that up from, uh, the podcast show notes.
I have no idea who this was from.
Let's check it out.
On another note, I was listening to, uh, Adam Curry's daily source code.
And he, of course, he's in the UK now.
And he was talking about getting used to driving on the left hand side of the road.
And I just have to relate a story.
A number of years ago, I was living in Guam.
And, uh, traveling a lot to Japan.
And, uh, Guam, they drive on the right hand side of the road, of course, in Japan.
They've been driving on the left hand side, which everybody says is the right way to drive.
But, you know, I, I mean, American, I, I much prefer to drive on the right hand side.
And you can always tell when you're in Japan.
And there's a new, uh, a new driver because they are, they are the ones that, uh,
they pull up to a light.
And, uh, instead of their, uh, uh, uh, uh, turn a single coming on.
They're windshield wifers start, uh, spiking back and forth.
Then when it's not even raining.
I mean, that's a good indication that you've got a newly driver across from you.
Or even next to you.
And I've been guilty of it a few times.
But I've been traveling back and forth a lot.
And actually, it's been like two months in Japan.
And, uh, so my car had been parked at the, uh,
a long-term parking in Guam.
And I arrived back and I got to, got the car started just fine.
And everything was good and it was dark.
And I get out on the road and, you know, I got my lights on.
And I'm looking down the street.
And there's this guy coming down the street on the wrong side of the street.
I don't think of myself.
Who is this knucklehead?
This is on the wrong side of the street.
So I start flashing my lights at the guy.
And, and I'm finally, I'm trying to think, what in the world?
You know, we're going to have a collision here.
And it dawned on me.
Hey, dumbass.
You're the one that's on the wrong side of the road.
It's a boy on the road.
I had become so accustomed to driving on the left hand side of the road.
Because when I pulled all that parking lot,
I immediately got in the left hand lane and started trucking down the street
without even, you know, subconsciously thinking that, you know,
this guy that's coming at me, you know, it wasn't me.
It was him, you know.
It was, it was pretty funny.
So if Adam, if you're listening to the show,
when I may send you this clip,
don't be surprised if you make a few mistakes.
So when they're getting used to driving on the left hand side of the street.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Actually, that's what I really like about the Audi.
It's the 4.2 liter show.
The roundabout to the scariest thing.
You know, you get into the roundabout.
And you're going to left hand side.
And you just, you know,
that's, you want to have a car that can accelerate quick at that moment.
You know, so you just like,
I think it's great.
Go.
I did that in New York once.
I drove everyone home.
I was like, three in the morning,
but working on a pitch at think new ideas.
And I can't remember what Avenue it is.
I turned right on.
But I turned right onto something that was totally not possible
because they were, they were most of an eight cars all coming at us.
They're like, just changed as well.
I turned up the wrong way out of one way.
Straight at his quite a frightening, frightening thing to see.
Hey, email from yourtmentink.
I guess he's Dutch.
Yourtmentink.com.
Okay, that doesn't say anything about his background.
But he sent me a clip.
He says that Amy Poolor performed a nice little boing.
On last Saturdays, Saturday Night Live.
Check it out.
Pfizer has agreed to pull its wild thing.
Viagra television ads Monday.
After the FDA complained that they made the impenence drug
sound like a recreational sex aid.
And not the preferred form of grandma abuse that it is.
They've also decided...
Pfizer has also decided to drop the idea of changing the name of the drug
to boing.
That was a good one.
The drug to boing.
She really got it down.
Didn't she?
Oh, man.
You know, you know.
We're going to get that.
We're going to be changing the name of the drug to boing.
Excellent.
Okay, time for some tunes on your daily source code.
This is a mashup.
Something that you'll never see a fisher released.
It's done by a...
A...
It was to say a quote, band called Bittalica.
The bassley mashup, the Beatles, and the tower.
You'll get it.
You'll dig it.
It...
You...
It's true not...
See...
I...
Take a grassaw
And make it better.
Remember...
The melody is in your heart
And you can start to be your friend.
And you...
Don't be fucking bread.
Now...
You will meet too.
You'll be a charader.
So many eyes.
You'll let us on your sky.
Then you'll be gay.
To be a predator.
So crank around.
I'm in the middle of it.
Hey, dude.
You're fucking insane.
The rivers run real.
Hey, I...
With a whiter, who's worse.
And no too tall That is a blue one.
Full pleased equal.
Fuck These boys.
They are!
To be here to live
It's right, never until it's the whole
You must pound her, I mean, keep a wing of war
New will or British heavy metal is in your heart
And you can't start with diamond hills
So, let it out already, I'll pay you
Be careful, don't wait for it, I ain't up to me
Hold on, hey
You never know what the top one you are, pay you
You'll do it, to sing that I am
Yeah, because you're shows of
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, yeah
Yeah, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it
it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true
on, No gotta
No gotta
Let them do your feeling
love a sexy a
no gotta
No I
They won't steal
See
The tears I hear what we hear
No, no, no, no, no
No, no, no
What's it ever going to be?
It's the colds that I hear
No, no, no, no, no
No, no, no
Do that do it, do it, do it
And where will we end, fucking new?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Get away or do it, until it's you, yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
No, no, no, no
We can muggle, let's, the only other play
It's gonna do...
Go, do it
Woo, do it
We are nah, I'm tankin'
Come and do it
Is that different?
And do
Ahhh
Ahh
Kylie
If they play it's being
We won't?!"
зах
For me now do
Ahhh
Oh, I do, yeah, I do
Oh, I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know
I know to read the ones inside of things
Better than you do, I know, I know
I see no more hate
All right, just...just-how cool is that?
Vitalik is hey dude on the daily source code for Tuesday November 23rd, 2004 coming to you from the UK from the region of Seren
Man, I gotta stop doing it again. I gotta stop doing it
But what's cool about people not knowing me here, which is just cool by itself, you know being
Coming from celebrity status to zero is fucking awesome
You know you can have so much fun with people and you know there's they have no preconceived notions about you or you know
Who you are what you are or what you what you're about and so the set first impression. I like playing with that
It's it's cool
I have a lot of fun over here in
You know new digs
I've been right played the lascivious bitties yesterday for you. This is
The band from New York this girls have a very very very typical sound and we've been in touch for a couple of years
I can't remember when the first time I heard about them
Shoot I Patricia even remembered
But we've we've been in touch over the years and Leanne
Aliana Westover. It says she was really happy actually
Overjoyed that she was playing on the daily source code
Particularly because they're they're going through a rough time right now
They were on a trip to Boston. I guess they're playing some gigs over the weekend
So I'm broken to the room. They were sleeping in stole diggers keyboard and a keyboard amp a man does new Brian more guitar and
Unfortunately Leanne's not backed up lately laptop
That does totally freaking bite I hate that
But she goes on to say that and of course all these emails are in the in the show notes
She says I'm renting out a room for the holidays or someone who who says that you wrote the email tour
Not only your cool because you gave us a great deal on the room, but not even cooler because you were played on the daily source code
And you know my my radio mentor Lex Harding
Who was a one of the original
Broadcasters on the pirate radio stations on the North Sea back in the very early 70s even the late 60s
I think
Went on to found the public broadcast of Veronica television. He's done a lot of a lot of radio stuff
But he even sent me an SMS the other day and said wow, you know like I got some guy
I know from Singapore who listens to your podcast every day. It's just cool. It's really getting around and um, and oh, yeah, there was a
I just posted that on an I potted out org
There was a an article in the London Times
podcast in the next the next the next big thing so
Just moving
Anyway, back to the city as bitties and we'll get back to the UK in a second in the BBC
I feel really bad about you know when your shit gets stolen that is just so that really really really sucks
Yes, that I played I want to be famous which is one of my favorite tracks off their new album
This is something though even though it's totally not the kind of music this tracking when it played with it by the city as bitties
It's not
It's not really the type of music that I'm into but there's something about it that just you know
I can't help but sing along with the song. It's very a country in western, but then again you don't hear enough of that on radio
Anyway, do you use Texas girl the busbiest bitties on the daily source code
Oh
Son in the blue Texas guy. You can take the girl
Like a flower you can look from the world
But no matter where she roam she is never by my home because you can take Texas out of the girl
I am thankful for the things that the Lord has given
I am proud of the things for myself
I have earned but I still miss the big old fields of cotton and I long for the song of my
Buckingbird you can take the girl out of Texas like an apple you can look from the world
No matter where she roam she is never by my home because you can take Texas out of the girl
I have earned but I still miss the big old fields of cotton
Texas like a flower you can look from the world
But no matter where she roam she is never by home because you can take Texas out of this girl
Oh you can take the girl out of Texas like an apple you can look from the world
But no matter where she roam she is never by my home because you can take Texas out of the
Take Texas out of the girl everybody now you have Texas girl
The Civius Bitties on your daily source code
Okay, let me see you want to talk about oh of course I want to plug the the BBC culture show
Since it's coming up on Thursday and you know the way iPodders work and the way it works with me uploading and time differences
Everything like that it'll be online they do have an archive that's up for cut the
BPS do is BBC is doing some interesting things these days and they aren't they do seem to be keeping archives up for a couple of days of of most of their or a lot of their stuff
So it's on Thursday BBC to the culture show
7 p.m. I got a lovely email from Colin the producer
I don't came in if I told you about that yesterday, but he says they cut it down from nine minutes to six minutes or not he but the powers that be
And what he said that he was he really was really happy with it. So we'll see what happens now
I was just reading in the Guardian and by a man
Compared to Holland and Belgium the UK what a what a newspaper country. There's so many different newspapers
And the Guardian of course I know from online and
And I picked up the copy the Guardian and the BBC is in the midst of a huge huge huge
shake up
There's I think the number was 27,000 people work for the beat 27,000 people work for the BBC
Now they do have a lot of a lot of stations and you know TV and radio and in an incarnate and all the stuff that they have to you know have to manage and fill up and
You have to pay for a TV license which I still have to arrange before they serve me a warrant
Which said was it made a hundred pounds or something like that so yeah, it's probably it's probably a good
Close to two hundred dollars. I would say probably
So you know you do kind of feel like you know, you're you want to get what you pay for and
Man 27,000 people is a lot to run you know some TV and radio stations
And they're talking about letting independent producers in to produce more of
Of this public broadcast
Programming which is commercial free obviously very high quality. I love it. I love the BBC programming. I really do
And sure there's the ITV stuff and you know channel four channel five
Which has the I'm a celebrity get me out of here and you know so the millionaire
We want to be a millionaire and those are good too. You need some chewing gum, but man the BBC there's some awesome awesome programs on the radio as well just fabulous stuff
And so my own experience as as
The United Kingdom is going through this and they're trying to figure out you know what should we do and
What's the what are the right moves to make clearly clearly? They have too many people working for them that is just that's an outrage
But I'm a little wary about letting all these commercial independent producers in because they did that in Holland and it really sucks
You know because these guys are about making money not about making necessarily not about making great television
And of course the country is smaller so maybe it's harder to make a buck in in the lowlands, but
You know a lower level of independent producers. I think it's good
Not not too much because you really that's my experience. You're going to lose lose a lot of the good creativity
But certainly the bureaucracy that is
You know that makes up that amount of people working on you know on that much there's only 24 hours in a day, right?
That's that's pretty amazing. So I'm following this
It was really was a big article like six or seven pages and
You know there's there's a lot of stake. They're also they've moved or in the throws of moving a lot of people out of London into
I think it was
Was it I don't have it here
Manchester Birmingham
I'll have to look into that but so clearly a lot of BBC history and a lot of changes going on as we speak and there as I mentioned before
There's so much media going on here. You know we have the the free view which plugs
Digital signals out of thin air and gives you like 30 channels for free and you can order stuff
And it's just you buy a box once and that's it. No cable company nothing. It's just coming right out of the air
I'm gonna get the sky box as well, which is pretty much a dish
I want that in Christina's hangout room
Yeah, so you know I'll be able to fill you in on on that experience
um
And then what else do they have and they've cable? I think we might even have cable here. I'm just gonna try and get everything
But keeping a sharp eye on what's happening here
With the with broadcasting in general BBC in particular and I'm really excited about
a new piece of knowledge that I gained Dave wine and wrote how to
um
I want to say it right it was a how to extend RSS in namespaces
And this is something that I've been you know
Not only I but I see it on the iPod or developers list. We've been you know thinking about how can we group different kinds of
Inclosures or files or you know what if you want to put in my big thing as I want to make sure that's somehow
We can attach this opml show notes file
To each podcast which is an MP3 and and basically
I have no I had no fucking clue on how to do that and you know just a I'm just a guy who kind of put some scripts and strings and stuff together
But now that I understand it
It's it's really quite simple in fact. I'm gonna be working with with August and Ray who do iPod or X
Which is the iPod or I use
On hopefully creating a namespace either for production notes or podcasting or you know we're still kind of in
Kind of figuring this out and
Another when we get stuck we can and you will be able to reach out and ask for help
I'm hoping Dave's gonna watch over my shoulder. I'm sure he will make sure we get this right because
It would be so cool to be able to basically make relationships between multiple things in a in a podcast feed
But keeping RSS intact that that's obviously important. I've learned now how important that really is because
Man you the last thing we want to do was create more work for developers, right?
We want to make sure that there's one set wave doing it that we all agree on it as best as possible
I'm sure that you know once we start implementing it
People will we'll help us out and we'll we'll all figure it out together and
And then we'll have some extra functionality in these things. I'm looking forward to that
Working with those guys and I'm just needing a need of a little bit of bandwidth because that's that's really holding me back on
Jumping back into the iPod or developer list and and really getting deep into stuff because it just takes so long to manage all the information
And oh I forgot to say about the BBC
I think that the BBC is doing more podcasting experiments than we're aware of
Andrew Whitehurst sent me an email also in the podcast show notes opml
He sent me a couple of links a particularly for the five live program, which is BBC five
I think it's the late night show
Fighting talk is that it hold on have the
You were all here. I just check
Oh, excuse me for my stomach
Fighting talk next and I give us a weekly Punditary contest of gladiatorial
Proportions hosted by christianocony so what they have here is okay. This is the deal. They have these
Downloads so they're doing MP3 downloads and if you hunt around
Basically trying on different URLs that end in dot XML you'll find that a lot of these programs already have podcast feeds it's almost like there
I don't know if this is a concerted effort or I mean something clearly someone is doing this someone knows what's going on
And I hope that they'll reach out to us and and let us know because I really want to point to these podcasts
I mean this is the stuff that
You know, this is if we can get all that BBC programming in in podcast form and maybe the stuff that
Doesn't make it on the air. Wow. I mean when it comes to radio BBC totally has that down
And
Just wanted to mention that Linux questions.org is also working at a podcast thanks to
Martin for
Learning me to that by email and one last
I potter feed. I think you should subscribe to
Which I put a link to the
To the RSS 2.0 feed in the show notes is I potio and I potio is interesting
because it's basically a collection of
Audio that can be freely used and redistributed so it's sometimes it's the president's address the weekly radio address
You know, I never go to whitehouse.gov and click on that, you know, so I'd love that coming in automatically
There's voice of America reports
All kinds of just different interesting things and the guy that runs this I think yeah, this is so I'm thinking of actually we we spoke on Skype a while back
as a Thomas I think
Real fuzzy so I apologize
If I got that wrong
He has a like a medium size ISP and he's well, he's looking for ways to fill up his pipe and I think I potio is great
So there's a link to that
From the show notes. All right
Almost made my 40 minutes 33 little bit less than yesterday, but I just got to get to be
Got to get out of here for
Rest in relaxation of course we back tomorrow with the Wednesday edition of your daily source code
That'll be hum day so we'll see we can
I'm around right. Oh, I'll go to Starbucks. That's right and I'll have lots of you stuff to talk about
After I've been able to
Check out all of my favorite podcasts
Comments love to have them out of a curry dot com send me a link here at p3 five or it was not too big attached
You can always comment on my weblog at curry dot com and for all the latest
The newest and the archived source codes its daily source code dot com and of course
We can feed for the podcast. Let's take the source code dot com slash and we'll see us back next
Okay
Take these everybody. I'll see you thanks for listening. Thanks for subscribing y'all
You